<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"

	xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
	xmlns:geo="http://www.w3.org/2003/01/geo/wgs84_pos#"
	>

<channel>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.newsbtc.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<description>Bitcoin &#38; Cryptocurrency News Today</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 15:34:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-cropped-favicon.png?fit=32%2C32</url>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
<site xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">221170450</site>	<item>
		<title>Sei Takes A Hit: Price Suffers 26% Plunge Amid Airdrop Claim Expansion</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/altcoin/sei-takes-a-hit-price-suffers-plunge-amid-airdrop/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samuel Edyme]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 02:30:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEI]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEIUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=547752</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Sei, a specialized trading network within the Cosmos ecosystem, has recently recorded a significant downward trend.  Notably, on a day rife with anticipation, the price of Sei plunged by more than 20%, plummeting from its initial spike above $0.28 to somewhere below $0.18. This decline coincided with the Sei Foundation&#8217;s decision to open airdrop claims, arguing free tokens are often distributed to early participants or testers of a new crypto project. Related Reading: SEI Token Breaks Into Top 100 One Day Post-Debut On Major Exchanges Airdrop Details And The Impact On Sei&#8217;s Price The crypto community has since waited with bated breath for the Sei blockchain to launch and initiate its airdrop. And finally, on August 15, Sei launched its mainnet beta, with the airdrop initiatives happening after. Today, the blockchain reported an upsurge in the number of wallets eligible for the airdrop. Initially planned for 500,000 wallets, the number swelled to roughly 1.5 million in response to what the foundation termed &#8220;fervent demand.&#8221; Due to fervent demand, Sei Foundation has increased the number of eligible wallets for the cross-bridge airdrop from 500K to 1.5M on @ethereum, @0xPolygonLabs, @arbitrum, @BNBCHAIN, @solana, @optimismFND and @osmosiszone. — Sei Foundation (@Sei_FND) August 17, 2023 This enlargement incorporated users from a variety of blockchain networks, including but not limited to Ethereum, Polygon, Arbitrum, BNB Chain, and Solana. From its coin supply, the Sei team earmarked 3% specifically for the airdrop. This translates to a figure of 300 million coins. To put this into perspective, according to a report by Binance, these coins form a significant chunk of the 1.8 billion Sei coins currently circulating out of 10 billion coins.  Sei Price Plunges More Than 20% In The Past Day Sei has plummeted by more than 20% over the past 24 hours. This plummet contributes to the asset&#8217;s fall from its rank among the top 100 in crypto on the day of launch to a current rank of 107 among the most prominent crypto by market capitalization, according to CoinGecko. Despite the token&#8217;s listing on exchanges such as Binance, it has seen quite a plunge in the past day with a current market price of $1.80, a 22% drop from its initial trading price above $0.25. The reason behind Sei&#8217;s plummet is evident as it comes amid the asset&#8217;s airdrop expansion. It is worth noting that an event such as an airdrop can often trigger a cascade of sell-offs as eligible users rush to convert their newfound assets into cash or other cryptocurrencies. Alongside its declining value, Sei&#8217;s market capitalization plunged from $413 million on Wednesday to $319 million at the time of writing. The asset&#8217;s trading volume has declined from a high of $1.2 billion yesterday to $705 million in the past 24 hours. Related Reading: Kraken Surges Ahead In Altcoin Liquidity To Overtake Coinbase In US: Kaiko Sei is a new trading-focused blockchain claiming a faster transaction initiation than its counterparts. The blockchain touts the capability to execute sub-second blocks making its transaction more efficient. In the ever-demanding realm of cryptocurrency trading, where speed is of the essence, this feature makes the blockchain worth paying attention to. Featured image from Unsplash, Chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Sei, a specialized trading network within the Cosmos ecosystem, has recently recorded a significant downward trend.  Notably, on a day rife with anticipation, the price of Sei plunged by more than 20%, plummeting from its initial spike above $0.28 to somewhere below $0.18.</p>
<p>This decline coincided with the Sei Foundation&#8217;s decision to <a href="https://blog.sei.io/the-sei-airdrop/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">open airdrop claims</a>, arguing free tokens are often distributed to early participants or testers of a new crypto project.</p>

<h2>Airdrop Details And The Impact On Sei&#8217;s Price</h2>
<p>The crypto community has since waited with bated breath for the Sei <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/crypto-analyst-deciphers-xrp-price-movement/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">blockchain</a> to launch and initiate its airdrop. And finally, on August 15, Sei <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/altcoin/sei-into-top-100-post-debut-on-major-exchanges/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">launched its mainnet beta</a>, with the airdrop initiatives happening after.</p>
<p>Today, the blockchain reported an upsurge in the number of wallets eligible for the airdrop. Initially planned for 500,000 wallets, the number swelled to roughly 1.5 million in response to what the foundation <a href="https://twitter.com/Sei_FND/status/1692070808783368592?s=20" rel="nofollow">termed</a> &#8220;fervent demand.&#8221;</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Due to fervent demand, Sei Foundation has increased the number of eligible wallets for the cross-bridge airdrop from 500K to 1.5M on <a href="https://twitter.com/ethereum?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">@ethereum</a>, <a href="https://twitter.com/0xPolygonLabs?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">@0xPolygonLabs</a>, <a href="https://twitter.com/arbitrum?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">@arbitrum</a>, <a href="https://twitter.com/BNBCHAIN?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">@BNBCHAIN</a>, <a href="https://twitter.com/solana?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">@solana</a>, <a href="https://twitter.com/optimismFND?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">@optimismFND</a> and <a href="https://twitter.com/osmosiszone?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">@osmosiszone</a>.</p>
<p>— Sei Foundation (@Sei_FND) <a href="https://twitter.com/Sei_FND/status/1692070808783368592?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">August 17, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w g0rxnol2" dir="ltr">This enlargement incorporated users from a variety of blockchain networks, including but not limited to Ethereum, Polygon, Arbitrum, BNB Chain, and Solana. From its coin supply, the Sei team earmarked 3% specifically for the airdrop. This translates to a figure of 300 million coins.</p>
<p dir="ltr">To put this into perspective, according to a <a href="https://www.binance.com/en/support/announcement/introducing-sei-sei-on-binance-launchpool-farm-sei-by-staking-bnb-tusd-and-fdusd-b1d3b4df9cb34f679783a4fdb891f643" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">report</a> by Binance, these coins form a significant chunk of the 1.8 billion Sei coins currently circulating out of 10 billion coins. </p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Sei Price Plunges More Than 20% In The Past Day</h2>
<p>Sei has plummeted by more than 20% over the past 24 hours. This plummet contributes to the asset&#8217;s fall from its rank among the top 100 in crypto on the day of launch to a current rank of 107 among the most prominent crypto by market capitalization, according to CoinGecko.</p>
<p>Despite the token&#8217;s listing on <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/kraken-ahead-in-altcoin-liquidity/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">exchanges</a> such as Binance, it has seen quite a plunge in the past day with a current market price of $1.80, a 22% drop from its initial trading price above $0.25. The reason behind Sei&#8217;s plummet is evident as it comes amid the asset&#8217;s airdrop expansion.</p>
<img decoding="async" fetchpriority="high" class="size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/mPf8KRbN/" alt="Sei price chart on TradingView" width="2770" height="1408" loading="lazy"/>
<p>It is worth noting that an event such as an airdrop can often trigger a cascade of sell-offs as eligible users rush to convert their newfound assets into cash or other cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p>Alongside its declining value, Sei&#8217;s market capitalization plunged from $413 million on Wednesday to $319 million at the time of writing. The asset&#8217;s trading volume has declined from a high of $1.2 billion yesterday to $705 million in the past 24 hours.</p>

<p>Sei is a new trading-focused blockchain claiming a faster transaction initiation than its counterparts. The blockchain touts the capability to execute sub-second blocks making its transaction more efficient. In the ever-demanding realm of cryptocurrency trading, where speed is of the essence, this feature makes the blockchain worth paying attention to.</p>
<p>Featured image from Unsplash, Chart from TradingView</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Optimism.jpeg?fit=460%2C259" width="460" height="259" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">547752</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>LUNC Sheds 13% Of Its Value &#8211; A Further Retreat In The Offing?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/all/lunc-sheds-13-of-its-value-a-further-retreat-in-the-offing/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 01:10:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[All]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LUNC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price action]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Terra Luna Classic]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=547716</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Terra Luna Classic (LUNC) finds itself grappling with a significant setback as its price takes a sharp dive. Within the span of just 24 hours, the coin experienced a 13% decline in value.  The swift sell-off, which began on August 16, triggered a cascading effect that sent LUNC&#8217;s price plummeting from its recent peg of $0.00007734 to a new low of $0.00006512. While this may appear as a dramatic swing, it echoes the bearish sentiment that has persistently lingered around the coin throughout the past month. Related Reading: Chiliz (CHZ) Empowers Smart Contracts With Upgrades – Positive Impact On Price? LUNC Battles To Maintain Essential Support For a duration exceeding three weeks, LUNC&#8217;s price showcased resilience as it managed to keep itself above a crucial support zone resting at $0.000076. This period of relative stability served as a reflection of the overarching uncertainty pervading in the market.  However, with the breach of this monthly support threshold, experts caution that the existing selling pressure could magnify significantly. This breach also carries the potential to indicate a prolonged period of downward movement for the Terra classic coin. Beyond The Surface Scrutinizing the Luna Classic community on Twitter reveals a landscape marred by internal conflicts, particularly concerning the governance protocols. Recent days have witnessed heated debates revolving around the proposed implementation of the LUNC DAO validator, which would have assumed a prominent role in leading the chain. Unfortunately, this proposal met its end, and the aftermath was telling – a substantial sell-off unfolded.  This is undeniable proof that OX DAO (Formerly known as $LUNC Dao) is trying to take over #LUNC by dumping the price. pic.twitter.com/kqtDdwIxbr — Classy 🔮 (@ClassyCrypto_) August 15, 2023 Notably, Crypto Classy, a prominent LUNC validator, alleges that the sell-off was meticulously orchestrated by the LUNC DAO itself. The assertion is that the DAO orchestrated deliberate coin sales to incite panic within the investor community, ultimately facilitating coin repurchases at lower prices – a move perceived as an attempt to gain control over the network. Impact On Price Dynamics The repercussions of these recent events reverberate through LUNC&#8217;s price dynamics. As per CoinGecko&#8217;s data, the coin currently hovers around $0.00006770. A decline of 2.4% over the past 24 hours coupled with a substantial seven-day slump of 12.5% underscores the mounting strain that the coin is grappling with. Terra Luna Classic (LUNC) is currently trading at $0.00006703. Chart: TradingView.com As the LUNC community grapples with these internal struggles, governance challenges, and potential market manipulation, the future path remains uncertain. Related Reading: Cardano Holder Resilience Tested As ADA Fends Off Bearish Onslaught Investors and stakeholders are keeping a watchful eye on the evolving situation within the LUNC ecosystem, anticipating whether Terra Luna Classic can navigate these tumultuous waters and regain its footing while working to restore trust among its dedicated supporters. (This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk). Featured image from Matthias Hangst/Getty]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Terra Luna Classic (LUNC) finds itself grappling with a significant setback as its price takes a sharp dive. Within the span of just 24 hours, the coin experienced a 13% decline in value. </p>
<p>The swift sell-off, which began on August 16, triggered a cascading effect that sent LUNC&#8217;s price plummeting from its recent peg of $0.00007734 to a new low of $0.00006512. </p>
<p>While this may appear as a dramatic swing, it echoes the bearish sentiment that has persistently lingered around the coin throughout the past month.</p>

<h2><strong>LUNC Battles To Maintain Essential Support</strong></h2>
<p>For a duration exceeding three weeks, <a href="https://coingape.com/markets/terra-classic-coin-analysis-what-for-lunc-15-drop/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">LUNC&#8217;s price</a> showcased resilience as it managed to keep itself above a crucial support zone resting at $0.000076. This period of relative stability served as a reflection of the overarching uncertainty pervading in the market. </p>
<p>However, with the breach of this monthly support threshold, experts caution that the existing selling pressure could magnify significantly. This breach also carries the potential to indicate a prolonged period of downward movement for the Terra classic coin.</p>
<h2><strong>Beyond The Surface</strong></h2>
<p>Scrutinizing the <a href="https://finbold.com/terra-luna-classic-price-down-12-3-best-penny-cryptos-to-buy-now-instead/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Luna Classic community</a> on Twitter reveals a landscape marred by internal conflicts, particularly concerning the governance protocols. </p>
<p>Recent days have witnessed heated debates revolving around the proposed implementation of the LUNC DAO validator, which would have assumed a prominent role in leading the chain. Unfortunately, this proposal met its end, and the aftermath was telling – a substantial sell-off unfolded. </p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">This is undeniable proof that OX DAO (Formerly known as <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24LUNC&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$LUNC</a> Dao) is trying to take over <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/LUNC?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#LUNC</a> by dumping the price. <a href="https://t.co/kqtDdwIxbr" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/kqtDdwIxbr</a></p>
<p>— Classy <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f52e.png" alt="🔮" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> (@ClassyCrypto_) <a href="https://twitter.com/ClassyCrypto_/status/1691536105290543105?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">August 15, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p>Notably, <a href="https://twitter.com/ClassyCrypto_/status/1691536105290543105" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Crypto Classy</a>, a prominent LUNC validator, alleges that the sell-off was meticulously orchestrated by the LUNC DAO itself. The assertion is that the DAO orchestrated deliberate coin sales to incite panic within the investor community, ultimately facilitating coin repurchases at lower prices – a move perceived as an attempt to gain control over the network.</p>
<strong>Impact On Price Dynamics</strong>
<p>The repercussions of these recent events reverberate through LUNC&#8217;s price dynamics. As per <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/terra-luna-classic" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">CoinGecko&#8217;s data</a>, the coin currently hovers around $0.00006770. A decline of 2.4% over the past 24 hours coupled with a substantial seven-day slump of 12.5% underscores the mounting strain that the coin is grappling with.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/ZEfXy5mg/" width="1835" height="893" loading="lazy"/></p>

<p>As the LUNC community grapples with these internal struggles, governance challenges, and potential market manipulation, the future path remains uncertain. </p>

<p>Investors and stakeholders are keeping a watchful eye on the evolving situation within the LUNC ecosystem, anticipating whether Terra Luna Classic can navigate these tumultuous waters and regain its footing while working to restore trust among its dedicated supporters.</p>
<p><em>(This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk).</em></p>
<p><em>Featured image from Matthias Hangst/</em><em>Getty</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-25.jpg?fit=460%2C307" width="460" height="307" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">547716</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Post-Hack Shenanigans: Curve (CRV) To Launch On TRON Following $2 Million Investment</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/defi/curve-to-launch-on-tron/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 00:10:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[DeFi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CRV]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Curve]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Curve DAO]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Justin Sun]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[TRON]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tron founder]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[TRON Network]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=547764</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Curve Finance, a decentralized liquidity pool for stableswap and stablecoin trading, has disclosed a strategic partnership that will see the decentralized exchange (DEX) launch on the TRON network.  Curve Set To Launch On Tron And BTTC Networks Decentralized Exchange, Curve Finance has solidified its position as the second largest DEX, following the announcement of its integration into the TRON network. Curve Finance&#8217;s recent alliance with the TRON network has prompted a substantial investment from TRON DAO Ventures, a venture capital firm established by the TRON network. On Thursday, August 17, TRON Founder, Justin Sun purchased $2 million worth of CRV, the native token of the DeFi protocol.  Similarly, Curve Finance has stated that it will be launching on the BitTorrent Chain (BTTC) network, a peer-to-peer network blockchain scaling solution for file and data sharing. The Integration of the protocol into TRON DAO and BTTC networks aims to fuel the development of innovative DeFi projects and the growth of DeFi ecosystems.  Curve Finance is widely known for its role in stable coin trading by providing low slippage exchanges through automated market maker (AMM) algorithms. By aligning with the protocol, TRON  and BTTC will benefit from lower financial costs and indirect backing from prominent blockchains Curve DAO supports including Avalanche, Ethereum, and Arbitrum. Justin Sun welcomed the newly formed alliance with enthusiasm. He commented that Curve Finance plays a pivotal role in the DeFi ecosystem and blockchain industry and looked forward to new innovative solutions promoted by the partnership.  &#8220;Curve is an essential DeFi infrastructure for the blockchain industry. Our thoughts are with the team and the users affected. As a community, let&#8217;s support and strengthen the security measures to protect our decentralized ecosystem,” Sun stated.  CRV price resting at $0.54 &#124; Source: CRVUSDT on Tradingview.com Compensation For Hack Victims Following Tron Alliance The decentralized finance (DeFi) landscape was previously shaken up following news of a hack on the DEX. On July 30, Curve Finance fell victim to a reentrancy attack that exploited vulnerabilities in its smart contract codes, resulting in a loss of $62 million.  Following the news of the hack attack, the CRV token declined and the majority of the DeFi ecosystem was in panic. However, Curve Finance has reportedly recovered 70% of the funds and to recover the rest of the stolen funds, the protocol has placed a bounty on the attacker, promising $1.85 million to anyone able to reveal the hacker’s identity.  Curve Finance has also promised to compensate victims of the security breach. The DEX has stated that it will distribute reimbursements fairly as they determine the extent of damages and work toward recovering the stolen funds.  Featured image from Zipmex, chart from Tradingview.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Curve Finance, a decentralized liquidity pool for stableswap and stablecoin trading, has disclosed a strategic partnership that will see the decentralized exchange (DEX) launch on the TRON network. </p>
<h2>Curve Set To Launch On Tron And BTTC Networks</h2>
<p>Decentralized Exchange, Curve Finance has solidified its position as the second largest DEX, following the announcement of its integration into the TRON network. </p>
<p>Curve Finance&#8217;s recent <a href="https://chainwire.org/2023/08/17/tron-dao-ventures-invests-2-million-in-crv-and-curve-to-launch-on-tron-and-bttc/" rel="nofollow">alliance</a> with the TRON network has prompted a substantial investment from TRON DAO Ventures, a venture capital firm established by the TRON network. On Thursday, August 17, TRON Founder, <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/justin-sun-buys-5-million-crv/" rel="nofollow">Justin Sun purchased $2 million worth of CRV</a>, the native token of the DeFi protocol. </p>
<p>Similarly, Curve Finance has stated that it will be launching on the BitTorrent Chain (BTTC) network, a peer-to-peer network blockchain scaling solution for file and data sharing. The Integration of the protocol into TRON DAO and BTTC networks aims to fuel the development of innovative DeFi projects and the growth of DeFi ecosystems. </p>
<p>Curve Finance is widely known for its role in stable coin trading by providing low slippage exchanges through automated market maker (AMM) algorithms. By aligning with the protocol, TRON  and BTTC will benefit from lower financial costs and indirect backing from prominent blockchains Curve DAO supports including <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/avalanche/avalanche-foundation-commits-50-million-to-tokenized-asset-purchases/">Avalanche</a>, <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/ethereum/ethereum-price-2000-august/">Ethereum</a>, and <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/is-arbitrum-promise-fading-downtime-metrics-decline-raise-arb-price-alarms/">Arbitrum</a>.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/huobi-ht/justin-sun-huobi-exchange-is-solvent/">Justin Sun</a> welcomed the newly formed alliance with enthusiasm. He commented that Curve Finance plays a pivotal role in the DeFi ecosystem and blockchain industry and looked forward to new innovative solutions promoted by the partnership. </p>
<p>&#8220;Curve is an essential DeFi infrastructure for the blockchain industry. Our thoughts are with the team and the users affected. As a community, let&#8217;s support and strengthen the security measures to protect our decentralized ecosystem,” Sun stated. </p>
<p><img decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/i3c2oKzF/" alt="Curve (CRV) price chart from Tradingview.com (TRON DAO)" width="2884" height="1746" loading="lazy"/></p>

<h2>Compensation For Hack Victims Following Tron Alliance</h2>
<p>The decentralized finance (DeFi) landscape was previously shaken up following news of a <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/curve-finance-fights-back-with-warning-and-unrefusable-offer-to-hacker/">hack</a> on the DEX. On July 30, Curve Finance fell victim to a reentrancy attack that exploited vulnerabilities in its smart contract codes, resulting in a loss of $62 million. </p>
<p>Following the news of the hack attack, the CRV token declined and the majority of the DeFi ecosystem was in panic. However, Curve Finance has <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/curve-finance-resurgence-70-of-stolen-funds-recovered-redemption-on-the-horizon/">reportedly recovered 70% of the funds</a> and to recover the rest of the stolen funds, the protocol has placed a <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/defi/curve-finance-announces-1-85-million-bounty/">bounty on the attacker, promising $1.85 million</a> to anyone able to reveal the hacker’s identity. </p>
<p>Curve Finance has also promised to compensate victims of the security breach. The DEX has stated that it will distribute reimbursements fairly as they determine the extent of damages and work toward recovering the stolen funds. </p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Curve-finance.jpeg?fit=460%2C274" width="460" height="274" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">547764</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Why Is Dogecoin Price Down Today?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/doge/why-is-dogecoin-price-down-today/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Best Owie]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 23:00:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[DOGE]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[doge]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Doge price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dogecoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dogeusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dogeusdt]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=547736</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Dogecoin price is down around 5% in the last day following the general market crash. The meme coin which had seen improved sentiment did a quick 180 and started to bleed. However, while the Dogecoin price could only be following Bitcoin’s descent, are there other factors driving the decline? Why Is Dogecoin Price Falling? One reason that the Dogecoin price is down today is due to its proximity to Shiba Inu. The latter saw a highly anticipated Shibarium launch go awry on Wednesday, sparking rapid declines among the meme coins in its ecosystem. Related Reading: Can Ethereum Price Cross $2,000 Before The End Of August? As a result of this unfortunate event, the price of SHIB fell almost 10% in a matter of hours and this seemed to have spilled over to Dogecoin. Dogecoin, being a meme coin and the largest competitor for Shiba Inu, was expected to rally if SHIB had gone up as a result of the Shibarium launch. There is also the issue of competition expected between Dogechain and Shibarium, further fueling this correlation. The problem with such correlations is that they tend to follow the same negative, as well as positive, path. Given this, when the price of Shiba Inu started to fall, Dogecoin followed suit with the expectations that both of these assets would go in the same direction. DOGE price falls alongside SHIB in volatile market conditions &#124; Source: DOGEUSD on Tradingview.com Additionally, DOGE, being one of the top 10 largest-crypto in the space, often tracks the performance of Bitcoin quite closely. So as Bitcoin declined off the back of the FOMC meeting, Dogecoin was hit with a double-decker bus, plunging it deep into the red territory. Can DOGE Price Recover From Here? It is not all bad news for Dogecoin according to crypto analyst “Tony The Bull.” In a recent analysis, he points out that DOGE had tagged the 1-month parabolic SAR. Now, this is notable because the last time the meme coin touched this level was back in 2021. DOGE tags 1M Parabolic SAR &#124; Source: Tony The Bull on X The result of this was that DOGE’s price went from $0.0018 to over $0.7. This translated to an over 24,000% increase at the time. So it stands to reason that if the altcoin is tagging this 1M parabolic SAR again, then there could be a rally in the near future. Related Reading: Will Bitcoin Price Crash Similarly To 2019 And 2020? However, it is unlikely that the price of DOGE will actually rise more than $50 at this level. This is because the crypto market is still in peak bear season while 2021 was peak bull season. Nevertheless, a rally toward $0.09 is not out of the question. Follow Best Owie on Twitter for market insights, updates, and the occasional funny tweet… Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="p2">The Dogecoin price is <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/doge/dogecoin-price-doge-weakness-below-0-07/">down around 5% in the last day</a> following the general market crash. The meme coin which had seen improved sentiment did a quick 180 and started to bleed. However, while the Dogecoin price could only be following Bitcoin’s descent, are there other factors driving the decline?</p>
<h2 class="p2">Why Is Dogecoin Price Falling?</h2>
<p class="p2">One reason that the Dogecoin price is down today is due to its proximity to Shiba Inu. The latter saw a highly <a href="http://Botched Shibarium Launch Sends Shiba Inu Price Spiraling Downward" rel="nofollow">anticipated Shibarium launch go awry</a> on Wednesday, sparking rapid declines among the meme coins in its ecosystem.</p>

<p class="p2">As a result of this unfortunate event, the price of <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/shiba-inu-shib-dips-by-7-following-shibarium-launch/">SHIB fell almost 10%</a> in a matter of hours and this seemed to have spilled over to Dogecoin. Dogecoin, being a meme coin and the largest competitor for Shiba Inu, was expected to rally if SHIB had gone up as a result of the Shibarium launch. There is also the issue of competition expected between Dogechain and Shibarium, further fueling this correlation.</p>
<p class="p2">The problem with such <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/ethereum/ethereum-ath-correlation-bitcoin-merge/">correlations</a> is that they tend to follow the same negative, as well as positive, path. Given this, when the price of Shiba Inu started to fall, Dogecoin followed suit with the expectations that both of these assets would go in the same direction.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/SOAQ2d9w/" alt="Dogecoin price chart from Tradingview.com" width="2884" height="1746"/></p>

<p class="p2">Additionally, DOGE, being one of the top 10 largest-crypto in the space, often tracks the performance of <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/early-signs-of-life-why-bitcoin-is-likely-to-move-away-from-30000-soon/">Bitcoin</a> quite closely. So as Bitcoin declined off the back of the FOMC meeting, Dogecoin was hit with a double-decker bus, plunging it deep into the red territory.</p>
<h2 class="p2">Can DOGE Price Recover From Here?</h2>
<p class="p2">It is not all bad news for Dogecoin according to crypto analyst “Tony The Bull.” In a recent <a href="https://twitter.com/tonythebullBTC/status/1690685052303069184?s=20" rel="nofollow">analysis</a>, he points out that DOGE had tagged the 1-month parabolic SAR. Now, this is notable because the last time the meme coin touched this level was back in 2021.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-547742 aligncenter" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Dogecoin-price.jpeg?w=460&#038;resize=460%2C286" alt="Dogecoin price" width="460" height="286" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Dogecoin-price.jpeg?w=2048 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Dogecoin-price.jpeg?w=460&#038;resize=460%2C286 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Dogecoin-price.jpeg?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Dogecoin-price.jpeg?w=860 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Dogecoin-price.jpeg?w=1536 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Dogecoin-price.jpeg?w=750 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Dogecoin-price.jpeg?w=1140 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px" data-recalc-dims="1"/></p>

<p class="p2">The result of this was that DOGE’s price went from $0.0018 to over $0.7. This translated to an over 24,000% increase at the time. So it stands to reason that if the altcoin is tagging this 1M parabolic SAR again, then there could be a rally in the near future.</p>

<p class="p2">However, it is unlikely that the price of DOGE will actually rise more than $50 at this level. This is because the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/crypto/crypto-trading-volumes-fall-to-lowest-level-in-2023/">crypto market is still in peak bear season</a> while 2021 was peak bull season. Nevertheless, a rally toward $0.09 is not out of the question.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/iStock-1325173675-1.jpg?fit=460%2C307" width="460" height="307" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">547736</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Will Bitcoin Volatility Continue? These Metrics Say Yes</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-volatility-continue-these-metrics-say-yes/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hououin Kyouma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 22:00:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin futures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Leverage Ratio]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Open interest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin volatility]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=547727</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin has observed some sharp price action today, and if data of these metrics is to go by, the asset may not be done being volatile just yet. Bitcoin&#8217;s Open Interest And Leverage Ratio Have Remained High As explained by an analyst in a CryptoQuant post, some metrics are forming a pattern that can lead to more volatility in the cryptocurrency&#8217;s price. These indicators are the open interest and the estimated leverage ratio. The &#8220;open interest&#8221; refers to the total amount of Bitcoin futures contracts that are open on all derivative exchanges. An increase in this metric suggests that the investors are opening more positions on the futures market right now, while a decrease implies some of them are closing their positions, or are getting liquidated. The other metric of interest here, the &#8220;estimated leverage ratio,&#8221; keeps track of the ratio between the open interest and the derivative exchange reserve (that is, the total amount of Bitcoin sitting in the wallets of these derivative platforms). What this metric tells us is the amount of leverage that futures users are opting for on average. High leverage can significantly increase the risk of a large number of contracts being liquidated, so whenever this metric has a high value, the market can become more probable to show high volatility due to violent liquidation events. Related Reading: Bitcoin Plunges To $28,500, Will This Historical Support Hold Again? Now, here is a chart that shows the trend in these two Bitcoin indicators over the past few days: Looks like both these metrics have observed high values in recent days &#124; Source: CryptoQuant As displayed in the above graph, the Bitcoin open interest and estimated leverage ratio had both been at relatively high values right before the plunge that the asset saw in the past 24 hours. In this sharp price plummet, the futures market naturally observed a high amount of liquidations, leading to the open interest registering some decrease. The metric, however, didn&#8217;t actually see that much of a cool down despite these liquidations, and it has now already reached back to the same levels it was at before the volatility. This would suggest that the futures market users have opened new positions since the mass liquidation event. While the open interest had gone down in this event, albeit briefly, the leverage ratio actually hadn&#8217;t budged even that much. Related Reading: Are Bitcoin Whales Selling? This Metric May Suggest So Rather, the indicator has only been going up, implying that the users opening up the new futures contracts are only opting for higher and higher amounts of leverage. Because of the open interest rebounding and the leverage ratio only trending higher, it would appear like a reasonable possibility that the Bitcoin price would observe more volatility in the near future. Such volatility can take the coin in either direction, but generally, the side of the market with the less amount of contracts is the more probable one. In the chart, the data for the &#8220;funding rates&#8221; is attached, which basically tells us whether the longs or the shorts are dominant in the futures market currently. The funding rates had been positive in the latest futures market overheat, as well as in the one seen earlier in the month, but following today&#8217;s long liquidations, the metric has turned negative. This may suggest that a liquidation event involving the shorts is more likely to happen next. BTC Price At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading around $28,500, down 3% in the last week. BTC has plunged during the past 24 hours &#124; Source: BTCUSD on TradingView Featured image from Kanchanara on Unsplash.com, charts from TradingView.com, CryptoQuant.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin has observed some sharp price action today, and if data of these metrics is to go by, the asset may not be done being volatile just yet.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin&#8217;s Open Interest And Leverage Ratio Have Remained High</h2>
<p>As explained by an analyst in a CryptoQuant <a href="https://cryptoquant.com/insights/quicktake/64ddfaa45b22350f81dccf79-Volatility-is-coming-again" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">post</a>, some metrics are forming a pattern that can lead to more volatility in the cryptocurrency&#8217;s price. These indicators are the open interest and the estimated leverage ratio.</p>
<p>The &#8220;<a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-open-interest-hits-peak-since-ftx-crash/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">open interest</a>&#8221; refers to the total amount of Bitcoin futures contracts that are open on all derivative exchanges. An increase in this metric suggests that the investors are opening more positions on the futures market right now, while a decrease implies some of them are closing their positions, or are getting liquidated.</p>
<p>The other metric of interest here, the &#8220;<a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-leverage-ratio-shoots-up-volatility-ahead/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">estimated leverage ratio</a>,&#8221; keeps track of the ratio between the open interest and the derivative exchange reserve (that is, the total amount of Bitcoin sitting in the wallets of these derivative platforms).</p>
<p>What this metric tells us is the amount of leverage that futures users are opting for on average. High leverage can significantly increase the risk of a large number of contracts being liquidated, so whenever this metric has a high value, the market can become more probable to show high volatility due to violent liquidation events.</p>

<p>Now, here is a chart that shows the trend in these two Bitcoin indicators over the past few days:</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone aligncenter" src="https://i0.wp.com/img.cryptoquant.com/35320/quicktake/KIT6TLr_90c78decbfad7b276a421da14e293aab518afe455daa71bc1881ecc17b451008.png?resize=1280%2C610&#038;ssl=1" alt="Bitcoin Open Interest &amp; Leverage Ratio" width="1280" height="610"  data-recalc-dims="1"/></p>

<p>As displayed in the above graph, the Bitcoin open interest and estimated leverage ratio had both been at relatively high values right before the plunge that the asset saw in the past 24 hours.</p>
<p>In this sharp price plummet, the futures market naturally observed a <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/crypto-futures-liquidations-150m-bitcoin-plummets/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">high amount of liquidations</a>, leading to the open interest registering some decrease. The metric, however, didn&#8217;t actually see that much of a cool down despite these liquidations, and it has now already reached back to the same levels it was at before the volatility.</p>
<p>This would suggest that the futures market users have opened new positions since the mass liquidation event. While the open interest had gone down in this event, albeit briefly, the leverage ratio actually hadn&#8217;t budged even that much.</p>

<p>Rather, the indicator has only been going up, implying that the users opening up the new futures contracts are only opting for higher and higher amounts of leverage.</p>
<p>Because of the open interest rebounding and the leverage ratio only trending higher, it would appear like a reasonable possibility that the Bitcoin price would observe more volatility in the near future.</p>
<p>Such volatility can take the coin in either direction, but generally, the side of the market with the less amount of contracts is the more probable one.</p>
<p>In the chart, the data for the &#8220;<a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-funding-rates-positive-feb-long-squeeze-soon/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">funding rates</a>&#8221; is attached, which basically tells us whether the longs or the shorts are dominant in the futures market currently.</p>
<p>The funding rates had been positive in the latest futures market overheat, as well as in the one seen earlier in the month, but following today&#8217;s long liquidations, the metric has turned negative. This may suggest that a liquidation event involving the shorts is more likely to happen next.</p>
<h2>BTC Price</h2>
<p>At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading around $28,500, down 3% in the last week.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium aligncenter" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/rNnQPOeY/" alt="Bitcoin Price Chart" width="1534" height="877"/></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/kanchanara-9BDBjEl_fDA-unsplash.jpg?fit=460%2C306" width="460" height="306" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">547727</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Faces A Weekly Double Top; This Needs To Happen</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-faces-weekly-double-top-this-needs-happen/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jake Simmons]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 20:00:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[double top]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=547709</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[In a recent analysis of the Bitcoin price, seasoned crypto analyst Rekt Capital discussed the looming presence of a potential double top formation on the weekly chart. The scenario paints a picture of impending volatility, with both bullish and bearish narratives emerging from this often foreboding pattern. &#8220;The BTC Double Top still remains intact,&#8221; tweeted Rekt Capital, emphasizing the technical structure&#8217;s significance. He continues, &#8220;Weekly Bearish Divergence lends additional bearish confluence to this structure as well. More, the bear div is developing a new lower high (dotted green) relative to its primary downtrend (solid green).&#8221; However, BTC would need to drop an additional -9% to -13% from current prices to complete its potential double top. But what makes this analysis particularly intriguing is the current state of Bitcoin&#8217;s volume. Rekt Capital further observes, &#8220;What&#8217;s interesting about the volume behind BTC&#8217;s price action is that the two recent peaks formed on inclining volume while the RSI formed lower highs.&#8221; For many, this simultaneous increase in volume with descending RSI hints at underlying market weakness, an insight further supported by the subsequent declining volume after the local top at approximately $31,000. Related Reading: Early Signs Of Life: Why Bitcoin Is Likely To Move Away From $30,000 Soon Diving deeper in his video analysis, Rekt Capital highlighted the need for a distinct &#8220;M&#8221;-shaped formation, a hallmark of the double top pattern. &#8220;For Bitcoin to form a double top here, we have to see an &#8216;M&#8217;-shaped formation take place. When we see a M form, that&#8217;s essentially a double top. One top here [at $30,800] and one top here [at $31,300].&#8221; Losing pivotal support levels could invite substantial downward movement. &#8220;Losing this [neckline] level at $26,000 as support would enable further downside,&#8221; warns the analyst. However, for traders and investors hoping for symmetrical behavior, Rekt Capital speculates, &#8220;And if we see symmetry here, a three month second part of this M could form so that&#8217;s going to prompt further downside and just slow bleeding into that 90 day-mark which would be around next month.&#8221; Related Reading: SEC Approval Could Propel Bitcoin To New Heights: Analyst Forecasts $150,000 Clearing Price But not all is bleak. Should Bitcoin trace back to $24,000, a retracement would &#8220;see us retest the neckline of this inverse head &#38; shoulders that we saw break out.&#8221; Rekt Capital adds, &#8220;So a retest of this level as a new support should actually enable further upside.&#8221; Also, a look at the 1-week chart also shows that there is another scenario for the invalidation of the double top. Bitcoin has formed an ascending trendline from its low in early January. Provided BTC can hold this trendline on a weekly basis and bounce up from there (at around $28,200), an invalidation would take place. The symmetry of the M would be broken, the uptrend on the higher time frames could continue. Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In a recent analysis of the Bitcoin price, seasoned crypto analyst Rekt Capital discussed the looming presence of a potential double top formation on the weekly chart. The <a href="https://twitter.com/rektcapital" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">scenario</a> paints a picture of impending volatility, with both bullish and bearish narratives emerging from this often foreboding pattern.</p>
<p>&#8220;The BTC Double Top still remains intact,&#8221; tweeted Rekt Capital, emphasizing the technical structure&#8217;s significance. He continues, &#8220;Weekly Bearish Divergence lends additional bearish confluence to this structure as well. More, the bear div is developing a new lower high (dotted green) relative to its primary downtrend (solid green).&#8221; However, BTC would need to drop an additional -9% to -13% from current prices to complete its potential double top.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-547730 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F3ufo5MWkAELnRE.jpg?resize=1788%2C1264" alt="Bitcoin weekly double top" width="1788" height="1264" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F3ufo5MWkAELnRE.jpg?resize=1788%2C1264?w=1788 1788w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F3ufo5MWkAELnRE.jpg?resize=1788%2C1264?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F3ufo5MWkAELnRE.jpg?resize=1788%2C1264?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F3ufo5MWkAELnRE.jpg?resize=1788%2C1264?w=860 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F3ufo5MWkAELnRE.jpg?resize=1788%2C1264?w=1536 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F3ufo5MWkAELnRE.jpg?resize=1788%2C1264?w=120 120w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F3ufo5MWkAELnRE.jpg?resize=1788%2C1264?w=750 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F3ufo5MWkAELnRE.jpg?resize=1788%2C1264?w=1140 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" data-recalc-dims="1"/>
<p>But what makes this analysis particularly intriguing is the current state of Bitcoin&#8217;s volume. Rekt Capital further observes, &#8220;What&#8217;s interesting about the volume behind BTC&#8217;s price action is that the two recent peaks formed on inclining volume while the RSI formed lower highs.&#8221; For many, this simultaneous increase in volume with descending RSI hints at underlying market weakness, an insight further supported by the subsequent declining volume after the local top at approximately $31,000.</p>

<p>Diving deeper in his video analysis, Rekt Capital highlighted the need for a distinct &#8220;M&#8221;-shaped formation, a hallmark of the double top pattern. &#8220;For Bitcoin to form a double top here, we have to see an &#8216;M&#8217;-shaped formation take place. When we see a M form, that&#8217;s essentially a double top. One top here [at $30,800] and one top here [at $31,300].&#8221;</p>
<p>Losing pivotal support levels could invite substantial downward movement. &#8220;Losing this [neckline] level at $26,000 as support would enable further downside,&#8221; warns the analyst. However, for traders and investors hoping for symmetrical behavior, Rekt Capital speculates, &#8220;And if we see symmetry here, a three month second part of this M could form so that&#8217;s going to prompt further downside and just slow bleeding into that 90 day-mark which would be around next month.&#8221;</p>

<p>But not all is bleak. Should Bitcoin trace back to $24,000, a retracement would &#8220;see us retest the neckline of this inverse head &amp; shoulders that we saw break out.&#8221; Rekt Capital adds, &#8220;So a retest of this level as a new support should actually enable further upside.&#8221;</p>
<p>Also, a look at the 1-week chart also shows that there is another scenario for the invalidation of the double top. Bitcoin has formed an ascending trendline from its low in early January. Provided BTC can hold this trendline on a weekly basis and bounce up from there (at around $28,200), an invalidation would take place. The symmetry of the M would be broken, the uptrend on the higher time frames could continue.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-547733 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD_2023-08-17_14-13-48.png?resize=3628%2C1672" alt="Bitcoin price" width="3628" height="1672" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD_2023-08-17_14-13-48.png?resize=3628%2C1672?w=3628 3628w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD_2023-08-17_14-13-48.png?resize=3628%2C1672?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD_2023-08-17_14-13-48.png?resize=3628%2C1672?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD_2023-08-17_14-13-48.png?resize=3628%2C1672?w=860 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD_2023-08-17_14-13-48.png?resize=3628%2C1672?w=1536 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD_2023-08-17_14-13-48.png?resize=3628%2C1672?w=2048 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD_2023-08-17_14-13-48.png?resize=3628%2C1672?w=750 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD_2023-08-17_14-13-48.png?resize=3628%2C1672?w=1140 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD_2023-08-17_14-13-48.png?resize=3628%2C1672?w=3000 3000w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" data-recalc-dims="1"/>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/iStock-1397377530.jpg?fit=460%2C259" width="460" height="259" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">547709</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>PayPal And The Crypto Conundrum: Understanding The UK Sales Suspension</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/paypal-and-the-crypto-conundrum-understanding-the-uk-sales-suspension/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 19:00:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto policy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Regulations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Financial Conduct Authority]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[paypal]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=547673</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[PayPal has announced a temporary suspension of cryptocurrency sales within the United Kingdom for a minimum of three months, commencing on October 1. This decision is in direct response to the recent regulatory reforms introduced by the Financial Conduct Authority, Britain&#8217;s financial regulator.  The FCA is set to implement more stringent guidelines aimed at curbing the advertising of cryptocurrencies to British consumers, which includes the mandatory inclusion of risk warnings and the discontinuation of &#8220;refer a friend&#8221; incentives. Related Reading: Chiliz (CHZ) Empowers Smart Contracts With Upgrades – Positive Impact On Price? Adapting To Regulatory Landscape In an email to customers, PayPal UK explained that customers who currently hold cryptocurrency in their PayPal accounts will be able to retain their holdings on the platform without incurring any fees. Furthermore, the option to sell their cryptocurrency at any time will remain available.  PayPal will &#8216;pause&#8217; crypto purchases in UK 🇬🇧 pic.twitter.com/NPkj7F61cC — Crypto Crib (@Crypto_Crib_) August 16, 2023 However, the ability to purchase cryptocurrencies using PayPal will be temporarily suspended during the company&#8217;s efforts to ensure compliance with the new regulations set forth by the FCA. This move comes against the backdrop of the impending enforcement of the &#8220;Travel Rule&#8221; in the UK. As of September 1, 2023, all cryptocurrency firms registered under the FCA will be obligated to adhere to the Travel Rule guidelines, a series of crucial Anti-Money Laundering and Know-Your-Customer regulations established by the Financial Action Task Force (FATF). This mandate was introduced following governmental amendments to relevant legislation in July 2022. Bitcoin (BTC) is currently trading at $28.525. Chart: TradingView.com PayPal: Foray In The Crypto Landscape PayPal, which has rapidly solidified its reputation as a crypto-friendly platform, introduced a notable addition to its offerings with the launch of its PayPal USD (PYUSD) stablecoin early this month. The company originally unveiled its foray into the cryptocurrency realm within the United States in late 2020, positioning itself as a key player in the ever-evolving landscape of financial technology. Source: PayPal As the financial industry grapples with the ongoing integration of cryptocurrencies, PayPal&#8217;s response to regulatory changes highlights the evolving nature of the relationship between traditional financial platforms and the burgeoning world of digital currencies.  Related Reading: Cardano Holder Resilience Tested As ADA Fends Off Bearish Onslaught While the company navigates these challenges, users and industry stakeholders alike are keenly observing how this temporary pause in cryptocurrency sales will shape the future of PayPal&#8217;s engagement with the crypto market within the UK. PayPal&#8217;s decision to temporarily suspend cryptocurrency sales in response to new FCA regulations underscores the complex interplay between regulatory developments and the cryptocurrency industry. As the company strives to align with evolving standards, the trajectory of its cryptocurrency ventures will continue to influence the broader financial landscape. Featured image from Francois Poirier/Shutterstock.com.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>PayPal has announced a temporary suspension of cryptocurrency sales within the United Kingdom for a minimum of three months, commencing on October 1. This decision is in direct response to the recent regulatory reforms introduced by the Financial Conduct Authority, Britain&#8217;s financial regulator. </p>
<p>The FCA is set to implement more stringent guidelines aimed at curbing the advertising of cryptocurrencies to British consumers, which includes the mandatory inclusion of risk warnings and the discontinuation of &#8220;refer a friend&#8221; incentives.</p>

<h2><strong>Adapting To Regulatory Landscape</strong></h2>
<p>In an email to customers, <a href="https://twitter.com/Crypto_Crib_/status/1691661748359614481" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">PayPal UK explained</a> that customers who currently hold cryptocurrency in their PayPal accounts will be able to retain their holdings on the platform without incurring any fees. Furthermore, the option to sell their cryptocurrency at any time will remain available. </p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">PayPal will &#8216;pause&#8217; crypto purchases in UK <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f1ec-1f1e7.png" alt="🇬🇧" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> <a href="https://t.co/NPkj7F61cC" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/NPkj7F61cC</a></p>
<p>— Crypto Crib (@Crypto_Crib_) <a href="https://twitter.com/Crypto_Crib_/status/1691661748359614481?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">August 16, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p>However, the ability to purchase cryptocurrencies using PayPal will be temporarily suspended during the company&#8217;s efforts to ensure compliance with the new regulations set forth by the FCA.</p>
<p>This move comes against the backdrop of the impending enforcement of the &#8220;Travel Rule&#8221; in the UK. As of September 1, 2023, all cryptocurrency firms registered under the FCA will be obligated to adhere to the Travel Rule guidelines, a series of crucial Anti-Money Laundering and Know-Your-Customer regulations established by the Financial Action Task Force (FATF). </p>
<p>This mandate was introduced following governmental amendments to relevant legislation in July 2022.<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/92UF3gyi/" width="1835" height="893"/></p>

<h2><strong>PayPal: Foray In The Crypto Landscape</strong></h2>
<p>PayPal, which has rapidly solidified its reputation as a <a href="https://finance.yahoo.com/news/paypal-halt-uk-crypto-sales-134938414.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">crypto-friendly platform</a>, introduced a notable addition to its offerings with the launch of its PayPal USD (PYUSD) stablecoin early this month. </p>
<p>The company originally unveiled its foray into the cryptocurrency realm within the United States in late 2020, positioning itself as a key player in the ever-evolving landscape of financial technology.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-547731" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-97.png?resize=465%2C484" alt="" width="465" height="484" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-97.png?resize=465%2C484?w=465 465w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-97.png?resize=465%2C484?w=442 442w" sizes="(max-width: 465px) 100vw, 465px" data-recalc-dims="1"/></p>

<p>As the financial industry grapples with the ongoing integration of cryptocurrencies, PayPal&#8217;s response to regulatory changes highlights the evolving nature of the relationship between traditional financial platforms and the burgeoning world of digital currencies. </p>

<p>While the company navigates these challenges, users and industry stakeholders alike are keenly observing how this temporary pause in cryptocurrency sales will shape the future of PayPal&#8217;s engagement with the <a href="https://forkast.news/headlines/paypal-uk-crypto-sales-pause/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">crypto market within the UK</a>.</p>
<p>PayPal&#8217;s decision to temporarily suspend cryptocurrency sales in response to new FCA regulations underscores the complex interplay between regulatory developments and the cryptocurrency industry. </p>
<p>As the company strives to align with evolving standards, the trajectory of its cryptocurrency ventures will continue to influence the broader financial landscape.</p>
<p><em>Featured image from Francois Poirier/Shutterstock.com.</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-23.jpg?fit=460%2C370" width="460" height="370" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">547673</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Buying The Dip? Shiba Inu Whale Activity Surges As Price Declines Nearly 10%</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/buying-the-dip-shiba-inu-whale-activity-surges/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samuel Edyme]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 18:00:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Shiba Inu]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIB]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIBUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=547695</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Shiba Inu (SHIB), a dog-inspired meme coin, originally dismissed by many as just another fleeting fad, is now drawing serious attention from big players, or &#8220;whales,&#8221; in the crypto space. This attention comes amid the tokens&#8217; recent sloppy launch of its other project, Shibarium. Blockchain security team Beosin recently reported that the newly deployed Shibarium platform has had transactions stalled in a pending state, tying up approximately 1,003 ether, equivalent to $1.8 million in locked funds.  🚨Transactions on #Shibarium are stuck in a pending state. $1.7M are currently locked on ETH. Users are advised to temporarily stop using shibarium.https://t.co/io5puAibBc https://t.co/q2SXqtthoO — Beosin Alert (@BeosinAlert) August 17, 2023 This sloppy launch has affected the SHIB token negatively seeing the tokens&#8217; price decline by nearly 10% over the past 24 hours. However, despite this plunge whales are reportedly still making moves on Shiba Inu. Related Reading: Shiba Inu’s DeFi Aspirations May Rattle DOGE’s Market As SHIB Turns To Digital IDs Shiba Inu Whale Activity Surges According to Santiment, a prominent blockchain data firm, there has been a noticeable increase in transaction activity by whales across several digital currencies, including SHIB and XRP. 🐳 As the crowd feels the pain, there are several assets seeing an increase in whale activity. As they attempt to capitalize on the discounted prices, read about the four projects we&#8217;re seeing some notable activity rises: $SHIB, $XRP, $SAND, &#38; $CAKE https://t.co/SnuKebg7h1 pic.twitter.com/VWKlH95yU0 — Santiment (@santimentfeed) August 17, 2023 Specifically, for Shiba Inu, the numbers are compelling. Santiment&#8217;s data shows that there&#8217;s been a surge in transfers of SHIB valued at $1 million or higher. According to Santiment, a possible reason for the increase in whale activity could be that these large investors are attempting to &#8220;capitalize on discount prices&#8221; of Shiba Inu and the other cryptocurrencies recording a surge in whale activity Furthermore, this uptick in activity closely follows significant events in the Shiba Inu ecosystem, particularly the mainnet launch of Shibarium, which could be another contributing factor. Shibarium represents a crucial advancement for the SHIB community and its broader ecosystem. And though its launch didn&#8217;t go as planned, its introduction likely plays a role in attracting these large investors and traders to SHIB, looking to capitalize on new opportunities brought about by the platform&#8217;s capabilities. SHIB Declines Nearly 10% In The Past Day Over the past 24 hours, Shiba Inu has been in red regardless of the surging whale activity. Particularly, the dog-inspired meme coin has recorded a loss of 9.9% over this period and with a current market price of $0.0000087, at the time of writing. This plunge is also reflected in the asset&#8217;s market capitalization which has seen a substantial loss of more than $600 million in the past day. Interestingly, despite the blood bath, Shiba Inu&#8217;s daily trading volume has remained resilient. Related Reading: Shiba Inu (SHIB) Dips By 7% Following Shibarium Launch Over the past day, SHIB&#8217;s trading volume has hovered above $450 million and currently stands at a value of $461 million at the time of writing. Featured image from Unsplash, Chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Shiba Inu (SHIB), a dog-inspired meme coin, originally dismissed by many as just another fleeting fad, is now drawing serious attention from big players, or &#8220;whales,&#8221; in the crypto space. This attention comes amid the tokens&#8217; recent sloppy launch of its <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/shiba-inu-defi-aspirations-may-rattle-doges-market-as-shib-turns-to-digital-ids/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">other project</a>, Shibarium.</p>
<p>Blockchain security team Beosin recently <a href="https://twitter.com/BeosinAlert/status/1692003409602445743?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">reported</a> that the newly deployed Shibarium platform has had transactions stalled in a pending state, tying up approximately 1,003 ether, equivalent to $1.8 million in locked funds. </p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en"><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f6a8.png" alt="🚨" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />Transactions on <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Shibarium?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#Shibarium</a> are stuck in a pending state.
$1.7M are currently locked on ETH.</p>
<p>Users are advised to temporarily stop using shibarium.<a href="https://t.co/io5puAibBc" rel="nofollow">https://t.co/io5puAibBc</a> <a href="https://t.co/q2SXqtthoO" rel="nofollow">https://t.co/q2SXqtthoO</a></p>
<p>— Beosin Alert (@BeosinAlert) <a href="https://twitter.com/BeosinAlert/status/1692003409602445743?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">August 17, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p>This sloppy launch has affected the SHIB token negatively seeing the tokens&#8217; price decline by nearly 10% over the past 24 hours. However, despite this plunge whales are reportedly still making moves on Shiba Inu.</p>

<h2>Shiba Inu Whale Activity Surges</h2>
<p>According to <a href="https://twitter.com/santimentfeed/status/1691982477710311568?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Santiment</a>, a prominent blockchain data firm, there has been a noticeable increase in transaction activity by whales across several digital currencies, including SHIB and XRP. </p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en"><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f433.png" alt="🐳" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> As the crowd feels the pain, there are several assets seeing an increase in whale activity. As they attempt to capitalize on the discounted prices, read about the four projects we&#8217;re seeing some notable activity rises: <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24SHIB&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$SHIB</a>, <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24XRP&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$XRP</a>, <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24SAND&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$SAND</a>, &amp; <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24CAKE&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$CAKE</a> <a href="https://t.co/SnuKebg7h1" rel="nofollow">https://t.co/SnuKebg7h1</a> <a href="https://t.co/VWKlH95yU0" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/VWKlH95yU0</a></p>
<p>— Santiment (@santimentfeed) <a href="https://twitter.com/santimentfeed/status/1691982477710311568?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">August 17, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p>Specifically, for Shiba Inu, the numbers are compelling. Santiment&#8217;s data shows that there&#8217;s been a surge in transfers of SHIB valued at <a href="https://insights.santiment.net/read/following-the-whale-while-others-fail-7360?utm_source=twitter&amp;utm_medium=post&amp;utm_campaign=twitter_following_the_whale_insight_b_081623/&amp;fpr=twitter" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">$1 million or higher</a>. </p>
<p>According to Santiment, a possible reason for the increase in whale activity could be that these large investors are attempting to &#8220;capitalize on discount prices&#8221; of Shiba Inu and the other cryptocurrencies recording a surge in whale activity</p>
<p>Furthermore, this uptick in activity closely follows significant events in the Shiba Inu ecosystem, particularly the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/shiba-inu-shib-dips-by-7-following-shibarium-launch/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">mainnet launch of Shibarium</a>, which could be another contributing factor.</p>
<p>Shibarium represents a crucial advancement for the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/shiba-inu-dao-advisory-firm/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">SHIB community</a> and its broader ecosystem. And though its launch didn&#8217;t go as planned, its introduction likely plays a role in attracting these large investors and traders to SHIB, looking to capitalize on new opportunities brought about by the platform&#8217;s capabilities.</p>
<h2>SHIB Declines Nearly 10% In The Past Day</h2>
<p>Over the past 24 hours, Shiba Inu has been in red regardless of the surging whale activity. Particularly, the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/voyager-sells-1-4-trillion-shiba-inu-but-good-news/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">dog-inspired meme coin</a> has recorded a loss of 9.9% over this period and with a current market price of $0.0000087, at the time of writing.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/YmjPCPC9/" alt="Shiba Inu (SHIB)’s price chart on TradingView" width="2770" height="1408"/>
<p>This plunge is also reflected in the asset&#8217;s market capitalization which has seen a substantial loss of more than $600 million in the past day. Interestingly, despite the blood bath, Shiba Inu&#8217;s daily trading volume has remained resilient.</p>

<p>Over the past day, SHIB&#8217;s trading volume has <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/shiba-inu-bulls-on-the-horizon-substantial-selling-pressure-seen-dropping/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">hovered above $450 million</a> and currently stands at a value of $461 million at the time of writing.</p>
<p>Featured image from Unsplash, Chart from TradingView</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/todd-cravens-QnBrjY-nFUs-unsplash-2.jpg?fit=460%2C305" width="460" height="305" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">547695</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ledger Users Can Now Buy Crypto Directly Using PayPal</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/crypto/ledger-paypal-buy-crypto/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 17:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto adoption]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ledger]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ledger Live]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[paypal]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=547689</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[PayPal has taken another step in its crypto mission following a team-up with hardware wallet provider Ledger. This time around, the payments giant is making it possible for users to purchase crypto directly without the need for extra verifications. Ledger Live Integration With Paypal On August 16, Ledger and PaPal announced an integration to make buying cryptocurrencies easier. This feature will allow users to purchase crypto using PayPal directly from the Ledger Live app. Chairman and CEO Pascal Gauthier of Ledger made a statement about integrating Ledger Live with Paypal to make crypto transactions easier. “Both PayPal and Ledger are focused on creating secure, seamless, and fast transactions no matter where you are in the world. PayPal,&#8221; Gauthier said. &#8220;We’re combining the uncompromising security of Ledger with PayPal&#8217;s leadership in protected payments technology to help facilitate a seamless platform for user crypto transactions.&#8221; Related Reading: Shiba Inu DAO Gets Serious With New Advisory And Investment Firm Ledger Live’s integration with Paypal currently offers four cryptocurrencies in the US, such as Bitcoin (BTC), Ether (ETH), Bitcoin Cash (BCH), and Litecoin (LTC), and this will allow US residents to be able to purchase these cryptocurrencies with their verified Paypal accounts with no extra verification required. What makes this integration so interesting is that no &#8220;withdrawal&#8221; process needs to be initiated by a user. All the crypto purchases made through Paypal via Ledger Live are immediately sent to the user&#8217;s wallet, according to the announcement. PYPL price drops to $59 &#124; Source: PayPal Holdings, Inc. on Tradingview.com Ledger Live’s integration with Paypal is indeed a significant step in the financial tech world, as the two giants share a similar vision of creating fast and seamless transactions on a universal scale. Ledger is one of the most notable hardware wallet manufacturers, recording over 6 million Ledger Nano hardware wallet sales all around the world since 2016. Also, Ledger launched its Tradelink service in 2023 that will enable &#8220;off-exchange trading, enhanced security, distribution of risk, zero transaction fees, and a more efficient and faster trading” for institutional investors. Paypal’s interest in the crypto world is by no means new. On August 7, Paypal made an announcement to launch its own Ethereum-based stablecoin called PYUSD.  However, nothing was said about PYUSD being listed as one of the coins that will be available on the Ledger Live just yet. Related Reading: Executives Of Crypto-Friendly Bank Silvergate Step Down As Lawsuits, Liquidation Rages On PYUSD’s launch has not been smooth either with regulators calling for more oversight following the launch. Last week, US congresswoman Maxine Waters called for federal oversight and enforcement of PayPal after launching the stablecoin. PayPal also revealed plans to allow select customers to purchase cryptocurrencies such as Bitcoin and Ethereum using PYUSD. However, amid the new UK regulatory system that will come into play on October 8, Paypal plans to temporarily pause the buying of cryptocurrencies in the country from October 1 to resume crypto services in the Q1 of 2024. Featured image from iStock, chart from Tradingview.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>PayPal has taken another step in its crypto mission following a team-up with hardware wallet provider Ledger. This time around, the payments giant is making it possible for users to purchase crypto directly without the need for extra verifications.</p>
<h2>Ledger Live Integration With Paypal</h2>
<p>On August 16, Ledger and PaPal <a href="https://www.ledger.com/ledger-and-paypal-team-up-to-simplify-entry-into-the-world-of-cryptocurrency" rel="nofollow">announced</a> an integration to make buying cryptocurrencies easier. This feature will allow users to purchase crypto using PayPal directly from the Ledger Live app.</p>
<p>Chairman and CEO Pascal Gauthier of Ledger made a statement about integrating Ledger Live with Paypal to make crypto transactions easier.</p>
<p>“Both PayPal and Ledger are focused on creating secure, seamless, and fast transactions no matter where you are in the world. PayPal,&#8221; Gauthier said. &#8220;We’re combining the uncompromising security of Ledger with PayPal&#8217;s leadership in protected payments technology to help facilitate a seamless platform for user crypto transactions.&#8221;</p>

<p>Ledger Live’s integration with Paypal currently offers four cryptocurrencies in the US, such as<a href="https://bitcoinist.com/why-is-bitcoin-price-down-today/" rel="nofollow"> Bitcoin (BTC)</a>, <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/ethereum-open-interest-rises-are-shorts-piling-up/" rel="nofollow">Ether (ETH)</a>, <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-cash-miners-withdrawals/" rel="nofollow">Bitcoin Cash (BCH)</a>, and <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/litecoin-hashrate-ath-despite-miner-rewards-halved/" rel="nofollow">Litecoin (LTC)</a>, and this will allow US residents to be able to purchase these cryptocurrencies with their verified Paypal accounts with no extra verification required.</p>
<p>What makes this integration so interesting is that no &#8220;withdrawal&#8221; process needs to be initiated by a user. All the crypto purchases made through Paypal via Ledger Live are immediately sent to the user&#8217;s wallet, according to the announcement.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/gz1vAJlb/" alt="PayPal stock price chart from Tradingview.com (Ledger Live)" width="2884" height="1746"/></p>

<p>Ledger Live’s integration with Paypal is indeed a significant step in the financial tech world, as the two giants share a similar vision of creating fast and seamless transactions on a universal scale.</p>
<p>Ledger is one of the most notable hardware wallet manufacturers, recording over 6 million Ledger Nano hardware wallet sales all around the world since 2016. Also, Ledger <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/ledger-launches-institutional-trading-platform/" rel="nofollow">launched</a> its Tradelink service in 2023 that will enable &#8220;off-exchange trading, enhanced security, distribution of risk, zero transaction fees, and a more efficient and faster trading” for institutional investors.</p>
<p>Paypal’s interest in the crypto world is by no means new. On August 7, Paypal made an <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/paypal-stablecoin-sparks-political-fury/" rel="nofollow">announcement</a> to launch its own Ethereum-based stablecoin called PYUSD. </p>
<p>However, nothing was said about PYUSD being listed as one of the coins that will be available on the Ledger Live just yet.</p>

<p>PYUSD’s launch has not been smooth either with regulators calling for more oversight following the launch. Last week, US congresswoman Maxine Waters <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/stablecoin/us-congresswoman-raises-concerns-about-paypal-pyusd-stablecoin/">called for federal oversight and enforcement</a> of PayPal after launching the stablecoin.</p>
<p>PayPal also revealed plans to allow select customers to purchase cryptocurrencies such as Bitcoin and Ethereum using PYUSD. However, amid the new UK regulatory system that will come into play on October 8, Paypal plans to <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/paypal-puts-crypto-sales-on-ice-uk-customers/" rel="nofollow">temporarily pause the buying of cryptocurrencies</a> in the country from October 1 to resume crypto services in the Q1 of 2024.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/iStock-1201823658.jpg?fit=460%2C307" width="460" height="307" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">547689</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Plunges To $28,500, Will This Historical Support Hold Again?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-plunges-28500-historical-support-hold-again/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hououin Kyouma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 15:50:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Realized Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin short-term holders]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin support]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=547642</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin has plunged toward the $28,500 mark during the past day, which happens to be quite near a historically significant support line. Bitcoin Is Now Near The Short-Term Holder Realized Price As pointed out by an analyst in a CryptoQuant post, BTC&#8217;s latest drawdown has brought it near the realized price of the short-term holders. The &#8220;realized price&#8221; here refers to a metric that&#8217;s derived from the &#8220;realized cap&#8221; model of Bitcoin. The realized cap calculates the total valuation of the asset by assuming that the actual value of any coin in circulation is not the current spot price, but the price at which the coin was last transacted on the chain. Since the last transfer price of any coin is likely to represent its buying price, this model accounts for the prices that each investor in the market bought their coins, and hence, the realized cap may be looked at as a measure of the total capital that holders have put into the cryptocurrency. When this model is divided by the total number of coins in circulation, the average cost basis or acquisition price in the market is obtained. This is precisely what the realized price is. Related Reading: Are Bitcoin Whales Selling? This Metric May Suggest So If the Bitcoin spot price goes below this indicator, it means that the average investor has gone underwater. Similarly, breaks above the metric signify a return to profits for the majority of the market. The realized price can also be defined for specific segments of the market. In the context of the current discussion, one part of the market is of relevance: the &#8220;short-term holders&#8221; (STHs). Here is a chart that shows the trend in the Bitcoin realized price for this cohort: Looks like the value of the metric has approached the price recently &#124; Source: CryptoQuant The STHs include all investors who bought their coins within the last 155 days. The holders that pass beyond this threshold are termed &#8220;long-term holders&#8221; (LTHs). From the chart, it&#8217;s visible that with the latest decline, the Bitcoin spot price has come very close to the STH realized price. This would suggest that these investors as a whole are about breaking even on their investment currently. In the chart, the quant has highlighted how previous retests of this line have gone in this year so far. Interestingly, both back in March and June, the cryptocurrency found support at this metric and observed a sharp rebound. This is a trend that has historically been seen during bullish periods. The reason behind this curious pattern may perhaps be the fact that the STHs look at their cost basis as a profitable point for accumulating more of the asset in such periods, as they believe that the price would only go up in the near future. Related Reading: Bitcoin &#38; Top Assets See High Loss Taking, Is This Bullish? The extraordinary buying pressure at the line may be why the asset finds support at this level as well. This is because the opposite happens during bearish periods, as holders look to escape the market at their break-even point. It now remains to be seen how Bitcoin&#8217;s interaction with the STH realized price will go this time around. Naturally, a successful retest would be a positive sign for the rally, as it would show that these investors haven&#8217;t yet lost their bullish conviction in the coin. BTC Price At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading around $28,500, down 3% in the last week. The value of the asset has plunged &#124; Source: BTCUSD on TradingView Featured image from iStock.com, charts from TradingView.com, CryptoQuant.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin has plunged toward the $28,500 mark during the past day, which happens to be quite near a historically significant support line.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Is Now Near The Short-Term Holder Realized Price</h2>
<p>As pointed out by an analyst in a CryptoQuant <a href="https://cryptoquant.com/insights/quicktake/64dd8346dcf5141b5e5d81f8-Short-Term-Holders-Realized-Price-STH-RP-A-Deeper-Look" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">post</a>, BTC&#8217;s latest drawdown has brought it near the realized price of the short-term holders. The &#8220;<a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-under-realized-price-163-days/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">realized price</a>&#8221; here refers to a metric that&#8217;s derived from the &#8220;realized cap&#8221; model of Bitcoin.</p>
<p>The realized cap calculates the total valuation of the asset by assuming that the actual value of any coin in circulation is not the current spot price, but the price at which the coin was last transacted on the chain.</p>
<p>Since the last transfer price of any coin is likely to represent its buying price, this model accounts for the prices that each investor in the market bought their coins, and hence, the realized cap may be looked at as a measure of the total capital that holders have put into the cryptocurrency.</p>
<p>When this model is divided by the total number of coins in circulation, the average cost basis or acquisition price in the market is obtained. This is precisely what the realized price is.</p>

<p>If the Bitcoin spot price goes below this indicator, it means that the average investor has gone underwater. Similarly, breaks above the metric signify a return to profits for the majority of the market.</p>
<p>The realized price can also be defined for specific segments of the market. In the context of the current discussion, one part of the market is of relevance: the &#8220;<a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-short-term-holders-exchange-inflows-price/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">short-term holders</a>&#8221; (STHs).</p>
<p>Here is a chart that shows the trend in the Bitcoin realized price for this cohort:</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone aligncenter" src="https://i0.wp.com/img.cryptoquant.com/280562/quicktake/iDT5g_14926cbbdc30456362f8f22008a615384496d901c3720c505da404a0470fbc97.png?resize=1280%2C806&#038;ssl=1" alt="Bitcoin Short-Term Holders Realized Price" width="1280" height="806"  data-recalc-dims="1"/></p>

<p>The STHs include all investors who bought their coins within the last 155 days. The holders that pass beyond this threshold are termed &#8220;<a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-speculators-retreat-as-long-term-holders-double-down/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">long-term holders</a>&#8221; (LTHs).</p>
<p>From the chart, it&#8217;s visible that with the latest decline, the Bitcoin spot price has come very close to the STH realized price. This would suggest that these investors as a whole are about breaking even on their investment currently.</p>
<p>In the chart, the quant has highlighted how previous retests of this line have gone in this year so far. Interestingly, both back in March and June, the cryptocurrency found support at this metric and observed a sharp rebound.</p>
<p>This is a trend that has historically been seen during bullish periods. The reason behind this curious pattern may perhaps be the fact that the STHs look at their cost basis as a profitable point for accumulating more of the asset in such periods, as they believe that the price would only go up in the near future.</p>

<p>The extraordinary buying pressure at the line may be why the asset finds support at this level as well. This is because the opposite happens during bearish periods, as holders look to escape the market at their break-even point.</p>
<p>It now remains to be seen how Bitcoin&#8217;s interaction with the STH realized price will go this time around. Naturally, a successful retest would be a positive sign for the rally, as it would show that these investors haven&#8217;t yet lost their bullish conviction in the coin.</p>
<h2>BTC Price</h2>
<p>At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading around $28,500, down 3% in the last week.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium aligncenter" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/OeByFnql/" alt="Bitcoin Price Chart" width="1534" height="877"/></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/iStock-1304093999.jpg?fit=460%2C299" width="460" height="299" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">547642</post-id>	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
