<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"

	xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
	xmlns:geo="http://www.w3.org/2003/01/geo/wgs84_pos#"
	>

<channel>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.newsbtc.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<description>Bitcoin &#38; Cryptocurrency News Today</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 19:25:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-cropped-favicon.png?fit=32%2C32</url>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
<site xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">221170450</site>	<item>
		<title>Maker Large Holders Accumulate, MKR Rally To Continue?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/maker-mkr/maker-large-holders-accumulate-mkr-rally-continue/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hououin Kyouma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 20:00:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Maker (MKR)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[maker]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Maker Large Holders]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Maker Rally]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Maker Whales]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MKR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MKRUSD]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=547172</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[On-chain data shows large Maker holders have accumulated recently, a sign that the rally could extend soon. Maker Large Holders Have Continued To Expand Their Holdings Recently According to data from the market intelligence platform IntoTheBlock, inflows to the wallets of the large MKR investors have been taking place for a while now. The &#8220;large holders&#8221; here refer to those investors who hold at least 0.1% of the cryptocurrency&#8217;s circulating supply. In Maker&#8217;s case, this value would equal about $1.2 million. Thus, the only holders who would clear these criteria would be the sharks and whales, the largest entities on the network. These investors generally hold some influence in the market, as they can move many tokens at once. Thus, the behavior of this cohort could be worth watching, as it may reveal answers about where the asset might be heading next. One way to track the behavior of these humongous holders is through the &#8220;netflow&#8221; metric, which measures the net amount of MKR that these large investors are adding into or moving out of their combined holdings right now. When the value of this metric is positive, it means that a net number of coins is entering into the supply of these investors currently, suggesting that they are participating in buying. On the other hand, negative values could imply that this group may be selling as its members are transferring a net amount of the asset away from their wallets. Related Reading: SHIB, PEPE, APE Gain Against Bitcoin, Santiment Explains What This Means Now, here is a chart that shows the trend in the Maker large holders netflow over the last few months: The value of the metric seems to have been positive in recent days &#124; Source: IntoTheBlock on X The above graph shows that the Maker large holders&#8217; netflow has been almost entirely positive during the past few months. There were a few dips into the negative territory, but the net outflows weren&#8217;t significant in scale then. In the past few weeks, there haven&#8217;t been any drops below the zero mark, suggesting that the large holders have only continued accumulating more MKR recently. Something to note here is that a positive netflow doesn&#8217;t mean that there isn&#8217;t any selling taking place at all. Instead, it simply suggests that the accumulation is enough to cancel any distribution. Related Reading: Goldman Foresees Q2 2024 Fed Rate Cut: A Boost For Bitcoin? In the past couple of months, the cryptocurrency has seen an overall uptrend, which could be a consequence of the net buying these investors have been participating in. Since this month has started, though, the asset has declined. Nonetheless, as the netflows have only remained positive throughout this decline, the large holders have been buying regardless. This conviction from these large holders can naturally be a positive sign for Maker, as the asset could potentially continue its rally soon. MKR Price At the time of writing, Maker is trading around $1,200, up 4% in the last week. Looks like the value of the asset has been moving sideways recently &#124; Source: MKRUSD on TradingView Featured image from iStock.com, charts from TradingView.com, IntoTheBlock.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On-chain data shows large Maker holders have accumulated recently, a sign that the rally could extend soon.</p>
<h2>Maker Large Holders Have Continued To Expand Their Holdings Recently</h2>
<p>According to data from the market intelligence platform <a href="https://twitter.com/intotheblock/status/1690362652982149120" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">IntoTheBlock</a>, inflows to the wallets of the large MKR investors have been taking place for a while now. The &#8220;large holders&#8221; here refer to those investors who hold at least 0.1% of the cryptocurrency&#8217;s circulating supply.</p>
<p>In Maker&#8217;s case, this value would equal about $1.2 million. Thus, the only holders who would clear these criteria would be the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-sharks-continue-accumulation-whales-stagnate/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">sharks and whales</a>, the largest entities on the network.</p>
<p>These investors generally hold some influence in the market, as they can move many tokens at once. Thus, the behavior of this cohort could be worth watching, as it may reveal answers about where the asset might be heading next.</p>
<p>One way to track the behavior of these humongous holders is through the &#8220;<a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-bearish-signal-exchange-netflows-spike-up/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">netflow</a>&#8221; metric, which measures the net amount of MKR that these large investors are adding into or moving out of their combined holdings right now.</p>
<p>When the value of this metric is positive, it means that a net number of coins is entering into the supply of these investors currently, suggesting that they are participating in buying.</p>
<p>On the other hand, negative values could imply that this group may be selling as its members are transferring a net amount of the asset away from their wallets.</p>

<p>Now, here is a chart that shows the trend in the Maker large holders netflow over the last few months:</p>
<p><img decoding="async" fetchpriority="high" class="alignnone aligncenter" src="https://pbs.twimg.com/media/F3Vf4EVW8AIhHzM?format=png&amp;name=medium" alt="Maker (MKR) Large Holders Netflow" width="1120" height="583" loading="lazy"/></p>

<p>The above graph shows that the Maker large holders&#8217; netflow has been almost entirely positive during the past few months. There were a few dips into the negative territory, but the net outflows weren&#8217;t significant in scale then.</p>
<p>In the past few weeks, there haven&#8217;t been any drops below the zero mark, suggesting that the large holders have only continued accumulating more MKR recently.</p>
<p>Something to note here is that a positive netflow doesn&#8217;t mean that there isn&#8217;t any selling taking place at all. Instead, it simply suggests that the accumulation is enough to cancel any distribution.</p>

<p>In the past couple of months, the cryptocurrency has seen an overall uptrend, which could be a consequence of the net buying these investors have been participating in.</p>
<p>Since this month has started, though, the asset has declined. Nonetheless, as the netflows have only remained positive throughout this decline, the large holders have been buying regardless.</p>
<p>This conviction from these large holders can naturally be a positive sign for Maker, as the asset could potentially continue its <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/maker-mkr/maker-mkr-signals-bullish-price-formation-is-1-300-around-the-corner/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">rally</a> soon.</p>
<h2>MKR Price</h2>
<p>At the time of writing, Maker is trading around $1,200, up 4% in the last week.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" class="alignnone size-medium aligncenter" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/77C4HB36/" alt="Maker Price Chart" width="1534" height="877" loading="lazy"/></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/iStock-1367449613.jpg?fit=460%2C307" width="460" height="307" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">547172</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Michael Burry&#8217;s Massive $1.6 Billion Short: Is A $DXY Collapse The Catalyst For A Crypto Bloodbath?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/michael-burrys-massive-1-6-billion-short-is-a-dxy-collapse-the-catalyst-for-a-crypto-bloodbath/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 19:25:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Nasdaq 100]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=547250</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Michael Burry, renowned investor, and hedge fund manager, has once again made headlines with his significant short position in the traditional market, which could impact the nascent crypto industry if his bet is to materialize. Burry, known for accurately predicting the subprime mortgage crisis, recently went mega-short with over $1.6 billion in S&#38;P 500 (SPY) and Nasdaq 100 (QQQ) puts. These indexes often record a high correlation with the crypto market as they attract similar investors.  Burry&#8217;s $1.6 Billion Short Signals Potential Implications For Crypto Market Burry&#8217;s track record as an astute investor lends weight to his latest bet. By predicting and profiting from the subprime mortgage crisis, he gained a reputation as an investor capable of identifying market trends before they unfold.  It is important to consider that Burry has established himself as a prognosticator who is often ahead of the curve and is willing to wait for the anticipated market changes to come to fruition. Related Reading: HBAR Token Spikes 16% In One Day, Can Bulls Sustain the Momentum? On this matter, Yan Alleman, co-founder of Glassnode, has supported Burry&#8217;s approach, suggesting that while the short-term effects may not be immediately evident, the long-term payoff is likely to be significant. Alleman also highlighted the potential impact of the US Dollar Index (DXY) on the cryptocurrency market, specifically Bitcoin. According to Alleman, the recent renewed strength of the DXY could exert pressure on Bitcoin. The DXY measures the value of the U.S. dollar against a basket of major currencies.  On The Verge Of A Final Leg Up? As Burry predicts, a drop in the DXY could result in a significant surge in crypto assets, including Bitcoin, as investors seek alternative stores of value. This surge would represent a final leg up before a presumed deep correction across financial markets. While the correlation between the DXY and Bitcoin has been subject to debate, the potential consequences of Burry&#8217;s short position on the market cannot be ignored.  If his prediction were to come true, it could trigger a domino effect, leading to a substantial downturn in traditional markets and a subsequent surge in crypto assets. Nevertheless, the implications for Bitcoin and the broader crypto market in such a scenario are twofold. On the one hand, Bitcoin has often been hailed as a digital store of value and a hedge against traditional market downturns.  Burry&#8217;s short position on the market could reinforce this narrative, attracting more investors to Bitcoin as a safe haven asset. On the other hand, the cryptocurrency market&#8217;s extreme volatility could magnify the potential crypto bloodbath if Burry&#8217;s bet materialized.  A sudden surge in selling pressure for Bitcoin and other cryptocurrencies, coupled with a widespread market correction, could result in a sharp decline in the crypto market, causing substantial losses for investors who entered the market at its peak. Related Reading: Winds Of Change: Bitcoin Miner Riot Sees Substantial Increase In BTC Holdings As the market unfolds in the coming weeks and months, all eyes will be on Michael Burry&#8217;s $1.6 billion short position and its potential impact on traditional markets and crypto.  Only time will tell if Burry&#8217;s bet proves prescient once again or if the market defies his expectations, leaving investors to navigate the ever-changing landscape of investment opportunities. As of the current writing, Bitcoin (BTC) is trading at $29,300, indicating a marginal 0.3% decline over the past 24 hours. The cryptocurrency has continued to be in a consolidation phase since the start of August. Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Michael Burry, renowned investor, and hedge fund manager, has once again made headlines with his significant short position in the traditional market, which could impact the nascent crypto industry if his bet is to materialize.</p>
<p>Burry, known for accurately predicting the subprime mortgage crisis, recently went<a href="https://twitter.com/CramerTracker/status/1691123591717548032?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow"> mega-short</a> with over $1.6 billion in S&amp;P 500 (SPY) and Nasdaq 100 (QQQ) puts. These indexes often record a high correlation with the crypto market as they attract similar investors. </p>
<h2>Burry&#8217;s $1.6 Billion Short Signals Potential Implications For Crypto Market</h2>
<p>Burry&#8217;s track record as an astute investor lends weight to his latest bet. By predicting and profiting from the subprime mortgage crisis, he gained a reputation as an investor capable of identifying market trends before they unfold. </p>
<img decoding="async" class="size-large wp-image-547251" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F3gTrdCWAAEbXWt.jpeg?w=860&#038;resize=860%2C183" alt="Crypto" width="860" height="183" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F3gTrdCWAAEbXWt.jpeg?w=1244 1244w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F3gTrdCWAAEbXWt.jpeg?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F3gTrdCWAAEbXWt.jpeg?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F3gTrdCWAAEbXWt.jpeg?w=860&#038;resize=860%2C183 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F3gTrdCWAAEbXWt.jpeg?w=750 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F3gTrdCWAAEbXWt.jpeg?w=1140 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" loading="lazy" data-recalc-dims="1"/>
<p>It is important to consider that Burry has established himself as a prognosticator who is often ahead of the curve and is willing to wait for the anticipated market changes to come to fruition.</p>

<p>On this matter, Yan Alleman, co-founder of Glassnode, has <a href="https://twitter.com/Negentropic_/status/1691140802603266055?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">supported</a><a href="https://twitter.com/Negentropic_/status/1691140802603266055?s=20" rel="nofollow"> </a>Burry&#8217;s approach, suggesting that while the short-term effects may not be immediately evident, the long-term payoff is likely to be significant.</p>
<p>Alleman also <a href="https://twitter.com/Negentropic_/status/1691134948822994953?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">highlighted </a>the potential impact of the US Dollar Index (DXY) on the cryptocurrency market, specifically Bitcoin.</p>
<p>According to Alleman, the recent renewed strength of the DXY could exert pressure on Bitcoin. The DXY measures the value of the U.S. dollar against a basket of major currencies. </p>
<h2>On The Verge Of A Final Leg Up?</h2>
<p>As Burry predicts, a drop in the DXY could result in a significant surge in crypto assets, including Bitcoin, as investors seek alternative stores of value. This surge would represent a final leg up before a presumed deep correction across financial markets.</p>
<p>While the correlation between the DXY and Bitcoin has been subject to debate, the potential consequences of Burry&#8217;s short position on the market cannot be ignored. </p>
<p>If his prediction were to come true, it could trigger a domino effect, leading to a substantial downturn in traditional markets and a subsequent surge in crypto assets.</p>
<p>Nevertheless, the implications for Bitcoin and the broader crypto market in such a scenario are twofold. On the one hand, Bitcoin has often been hailed as a digital store of value and a hedge against traditional market downturns. </p>
<p>Burry&#8217;s short position on the market could reinforce this narrative, attracting more investors to Bitcoin as a safe haven asset.</p>
<p>On the other hand, the cryptocurrency market&#8217;s extreme volatility could magnify the potential crypto bloodbath if Burry&#8217;s bet materialized. </p>
<p>A sudden surge in selling pressure for Bitcoin and other cryptocurrencies, coupled with a widespread market correction, could result in a sharp decline in the crypto market, causing substantial losses for investors who entered the market at its peak.</p>

<p>As the market unfolds in the coming weeks and months, all eyes will be on Michael Burry&#8217;s $1.6 billion short position and its potential impact on traditional markets and crypto. </p>
<p>Only time will tell if Burry&#8217;s bet proves prescient once again or if the market defies his expectations, leaving investors to navigate the ever-changing landscape of investment opportunities.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/FysOi2T6/" alt="Crypto" width="1814" height="858"/>
<p>As of the current writing, Bitcoin (BTC) is trading at $29,300, indicating a marginal 0.3% decline over the past 24 hours. The cryptocurrency has continued to be in a consolidation phase since the start of August.</p>
<p>Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Downloader.la-64da7a7105a0d.jpg?fit=460%2C221" width="460" height="221" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">547250</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>HBAR Token Spikes 16% In One Day, Can Bulls Sustain the Momentum?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/trending-projects/hbar-token-spikes-16-in-one-day-can-bulls-sustain-the-momentum/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Kent Glory]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 19:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Trending Projects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[HBAR analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[HBAR Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[HBARUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hedera hashgraph]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=547199</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[HBAR has soared with momentum after the US Federal Reserve adopted the Hedera Hashgraph-based Dropp micropayments platform. According to the announcement, Dropp is now on the list of service providers on Fed’s FedNow instant payment system.  Following this news, HBAR&#8217;s market sentiment improved, causing a rapid price surge that propelled the token from $ 0.0561 to $0.06544. This represents an over 16% increase in the last 24 hours. However, HBAR price has crossed the overbought region, raising questions about how long the current rally can last. FedNow Adds Hedera Hashgraph-Powered Dropp To Its List Of Service Providers On July 20, the US Federal Reserve launched the FedNow instant payment system. This payment system allows banks and credit unions to transfer money for customers any time, any day, instantly. However, according to the latest development, FedNow adopted Dropp, a micropayment platform built on Hedera as a service provider. Dropp allows users to use micropayments for small-valued transactions in USD Coin (USDC), HBAR, and US dollars. Related Reading: SHIB, PEPE, APE Gain Against Bitcoin, Santiment Explains What This Means Adopting Dropp as a FedNow service provider implies that banks and other financial service providers can use the micropayment platform for real-time payments. This feat marks a milestone for Hedera as FedNow indirectly supports the token, granting the Hedera blockchain support from traditional finance companies.  Similarly, Hedera is already benefiting from this partnership as its price has increased by over 16% in the last 24 hours. Also, Hedera garnered massive investor attention in the past week due to increased partnerships, such as South Korean automobile companies Kia and Hyundai, which have adopted Hedera’s infrastructure to track vehicle carbon emissions. HBAR Price Outlook; How Long Can The Bulls Hold? HBAR soared over 16% within a few hours after the FedNow support announcement. That brought the token’s seven-day price increase to nearly 17%. In addition, HBAR’s valuation is now 25% higher than its price 30 days ago. HBAR trades at $0.065, with a day high of $0.06625 and a low of $0.05046. One remarkable thing about HBAR’s performance is the massive surge in trading volume, which signifies increased network activity and investor interest. As of the time of writing, HBAR has recorded an over 1,219% surge in 24-hour trading volume, after securing its position as the highest-gaining cryptocurrency today.  According to the daily chart, HBAR trades above two key support levels at $0.063035 and $0.06005. Moreover, the bulls have formed green bars above the support levels as they vie to push HBAR to higher highs. The Relative Strength Index is at 72. But while this signifies increased buying pressure, the sideways movement of the RSI graph suggests a weakening trend. So HBAR buyers have reached saturation and are probably about to lose momentum. Related Reading: Shiba Inu (SHIB) Poised For Golden Cross – How Will Prices React? Additionally, the faded green histogram bars show the buying demand for HBAR tokens has dwindled slightly. If this continues, the HBAR rally could stall, allowing the bears to push prices downward. Featured image from Pixabay and chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>HBAR has soared with momentum after the US Federal Reserve adopted the Hedera Hashgraph-based Dropp micropayments platform. According to the <a href="https://twitter.com/MasonVersluis/status/1690919025130487809" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">announcement</a>, Dropp is now on the list of service providers on Fed’s FedNow instant payment system. </p>
<p>Following this news, HBAR&#8217;s market sentiment improved, causing a rapid price surge that propelled the token from $ 0.0561 to $0.06544. This represents an over 16% increase in the last 24 hours. However, HBAR price has crossed the overbought region, raising questions about how long the current rally can last.</p>
<h2>FedNow Adds Hedera Hashgraph-Powered Dropp To Its List Of Service Providers</h2>
<p>On July 20, the US Federal Reserve <a href="https://www.federalreserve.gov/newsevents/pressreleases/other20230720a.htm" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">launched</a> the FedNow instant payment system. This payment system allows banks and credit unions to transfer money for customers any time, any day, instantly.</p>
<p>However, according to the latest development, FedNow <a href="https://explore.fednow.org/explore-the-city?id=10&amp;building=showcase-theater&amp;sortBy=newest&amp;postId=108&amp;vendor=dropp-inc." target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">adopted</a> Dropp, a micropayment platform built on Hedera as a service provider. Dropp allows users to use micropayments for small-valued transactions in USD Coin (USDC), HBAR, and US dollars.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/altcoin/shib-pepe-ape-gain-bitcoin-santiment-explains-means/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">SHIB, PEPE, APE Gain Against Bitcoin, Santiment Explains What This Means</a></p>
<p>Adopting Dropp as a FedNow service provider implies that banks and other financial service providers can use the micropayment platform for real-time payments. This feat marks a milestone for Hedera as FedNow indirectly supports the token, granting the Hedera blockchain support from traditional finance companies. </p>
<p>Similarly, Hedera is already benefiting from this partnership as its price has increased by over 16% in the last 24 hours. Also, Hedera garnered massive investor attention in the past week due to increased partnerships, such as South Korean automobile companies Kia and Hyundai, which have adopted Hedera’s infrastructure to track vehicle carbon emissions.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/KEXMjBWF/" alt="HBARUSD price chart" width="980" height="589"/>
<h2>HBAR Price Outlook; How Long Can The Bulls Hold?</h2>
<p>HBAR soared over 16% within a few hours after the FedNow support announcement. That brought the token’s seven-day price increase to nearly 17%.</p>
<p>In addition, HBAR’s valuation is now 25% higher than its price 30 days ago. HBAR trades at $0.065, with a day high of $0.06625 and a low of $0.05046.</p>
<p>One remarkable thing about HBAR’s performance is the massive surge in trading volume, which signifies increased network activity and investor interest. As of the time of writing, HBAR has recorded an over 1,219% surge in 24-hour trading volume, after securing its position as the highest-gaining cryptocurrency today. </p>
<p>According to the daily <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/x/xdZgXpzG/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">chart</a>, HBAR trades above two key support levels at $0.063035 and $0.06005. Moreover, the bulls have formed green bars above the support levels as they vie to push HBAR to higher highs.</p>
<p>The Relative Strength Index is at 72. But while this signifies increased buying pressure, the sideways movement of the RSI graph suggests a weakening trend. So HBAR buyers have reached saturation and are probably about to lose momentum.</p>

<p>Additionally, the faded green histogram bars show the buying demand for HBAR tokens has dwindled slightly. If this continues, the HBAR rally could stall, allowing the bears to push prices downward.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/HBAR-1.png?fit=460%2C345" width="460" height="345" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">547199</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Here’s Why This Former SEC Lawyer Thinks A Spot Bitcoin ETF Isn’t Coming</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/former-sec-lawyer-spot-bitcoin-etf/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 18:00:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Spot Bitcoin ETF]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=547201</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Recent comments from former SEC Attorney John Reed Stark have further dampened optimism about the regulator approving any of the pending Spot Bitcoin ETF applications. Spot Bitcoin ETF Approval Looking More Unlikely The United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has continuously denied applications for a Spot Bitcoin ETF, and Stark has suggested that this trend isn’t going to change anytime soon as the SEC will likely deny all the pending applications due to several “compelling reasons.” While aligning his opinion with that of Better Markets, Stark stated that the arguments laid forward in the nonprofit’s letters to the SEC “brilliantly” highlighted why the SEC would not approve any of these applications. Related Reading: Want A Bitcoin Spot ETF? Then Prove BTC Is Not Manipulated, Says SEC Better Markets had, in two separate letters (here and here) dated August 8, laid out arguments why the SEC should reject the proposed rule changes by the Cboe BZX Exchange and the Nasdaq Stock Market “to list and trade shares in Spot bitcoin-based exchange-traded products (ETP).”  According to them, the Spot Bitcoin market is known to show inflated trading volumes due to illicit practices like market manipulation and wash trading. They argue that the markets are highly concentrated and Bitcoin’s network is maintained by a “select group of individuals and entities.” All this makes any proposed Spot Bitcoin ETP susceptible to manipulation by “bad actors” and puts investors and the public interest at risk.  In their applications, these exchanges stated that CME Bitcoin futures, a regulated market of significant size, could provide the necessary data and insights relating to any fraud and manipulation in the Spot Bitcoin ETF market. Additionally, they had entered into a surveillance-sharing agreement with Coinbase as an extra measure to prevent fraud and market manipulation. However, Better Market has labeled these measures as “wholly inadequate.” They argue that the CME Bitcoin futures market is not a “regulated market of significant size” and the surveillance-sharing agreement with Coinbase is insufficient to prevent market manipulation. BTC remains weak as market awaits SEC decision &#124; Source: BTCUSD on Tradingview.com Is Crypto Regulation Now Political? Stark believes that the “crypto-regulatory tides could shift exponentially” once the US 2024 elections take place. He noted the political divide regarding crypto and how this has also played out in the SEC’s clampdown on the crypto industry.  Related Reading: Bitcoin-Friendly Javier Milei Wins Presidential Primaries In Argentina The SEC has been known to come on hard at several crypto firms, including two of the world’s largest crypto exchanges, Binance and Coinbase, accusing them of securities violations. However, Stark predicts that the SEC will abandon this crypto-enforcement effort and focus more on mostly fraud cases should a Republican get elected as President next year. Although the elections are slated for November 2024 (long after the SEC might have decided on the pending Spot Bitcoin ETF applications), Stark has forecasted that a GOP-led administration could bring about the approval of a Spot Bitcoin ETF.  Featured image from iStock, chart from Tradingview.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Recent comments from former SEC Attorney John Reed Stark have further dampened optimism about the regulator approving any of the pending Spot Bitcoin ETF <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/blackrock-first-spot-bitcoin-etf/">applications</a>.</p>
<h2>Spot Bitcoin ETF Approval Looking More Unlikely</h2>
<p>The <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/sec-prove-bitcoin-is-not-manipulated/">United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC)</a> has continuously denied applications for a Spot Bitcoin ETF, and Stark has <a href="https://twitter.com/JohnReedStark/status/1690707913789112320?s=20" rel="nofollow">suggested </a>that this trend isn’t going to change anytime soon as the SEC will likely deny all the pending applications due to several “compelling reasons.”</p>
<p>While aligning his opinion with that of Better Markets, Stark stated that the arguments laid forward in the nonprofit’s letters to the SEC “brilliantly” highlighted why the SEC would not approve any of these applications.</p>

<p>Better Markets had, in two separate letters (<a href="https://bettermarkets.org/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Better_Markets_Comment_Letter_BitcoinETPs.pdf" rel="nofollow">here</a> and <a href="https://bettermarkets.org/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Better_Markets_Comment_Letter_BitcoinETP.pdf" rel="nofollow">here</a>) dated August 8, laid out arguments why the SEC should reject the proposed rule changes by the Cboe BZX Exchange and the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/why-isnt-bitcoin-outperforming-most-risk-assets-a-market-conundrum/">Nasdaq Stock Market</a> “to list and trade shares in Spot bitcoin-based exchange-traded products (ETP).” </p>
<p>According to them, the Spot Bitcoin market is known to show inflated trading volumes due to illicit practices like market manipulation and wash trading. They argue that the markets are highly concentrated and Bitcoin’s network is maintained by a “select group of individuals and entities.” All this makes any proposed Spot Bitcoin ETP susceptible to manipulation by “bad actors” and puts investors and the public interest at risk. </p>
<p>In their applications, these exchanges stated that CME Bitcoin futures, a regulated market of significant size, could provide the necessary data and insights relating to any fraud and manipulation in the Spot Bitcoin ETF market. Additionally, they had entered into a surveillance-sharing agreement with Coinbase as an extra measure to prevent fraud and market manipulation.</p>
<p>However, Better Market has labeled these measures as “wholly inadequate.” They argue that the CME Bitcoin futures market is not a “regulated market of significant size” and the surveillance-sharing agreement with Coinbase is insufficient to prevent market manipulation.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/clHZsKl6/" alt="Bitcoin (BTC) price chart from Tradingview.com (Spot Bitcoin ETF SEC)" width="2884" height="1746"/></p>

<h2>Is Crypto Regulation Now Political?</h2>
<p>Stark believes that the “crypto-regulatory tides could shift exponentially” once the US 2024 elections take place. He noted the political divide regarding <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/link/crypto-analyst-shares-bullish-insights-on-chainlink-as-users-accumulate-295-million-link/">crypto</a> and how this has also played out in the SEC’s clampdown on the crypto industry. </p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-friendly-javier-milei-wins-presidential-primaries/">Bitcoin-Friendly Javier Milei Wins Presidential Primaries In Argentina</a></p>
<p>The SEC has been known to come on hard at several crypto firms, including two of the world’s largest crypto exchanges, <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/sec-sues-binance-coinbase-blackrock-bitcoin-etf-inside-job/">Binance</a> and <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/coinbase-coin-drops-10-amidst-absurd-sec-request/">Coinbase</a>, accusing them of securities violations. However, Stark predicts that the SEC will abandon this crypto-enforcement effort and focus more on mostly fraud cases should a Republican get elected as President next year.</p>
<p>Although the elections are slated for November 2024 (long after the SEC might have decided on the pending Spot Bitcoin ETF applications), Stark has forecasted that a GOP-led administration could bring about the approval of a Spot Bitcoin ETF. </p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/iStock-879153690.jpg?fit=460%2C307" width="460" height="307" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">547201</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Base TVL Surges 900% In 2 Weeks, What’s Driving The Growth?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/coinbase/base-tvl-surges-900-in-2-weeks/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Best Owie]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 17:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BALD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Base]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Base Layer 1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Base TVL]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[TVL]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=547160</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Base, the Ethereum Layer 2 rollup developed by crypto exchange Coinbase, is already making a name for itself in the market. The blockchain’s Total Value Locked (TVL) has been on a rapid rise over the last few weeks, rising triple-digits in just the last two weeks alone. So the question now is, what’s driving the TVL growth? Meme Coins, Rugs, And Newcomers Unlike other Layer 2 networks, Base seemed to have gotten its big break with the growing trend of meme coins being launched on the network. The most notable of these was the BALD meme coin which went from less than $100,000 in market cap to over $50 million in a matter of days. As the popularity of BALD ramped up, so did the popularity of Base and decentralized finance (DeFi) traders clamored to bridge to the blockchain. Related Reading: Regulatory Pressure Mounts On Worldcoin, Can WLD Price Recover? The rug deployer rugged the project not long after, making off with over $9 million in liquidity. Following this, there were speculations of former FTX CEO and founder Sam Bankman-Fried Nverbeing the mastermind behind BALD, although nothing came from these accusations. However, instead of the blockchain’s first big project rugging being a deterrent, it seems to have had the opposite effect. More developers have moved to launch their projects on the blockchain seeing the potential. This includes the likes of SushiSwap, Uniswap, and Compound, among others, which have all provided support for the Base network. New projects such as Alien Base, SwapBased, and Krav have also been gaining ground with their TVL growing rapidly during this time as well. So for Base, it has been able to turn a negative situation into a positive one. Base Joining The Layer 2 Blockchain Race In the last two weeks, the Base TVL has grown from $13 million to more than $130 million, data from DefiLlama shows. This represents an almost 900% increase in TVL during this time, making it the fastest-growing Ethereum Layer 2 blockchain in terms of TVL. Related Reading: Terra Classic (LUNC) Chances Of Revival Grow Slimmer, Here’s Why Base’s rapid growth has already put it in the race with other Layer 2s. However, when put in comparison against other established Layer 2 networks, Base still has a long way to go. It is currently the 5th-largest Layer 2 in terms of TVL, lagging well behind the likes of Arbitrum, Polygon, and Avalanche. Nevertheless, Base’s bull case continues to grow with over $203 million already bridged to the blockchain and daily active users sitting above 100,000 over the last four days. Given Coinbase’s backing and Base’s growing popularity, it may not be long until it becomes one of the most prominent Layer 2 blockchains in the space. DeFi makes up 19.14% of the Ethereum market cap &#124; Source: Market Cap DeFi/Ethereum on Tradingview.com Follow Best Owie on Twitter for market insights, updates, and the occasional funny tweet… Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="p2">Base, the Ethereum Layer 2 rollup developed by crypto exchange Coinbase, is already making a name for itself in the market. The blockchain’s Total Value Locked (TVL) has been on a rapid rise over the last few weeks, rising triple-digits in just the last two weeks alone. So the question now is, what’s driving the TVL growth?</p>
<h2 class="p2">Meme Coins, Rugs, And Newcomers</h2>
<p class="p2">Unlike other <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/matic/polygon-labs-unveils-major-upgrade-to-sidechain-with-zkevm-validium-layer-2/">Layer 2</a> networks, Base seemed to have gotten its big break with the growing trend of meme coins being launched on the network. The most notable of these was the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/29-meme-coins-bald-rugged-base-investors-lose-millions/">BALD meme coin</a> which went from less than $100,000 in market cap to over $50 million in a matter of days. As the popularity of BALD ramped up, so did the popularity of Base and decentralized finance (DeFi) traders clamored to bridge to the blockchain.</p>

<p class="p2">The rug deployer rugged the project not long after, making off with over $9 million in liquidity. Following this, there were speculations of former FTX CEO and founder Sam Bankman-Fried Nverbeing the mastermind behind BALD, although nothing came from these accusations.</p>
<p class="p2">However, instead of the blockchain’s first big project rugging being a deterrent, it seems to have had the opposite effect. More developers have moved to launch their projects on the blockchain seeing the potential. This includes the likes of <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/defi/sushiswap-burns-5-million-per-year-but-will-it-rebrand-in-2023/">SushiSwap</a>, <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/uni/why-the-uniswap-uni-token-is-almost-worthless/">Uniswap</a>, and <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/compound-comp-bears-take-full-control-as-price-dips-20-in-7-days/">Compound</a>, among others, which have all provided support for the Base network.</p>
<p class="p2">New projects such as Alien Base, SwapBased, and Krav have also been gaining ground with their TVL growing rapidly during this time as well. So for Base, it has been able to turn a negative situation into a positive one.</p>
<h2 class="p2">Base Joining The Layer 2 Blockchain Race</h2>
<p class="p2">In the last two weeks, the Base TVL has grown from $13 million to more than $130 million, <a href="https://defillama.com/chain/Base?volume=true" rel="nofollow">data</a> from DefiLlama shows. This represents an almost 900% increase in TVL during this time, making it the fastest-growing Ethereum Layer 2 blockchain in terms of TVL.</p>

<p class="p2">Base’s rapid growth has already put it in the race with other Layer 2s. However, when put in comparison against other established Layer 2 networks, Base still has a long way to go. It is currently the 5th-largest Layer 2 in terms of TVL, lagging well behind the likes of <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/is-arbitrum-promise-fading-downtime-metrics-decline-raise-arb-price-alarms/">Arbitrum</a>, <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/when-will-polygon-matic-rebound-analyzing-this-months-recovery-potential/">Polygon</a>, and <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/avalanche/avalanche-foundation-commits-50-million-to-tokenized-asset-purchases/">Avalanche</a>.</p>
<p class="p2">Nevertheless, Base’s bull case continues to grow with over $203 million already bridged to the blockchain and <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/coinbase-newly-launched-layer-2-network-records/" rel="nofollow">daily active users sitting above 100,000</a> over the last four days. Given Coinbase’s backing and Base’s growing popularity, it may not be long until it becomes one of the most prominent Layer 2 blockchains in the space.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/1m7qfkSp/" alt="DeFi/Ethereum market cap ration chart from Tradingview.com (Base)" width="2884" height="1746"/></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/iStock-1015828796.jpg?fit=460%2C263" width="460" height="263" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">547160</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Winds Of Change: Bitcoin Miner Riot Sees Substantial Increase In BTC Holdings</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-miner-riot-increase-btc/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 16:00:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin miner]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Riot Blockchain]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=547179</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin mining has been up by a considerable fraction this year, as the blockchain network recorded a new all-time high in hash rate in the second quarter of the year. Mining revenue is also up, as the bitcoin Bitcoin recorded a spike in transaction volume.  As a result, Riot Blockchain, one of the largest publicly traded Bitcoin mining companies in the US, has recorded an increase in operations in the second quarter. According to its 2023 second-quarter financial results, the mining company recorded a new all-time record hash while ramping up its Bitcoin mining operations. Solid Second Quarter 2023 According to its financial report, Riot has seriously ramped up its Bitcoin mining operations. As a result, the mining company produced 1,775 BTC during the second quarter of 2023, a 27% increase compared to the 1,395 BTC it produced during that same period in 2022.  In May 2023 alone, the company produced 676 BTC at an average of 21.8 BTC per day. The average cost to mine each bitcoin was $8,389, beating Q2 2022&#8217;s average of $11,316. Related Reading: More Selling? Bankrupt Voyager Sends Millions In SHIB And ETH To Coinbase Riot also witnessed an increase in mining revenue, as Bitcoin miners generated a remarkable total revenue of $2.4 billion. Although the price of Bitcoin during the quarter was 15% less than what it was in Q2 2022, Riot saw a total revenue of $76.7 million, as compared to $72.9 million in Q2 2022. Mining revenue ($49.7 million), engineering revenue ($19.3 million), data hosting revenue ($7.7 million), and power curtailment credits ($13.5 million) were also higher than in Q2 2022.  Not only has RIOT’s revenue from bitcoin mining increased, but their actual bitcoin holdings have also grown substantially. As of June 30, Riot held 7,264 BTC with the price of each BTC at $30,477. In total, Riot finished the quarter with $408.4 million in working capital, including $289.2 million in cash on hand and $221.4 million in Bitcoin, while also reducing its net loss to $27.7 million compared to $353.6 million in Q2 2022. BTC price remains volatile &#124; Source: BTCUSD on Tradingview.com  Increase In Bitcoin Mining Power Riot Blockchain also drastically increased its hash rate throughout the quarter, reaching an all-time record hash rate capacity of 10.7 EH/s. However, the company is also looking to enhance its computational power.  Related Reading: Want A Bitcoin Spot ETF? Then Prove BTC Is Not Manipulated, Says SEC During the quarter, the company signed a long-term purchase agreement with MicroBT to acquire 33,280 next-generation miners. With an expanded mining fleet and facility, Riot believes it can see its hash rate grow to 20.1 EH/s by the second quarter of 2024.  Bitcoin mining is an energy-intensive process. However, Riot&#8217;s power strategy contributes to the stability of the energy grid in Texas at times of high demand by selling extra power back to the grid. At the time of writing Riot&#8217;s stock is up by 1.53% in a daily timeframe and 158.14% in the past six months. Featured image from PYMNTS, chart from Tradingview.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin mining has been up by a considerable fraction this year, as the blockchain network recorded a new all-time high in hash rate in the second quarter of the year. Mining revenue is also up, as the bitcoin Bitcoin recorded a spike in transaction volume. </p>
<p>As a result, Riot Blockchain, one of the largest publicly traded Bitcoin mining companies in the US, has recorded an increase in operations in the second quarter. According to its 2023 second-quarter financial results, the mining company recorded a new all-time record hash while ramping up its Bitcoin mining operations.</p>
<h2>Solid Second Quarter 2023</h2>
<p>According to its <a href="https://www.riotplatforms.com/news-media/press-releases/detail/158/riot-platforms-reports-second-quarter-2023-financial" rel="nofollow">financial report</a>, Riot has seriously ramped up its Bitcoin mining operations. As a result, the mining company produced 1,775 BTC during the second quarter of 2023, a 27% increase compared to the 1,395 BTC it produced during that same period in 2022. </p>
<p>In May 2023 alone, the company produced 676 BTC at an average of 21.8 BTC per day. The average cost to mine each bitcoin was $8,389, beating Q2 2022&#8217;s average of $11,316.</p>

<p>Riot also witnessed an increase in mining revenue, as Bitcoin miners generated a remarkable total revenue of $2.4 billion. Although the price of Bitcoin during the quarter was 15% less than what it was in Q2 2022, Riot saw a total revenue of $76.7 million, as compared to $72.9 million in Q2 2022. Mining revenue ($49.7 million), engineering revenue ($19.3 million), data hosting revenue ($7.7 million), and power curtailment credits ($13.5 million) were also higher than in Q2 2022. </p>
<p>Not only has RIOT’s revenue from bitcoin mining increased, but their actual bitcoin holdings have also grown substantially. As of June 30, Riot held 7,264 BTC with the price of each BTC at $30,477. </p>
<p>In total, Riot finished the quarter with $408.4 million in working capital, including $289.2 million in cash on hand and $221.4 million in Bitcoin, while also reducing its net loss to $27.7 million compared to $353.6 million in Q2 2022.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/lVqqedFY/" alt="Bitcoin (BTC) price chart from Tradingview.com (Riot Blockchain)" width="2884" height="1746"/></p>

<h2>Increase In Bitcoin Mining Power</h2>
<p>Riot Blockchain also drastically increased its hash rate throughout the quarter, reaching an all-time record hash rate capacity of 10.7 EH/s. However, the company is also looking to enhance its computational power. </p>

<p>During the quarter, the company signed a long-term purchase <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/riot-power-strategy-pays-off-10-million-in-revenue/" rel="nofollow">agreement </a>with MicroBT to acquire 33,280 next-generation miners. With an expanded mining fleet and facility, Riot believes it can see its hash rate grow to 20.1 EH/s by the second quarter of 2024. </p>
<p>Bitcoin mining is an energy-intensive process. However, Riot&#8217;s power strategy contributes to the stability of the energy grid in Texas at times of high demand by selling extra power back to the grid. At the time of writing Riot&#8217;s stock is up by 1.53% in a daily timeframe and 158.14% in the past six months.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-mining.jpeg?fit=460%2C276" width="460" height="276" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">547179</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Silent Bitcoin Storm: Glassnode Uncovers What Lies Beneath The Surface</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/silent-bitcoin-storm-glassnode-revelations/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jake Simmons]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 15:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin LTHs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin STHs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[glassnode]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=547190</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[In the dynamic realm of Bitcoin, the ability to discern patterns and trends from raw data is invaluable. Glassnode&#8217;s latest report, &#8220;Exhaustion and Apathy,&#8221; serves as a beacon, illuminating the intricate nuances of the current state of the market. Let&#8217;s delve deeper into the numbers and their implications. Historic Lows In Bitcoin Volatility The overarching theme of Glassnode&#8217;s findings is the unprecedented stagnation in Bitcoin&#8217;s volatility. The data reveals that the digital asset has been trading within a remarkably narrow $29,000 to $30,000 range. Historically, Bitcoin has been synonymous with volatility, making this current phase an anomaly. The report underscores this by highlighting the Bollinger Bands&#8217; tightness, noting, &#8220;The upper and lower Bollinger Bands are currently separated by just 2.9%.&#8221; Such constricted movement has been a rarity in Bitcoin&#8217;s tumultuous history. Related Reading: Goldman Foresees Q2 2024 Fed Rate Cut: A Boost For Bitcoin? Meanwhile, the dynamics between short-term holders (STH) and long-term holders (LTH) offer a captivating narrative. Glassnode&#8217;s data indicates a significant shift in wealth between these two cohorts. The STH&#8217;s wealth has burgeoned by +$22B this year, while the LTH has witnessed a near-identical reduction of -$21B. This shift is not merely about numbers but also about market sentiment and strategy. The cost basis further elucidates this dynamic. The STH cost basis has surged by +59% YTD, settling at $28.6k. In stark contrast, the LTH cost basis lingers considerably lower, around $20.3k. This divergence suggests that recent market entrants might be paying a premium, potentially due to FOMO (Fear of Missing Out) or speculative behavior. Glassnode&#8217;s exploration into spending patterns in this low volatility environment is also particularly enlightening. The data suggests that in such periods, the majority of coins moved on-chain have a cost basis that hews closely to the spot rate, resulting in minuscule realized profits or losses. The Sell-Side Risk Ratio, a pivotal metric in this context, is languishing at an all-time low. To put it in perspective, fewer than 27 trading days (0.57%) have recorded a value lower than the current one, signaling a market teetering on the edge of a potential volatility resurgence. Segmented View Of BTC&#8217;s Supply The report&#8217;s segmented analysis of Bitcoin&#8217;s supply, based on &#8216;investor holding time,&#8217; offers a layered understanding of market behavior. The &#8216;Hot Supply,&#8217; representing the most active coins, constitutes a mere 2.8% of all invested value in BTC. This suggests a market dominated by holders rather than traders. Related Reading: SHIB, PEPE, APE Gain Against Bitcoin, Santiment Explains What This Means The &#8216;Warm Supply,&#8217; spanning from a week to six months, has seen a modest uptick year-to-date, now accounting for around 30% of Bitcoin&#8217;s wealth. This segment&#8217;s behavior is crucial as it often acts as a bridge between short-term reactions and long-term convictions. The &#8216;Single-Cycle Long-Term Holders,&#8217; those entrenched in the 2020-23 cycle, are the behemoths, holding a staggering 63% of the invested capital. Their cost basis, as per Glassnode, stands at $33.8k, indicating an average unrealized loss of -13.3%. In juxtaposition, the classic LTH cohort, which includes the long-dormant and deep HODLed supply, boasts a cost basis of $20.4k, translating to an unrealized profit of +43.6%. This stark contrast underscores the lingering impact of the 2022 bear market and the cautious optimism of early adopters. In conclusion, Glassnode&#8217;s data-driven insights paint a nuanced picture of the Bitcoin market. The dominance of long-term holders, the historic lows in volatility, and the evident investor apathy all converge to suggest a market in a state of stasis. The numbers indicate a market that&#8217;s waiting, perhaps for a Goldman Foresees Q2 2024 Fed Rate Cut: A Boost For Bitcoin? or a significant event, to determine its next direction. At press time, Bitcoin was trading just above the 50-day EMA. Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In the dynamic realm of Bitcoin, the ability to discern patterns and trends from raw data is invaluable. Glassnode&#8217;s latest <a href="https://twitter.com/glassnode/status/1691052457139355648" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">report</a>, &#8220;Exhaustion and Apathy,&#8221; serves as a beacon, illuminating the intricate nuances of the current state of the market. Let&#8217;s delve deeper into the numbers and their implications.</p>
<h2>Historic Lows In Bitcoin Volatility</h2>
<p>The overarching theme of Glassnode&#8217;s findings is the unprecedented stagnation in Bitcoin&#8217;s volatility. The data reveals that the digital asset has been trading within a remarkably narrow $29,000 to $30,000 range. Historically, Bitcoin has been synonymous with volatility, making this current phase an anomaly.</p>
<p>The report underscores this by highlighting the Bollinger Bands&#8217; tightness, noting, &#8220;The upper and lower Bollinger Bands are currently separated by just 2.9%.&#8221; Such constricted movement has been a rarity in Bitcoin&#8217;s tumultuous history.</p>

<p>Meanwhile, the dynamics between short-term holders (STH) and long-term holders (LTH) offer a captivating narrative. Glassnode&#8217;s data indicates a significant shift in wealth between these two cohorts. The STH&#8217;s wealth has burgeoned by +$22B this year, while the LTH has witnessed a near-identical reduction of -$21B. This shift is not merely about numbers but also about market sentiment and strategy.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-547194 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Group-137691310-1-.png?resize=2400%2C1382" alt="Bitcoin Long-/Short Term Realized Cap" width="2400" height="1382" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Group-137691310-1-.png?resize=2400%2C1382?w=2400 2400w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Group-137691310-1-.png?resize=2400%2C1382?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Group-137691310-1-.png?resize=2400%2C1382?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Group-137691310-1-.png?resize=2400%2C1382?w=860 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Group-137691310-1-.png?resize=2400%2C1382?w=1536 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Group-137691310-1-.png?resize=2400%2C1382?w=2048 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Group-137691310-1-.png?resize=2400%2C1382?w=750 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Group-137691310-1-.png?resize=2400%2C1382?w=1140 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" data-recalc-dims="1"/>
<p>The cost basis further elucidates this dynamic. The STH cost basis has surged by +59% YTD, settling at $28.6k. In stark contrast, the LTH cost basis lingers considerably lower, around $20.3k. This divergence suggests that recent market entrants might be paying a premium, potentially due to FOMO (Fear of Missing Out) or speculative behavior.</p>
<p>Glassnode&#8217;s exploration into spending patterns in this low volatility environment is also particularly enlightening. The data suggests that in such periods, the majority of coins moved on-chain have a cost basis that hews closely to the spot rate, resulting in minuscule realized profits or losses.</p>
<p>The Sell-Side Risk Ratio, a pivotal metric in this context, is languishing at an all-time low. To put it in perspective, fewer than 27 trading days (0.57%) have recorded a value lower than the current one, signaling a market teetering on the edge of a potential volatility resurgence.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-547193 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Group-137691312-1-.png?resize=2400%2C1383" alt="Bitcoin STH Sell Side Risk Ratio" width="2400" height="1383" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Group-137691312-1-.png?resize=2400%2C1383?w=2400 2400w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Group-137691312-1-.png?resize=2400%2C1383?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Group-137691312-1-.png?resize=2400%2C1383?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Group-137691312-1-.png?resize=2400%2C1383?w=860 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Group-137691312-1-.png?resize=2400%2C1383?w=1536 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Group-137691312-1-.png?resize=2400%2C1383?w=2048 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Group-137691312-1-.png?resize=2400%2C1383?w=750 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Group-137691312-1-.png?resize=2400%2C1383?w=1140 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" data-recalc-dims="1"/>
<h2>Segmented View Of BTC&#8217;s Supply</h2>
<p>The report&#8217;s segmented analysis of Bitcoin&#8217;s supply, based on &#8216;investor holding time,&#8217; offers a layered understanding of market behavior. The &#8216;Hot Supply,&#8217; representing the most active coins, constitutes a mere 2.8% of all invested value in BTC. This suggests a market dominated by holders rather than traders.</p>

<p>The &#8216;Warm Supply,&#8217; spanning from a week to six months, has seen a modest uptick year-to-date, now accounting for around 30% of Bitcoin&#8217;s wealth. This segment&#8217;s behavior is crucial as it often acts as a bridge between short-term reactions and long-term convictions.</p>
<p>The &#8216;Single-Cycle Long-Term Holders,&#8217; those entrenched in the 2020-23 cycle, are the behemoths, holding a staggering 63% of the invested capital. Their cost basis, as per Glassnode, stands at $33.8k, indicating an average unrealized loss of -13.3%.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-547195 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Group-137691337.png?resize=2400%2C1383" alt="Single Cycle HODLers Supply Cost Basis" width="2400" height="1383" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Group-137691337.png?resize=2400%2C1383?w=2400 2400w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Group-137691337.png?resize=2400%2C1383?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Group-137691337.png?resize=2400%2C1383?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Group-137691337.png?resize=2400%2C1383?w=860 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Group-137691337.png?resize=2400%2C1383?w=1536 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Group-137691337.png?resize=2400%2C1383?w=2048 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Group-137691337.png?resize=2400%2C1383?w=750 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Group-137691337.png?resize=2400%2C1383?w=1140 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" data-recalc-dims="1"/>
<p>In juxtaposition, the classic LTH cohort, which includes the long-dormant and deep HODLed supply, boasts a cost basis of $20.4k, translating to an unrealized profit of +43.6%. This stark contrast underscores the lingering impact of the 2022 bear market and the cautious optimism of early adopters.</p>
<p>In conclusion, Glassnode&#8217;s data-driven insights paint a nuanced picture of the Bitcoin market. The dominance of long-term holders, the historic lows in volatility, and the evident investor apathy all converge to suggest a market in a state of stasis. The numbers indicate a market that&#8217;s waiting, perhaps for a <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/goldman-foresees-q2-2024-fed-rate-cut-boost-bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Goldman Foresees Q2 2024 Fed Rate Cut: A Boost For Bitcoin?</a> or a significant event, to determine its next direction.</p>
<p>At press time, Bitcoin was trading just above the 50-day EMA.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-547196 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD_2023-08-14_14-21-35.png?resize=3628%2C1672" alt="Bitcoin price" width="3628" height="1672" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD_2023-08-14_14-21-35.png?resize=3628%2C1672?w=3628 3628w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD_2023-08-14_14-21-35.png?resize=3628%2C1672?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD_2023-08-14_14-21-35.png?resize=3628%2C1672?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD_2023-08-14_14-21-35.png?resize=3628%2C1672?w=860 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD_2023-08-14_14-21-35.png?resize=3628%2C1672?w=1536 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD_2023-08-14_14-21-35.png?resize=3628%2C1672?w=2048 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD_2023-08-14_14-21-35.png?resize=3628%2C1672?w=750 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD_2023-08-14_14-21-35.png?resize=3628%2C1672?w=1140 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD_2023-08-14_14-21-35.png?resize=3628%2C1672?w=3000 3000w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" data-recalc-dims="1"/>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/iStock-1327896562.jpg?fit=460%2C297" width="460" height="297" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">547190</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>XRP Volume Jolt: How Did The $3 Billion Surge Impact Price Action?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/all/xrp-volume-jolt-how-did-the-3-billion-surge-impact-price-action/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 14:00:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[All]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price action]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=547153</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[XRP has recently witnessed a remarkable surge in trading volume, with an impressive increase of $3 billion reported by Messari. This surge reflects the cryptocurrency&#8217;s enduring appeal, adaptability to market trends, and potential to disrupt traditional finance. Speculations abound about the factors driving this surge, sparking discussions on its implications for both XRP&#8217;s future trajectory and the broader cryptocurrency market. Despite this surge in trading activity, the expected correlation between volume and price failed to materialize, leaving market analysts puzzled by the intriguing phenomenon. XRP transaction volume. Source: Messari The cryptocurrency market is no stranger to unexpected fluctuations, but the recent surge in XRP&#8217;s trading volume has brought forth a unique puzzle. Unlike the traditional market dynamics, where a surge in volume often corresponds with a significant price movement, XRP&#8217;s price remained relatively muted.  Related Reading: Shiba Inu Steals The Spotlight, Leaving Bitcoin Behind In A Week Of Price Surges This divergence has led experts to speculate that the surge in volume might not primarily represent genuine buying support for the asset. XRP Buyers&#8217; Attempt To Reclaim Higher Ground In a separate report, it was highlighted that the XRP price had staged a minor recovery attempt from the $0.6 support level the previous week. In an endeavor to regain higher ground, the coin price exhibited a short-lived 11.4% jump, only to encounter immediate resistance at $0.665.  The subsequent rejection candle at this crucial barrier spoke volumes about the prevailing market sentiment. Traders, it seems, are still inclined to sell on bounces, a strategy often observed in established downtrends. XRP is trading at $0.6286, according to TradingView.com Over the course of seven days, the gains amounted to a mere 0.1%, underscoring the tenuous nature of the recovery attempts. Anticipating A Potential Turnaround Amidst the price volatility, a key question emerges: can the falling XRP price rally once more? If the price does indeed witness another surge in buying pressure that propels it to the $0.6 support level, it could signal a concerted effort by buyers to accumulate the asset at a discounted rate. All eyes are now on the critical resistance level of $0.665. Should the XRP price manage to break through this barrier, it could serve as the initial sign of a broader recovery trend. Market participants and analysts alike are closely monitoring these developments, seeking clues that could shed light on the elusive interplay between trading volume, price movements, and market sentiment. Related Reading: Cardano (ADA) Approaches The $0.3 Resistance: What Lies Ahead? XRP price action today. Source: Coingecko Meanwhile, XRP is currently trading at at $0.627, according to CoinGecko, unchanged in the last 24 hours, while exhibiting a modest 1.7% gain over the span of the last seven days. (This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk). Featured image from The State Farm Newsroom]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>XRP has recently witnessed a remarkable surge in trading volume, with an impressive increase of $3 billion reported by Messari. This surge reflects the cryptocurrency&#8217;s enduring appeal, adaptability to market trends, and potential to disrupt traditional finance.</p>
<p>Speculations abound about the factors driving this surge, sparking discussions on its implications for both XRP&#8217;s future trajectory and the broader cryptocurrency market.</p>
<p>Despite this <a href="https://messari.io/asset/xrp/chart/txn-vol" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">surge in trading activity</a>, the expected correlation between volume and price failed to materialize, leaving market analysts puzzled by the intriguing phenomenon.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-547163 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-77.png?w=860&#038;resize=860%2C321" alt="" width="860" height="321" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-77.png?w=1256 1256w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-77.png?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-77.png?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-77.png?w=860&#038;resize=860%2C321 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-77.png?w=750 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-77.png?w=1140 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" data-recalc-dims="1"/></p>

<p>The cryptocurrency market is no stranger to unexpected fluctuations, but the recent surge in XRP&#8217;s trading volume has brought forth a unique puzzle. Unlike the traditional market dynamics, where a surge in volume often corresponds with a significant price movement, XRP&#8217;s price remained relatively muted. </p>

<p>This divergence has led experts to speculate that the surge in volume might not primarily represent genuine buying support for the asset.</p>
<h2><strong>XRP Buyers&#8217; Attempt To Reclaim Higher Ground</strong></h2>
<p>In a <a href="https://coingape.com/markets/xrp-price-analysis-bulls-defend-this-level/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">separate report</a>, it was highlighted that the XRP price had staged a minor recovery attempt from the $0.6 support level the previous week. In an endeavor to regain higher ground, the coin price exhibited a short-lived 11.4% jump, only to encounter immediate resistance at $0.665. </p>
<p>The subsequent rejection candle at this crucial barrier spoke volumes about the prevailing market sentiment. Traders, it seems, are still inclined to sell on bounces, a strategy often observed in established downtrends.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/4C487StI/" width="1835" height="893"/></p>

<p>Over the course of seven days, the gains amounted to a mere 0.1%, underscoring the tenuous nature of the recovery attempts.</p>
<h2><strong>Anticipating A Potential Turnaround</strong></h2>
<p>Amidst the price volatility, a key question emerges: can the <a href="https://u.today/xrps-3-billion-volume-surge-paints-interesting-picture" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">falling XRP price</a> rally once more? If the price does indeed witness another surge in buying pressure that propels it to the $0.6 support level, it could signal a concerted effort by buyers to accumulate the asset at a discounted rate. </p>
<p>All eyes are now on the critical resistance level of $0.665. Should the XRP price manage to break through this barrier, it could serve as the initial sign of a broader recovery trend.</p>
<p>Market participants and analysts alike are closely monitoring these developments, seeking clues that could shed light on the elusive interplay between trading volume, price movements, and market sentiment.</p>

<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-547169" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-78.png?resize=1024%2C55" alt="" width="1024" height="55" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-78.png?resize=1024%2C55?w=1147 1147w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-78.png?resize=1024%2C55?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-78.png?resize=1024%2C55?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-78.png?resize=1024%2C55?w=860 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-78.png?resize=1024%2C55?w=1140 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-78.png?resize=1024%2C55?w=750 750w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" data-recalc-dims="1"/></p>

<p>Meanwhile, XRP is currently trading at at $0.627, according to <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/xrp" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">CoinGecko</a>, unchanged in the last 24 hours, while exhibiting a modest 1.7% gain over the span of the last seven days.</p>
<p><em>(This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk).</em></p>
<p><em>Featured image from The State Farm Newsroom</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-21.jpg?fit=460%2C306" width="460" height="306" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">547153</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin-Friendly Javier Milei Wins Presidential Primaries In Argentina</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-friendly-javier-milei-wins-presidential-primaries/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 12:50:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[argentina]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Argentine presidential primaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin support]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Javier Milei]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=547180</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Argentine libertarian Presidential candidate and Bitcoin enthusiast Javier Milei has shocked the world by emerging victorious in Argentina’s recent primary elections. The pro-Bitcoin advocate scored the majority of the votes, making a stinging win during the Primaries on August 13. Javier Milei Demolishes Electoral Competition Javier Milei, an outspoken Argentine economist, is known for his sharp criticism of traditional politics and his fervent support of cryptocurrencies, including Bitcoin. Due to this, previous poll predictions had stated that Milei would score no higher than third place in the recent elections.  Related Reading: Did XRP Price Really Hit $50 On Gemini Exchange? However, Milei decimated the August elections with a stunning display of voter support, accumulating over 30% of the 90% of votes counted. Milei leads the libertarian party, “La Libertad Avanza” and the party is dominating with 32% of votes.  In comparison, Argentine presidential candidates like Patricia Bullrich in “Juntos por el Cambio” (Together for Change) party received 28.14% votes, and Sergio Massa in “Unidos por la Patria” (Union for the Homeland) party received 26.84% votes.  From the onset, Milei has attracted the attention of the Argentine population through his outspoken support of cryptocurrency, lack of political interventions, and the abolishment of the country’s central bank.  Milei has stated that the country&#8217;s central banks should be destroyed to eliminate corrupt political authorities that influence the country&#8217;s economy and inflation rates. He has also said that Argentina’s adoption of bitcoin cryptocurrency would help create a more stable and accountable government, reducing government bureaucracy and improving the country’s declining economy.  “The central bank is a scam, a mechanism by which politicians cheat the good people with inflationary tax,” Milei stated.  BTC price recovers after brief dip &#124; Source: BTCUSD on Tradingview.com  Argentina Grapples with Spiraling Economic Crisis The daily reality of the Argentine country is filled with significant growth fluctuations, high inflation, and a deteriorating GDP. Argentina’s inflation is the third highest in the world, following Venezuela and Lebanon. Reports also state that the country faces one of the worst economic crises since the depression from 1998 to 2002.  Recently, Argentina has hit new record lows against the dollar weekly. Since the beginning of 2023, the Argentine peso has lost 24% in value against the dollar, resulting in black market rates selling one dollar for 500 pesos. Argentina is also in debt, owing the International Monetary Fund (IMF) an astonishing $44 billion. Milei’s approach toward adopting cryptocurrency triggers several governmental agencies, including the IMF, which strongly opposes Bitcoin cryptocurrency. Milei’s manifesto includes plans to dollarize the country’s economy, which aims to stabilize the country’s native currency.  Related Reading: San Francisco’s SoFi Bank Reveals Significant Holdings In BTC, ETH, And DOGE Argentina’s current economic crisis has also struck a nerve in Argentines, with many young citizens strongly supporting Milei’s views and commitment to free-market policies.  Although Milei’s victory in the primaries is a positive step forward toward the general elections coming up on October 22, his success is not without controversy, as critics publicly oppose his policies and views.  Milei’s win in the August primary election also does not guarantee a win in the general election. However, his victory has undoubtedly upended the country’s political system and sparked conversations about Argentina’s future. Featured image from Merco Press, chart from Tradingview.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Argentine libertarian Presidential candidate and Bitcoin enthusiast Javier Milei has shocked the world by emerging victorious in Argentina’s recent primary elections. The pro-Bitcoin advocate scored the majority of the votes, making a stinging win during the Primaries on August 13.</p>
<h2>Javier Milei Demolishes Electoral Competition</h2>
<p>Javier Milei, an outspoken Argentine economist, is known for his sharp criticism of traditional politics and his fervent support of cryptocurrencies, including Bitcoin. Due to this, previous poll predictions had stated that Milei would score no higher than third place in the recent elections. </p>

<p>However, Milei decimated the <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/graphics/2023-argentina-election/" rel="nofollow">August elections</a> with a stunning display of voter support, accumulating over 30% of the 90% of votes counted. Milei leads the libertarian party, “La Libertad Avanza” and the party is dominating with 32% of votes. </p>
<p>In comparison, Argentine presidential candidates like Patricia Bullrich in “Juntos por el Cambio” (Together for Change) party received 28.14% votes, and Sergio Massa in “Unidos por la Patria” (Union for the Homeland) party received 26.84% votes. </p>
<p>From the onset, Milei has attracted the attention of the Argentine population through his outspoken support of cryptocurrency, lack of political interventions, and the abolishment of the country’s central bank. </p>
<p>Milei has stated that the country&#8217;s central banks should be destroyed to eliminate corrupt political authorities that influence the country&#8217;s economy and inflation rates. He has also said that Argentina’s adoption of bitcoin cryptocurrency would help create a more stable and accountable government, reducing government bureaucracy and improving the country’s declining economy. </p>
<p>“The central bank is a scam, a mechanism by which politicians cheat the good people with inflationary tax,” Milei stated. </p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/lVqqedFY/" alt="Bitcoin (BTC) price chart from Tradingview.com (Javier Milei Argentina)" width="2884" height="1746"/></p>

<h2>Argentina Grapples with Spiraling Economic Crisis</h2>
<p>The daily reality of the Argentine country is filled with significant growth fluctuations, high inflation, and a deteriorating GDP. Argentina’s inflation is the third highest in the world, following Venezuela and Lebanon. Reports also state that the country faces one of the worst economic crises since the depression from 1998 to 2002. </p>
<p>Recently, Argentina has hit new record lows against the dollar weekly. Since the beginning of 2023, the Argentine peso has lost 24% in value against the dollar, resulting in black market rates selling one dollar for 500 pesos. Argentina is also in debt, owing the International Monetary Fund (IMF) an astonishing $44 billion.</p>
<p>Milei’s approach toward adopting cryptocurrency triggers several governmental agencies, including the IMF, which strongly opposes Bitcoin cryptocurrency. Milei’s manifesto includes plans to dollarize the country’s economy, which aims to stabilize the country’s native currency. </p>

<p>Argentina’s current economic crisis has also struck a nerve in Argentines, with many young citizens strongly supporting Milei’s views and commitment to free-market policies. </p>
<p>Although Milei’s victory in the primaries is a positive step forward toward the general elections coming up on October 22, his success is not without controversy, as critics publicly oppose his policies and views. </p>
<p>Milei’s win in the August primary election also does not guarantee a win in the general election. However, his victory has undoubtedly upended the country’s political system and sparked conversations about Argentina’s future.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-Javier-Milei.jpeg?fit=460%2C259" width="460" height="259" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">547180</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>SHIB, PEPE, APE Gain Against Bitcoin, Santiment Explains What This Means</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/altcoin/shib-pepe-ape-gain-bitcoin-santiment-explains-means/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hououin Kyouma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 11:40:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[APE]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ApeCoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[APEUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PEPE]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[pepeusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIB]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shiba Inu]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIBUSD]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=547127</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Shiba Inu (SHIB), Pepe (PEPE), and ApeCoin (APE) have performed well against Bitcoin recently. Here&#8217;s what the memecoins&#8217; profits mean. SHIB, PEPE, And APE Have Enjoyed An Uptrend Recently Bitcoin has been going through a major phase of stagnation recently as the number 1 cryptocurrency&#8217;s price has remained stuck between the $29,000 and $30,000 levels. Much of the other market hasn&#8217;t been all that different, either. Out of the few coins that have gone against the grain and have displayed some volatility. However, the meme coins have especially stood out. Shiba Inu, Pepe, and Apecoin, in particular, have all pulled away from BTC. Dogecoin (DOGE), the original meme coin, also saw bullish momentum earlier, but the asset has slowed down recently. Out of these assets, PEPE has been the best performer, as it has observed profits of about 22% within the past week. Looks like PEPE has been going up recently &#124; Source: PEPEUSD on TradingView While Pepe&#8217;s weekly gains are certainly the most impressive of the bunch, the meme coin is actually in severe losses of 17% when considering the period of the past month. Related Reading: Want A Bitcoin Spot ETF? Then Prove BTC Is Not Manipulated, Says SEC ApeCoin has risen by 12% in the past week, and while the coin isn&#8217;t in negative during the past month, its performance for the period is still only flat. APE has also gone up in recent days &#124; Source: APEUSD on TradingView Unlike these two assets with significantly smaller market caps, Shiba Inu has not only registered impressive gains of 16% during the past week, but it has also observed a massive 32% rise during the last month. SHIB has sharply jumped recently &#124; Source: SHIBUSD on TradingView The reason behind the solid Shiba Inu performance is likely to be the much-hyped Shibarium upgrade, which is expected to launch sometime later in the current week. Does The Memecoin Rally Hold Any Significance For The Greater Market? All in all, it&#8217;s clear that these three meme coins have been building up bullish momentum recently, and they have been doing so simultaneously. In a new insight post, the on-chain analytics firm Santiment has revealed that while these assets may be rising, their social volumes haven&#8217;t budged much. SHIB and others haven't seen too high social volumes &#124; Source: Santiment The &#8220;social volume&#8221; here is a metric that keeps track of the degree of discussion that an asset is receiving on the major social media platforms. When this indicator has a high value, it&#8217;s a sign that a large number of users are talking about the coin and that there may be FUD or hype present around the coin. In uptrends, this metric reaching very high values is generally not a good sign, as it shows that FOMO is on the rise among social media users, which is something that has historically had an opposite effect on the price and has led to top formations. Since these metrics have risen for SHIB and the other meme coins, it means that social media users haven&#8217;t been paying too much attention so far to the pumps that these cryptocurrencies have been going through. Related Reading: Goldman Foresees Q2 2024 Fed Rate Cut: A Boost For Bitcoin? In the same post, Santiment also explains that the meme coins pulling away from Bitcoin have historically held significance for the entire sector. &#8220;This can often signal that the entire crypto market may be veering toward &#8216;overheated&#8217; territory,&#8221; notes the analytics firm. Santiment also says that when SHIB and co. see isolated pumps, &#8220;it is often associated with greed and/or boredom from the crowd. And these two behaviors often have adverse impacts on the markets.&#8221; Featured image from iStock.com, charts from TradingView.com, Santiment.net]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Shiba Inu (SHIB), Pepe (PEPE), and ApeCoin (APE) have performed well against Bitcoin recently. Here&#8217;s what the memecoins&#8217; profits mean.</p>
<h2>SHIB, PEPE, And APE Have Enjoyed An Uptrend Recently</h2>
<p>Bitcoin has been going through a major phase of <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/will-record-low-volatility-awaken-a-behemoth-bitcoin-surge-4000-signal-returns/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">stagnation</a> recently as the number 1 cryptocurrency&#8217;s price has remained stuck between the $29,000 and $30,000 levels.</p>
<p>Much of the other market hasn&#8217;t been all that different, either. Out of the few coins that have gone against the grain and have displayed some volatility. However, the meme coins have especially stood out.</p>
<p>Shiba Inu, Pepe, and Apecoin, in particular, have all pulled away from BTC. Dogecoin (DOGE), the original meme coin, also saw bullish momentum earlier, but the asset has slowed down recently.</p>
<p>Out of these assets, PEPE has been the best performer, as it has observed profits of about 22% within the past week.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium aligncenter" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/FMZd78RQ/" alt="Pepe Price Chart" width="1534" height="877"/></p>

<p>While Pepe&#8217;s weekly gains are certainly the most impressive of the bunch, the meme coin is actually in severe losses of 17% when considering the period of the past month.</p>

<p>ApeCoin has risen by 12% in the past week, and while the coin isn&#8217;t in negative during the past month, its performance for the period is still only flat.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium aligncenter" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/mDHyaJGy/" alt="Apecoin Price Chart" width="1534" height="877"/></p>

<p>Unlike these two assets with significantly smaller market caps, Shiba Inu has not only registered impressive gains of 16% during the past week, but it has also observed a massive 32% rise during the last month.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/QsltnAMg/" alt="Shiba Inu (SHIB) Price Chart" width="1534" height="877"/></p>

<p>The reason behind the solid Shiba Inu performance is likely to be the much-hyped <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/shib/shiba-inu-shib-rides-on-bullish-waves-as-shibarium-launch-nears-buy-now/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Shibarium</a> upgrade, which is expected to launch sometime later in the current week.</p>
<h2>Does The Memecoin Rally Hold Any Significance For The Greater Market?</h2>
<p>All in all, it&#8217;s clear that these three meme coins have been building up bullish momentum recently, and they have been doing so simultaneously.</p>
<p>In a new insight post, the on-chain analytics firm <a href="https://insights.santiment.net/read/what-do-you-meme-7358?fpr=twitter" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Santiment</a> has revealed that while these assets may be rising, their social volumes haven&#8217;t budged much.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone aligncenter" src="https://i0.wp.com/production-sanbase-images.s3.amazonaws.com/uploads/58091ed4fb213f38c3dcff33e8e119641f2d9cda81d31ef300a097cc7e010105_1691834888401_Screenshot%202023-08-12%20030811.png?resize=3070%2C1692&#038;ssl=1" alt="SHIB Social Volume" width="3070" height="1692"  data-recalc-dims="1"/></p>

<p>The &#8220;<a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/altcoin/internet-computer-icp-social-dominance-hits-top-in/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">social volume</a>&#8221; here is a metric that keeps track of the degree of discussion that an asset is receiving on the major social media platforms. When this indicator has a high value, it&#8217;s a sign that a large number of users are talking about the coin and that there may be FUD or hype present around the coin.</p>
<p>In uptrends, this metric reaching very high values is generally not a good sign, as it shows that FOMO is on the rise among social media users, which is something that has historically had an opposite effect on the price and has led to top formations.</p>
<p>Since these metrics have risen for SHIB and the other meme coins, it means that social media users haven&#8217;t been paying too much attention so far to the pumps that these cryptocurrencies have been going through.</p>

<p>In the same post, Santiment also explains that the meme coins pulling away from Bitcoin have historically held significance for the entire sector. &#8220;This can often signal that the entire crypto market may be veering toward &#8216;overheated&#8217; territory,&#8221; notes the analytics firm.</p>
<p>Santiment also says that when SHIB and co. see isolated pumps, &#8220;it is often associated with greed and/or boredom from the crowd. And these two behaviors often have adverse impacts on the markets.&#8221;</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/iStock-1353098980.jpg?fit=460%2C307" width="460" height="307" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">547127</post-id>	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
