<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
>

<channel>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.newsbtc.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<description>Bitcoin &#38; Cryptocurrency News Today</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 03:03:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Price At Significant Risk of Crash Below $25,400</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-at-significant-risk-25400/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 03:03:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xbtusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=537424</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin price is struggling below the $26,150 support. BTC could start another decline if it breaks the key $25,400 support in the near term. Bitcoin is moving lower below the $26,150 support zone. The price is trading below $26,000 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average. There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $26,000 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Kraken). The pair could decline again if there is a move below the $25,400 support zone. Bitcoin Price Remains In Downtrend Bitcoin price struggled to settle above the $26,500 resistance zone. BTC declined below the $26,150 support to move into a bearish zone. The recent high was formed near $26,133 and the price is now moving lower. There was a break below the 50% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $25,400 swing low to the $26,133 high. The price also traded below the $25,750 support. Bitcoin price is now trading below $26,000 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average. There is also a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $26,000 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair. It seems to be holding the $25,570 support level. It is close to the 76.4% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $25,400 swing low to the $26,133 high. Immediate resistance is near the $26,000 level and the trend line region. The first major resistance is near the $26,150 level. A clear move above the $26,150 resistance might start a decent increase. The next major resistance is near the $26,500 level. A close above $26,500 might send the price further higher. Source: BTCUSD on TradingView.com The next key resistance is near the $27,000 level, above which Bitcoin might rise toward the $27,500 resistance. Any more gains above the $27,500 resistance zone might send the price toward the $28,500 resistance zone. More Losses in BTC? If Bitcoin’s price fails to clear the $26,000 resistance, it could continue to move down. another decline. Immediate support on the downside is near the $25,570 level. The next major support is near the $25,400 level, below which the price might accelerate lower. In the stated case, the price could drop toward the $25,000 support in the near term. Technical indicators: Hourly MACD – The MACD is now gaining pace in the bearish zone. Hourly RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BTC/USD is below the 50 level. Major Support Levels – $25,570, followed by $25,500. Major Resistance Levels – $26,000, $26,150, and $26,500.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>Bitcoin price is struggling below the $26,150 support. BTC could start another decline if it breaks the key $25,400 support in the near term.</em></p>
<ul>
<li>Bitcoin is moving lower below the $26,150 support zone.</li>
<li>The price is trading below $26,000 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average.</li>
<li>There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $26,000 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could decline again if there is a move below the $25,400 support zone.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Bitcoin Price Remains In Downtrend</h2>
<p>Bitcoin price <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-defies-gravity-26k/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">struggled to settle above the $26,500 resistance zone</a>. BTC declined below the $26,150 support to move into a bearish zone.</p>
<p>The recent high was formed near $26,133 and the price is now moving lower. There was a break below the 50% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $25,400 swing low to the $26,133 high. The price also traded below the $25,750 support.</p>
<p>Bitcoin price is now trading below $26,000 and the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-could-increase-26600/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">100 hourly Simple moving average</a>. There is also a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $26,000 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair.</p>
<p>It seems to be holding the $25,570 support level. It is close to the 76.4% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $25,400 swing low to the $26,133 high. Immediate resistance is near the $26,000 level and the trend line region.</p>
<p>The first major resistance is near the $26,150 level. A clear move above the $26,150 resistance might start a decent increase. The next major resistance is near the $26,500 level. A close above $26,500 might send the price further higher.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-537425" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-7.png" alt="Bitcoin Price" width="1834" height="845" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-7.png 1834w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-7-460x212.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-7-860x396.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-7-768x354.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-7-1536x708.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-7-750x346.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-7-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1834px) 100vw, 1834px"/></p>
<p>Source: <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BTCUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">BTCUSD on TradingView.com</a></p>
<p>The next key resistance is near the $27,000 level, above which Bitcoin might rise toward the $27,500 resistance. Any more gains above the $27,500 resistance zone might send the price toward the $28,500 resistance zone.</p>
<h2>More Losses in BTC?</h2>
<p>If Bitcoin’s price fails to clear the $26,000 resistance, it could continue to move down. another decline. Immediate support on the downside is near the $25,570 level.</p>
<p>The next major support is near the $25,400 level, below which the price might accelerate lower. In the stated case, the price could drop toward the $25,000 support in the near term.</p>
<p>Technical indicators:</p>
<p>Hourly MACD – The MACD is now gaining pace in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>Hourly RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BTC/USD is below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Levels – $25,570, followed by $25,500.</p>
<p>Major Resistance Levels – $26,000, $26,150, and $26,500.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/shutterstock_215569255-460x306.jpg" width="460" height="306" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>BNB Displays Short-Term Bullish Momentum Amidst Massive Binance Outflows</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bnb-displays-short-term-bullish-momentum-amidst-massive-binance-outflows/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 16:13:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance Coin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BNB]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[securities]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=537406</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Binance finds itself entangled in a lawsuit filed by the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), dealing a heavy blow to BNB, the token issued by Binance. The allegations leveled against the crypto exchange suggest its involvement in unlawful activities, specifically multiple violations of securities laws. Consequently, the impact of these allegations manifested as substantial outflows from the exchange, prompting Changpeng Zhao, the CEO, to disclose an astonishing figure of over $392 million in net outflows in the last 24 hours. It&#8217;s worth noting that Binance has dealt with significant outflows before, indicating a history of navigating such challenges. Related Reading: Bleak Dogecoin (DOGE) Social Sentiment Raises Questions About Price Reversal According to our data, last 24hrs, @Binance net outflow is about $392m. Our wallet addresses are public. Some 3rd party analytics measure Change in AUM (asset under management) in USD equivalent as outflow. This would include crypto price drops (which decrease AUM) as &#8220;outflow&#8221;.… — CZ 🔶 Binance (@cz_binance) June 10, 2023 Meanwhile, in the wake of the SEC filing, Nansen data indicates that Binance witnessed a staggering amount of nearly $3 billion in outflows. The aftermath of the recent lawsuit has caused BNB to plummet in value. Coingecko reports that the token has experienced a drastic decline of over 23% in just the span of a week. Source: Nansen Binance Vs. The SEC: What’s The Gist?  According to the official SEC press release, the company and 13 other entities are being sued for the operation of an unregistered exchange and the commingling of customer funds through companies related to Binance. The regulatory body also alleges that Binance had knowledge of the regulations regarding exchanges and securities but chose to ignore those laws, putting investor funds at risk just to maximize profits.  They also highlighted the sale of unregistered securities. The SEC targets the company’s “Simple Earn” and “BNB Vault” crypto-lending products. These products are part of Binance’s staking service and, with the recent crackdown on staking services by the SEC, are considered securities by the regulatory body. BNB market cap currently at $36.6 billion on the weekend chart: TradingView.com The SEC also targeted Binance’s failure to restrict the exchange’s services to US citizens. Just this March, the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) alleged that the company is breaking various financial laws including the ones intended to stop money laundering. The SEC also remarked that Binance misled customers through “strategic and targeted wash trading”.  Related Reading: MATIC Faces Long-Term Struggle For Growth As SEC Claims It’s A Security BNB Yet To Make A Comeback Since then, BNB is the only altcoin that has not rebounded since the general market downturn. However, analysts are still somewhat bullish in the short-term capacity of the coin despite the market’s recent slippage.  Source - Coingecko At the token’s current price point of $235, BNB bulls should defend the $234 support level to target higher highs in the short term as long as no bearish news hits the market. But at the moment, it seems that the weight of the bears will defeat any attempt for a bullish breakout.  However, if the bulls are able to defend this support level, a return to the $300 price point might be possible. Despite the optimism in the market, developments in the lawsuit will surely affect BNB in the long term.  Featured image from Protos]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Binance finds itself entangled in a <a href="https://www.sec.gov/news/press-release/2023-101" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">lawsuit</a> filed by the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), dealing a heavy blow to BNB, the token issued by Binance. The allegations leveled against the crypto exchange suggest its involvement in unlawful activities, specifically multiple violations of securities laws.</p>
<p>Consequently, the impact of these allegations manifested as substantial outflows from the exchange, prompting Changpeng Zhao, the CEO, to <a href="https://twitter.com/cz_binance/status/1667554966662266883" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">disclose</a> an astonishing figure of over $392 million in net outflows in the last 24 hours. It&#8217;s worth noting that Binance has dealt with significant outflows before, indicating a history of navigating such challenges.</p>

<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">According to our data, last 24hrs, <a href="https://twitter.com/binance?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">@Binance</a> net outflow is about $392m.</p>
<p>Our wallet addresses are public. Some 3rd party analytics measure Change in AUM (asset under management) in USD equivalent as outflow. This would include crypto price drops (which decrease AUM) as &#8220;outflow&#8221;.…</p>
<p>— CZ <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f536.png" alt="🔶" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> Binance (@cz_binance) <a href="https://twitter.com/cz_binance/status/1667554966662266883?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">June 10, 2023</a></p></blockquote>






<p>Meanwhile, in the wake of the SEC filing, Nansen data <a href="https://twitter.com/nansen_ai/status/1666145237474095104?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">indicates</a> that Binance witnessed a staggering amount of nearly $3 billion in outflows. The aftermath of the recent lawsuit has caused BNB to plummet in value. Coingecko <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/bnb" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">reports</a> that the token has experienced a drastic decline of over 23% in just the span of a week.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-537408 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-55-860x507.png" alt="" width="860" height="507" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-55-860x507.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-55-460x271.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-55-768x453.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-55-750x442.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-55-1140x672.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-55.png 1196w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/></p>







<h2><strong>Binance Vs. The SEC: What’s The Gist? </strong></h2>
<p>According to the <a href="https://www.sec.gov/news/press-release/2023-101" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">official</a> SEC press release, the company and 13 other entities are being sued for the operation of an unregistered exchange and the commingling of customer funds through companies related to Binance. </p>
<p>The regulatory body also alleges that Binance had knowledge of the regulations regarding exchanges and securities but chose to ignore those laws, putting investor funds at risk just to maximize profits. </p>
<p>They also highlighted the sale of unregistered securities. The SEC targets the company’s “Simple Earn” and “BNB Vault” crypto-lending products. These products are part of Binance’s staking service and, with the recent crackdown on staking services by the SEC, are considered securities by the regulatory body.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/HDtqOdLb/" width="2047" height="979"/></p>

<p>The SEC also targeted Binance’s failure to restrict the exchange’s services to US citizens. Just this March, the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) alleged that the company is breaking various financial laws including the ones intended to stop money laundering. The SEC also remarked that Binance misled customers through “strategic and targeted wash trading”. </p>

<h2><strong>BNB Yet To Make A Comeback</strong></h2>
<p>Since then, BNB is the only altcoin that has not rebounded since the general market downturn. However, analysts are still somewhat <a href="https://www.cryptoglobe.com/latest/2023/06/bnb-bnb-usd-price-analysis-for-11-june-2023-a-strong-buy-signal-in-the-short-term/?utm_source=CryptoNews&amp;utm_medium=app&amp;utm_campaign=shared" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">bullish</a> in the short-term capacity of the coin despite the market’s recent slippage. </p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-537410" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-56.png" alt="" width="1137" height="66" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-56.png 1137w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-56-460x27.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-56-860x50.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-56-768x45.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-56-750x44.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 1137px) 100vw, 1137px"/></p>

<p>At the token’s current price point of $235, BNB bulls should defend the $234 support level to target higher highs in the short term as long as no bearish news hits the market. But at the moment, it seems that the weight of the bears will defeat any attempt for a bullish breakout. </p>
<p>However, if the bulls are able to defend this support level, a return to the $300 price point might be possible. Despite the optimism in the market, developments in the lawsuit will surely affect BNB in the long term. </p>
<p><em>Featured image from Protos</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-57-460x234.png" width="460" height="234" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>MATIC Faces Long-Term Struggle For Growth As SEC Claims It&#8217;s A Security</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/matic-faces-long-term-struggle/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 13:48:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MATIC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[price analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=537386</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[MATIC is currently facing increased uncertainty as it has been officially classified as a security by the US Securities and Exchange Commission, as revealed in the recent filing against Binance. Consequently, the Polygon blockchain token experienced a significant drop of 31% within a week, setting a new record. However, there is some positive news as it has managed to recover, witnessing a promising rebound of over 11% in the last 24 hours. Related Reading: Bleak Dogecoin (DOGE) Social Sentiment Raises Questions About Price Reversal Source: Coingecko L2 coins will be the next bullrun coins. Already knew, already confirmed.$SOL $ADA $MATIC and others L1&#8217;s got the security stamp. Regulation will kick hard = tight choice of L1/L2 coins. Where will all this money flow to? pic.twitter.com/jw5xpLRA4j — Zoomer Oracle (@ZoomerOracle) June 5, 2023 MATIC is one of the 13 tokens within the Binance lawsuit to be designated as a security. Polygon Labs, the developer of MATIC, issued a statement on Twitter defending Polygon saying that the network is “developed outside the US, deployed outside the US, and focused to this day on the global community that supports the network.” This recent lawsuit against Binance was followed up by the SEC’s lawsuit against Coinbase, citing that the company is operating an unregistered exchange in connection with the company’s staking service. Fear, Uncertainty And Doubt In The Market  With the recent classification of several cryptocurrencies as securities, the market has slid considerably within the past week. Bitcoin, the top cryptocurrency, gained dominance in light of the recent regulatory fillings against Binance and Coinbase. The other tokens in the list are SOL, ADA, FIL, ATOM, SAND, MANA, ALGO, and COTI. According to the lawsuit, the tokens are listed as investment contracts. This made the SEC label them as securities in accordance with the Howey Test, which is a test to know whether a certain asset is a security or not. MATIC market cap at $5.8 billion. Chart: TradingView.com This move by the SEC was in line with its recent actions against the crypto industry. Just this February, the regulatory body cracked down on Kraken’s staking service along with forcing the company to pay $30 million in penalties for the violations. If the mentioned tokens and companies fail to comply with the SEC, it may lead to another Ripple-like event which will affect the market. MATIC Bulls Should Watch This Level At the time of writing, MATIC is being supported at the $0.6 price level which will act as the launch pad for future bullishness. However, external market forces still hold sway in the token’s momentum and price actions in the near future. The recent lawsuits already slashed millions upon millions of possible gains for investors. Source: Coinglass Related Reading: Bearish BNB Signs Hint Downtrend May Persist Beyond Expectations Meanwhile, CoinGlass data shows MATIC long positions being liquidated as the market crashed after the lawsuits were made public. Despite this, buying pressure after the crash continued with MATIC bulls holding $0.6 support. If they can hold on to this support level, we might be able to see a return towards the $0.83 support in the medium to long term. Featured image from The Daily Hodl]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MATIC is currently facing increased uncertainty as it has been officially <a href="https://twitter.com/ZoomerOracle/status/1665748915176501249?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">classified</a> as a security by the US Securities and Exchange Commission, as revealed in the recent filing against Binance.</p>
<p>Consequently, the Polygon blockchain token experienced a significant <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/polygon" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">drop</a> of 31% within a week, setting a new record. However, there is some positive news as it has managed to recover, witnessing a promising rebound of over 11% in the last 24 hours.</p>

<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-537398" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-53.png" alt="" width="1148" height="59" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-53.png 1148w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-53-460x24.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-53-860x44.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-53-768x39.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-53-1140x59.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-53-750x39.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 1148px) 100vw, 1148px"/></p>

<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">L2 coins will be the next bullrun coins. Already knew, already confirmed.<a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24SOL&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$SOL</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24ADA&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$ADA</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24MATIC&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$MATIC</a> and others L1&#8217;s got the security stamp. Regulation will kick hard = tight choice of L1/L2 coins. Where will all this money flow to? <a href="https://t.co/jw5xpLRA4j" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/jw5xpLRA4j</a></p>
<p>— Zoomer Oracle (@ZoomerOracle) <a href="https://twitter.com/ZoomerOracle/status/1665748915176501249?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">June 5, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p>MATIC is one of the 13 tokens within the Binance lawsuit to be designated as a security. Polygon Labs, the developer of MATIC, issued a statement on Twitter defending Polygon saying that the network is “developed outside the US, deployed outside the US, and focused to this day on the global community that supports the network.”</p>
<p>This recent lawsuit against Binance was <a href="https://www.sec.gov/news/press-release/2023-102" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">followed up</a> by the SEC’s lawsuit against Coinbase, citing that the company is operating an unregistered exchange in connection with the company’s staking service.</p>
<h2><strong>Fear, Uncertainty And Doubt In The Market </strong></h2>
<p>With the recent classification of several cryptocurrencies as securities, the market has slid considerably within the past week. Bitcoin, the top cryptocurrency, <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bitcoin-dominance-soars-to-47-5-highest-level-in-a-year-as-other-crypto-assets-suffer/" rel="nofollow">gained</a> dominance in light of the recent regulatory fillings against Binance and Coinbase.</p>
<p>The other tokens in the <a href="https://twitter.com/ZoomerOracle/status/1665748915176501249/photo/1" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">list</a> are SOL, ADA, FIL, ATOM, SAND, MANA, ALGO, and COTI. According to the lawsuit, the tokens are listed as investment contracts. This made the SEC label them as securities in accordance with the <a href="https://www.investopedia.com/terms/h/howey-test.asp" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Howey Test</a>, which is a test to know whether a certain asset is a security or not.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/hstPQg1x/" width="2047" height="979"/></p>

<p>This move by the SEC was in line with its recent actions against the crypto industry. Just this February, the regulatory body cracked down on Kraken’s staking service along with forcing the company to pay $30 million in penalties for the violations.</p>
<p>If the mentioned tokens and companies fail to comply with the SEC, it may lead to another Ripple-like event which will affect the market.</p>
<h2><strong>MATIC Bulls Should Watch This Level</strong></h2>
<p>At the time of writing, MATIC is being supported at the $0.6 price level which will act as the launch pad for future bullishness. However, external market forces still hold sway in the token’s momentum and price actions in the near future. The recent lawsuits already slashed millions upon millions of possible gains for investors.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-537396 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-52.png" alt="" width="1391" height="438" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-52.png 1391w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-52-460x145.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-52-860x271.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-52-768x242.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-52-750x236.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-52-1140x359.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1391px) 100vw, 1391px"/></p>


<p>Meanwhile, <a href="https://www.coinglass.com/LiquidationData" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">CoinGlass</a> data shows MATIC long positions being liquidated as the market crashed after the lawsuits were made public.</p>
<p>Despite this, buying pressure after the crash continued with MATIC bulls holding $0.6 support. If they can hold on to this support level, we might be able to see a return towards the $0.83 support in the medium to long term.</p>
<p><em>Featured image from The Daily Hodl</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-54-460x243.png" width="460" height="243" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum&#8217;s Vitalik Buterin, Polygon&#8217;s Sandeep Nailwal Donate $100 Million To COVID-19 Research</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/ethereum/ethereums-vitalik-buterin-polygons-sandeep-nailwal-donate-100-million-to-covid-19-research/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 18:09:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[COVID]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[philanthropy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Polygon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sanddep Nailwal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Vitalik Buterin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=537374</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Vitalik Buterin, co-founder of Ethereum, and Sandeep Nailwal, co-founder of Polygon, have pledged $100 million to help accelerate COVID-19 research and relief efforts in India.  With COVID-19 variants continuing to emerge and spread, and with a very high number of people experiencing long-term symptoms speeding up, research efforts are critical. How The Donation Will Be Used To Support COVID-19 Research The donations from Buterin and Nailwal are some of the largest philanthropic contributions ever made in crypto. Buterin made the announcement in a Twitter thread and according to the thread, the fund will be donated to Crypto Relief, with the funds going directly to researchers working on solutions to combat the long-term effects of coronavirus.  Related Reading: Terra Classic (LUNC) Analysis: Is The $0.00012 Target Within Reach? Crypto Relief is a project led by set up by Nailwal during the height of the COVID pandemic as an emergency relief fund. The polygon co-founder said the non-profit organization is now upgrading into a long-term strategic fund for healthcare donations in India. Buterin also confirmed this change of approach in his Twitter post, noting that dealing with Covid and future pandemics needs to take an integrated global approach. “Work in India continues to be a key part of the solution, but we also need an integrated global approach,” the co-founder said. The money will go to fund research projects related to cutting-edge scientific discoveries &#38; inventions in India and other developing nations. Overall, it’s a win for science, a win for global health, and a win for humanity. ETH price falls to the $1,700 level &#124; Source: ETHUSD on TradingView.com Past Donations Of Vitalik Buterin To COVID Relief Vitalik Buterin has a history of donating to important causes like COVID-19 relief, with him donating cryptocurrencies worth $1.5 billion to several non-profit organizations in 2021. During this period, Buterin donated over $1 billion worth of Shiba Inu coin to aid India&#8217;s fight against the coronavirus.  Related Reading: Optimism Bedrock Upgrade: Transaction Fee Savings Hit $150,000 And Counting Buterin made the donation by offloading 50 trillion SHIB tokens worth $1.2 billion, which he was gifted by the creators of the Shiba Inu coin. With India being one of the most badly affected countries during the pandemic, the fund helped provide medical equipment and supplies as the country battled a deadly second wave of COVID-19 infections. Outside of the pandemic, Buterin has donated millions of dollars in crypto to various charities and causes. Last year, he quietly donated $5 million to Ukraine relief efforts following the Russian invasion. Featured image from Coingape, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Vitalik Buterin, co-founder of Ethereum, and Sandeep Nailwal, co-founder of Polygon, have pledged $100 million to help accelerate COVID-19 research and relief efforts in India. </p>
<p>With COVID-19 variants continuing to emerge and spread, and with a very high number of people experiencing long-term symptoms speeding up, research efforts are critical.</p>
<h2>How The Donation Will Be Used To Support COVID-19 Research</h2>
<p>The donations from Buterin and Nailwal are some of the largest philanthropic contributions ever made in crypto. Buterin made the announcement in a <a href="https://twitter.com/VitalikButerin/status/1666860069273710606?s=20" rel="nofollow">Twitter thread</a> and according to the thread, the fund will be donated to Crypto Relief, with the funds going directly to researchers working on solutions to combat the long-term effects of coronavirus. </p>

<p>Crypto Relief is a project led by set up by Nailwal during the height of the COVID pandemic as an emergency relief fund. The polygon co-founder said the non-profit organization is now upgrading into a long-term strategic fund for healthcare donations in India. Buterin also confirmed this change of approach in his Twitter post, noting that dealing with Covid and future pandemics needs to take an integrated global approach.</p>
<p>“Work in India continues to be a key part of the solution, but we also need an integrated global approach,” the co-founder said.</p>
<p>The money will go to fund research projects related to cutting-edge scientific discoveries &amp; inventions in India and other developing nations. Overall, it’s a win for science, a win for global health, and a win for humanity.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/jBQQI01b/" alt="Ethereum price chart from TradingView.com (COVID-19)" width="2882" height="1724"/></p>

<h2>Past Donations Of Vitalik Buterin To COVID Relief</h2>
<p>Vitalik Buterin has a history of donating to important causes like COVID-19 relief, with him donating cryptocurrencies worth $1.5 billion to several non-profit organizations in 2021. During this period, Buterin donated over $1 billion worth of Shiba Inu coin to aid India&#8217;s fight against the coronavirus. </p>

<p>Buterin made the donation by offloading 50 trillion SHIB tokens worth $1.2 billion, which he was gifted by the creators of the Shiba Inu coin. With India being one of the most badly affected countries during the pandemic, the fund helped provide medical equipment and supplies as the country battled a deadly second wave of COVID-19 infections.</p>
<p>Outside of the pandemic, Buterin has donated millions of dollars in crypto to various charities and causes. Last year, he quietly donated $5 million to Ukraine relief efforts following the Russian invasion.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Ethereum-Vitalik-Buterin-460x307.png" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Terra Classic (LUNC) Analysis: Is The $0.00012 Target Within Reach?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/terra-luna/terra-classic-lunc-analysis/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Olowoporoku Adeniyi]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 15:20:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Terra (LUNA)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LUNC analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LUNC Classic]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[terra lunc]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=537337</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[During the past seven days, the price of LUNC, the cryptocurrency of Terra Classic, has displayed a back-and-forth movement characterized by alternating green and red candles. This pattern suggests a lack of dominance from buyers or sellers, indicating uncertainty in the market regarding the direction of the trend.  Related Reading: Bitcoin (BTC) Lower Timeframe Outlook: $26,800 Breakthrough Could Spark Rally The recent legal actions taken by the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) against prominent crypto exchanges like Binance and Coinbase could contribute to this hesitation among market participants. As a result, the Terra classic coin is anticipated to undergo a prolonged period of consolidation in the upcoming days, as the overall trend remains bearish due to the influence of a wedge pattern. LUNC Price Analysis, Impact Of Regulatory Actions On Crypto Market In the midst of regulatory actions taken against major crypto exchanges, caution and uncertainty have permeated the cryptocurrency market, impacting traders and investors alike. This climate of uncertainty is reflected in the LUNC price chart, where alternating green and red candles indicate a lack of clear dominance from buyers or sellers. As market participants await further clarity and resolution regarding the regulatory actions, hesitation in making significant moves has emerged.  Consequently, the Terra classic coin is expected to undergo a period of consolidation, characterized by a relatively stable price, as market participants reassess the situation and evaluate the potential implications of the legal actions on the broader cryptocurrency ecosystem. Related Reading: Bleak Dogecoin (DOGE) Social Sentiment Raises Questions About Price Reversal However, it is worth noting that if the LUNC price continues its upward trajectory, it may potentially lead to a retest of the overhead trendline. A successful break above this trendline would serve as a pivotal signal, indicating the beginning of a new recovery rally for LUNC. Such a breakout would represent a shift in market sentiment and attract more buyers into the market, potentially altering the course of the cryptocurrency&#8217;s price trajectory. As the market dynamics continue to unfold, traders and investors will closely monitor the price action of LUNC, paying particular attention to the development of the wedge pattern and the resolution of regulatory actions. These factors will play a crucial role in shaping the future direction of LUNC and the broader cryptocurrency market. Will LUNC Price Rise To $0.00012? Affected by the descending wedge pattern, the LUNC price remains bearish, with the recent reversal signaling a possible decline. This downward movement could lead the price towards crucial support levels at $0.000082 and $0.00007, followed by a lower trendline. On the other hand, a recovery above $0.00012 would require buyers to break above the aforementioned trendline successfully. Currently, the coin is trading at $0.00008718 and appears to be moving sideways, indicating a lack of clear direction from market participants. Featured Image from iStock and charts from TradingView.com and Coingecko.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>During the past seven days, the price of LUNC, the cryptocurrency of Terra Classic, has displayed a back-and-forth movement characterized by alternating green and red candles. This pattern suggests a lack of dominance from buyers or sellers, indicating uncertainty in the market regarding the direction of the trend. </p>
<p><b>Related Reading</b>: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-btc-lower-timeframe-outlook-26800-breakthrough-could-spark-rally/?swcfpc=1">Bitcoin (BTC) Lower Timeframe Outlook: $26,800 Breakthrough Could Spark Rally</a></p>
<p>The recent <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/binance/sec-files-emergency-action-application-to-freeze-binance-us-assets/?swcfpc=1">legal actions</a> taken by the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) against prominent crypto exchanges like Binance and Coinbase could contribute to this hesitation among market participants. As a result, the Terra classic coin is anticipated to undergo a prolonged period of consolidation in the upcoming days, as the overall trend remains bearish due to the influence of a wedge pattern.</p>
<h2>LUNC Price Analysis, Impact Of Regulatory Actions On Crypto Market</h2>
<p>In the midst of regulatory actions taken against major crypto exchanges, caution and uncertainty have permeated the cryptocurrency market, impacting traders and investors alike. This climate of uncertainty is reflected in the LUNC price chart, where alternating green and red candles indicate a lack of clear dominance from buyers or sellers. As market participants await further clarity and resolution regarding the regulatory actions, hesitation in making significant moves has emerged. </p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium wp-image-537339" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Screenshot_148-460x63.png" alt="Terra Lunc gains wiped out in the past 24 hours: source @coingecko" width="460" height="63" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Screenshot_148-460x63.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Screenshot_148-768x105.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Screenshot_148-750x103.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Screenshot_148.png 832w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px"/>
<p>Consequently, the Terra classic coin is expected to undergo a period of consolidation, characterized by a relatively stable price, as market participants reassess the situation and evaluate the potential implications of the legal actions on the broader cryptocurrency ecosystem.</p>
<p><b>Related Reading</b>: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/dogecoin-experiences-bleak-social-sentiment/?swcfpc=1">Bleak Dogecoin (DOGE) Social Sentiment Raises Questions About Price Reversal</a></p>
<p>However, it is worth noting that if the LUNC price continues its upward trajectory, it may potentially lead to a retest of the overhead trendline. A successful break above this trendline would serve as a pivotal signal, indicating the beginning of a new recovery rally for LUNC. Such a breakout would represent a shift in market sentiment and attract more buyers into the market, potentially altering the course of the cryptocurrency&#8217;s price trajectory.</p>
<p>As the market dynamics continue to unfold, traders and investors will closely monitor the price action of LUNC, paying particular attention to the development of the wedge pattern and the resolution of regulatory actions. These factors will play a crucial role in shaping the future direction of LUNC and the broader cryptocurrency market.</p>
<h2>Will LUNC Price Rise To $0.00012?</h2>
<p>Affected by the descending wedge pattern, the LUNC price remains bearish, with the recent reversal signaling a possible decline. This downward movement could lead the price towards crucial support levels at $0.000082 and $0.00007, followed by a lower trendline. On the other hand, a recovery above $0.00012 would require buyers to break above the aforementioned trendline successfully. Currently, the coin is trading at $0.00008718 and appears to be moving sideways, indicating a lack of clear direction from market participants.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-537338 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image2-1-860x474.png" alt="Terra Classic Has experienced a steep correction in the past 24-hours: source @Tradingview.com" width="860" height="474" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image2-1-860x474.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image2-1-460x254.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image2-1-768x424.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image2-1-750x414.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image2-1.png 1079w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/>
<p><em>Featured Image from iStock and charts from TradingView.com and Coingecko.com</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/iStock-1291935777-460x263.jpg" width="460" height="263" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>SUI Price Plummets By 38% In 7 Days &#8211; Will It Recover Anytime Soon?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/altcoin/sui-price-plummets-by-38/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Olowoporoku Adeniyi]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 13:27:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SUI]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SUI price analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sui token]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=537328</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The price of SUI has experienced a significant decline in the past week, dropping by 38.13%. In the last 24 hours alone, the price has fallen by 21.51%. However, there is a glimmer of hope as the price slightly increased by 1.53% in the past hour. Currently priced at $0.58 per SUI, the token is 61.12% below its all-time high of $1.50. The question now remains whether SUI can regain its footing and initiate a recovery. SUI Coin Faces Bearish Pressure  The global crypto market cap has dropped below $1.10 trillion again, leading to a negative trading sentiment across most cryptocurrencies. SUI coin, in particular, has experienced a significant decline of over 10% in the past 24 hours, with its price falling below $0.70. The asset&#8217;s technical analysis suggests a bearish trend, characterized by high selling pressure and struggles for buyers to reverse the downward momentum. Related Reading: Cardano (ADA) Faces Obstacles In Reaching Key Level In June – Here’s Why On the 4-hour timeframe chart, the SUI coin has been in a downtrend, seeking stable support. It trades below its short-term and long-term moving averages, with the 50-day MA at approximately $0.837 and the 200-day MA at $1.020. This positioning below the moving averages signifies a consistent decline in the coin&#8217;s price, potentially indicating a lack of buying pressure and weakened market sentiment. The immediate support level for the SUI coin is at $0.50, while the resistance level stands at around $0.76. Recent rejection below the resistance level has fueled the downtrend. Furthermore, the Relative Strength Index (RSI) on the 4-hour timeframe chart confirms the bearish sentiment, with an RSI of 17.9 indicating oversold conditions. Sellers currently outnumber buyers, further adding to the downward pressure on the SUI coin. Partnership With Red Bull Racing: Can This Be A Catalyst For SUI Token’s Revival The recent multiyear partnership between Sui and Formula One&#8217;s Oracle Red Bull Racing team has the potential to rejuvenate the Sui token price. As Sui becomes the blockchain partner of a renowned and globally recognized racing team, it gains exposure and credibility within the crypto and motorsport communities. This association can drive increased demand for Sui tokens, heightening the token&#8217;s value. The collaboration aims to deliver engaging digital experiences for racing fans, creating a loyal user base and bolstering Sui&#8217;s reputation. With Red Bull Racing&#8217;s previous involvement in the crypto industry, its partnership with Sui signifies a shared interest in exploring the potential of cryptocurrencies and blockchain technology. Related Reading: Bleak Dogecoin (DOGE) Social Sentiment Raises Questions About Price Reversal While the partnership&#8217;s success and its impact on the Sui token price depend on several factors, including market conditions and investor sentiment, this collaboration holds promising prospects for the revival of the Sui token. Monitoring future developments and market reactions will provide valuable insights into the effectiveness of the partnership in driving the Sui token&#8217;s resurgence. At press time, SUI was trading at $0.5904 with a 24-hour drop of 19.8% in its price.  Featured image from iStock, charts from Tradingview.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The price of SUI has experienced a significant decline in the past week, dropping by 38.13%. In the last 24 hours alone, the price has fallen by 21.51%. However, there is a glimmer of hope as the price slightly increased by 1.53% in the past hour. Currently priced at $0.58 per SUI, the token is 61.12% below its all-time high of $1.50. The question now remains whether SUI can regain its footing and initiate a recovery.</p>
<h2>SUI Coin Faces Bearish Pressure </h2>
<p>The global crypto market cap has dropped below $1.10 trillion again, leading to a negative trading sentiment across most cryptocurrencies. SUI coin, in particular, has experienced a significant decline of over 10% in the past 24 hours, with its price falling below $0.70. The asset&#8217;s technical analysis suggests a bearish trend, characterized by high selling pressure and struggles for buyers to reverse the downward momentum.</p>
<p><strong>Related Reading:</strong> <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/cardano-ada-obstacles-in-hitting-0-3/?swcfpc=1">Cardano (ADA) Faces Obstacles In Reaching Key Level In June – Here’s Why</a></p>
<p>On the 4-hour timeframe chart, the SUI coin has been in a downtrend, seeking stable support. It trades below its short-term and long-term moving averages, with the 50-day MA at approximately $0.837 and the 200-day MA at $1.020. This positioning below the moving averages signifies a consistent decline in the coin&#8217;s price, potentially indicating a lack of buying pressure and weakened market sentiment.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium wp-image-537330" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image1-2-460x240.png" alt="Sui Price is currently heading in a downward trajectory: source @TradingView" width="460" height="240" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image1-2-460x240.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image1-2-860x450.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image1-2-768x401.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image1-2-750x392.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image1-2.png 966w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px"/>
<p>The immediate support level for the SUI coin is at $0.50, while the resistance level stands at around $0.76. Recent rejection below the resistance level has fueled the downtrend. Furthermore, the Relative Strength Index (RSI) on the 4-hour timeframe chart confirms the bearish sentiment, with an RSI of 17.9 indicating oversold conditions. Sellers currently outnumber buyers, further adding to the downward pressure on the SUI coin.</p>
<h2>Partnership With Red Bull Racing: Can This Be A Catalyst For SUI Token’s Revival</h2>
<p>The recent multiyear partnership between Sui and Formula One&#8217;s Oracle Red Bull Racing team has the potential to rejuvenate the Sui token price. As Sui becomes the blockchain partner of a renowned and globally recognized racing team, it gains exposure and credibility within the crypto and motorsport communities. This association can drive increased demand for Sui tokens, heightening the token&#8217;s value.</p>
<p>The collaboration aims to deliver engaging digital experiences for racing fans, creating a loyal user base and bolstering Sui&#8217;s reputation. With Red Bull Racing&#8217;s previous involvement in the crypto industry, its partnership with Sui signifies a shared interest in exploring the potential of cryptocurrencies and blockchain technology.</p>
<p><strong>Related Reading</strong>: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/dogecoin-experiences-bleak-social-sentiment/?swcfpc=1">Bleak Dogecoin (DOGE) Social Sentiment Raises Questions About Price Reversal</a></p>
<p>While the partnership&#8217;s success and its impact on the Sui token price depend on several factors, including market conditions and investor sentiment, this collaboration holds promising prospects for the revival of the Sui token. Monitoring future developments and market reactions will provide valuable insights into the effectiveness of the partnership in driving the Sui token&#8217;s resurgence. At press time, SUI was trading at $0.5904 with a 24-hour drop of 19.8% in its price. </p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-537331 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image2-860x474.png" alt="Sui is currently down by 20% in the past 24 hours: source@Tradingview.com" width="860" height="474" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image2-860x474.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image2-460x254.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image2-768x424.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image2-750x414.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image2.png 1079w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/>
<p><em>Featured image from iStock, charts from Tradingview.com</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/iStock-1385861326-1-460x248.jpg" width="460" height="248" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Optimism Bedrock Upgrade: Transaction Fee Savings Hit $150,000 And Counting</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/optimism-bedrock-upgrade-transaction-fee-savings-hit-150000-and-counting/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 11:26:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bedrock upgrade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[L2]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[optimism]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=537343</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Optimism Bedrock marks a significant milestone in the network&#8217;s evolution. This groundbreaking upgrade, successfully launched on June 7, ushers in a plethora of major advancements, most notably an impressive reduction in network costs. By implementing a so-called optimized batch compression and leveraging Ethereum as a data availability layer, the Bedrock upgrade has achieved a remarkable 56.1% decrease in transaction fees. These findings, meticulously compiled by OP Labs, Optimism&#8217;s core developer, highlight the tangible benefits that users have already begun to experience. Related Reading: Cardano (ADA) Faces Obstacles In Reaching Key Level In June – Here’s Why In just a matter of days, the Bedrock upgrade has resulted in nearly $150,000 in savings for users, showcasing the immediate impact and financial advantages brought forth by this transformative enhancement. Optimism&#8217;s expected total user savings since migration, or during the first month in US dollars, is around $210,929. Bedrock upgrade has drop in transaction fees. Source: Dune.com This development has brought about a significant cost advantage for Optimism, facilitating the swift confirmation of transaction batches on the Ethereum network. As a result, the average transaction fees on Optimism have experienced a substantial decrease, plummeting from $0.57 to a mere $0.16. Bedrock Upgrade: Paving The Way For Superchain Revolution While the reduction in transaction fees is undoubtedly a remarkable improvement, the Bedrock upgrade holds greater significance as a crucial component of the developer&#8217;s ambitious vision—the creation of a groundbreaking &#8220;Superchain.&#8221; This visionary concept revolves around establishing an interconnected network of chains, leveraging Optimism&#8217;s OP Stack software. To commemorate the Bedrock upgrade, we’re releasing an open-edition NFT with our friends at @manifoldxyz. Minting will close on Friday, June 16th at 11:59 PM UTC, so you have just over a week to collect this piece of Optimistic history! https://t.co/Wszqu3PA5h pic.twitter.com/jsOgGLl88L — Optimism (✨🔴_🔴✨) (@optimismFND) June 8, 2023 The Superchain aims to integrate these individual chains into a cohesive ecosystem, enabling seamless communication and fostering collaboration within a unified environment. By harnessing the power of the Bedrock upgrade, Optimism takes a significant stride towards realizing this revolutionary vision, setting the stage for a new era of interconnected blockchain innovation. Crypto total market cap at $1.01 trillion on the daily chart at TradingView.com Optimism Makes Strides In Market Share And TVL Optimism&#8217;s impressive performance in the market has recently come to light, with L2 Beats unveiling its significant standing. At present, Optimism holds the second-largest market share, commanding approximately 18% of the market, showcasing its growing influence and acceptance. Moreover, Optimism has achieved a substantial Total Value Locked (TVL) figure, surpassing $1.6 billion. This noteworthy metric signifies the platform&#8217;s robust engagement and high level of activity, underlining the trust and confidence users have placed in Optimism. &#160; Source: L2Beat Related Reading: Bearish BNB Signs Hint Downtrend May Persist Beyond Expectations Meanwhile, on-chain data on Optimism has revealed a decline in the 30-day active addresses metric. As of the current reporting period, the number of active addresses within this timeframe hovers around 147,000, indicating a noticeable decrease. These figures offer valuable insights into the level of interaction and user participation on the platform at the time of reporting. It will be interesting to see how the introduction of the Bedrock upgrade might influence these metrics, potentially shaping the future trajectory of user engagement on Optimism. Featured image from TokenInsight]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Optimism Bedrock marks a significant milestone in the network&#8217;s evolution. This groundbreaking upgrade, successfully launched on June 7, ushers in a plethora of major advancements, most notably an impressive reduction in network costs.</p>
<p>By implementing a so-called optimized batch compression and leveraging Ethereum as a data availability layer, the Bedrock upgrade has achieved a remarkable <a href="https://dune.com/oplabspbc/optimism-bedrock-migration-impact-dashboard" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">56.1% decrease in transaction fees</a>. </p>
<p>These findings, meticulously compiled by OP Labs, Optimism&#8217;s core developer, highlight the tangible benefits that users have already begun to experience.</p>

<p>In just a matter of days, the Bedrock upgrade has resulted in nearly <a href="https://www.theblock.co/post/233949/optimisms-bedrock-upgrade-has-already-saved-150000-in-transaction-fees" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">$150,000 in savings</a> for users, showcasing the immediate impact and financial advantages brought forth by this transformative enhancement.</p>
<p>Optimism&#8217;s expected total user savings since migration, or during the first month in US dollars, is around $210,929.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-537347" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-43.png" alt="" width="1881" height="295" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-43.png 1881w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-43-460x72.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-43-860x135.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-43-768x120.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-43-1536x241.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-43-750x118.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-43-1140x179.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1881px) 100vw, 1881px"/></p>

<p>This development has brought about a significant cost advantage for Optimism, facilitating the swift confirmation of transaction batches on the Ethereum network. As a result, the average transaction fees on Optimism have experienced a substantial decrease, plummeting from $0.57 to a mere $0.16.</p>
<h2><strong>Bedrock Upgrade: Paving The Way For Superchain Revolution</strong></h2>
<p>While the reduction in transaction fees is undoubtedly a remarkable improvement, the <a href="https://twitter.com/optimismFND/status/1666850603929042944" rel="nofollow">Bedrock upgrade</a> holds greater significance as a crucial component of the developer&#8217;s ambitious vision—the creation of a groundbreaking &#8220;Superchain.&#8221; This visionary concept revolves around establishing an interconnected network of chains, leveraging Optimism&#8217;s OP Stack software.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">To commemorate the Bedrock upgrade, we’re releasing an open-edition NFT with our friends at <a href="https://twitter.com/manifoldxyz?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">@manifoldxyz</a>.</p>
<p>Minting will close on Friday, June 16th at 11:59 PM UTC, so you have just over a week to collect this piece of Optimistic history! <a href="https://t.co/Wszqu3PA5h" rel="nofollow">https://t.co/Wszqu3PA5h</a> <a href="https://t.co/jsOgGLl88L" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/jsOgGLl88L</a></p>
<p>— Optimism (<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2728.png" alt="✨" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f534.png" alt="🔴" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />_<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f534.png" alt="🔴" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2728.png" alt="✨" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />) (@optimismFND) <a href="https://twitter.com/optimismFND/status/1666850603929042944?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">June 8, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p>The Superchain aims to integrate these individual chains into a cohesive ecosystem, enabling seamless communication and fostering collaboration within a unified environment. By harnessing the power of the Bedrock upgrade, Optimism takes a significant stride towards realizing this revolutionary vision, setting the stage for a new era of interconnected blockchain innovation.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/lcYDieGS/" width="2047" height="979"/></p>

<h2><strong>Optimism Makes Strides In Market Share And TVL</strong></h2>
<p>Optimism&#8217;s impressive performance in the market has recently come to light, with L2 Beats unveiling its significant standing. At present, Optimism holds the second-largest market share, commanding approximately 18% of the market, showcasing its growing influence and acceptance.</p>
<p>Moreover, Optimism has achieved a <a href="https://l2beat.com/scaling/tvl" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">substantial Total Value Locked</a> (TVL) figure, surpassing $1.6 billion. This noteworthy metric signifies the platform&#8217;s robust engagement and high level of activity, underlining the trust and confidence users have placed in Optimism.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-537349 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-45-860x495.png" alt="" width="860" height="495" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-45-860x495.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-45-460x265.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-45-768x442.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-45-750x432.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-45-1140x656.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-45.png 1206w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/></p>


<p>Meanwhile, on-chain data on Optimism has revealed a decline in the 30-day active addresses metric. As of the current reporting period, the number of active addresses within this timeframe hovers around 147,000, indicating a noticeable decrease.</p>
<p>These figures offer valuable insights into the level of interaction and user participation on the platform at the time of reporting. It will be interesting to see how the introduction of the Bedrock upgrade might influence these metrics, potentially shaping the future trajectory of user engagement on Optimism.</p>
<p><em>Featured image from TokenInsight</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-46-460x261.png" width="460" height="261" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bleak Dogecoin (DOGE) Social Sentiment Raises Questions About Price Reversal</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/dogecoin-experiences-bleak-social-sentiment/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 09:14:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Doge price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[meme coins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price action]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=537321</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Dogecoin (DOGE) has recently found itself at the center of a storm caused by the US Securities and Exchange Commission&#8217;s (SEC) lawsuit against major exchanges Binance and Coinbase. As media outlets spread fear, uncertainty, and doubt regarding the legal proceedings, the market capitalization of this meme coin has experienced a significant drop. However, despite the turbulence, on-chain data reveals that the long-term loyalists of the Dogecoin community remain resolute in their support. In the face of the dwindling media mentions and the calming of the storm, a compelling question arises: could this be the opportune moment for bullish investors to seize the dip and spur yet another impressive price rebound for DOGE? Related Reading: Cardano (ADA) Faces Obstacles In Reaching Key Level In June – Here’s Why Dogecoin (DOGE) Holders Show Resilience Amidst Market Turbulence According to detailed on-chain analysis, it appears that the recent sell-offs and price drops in DOGE were primarily driven by short-term traders rather than committed long-term holders. A comprehensive Santiment chart illustrates this phenomenon, showcasing a notable increase in Mean Coin Age within the Dogecoin ecosystem during the same period when massive sell-offs occurred. DOGE Mean Coin Age. Source: Santiment Examining the data between June 1 and June 9, the Mean Coin Age for DOGE has experienced a 5% increase, rising from 54,317 to 57,219. This upward trend in Mean Coin Age during a period of price retracement serves as a promising signal, indicating growing confidence among long-term DOGE holders. Remarkably, approximately 70% of the total circulating Dogecoin supply is currently held by steadfast long-term investors who have held their positions for more than a year. With such a significant portion of DOGE in the hands of committed holders, it follows logically that if they continue to hold onto their coins, the price of DOGE is likely to rebound in the near future. DOGE Social Volume Down: Potential Opportunity For Bullish Investors? Over a span of just four days, from June 5 to June 9, the Social Volume of DOGE has witnessed a staggering decline of 72%, plummeting from 8,219 mentions to 2,308. Santiment&#8217;s Social Volume metric serves as a reliable indicator of market sentiment by tracking the frequency of a project&#8217;s mentions across various channels, including Twitter and relevant crypto-media platforms. DOGE Social Volume. Source: Santiment When Social Volume experiences a substantial decrease like the one observed above, it signifies that many stakeholders are currently overlooking the asset. This situation presents an opportunity for strategic investors seeking to capitalize on market bottoms. It is common for bullish investors to strategically enter the market when sentiment hits a new low, aiming to purchase assets at their lowest possible value. $doge is like 🚀🚀🚀🚀🚀 today , a little promising and defying the gravity pic.twitter.com/zHNj0BvHcU — THOMAS (@thomasnegeri) June 9, 2023 Interpreting this drop in Social Volume as a potential turning point for the DOGE price dip, optimistic investors may consider this as an encouraging signal. If this bullish outlook materializes, the crypto community believes that DOGE will regain its upward momentum and ascend the charts once again in the days to come. Source: Coingecko As of now, CoinGecko reports the current price of DOGE at $0.060480, down 11.3% in the past 24 hours. The cryptocurrency has likewise experienced a decline of 16.7% over the course of the last seven days. Featured image from Getty Images]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Dogecoin (DOGE) has recently found itself at the center of a storm caused by the US Securities and Exchange Commission&#8217;s (SEC) lawsuit against major exchanges Binance and Coinbase. As media outlets spread fear, uncertainty, and doubt regarding the legal proceedings, the market capitalization of this meme coin has experienced a significant drop.</p>
<p>However, despite the turbulence, on-chain data reveals that the long-term loyalists of the Dogecoin community remain resolute in their support.</p>
<p>In the face of the dwindling media mentions and the calming of the storm, a compelling question arises: could this be the opportune moment for bullish investors to seize the dip and spur yet another impressive price rebound for DOGE?</p>

<h2><strong>Dogecoin (DOGE) Holders Show Resilience Amidst Market Turbulence</strong></h2>
<p>According to detailed on-chain analysis, it appears that the recent sell-offs and price drops in DOGE were primarily driven by short-term traders rather than committed long-term holders. A comprehensive Santiment chart illustrates this phenomenon, showcasing a notable increase in Mean Coin Age within the Dogecoin ecosystem during the same period when massive sell-offs occurred.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-537324 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-38-860x387.png" alt="" width="860" height="387" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-38-860x387.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-38-460x207.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-38-768x345.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-38-1536x691.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-38-750x337.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-38-1140x513.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-38.png 1888w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/></p>

<p>Examining the data between June 1 and June 9, the <a href="https://embed.santiment.net/chart?ps=dogecoin&amp;pt=DOGE&amp;df=2023-05-30T23%3A00%3A00.000Z&amp;dt=2023-06-08T23%3A00%3A00.000Z&amp;emcg=1&amp;wm=price_usd%3Bmean_age_90d&amp;wax=0%3B1&amp;wc=%2326C953%3B%23FF5B5B&amp;ws=%7B%22interval%22%3A%221d%22%7D%3B" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Mean Coin Age for DOGE</a> has experienced a 5% increase, rising from 54,317 to 57,219. This upward trend in Mean Coin Age during a period of price retracement serves as a promising signal, indicating growing confidence among long-term DOGE holders.</p>
<p>Remarkably, approximately 70% of the total circulating Dogecoin supply is currently held by steadfast long-term investors who have held their positions for more than a year. With such a significant portion of DOGE in the hands of committed holders, it follows logically that if they continue to hold onto their coins, the price of DOGE is likely to rebound in the near future.</p>
<h2><strong>DOGE Social Volume Down: Potential Opportunity For Bullish Investors?</strong></h2>
<p>Over a span of just four days, from June 5 to June 9, the <a href="https://embed.santiment.net/chart?ps=dogecoin&amp;pt=DOGE&amp;df=2023-05-30T23%3A00%3A00.000Z&amp;dt=2023-06-08T23%3A00%3A00.000Z&amp;emcg=1&amp;wm=price_usd%3Bsocial_volume_total&amp;wax=0%3B1&amp;wc=%2326C953%3B%2368DBF4&amp;ws=%7B%22interval%22%3A%221d%22%7D%3B%7B%22interval%22%3A%221d%22%7D" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Social Volume of DOGE</a> has witnessed a staggering decline of 72%, plummeting from 8,219 mentions to 2,308. </p>
<p>Santiment&#8217;s Social Volume metric serves as a reliable indicator of market sentiment by tracking the frequency of a project&#8217;s mentions across various channels, including Twitter and relevant crypto-media platforms.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-537329" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-40.png" alt="" width="964" height="493" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-40.png 964w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-40-460x235.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-40-860x440.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-40-768x393.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-40-750x384.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 964px) 100vw, 964px"/></p>

<p>When Social Volume experiences a substantial decrease like the one observed above, it signifies that many stakeholders are currently overlooking the asset. </p>
<p>This situation presents an opportunity for strategic investors seeking to capitalize on market bottoms. It is common for bullish investors to strategically enter the market when sentiment hits a new low, aiming to purchase assets at their lowest possible value.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en"><a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24doge&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$doge</a> is like <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f680.png" alt="🚀" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f680.png" alt="🚀" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f680.png" alt="🚀" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f680.png" alt="🚀" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f680.png" alt="🚀" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> today , a little promising and defying the gravity <a href="https://t.co/zHNj0BvHcU" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/zHNj0BvHcU</a></p>
<p>— THOMAS (@thomasnegeri) <a href="https://twitter.com/thomasnegeri/status/1667160209343811584?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">June 9, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p>Interpreting this drop in Social Volume as a potential turning point for the DOGE price dip, optimistic investors may consider this as an encouraging signal. If this bullish outlook materializes, the crypto community believes that <a href="https://twitter.com/thomasnegeri/status/1667160209343811584" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">DOGE will regain its upward momentum</a> and ascend the charts once again in the days to come.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-537322" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-37.png" alt="" width="1132" height="61" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-37.png 1132w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-37-460x25.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-37-860x46.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-37-768x41.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-37-750x40.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 1132px) 100vw, 1132px"/></p>

<p>As of now, <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/dogecoin" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">CoinGecko</a> reports the current price of DOGE at $0.060480, down 11.3% in the past 24 hours. The cryptocurrency has likewise experienced a decline of 16.7% over the course of the last seven days.</p>
<p><em>Featured image from Getty Images</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-39-460x304.png" width="460" height="304" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cardano (ADA) Faces Obstacles In Reaching Key Level In June &#8211; Here&#8217;s Why</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/cardano-ada-obstacles-in-hitting-0-3/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 05:31:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADA price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price action]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=537314</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Cardano (ADA), along with numerous other major altcoins, experienced a significant downturn in recent days, causing considerable losses for investors. However, the downward trajectory of prices observed across the cryptocurrency market did not provide a reassuring signal for a potential reversal in the near future. As panic and uncertainty gripped the crypto space, holders of Cardano and other altcoins found themselves questioning the stability and future prospects of these digital assets.  What factors contributed to this market-wide decline, and what lies ahead for Cardano amidst this turbulent period? Related Reading: Bearish BNB Signs Hint Downtrend May Persist Beyond Expectations Bearish Trend Emerges As Cardano (ADA) Price Plummets A recent report shed light on the alarming bearish scenario for Cardano (ADA) on its price charts.  Currently valued at $0.248073 according to CoinGecko, ADA has suffered a significant decline of 22.2% within the past 24 hours, further exacerbating the downward trend. Over the span of the last seven days, the cryptocurrency has experienced a staggering downturn, plummeting by 34.2%. Source: Coingecko A recent report emphasized the bearish landscape depicted by Cardano (ADA) on its charts, specifically noting its current price, and the breach below the $0.348 mark. This development set the stage for bears to take control of the market across higher timeframes. The report highlighted the significance of this downward movement, as it not only signaled a shift in momentum but also posed challenges for Cardano&#8217;s price recovery. Related Reading: ApeCoin Holders Suffer Financial Pain As 95% Endure Negative Returns With the breach of the crucial support level, bears gained the upper hand in dictating market dynamics, particularly on longer timeframes. This bearish sentiment cast a shadow over Cardano&#8217;s performance, making it increasingly difficult for the ADA token to regain lost ground and establish upward momentum. The report&#8217;s analysis underscored the implications of bears dominating the market, emphasizing the obstacles Cardano might face in its price trajectory. In an attempt to alter the prevailing trend, the bulls made a late May push and managed to establish a high at $0.386. However, their efforts to sustain this shift in market sentiment were futile as they failed to capitalize on this change in character. The failure to maintain the bullish momentum has left Cardano investors and market participants on edge, grappling with concerns about the cryptocurrency&#8217;s future trajectory. Cardano (ADA) market cap currently at $8.5 billion. Chart: TradingView.com SEC&#8217;s Security Label And Lawsuits Intensify Market Jitters Adding to the already gloomy market sentiment, the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) dealt a significant blow to Cardano by classifying ADA as a security. This categorization triggered a wave of apprehension among investors, leading many to flee from the cryptocurrency markets.  Cardano&#8217;s IOG Dismisses SEC&#8217;s Claim that ADA is a Security #Cardano #cardanofeed #ADA #crypto #cardanocommunity #bitcoin #CoinMarketCap #blockchain #cryptocurrency #CardanoADA #btc $ADAhttps://t.co/rOjRcaWXJN — Cardano Feed ($ADA) (@CardanoFeed) June 9, 2023 Compounding the unease, the SEC filed lawsuits against Coinbase and Binance, further exacerbating the panic surrounding the already bleak market outlook in the crypto sphere. (This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk) Featured image from iStock]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Cardano (ADA), along with numerous other major altcoins, experienced a significant downturn in recent days, causing considerable losses for investors. However, the downward trajectory of prices observed across the cryptocurrency market did not provide a reassuring signal for a potential reversal in the near future.</p>
<p>As panic and uncertainty gripped the crypto space, holders of Cardano and other altcoins found themselves questioning the stability and future prospects of these digital assets. </p>
<p>What factors contributed to this market-wide decline, and what lies ahead for Cardano amidst this turbulent period?</p>

<h2><strong>Bearish Trend Emerges As Cardano (ADA) Price Plummets</strong></h2>
<p>A recent report shed light on the alarming <a href="https://ambcrypto.com/why-cardano-will-remain-below-0-3-in-june/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">bearish scenario for Cardano</a> (ADA) on its price charts. </p>
<p>Currently valued at $0.248073 according to <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/cardano" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">CoinGecko</a>, ADA has suffered a significant decline of 22.2% within the past 24 hours, further exacerbating the downward trend. Over the span of the last seven days, the cryptocurrency has experienced a staggering downturn, plummeting by 34.2%.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-537316" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-35.png" alt="" width="1133" height="64" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-35.png 1133w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-35-460x26.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-35-860x49.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-35-768x43.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-35-750x42.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 1133px) 100vw, 1133px"/></p>

<p>A recent report emphasized the <a href="https://ambcrypto.com/why-cardano-will-remain-below-0-3-in-june/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">bearish landscape</a> depicted by Cardano (ADA) on its charts, specifically noting its current price, and the breach below the $0.348 mark.</p>
<p>This development set the stage for bears to take control of the market across higher timeframes. The report highlighted the significance of this downward movement, as it not only signaled a shift in momentum but also posed challenges for Cardano&#8217;s price recovery.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/apecoin-holders-suffer-financial-pain-as-95-endure-negative-returns/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">ApeCoin Holders Suffer Financial Pain As 95% Endure Negative Returns</a></p>
<p>With the breach of the crucial support level, bears gained the upper hand in dictating market dynamics, particularly on longer timeframes. This bearish sentiment cast a shadow over Cardano&#8217;s performance, making it increasingly difficult for the ADA token to regain lost ground and establish upward momentum.</p>
<p>The report&#8217;s analysis underscored the implications of bears dominating the market, emphasizing the obstacles Cardano might face in its price trajectory.</p>
<p>In an attempt to alter the prevailing trend, the bulls made a late May push and managed to establish a high at $0.386. However, their efforts to sustain this shift in market sentiment were futile as they failed to capitalize on this change in character.</p>
<p>The failure to maintain the bullish momentum has left Cardano investors and market participants on edge, grappling with concerns about the cryptocurrency&#8217;s future trajectory.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/S05foalu/" width="2047" height="979"/></p>

<h2><strong>SEC&#8217;s Security Label And Lawsuits Intensify Market Jitters</strong></h2>
<p>Adding to the already gloomy market sentiment, the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) dealt a significant blow to Cardano by <a href="https://twitter.com/CardanoFeed/status/1667158008311209987" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">classifying ADA as a security</a>. This categorization triggered a wave of apprehension among investors, leading many to flee from the cryptocurrency markets. </p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Cardano&#8217;s IOG Dismisses SEC&#8217;s Claim that ADA is a Security <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Cardano?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#Cardano</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/cardanofeed?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#cardanofeed</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/ADA?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#ADA</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/crypto?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#crypto</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/cardanocommunity?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#cardanocommunity</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/bitcoin?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#bitcoin</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/CoinMarketCap?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#CoinMarketCap</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/blockchain?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#blockchain</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/cryptocurrency?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#cryptocurrency</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/CardanoADA?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#CardanoADA</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/btc?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#btc</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24ADA&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$ADA</a><a href="https://t.co/rOjRcaWXJN" rel="nofollow">https://t.co/rOjRcaWXJN</a></p>
<p>— Cardano Feed ($ADA) (@CardanoFeed) <a href="https://twitter.com/CardanoFeed/status/1667158008311209987?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">June 9, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p>Compounding the unease, the SEC filed <a href="https://www.vox.com/23752826/binance-coinbase-sec-crypto-investors" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">lawsuits against Coinbase and Binance</a>, further exacerbating the panic surrounding the already bleak market outlook in the crypto sphere.</p>
<p><em>(This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk)</em></p>
<p><em>Featured image from iStock</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-36-460x295.png" width="460" height="295" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin (BTC) Lower Timeframe Outlook: $26,800 Breakthrough Could Spark Rally</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-btc-lower-timeframe-outlook-26800-breakthrough-could-spark-rally/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 00:00:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=537308</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC), the largest cryptocurrency in the market, made a fake attempt to breach the $27,500 barrier on Tuesday. Since then, it has been trading sideways, moving within a narrow channel.  The 50-day Moving Average, which is the nearest resistance, is at $27,200. Meanwhile, the strongest support is at the 200-day MA, placed at $25,200.  For Bitcoin to initiate a fully formed bull run in the market, it is essential to hold this support level, if BTC bulls expect another attempt to breach the $30,000 mark and propel the market in full force, the $25,200 support level is crucial, and it needs to be held to achieve this goal. Related Reading: Here’s How Current Bitcoin Capitulation Compares With Past Crashes XRP And LTC Poised For Breakouts As Bitcoin Eyes $28,000 The lower timeframe picture for Bitcoin is straightforward, according to cryptocurrency analyst Michael Van de Poppe. He believes that for BTC to continue its upward trend, it needs to break through the $26,800 level. If that level is breached and flipped, Van de Poppe predicts that $27,500 is a likely next target, with the possibility of further breakouts on XRP and Litecoin (LTC). Van de Poppe&#8217;s analysis is based on technical indicators and market trends. He highlights the significance of the $26,800 level as a key resistance level that must be overcome for BTC to gain momentum. The cryptocurrency has been trading in a narrow range, and a breakout could signal a shift in market sentiment. Van de Poppe&#8217;s predictions align with the overall bullish sentiment in the cryptocurrency market, with many analysts expecting BTC to continue its upward trajectory. However, there are also concerns about potential price corrections and volatility, which could impact short-term market movements. BTC In Period of Stability, Revisiting 200-Week MA Despite Downside Volatility According to cryptocurrency analyst Rekt Capital, BTC is currently in a period of stability. If this stability continues, BTC could revisit the $27,600 level and potentially break out. However, BTC is still retesting the 200-week Moving Average despite downside volatility below it during the week. Furthermore, BTC is currently trading below a series of Lower Highs, which is represented by the blue line in the chart. To move higher, BTC needs to invalidate this series of Lower Highs. On the other hand, the 200-week MA is acting as support, as indicated by the orange line in the chart. Together, these factors are creating a pennant-like structure, which is a pattern that typically indicates price compression and is often followed by a period of volatility. Rekt Capital&#8217;s analysis suggests that BTC is at a critical juncture, with the potential for a breakout or a breakdown depending on how it interacts with the 200-week MA and the series of Lower Highs. Related Reading: LUNC Token Continues To Surge During Market Uncertainty, What’s Behind It? Despite the potential risks, many investors remain bullish on BTC and other cryptocurrencies, with the overall market continuing to show strength and resilience. As institutional adoption of cryptocurrencies continues to grow, the demand for BTC and other digital assets is expected to increase, potentially driving prices higher in the long term. Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin (BTC), the largest cryptocurrency in the market, made a fake attempt to breach the $27,500 barrier on Tuesday. Since then, it has been trading sideways, moving within a narrow channel. </p>
<p>The 50-day Moving Average, which is the nearest resistance, is at $27,200. Meanwhile, the strongest support is at the 200-day MA, placed at $25,200. </p>
<p>For Bitcoin to initiate a fully formed bull run in the market, it is essential to hold this support level, if BTC bulls expect another attempt to breach the $30,000 mark and propel the market in full force, the $25,200 support level is crucial, and it needs to be held to achieve this goal.</p>

<h2>XRP And LTC Poised For Breakouts As Bitcoin Eyes $28,000</h2>
<p>The lower timeframe picture for Bitcoin is straightforward, <a href="https://twitter.com/CryptoMichNL/status/1667175968845250563?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">according </a>to cryptocurrency analyst Michael Van de Poppe. He believes that for BTC to continue its upward trend, it needs to break through the $26,800 level. If that level is breached and flipped, Van de Poppe predicts that $27,500 is a likely next target, with the possibility of further breakouts on XRP and Litecoin (LTC).</p>
<p>Van de Poppe&#8217;s analysis is based on technical indicators and market trends. He highlights the significance of the $26,800 level as a key resistance level that must be overcome for BTC to gain momentum. The cryptocurrency has been trading in a narrow range, and a breakout could signal a shift in market sentiment.</p>
<p>Van de Poppe&#8217;s predictions align with the overall bullish sentiment in the cryptocurrency market, with many analysts expecting BTC to continue its upward trajectory. However, there are also concerns about potential price corrections and volatility, which could impact short-term market movements.</p>
BTC In Period of Stability, Revisiting 200-Week MA Despite Downside Volatility
<p><a href="https://twitter.com/rektcapital/status/1666819605220986881?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">According </a>to cryptocurrency analyst Rekt Capital, BTC is currently in a period of stability. If this stability continues, BTC could revisit the $27,600 level and potentially break out. However, BTC is still retesting the 200-week Moving Average despite downside volatility below it during the week.</p>
<p>Furthermore, BTC is currently trading below a series of Lower Highs, which is represented by the blue line in the chart. To move higher, BTC needs to invalidate this series of Lower Highs.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large wp-image-537312" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/FyG7USMaQAgN3sF-860x628.jpg" alt="Bitcoin " width="860" height="628" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/FyG7USMaQAgN3sF-860x628.jpg 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/FyG7USMaQAgN3sF-460x336.jpg 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/FyG7USMaQAgN3sF-768x561.jpg 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/FyG7USMaQAgN3sF-1536x1123.jpg 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/FyG7USMaQAgN3sF-750x548.jpg 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/FyG7USMaQAgN3sF-1140x833.jpg 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/FyG7USMaQAgN3sF.jpg 1850w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/>
<p>On the other hand, the 200-week MA is acting as support, as indicated by the orange line in the chart. Together, these factors are creating a pennant-like structure, which is a pattern that typically indicates price compression and is often followed by a period of volatility.</p>
<p>Rekt Capital&#8217;s analysis suggests that BTC is at a critical juncture, with the potential for a breakout or a breakdown depending on how it interacts with the 200-week MA and the series of Lower Highs.</p>

<p>Despite the potential risks, many investors remain bullish on BTC and other cryptocurrencies, with the overall market continuing to show strength and resilience. As institutional adoption of cryptocurrencies continues to grow, the demand for BTC and other digital assets is expected to increase, potentially driving prices higher in the long term.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/iUUeXhz8/" alt="Bitcoin " width="1813" height="858"/>
<p>Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/iStock-531282429-1-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
