<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"

	xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
	xmlns:geo="http://www.w3.org/2003/01/geo/wgs84_pos#"
	>

<channel>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.newsbtc.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<description>Bitcoin &#38; Cryptocurrency News Today</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 19:50:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-cropped-favicon.png?fit=32%2C32</url>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
<site xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">221170450</site>	<item>
		<title>BlackRock CEO Larry Fink Is The Best Thing To Happen To Bitcoin, Mike Novogratz Says</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/blackrock-larry-fink-best-thing-to-happen-to-bitcoin/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 02:30:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BlackRock]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blackrock CEO]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Galaxy Digital]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Larry Fink]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mike Novogratz]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=545319</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[BlackRock officially announced its entrance into Bitcoin earlier this year by filing for a Spot Bitcoin ETF with the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). Although the regulator is yet to accept the filing, CEO Larry Fink has also made some supportive comments, comparing BTC to digital gold.  In light of these events, Galaxy Digital CEO Mike Novogratz has come forward to share his opinions on BlackRock CEO Larry Fink and how he affects the digital asset. BlackRock CEO&#8217;s Pivoting Sentiment Toward Bitcoin Galaxy Digital CEO Mike Novogratz has stated that BlackRock’s CEO Larry Fink&#8217;s change of heart is the best thing to happen to Bitcoin.  &#8220;I think the most important thing that happened this year in Bitcoin is Larry Fink,&#8221; Novogratz mentioned during an interview on Bloomberg TV with David Rubenstein. Related Reading: USDT Issuer Tether Reports A 30% Decline In Profit Novogratz believes Fink’s acceptance of Bitcoin highlights a shifting sentiment towards Bitcoin and other digital currencies worldwide.  According to him, &#8220;180 million people around the world, without a gun to their head, take their hard-earned savings and store it in this community of people that run this technology, you know, called bitcoin.&#8221; He further opined that Fink’s change of heart, alongside the increasing adoption of cryptocurrencies, could help Bitcoin surpass its all-time high of $69,000 recorded in 2021.  Blackrock’s CEO Larry Fink was long known to be a skeptic of cryptocurrencies as he once went as far as tagging BTC an “index of money laundering.”  “Bitcoin just shows you how much demand for money laundering there is in the world,” Fink stated in 2017. BTC price continues to fall as it trades at $28,789 &#124; Source: BTCUSD on Tradingview.com However, there has been a change of heart from the CEO as earlier in June, BlackRock filed an application to the SEC to establish a Bitcoin spot ETF, a move that saw some other institutions file a similar application.  In fact, in a show of support for cryptocurrencies, Fink stated that crypto, especially bitcoin could “revolutionize finance.” During an interview with Fox Business, he stated: “We do believe that if we can create more tokenization of assets and securities – that’s what bitcoin is – it could revolutionize finance.”  Regulatory Environment Far From Certain Novogratz also noted Ripple’s recent victory over the SEC, with a judge ruling that the XRP token isn’t a security when sold on secondary exchanges. The Galaxy Digital CEO believes the court’s decision highlights the fact that regulators are still not familiar with the crypto space, and regulations from these regulators &#8220;are nowhere close to clear.&#8221; Related Reading: US Presidential Candidate Defends Bitcoin, Calls Out Environmental Critics The United States Securities and Exchange Commission has, so far, continued to label many cryptocurrencies as “securities” and filed separate lawsuits against different crypto exchanges and firms for allowing the trade of “unregistered securities.”  However, if the recent ruling is anything to go by, it is obvious that the regulators are mistaken, and there is a need for the US Congress to enact crypto-related laws for stakeholders (including regulators) to gain more clarity on how to navigate the industry regulatory-wise.  Featured image from CryptoSlate, chart from Tradingview.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>BlackRock officially <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/sec-sues-binance-coinbase-blackrock-bitcoin-etf-inside-job/">announced</a> its entrance into Bitcoin earlier this year by filing for a Spot Bitcoin ETF with the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). Although the regulator is yet to accept the filing, CEO Larry Fink has also made some supportive comments, <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/blackrock-ceo-larry-fink-says-bitcoin-is-digital-gold-so-whats-the-digital-silver/">comparing BTC to digital gold</a>. </p>
<p>In light of these events, Galaxy Digital CEO Mike Novogratz has come forward to share his opinions on BlackRock CEO Larry Fink and how he affects the digital asset.</p>
<h2>BlackRock CEO&#8217;s Pivoting Sentiment Toward Bitcoin</h2>
<p>Galaxy Digital CEO Mike Novogratz has stated that BlackRock’s CEO Larry Fink&#8217;s change of heart is the best thing to happen to Bitcoin. </p>
<p>&#8220;I think the most important thing that happened this year in Bitcoin is Larry Fink,&#8221; Novogratz mentioned during an <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dj8NRqogAh4" rel="nofollow">interview</a> on Bloomberg TV with David Rubenstein.</p>

<p>Novogratz believes Fink’s acceptance of Bitcoin highlights a shifting sentiment towards Bitcoin and other digital currencies worldwide. </p>
<p>According to him, &#8220;180 million people around the world, without a gun to their head, take their hard-earned savings and store it in this community of people that run this technology, you know, called bitcoin.&#8221;</p>
<p>He further opined that Fink’s change of heart, alongside the increasing adoption of cryptocurrencies, could help Bitcoin surpass its all-time high of $69,000 recorded in 2021. </p>
<p>Blackrock’s CEO Larry Fink was long known to be a skeptic of cryptocurrencies as he once went as far as tagging BTC an “index of money laundering.” </p>
<p>“Bitcoin just shows you how much demand for money laundering there is in the world,” Fink stated in 2017.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/fdklWMBx/" alt="Bitcoin (BTC) price chart from Tradingview.com (BlackRock)" width="2884" height="1632"/></p>

<p>However, there has been a change of heart from the CEO as earlier in June, BlackRock filed an application to the SEC to establish a Bitcoin spot ETF, <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/valkyrie-follows-in-blackrocks-footsteps-refiles-for-spot-bitcoin-etf/">a move that saw some other institutions file a similar application</a>. </p>
<p>In fact, in a show of support for cryptocurrencies, Fink stated that crypto, especially bitcoin could “revolutionize finance.” During an interview with Fox Business, he stated: “We do believe that if we can create more tokenization of assets and securities – that’s what bitcoin is – it could revolutionize finance.” </p>
<h2>Regulatory Environment Far From Certain</h2>
<p>Novogratz also noted <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/ripples-legal-victory-boosts-xrp-price-could-reach-1-soon/">Ripple’s recent victory over the SEC</a>, with a judge ruling that the XRP token isn’t a security when sold on secondary exchanges. The Galaxy Digital CEO believes the court’s decision highlights the fact that regulators are still not familiar with the crypto space, and regulations from these regulators &#8220;are nowhere close to clear.&#8221;</p>

<p>The United States Securities and Exchange Commission has, so far, continued to label many cryptocurrencies as “securities” and filed separate lawsuits against different crypto exchanges and firms for allowing the trade of “unregistered securities.” </p>
<p>However, if the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/ripple-victory-against-the-sec-may-be-short-lived/">recent ruling</a> is anything to go by, it is obvious that the regulators are mistaken, and there is a need for the US Congress to enact crypto-related laws for stakeholders (including regulators) to gain more clarity on how to navigate the industry regulatory-wise. </p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Blackrock-bitcoin.jpeg?fit=460%2C242" width="460" height="242" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">545319</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Over $28 Million In SHIB Withdrawn From Exchanges Ahead Of Shibarium Launch</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/over-28-million-in-shib-withdrawn/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 01:09:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Shiba Inu]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIB]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIB exchange balances]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIB whales]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIB withdrawals]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIBUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIBUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=545320</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Shibarium Layer-2 upgrade is launching any day now, and it looks like some big SHIB players are making moves ahead of the launch. According to on-chain data, over $28 million in SHIB tokens have been withdrawn from major crypto exchanges in the just concluded month of July.  Massive Withdrawals Signal Investor Interest in Shibarium According to data shared on Twitter by crypto analyst Ali Martinez, backed up by on-chain chart data from IntoTheBlock, around 3.30 trillion SHIB were withdrawn from known crypto exchanges in July, the highest SHIB withdrawal rate in recent months. The chart’s data also shows that the circulating supply of the token within exchanges fell from 86.69 trillion to around 83 trillion by the end of the month. Related Reading: USDT Issuer Tether Reports A 30% Decline In Profit July 19 saw the most significant withdrawal from exchanges, with more than two trillion tokens going into unknown wallets. According to on-chain data from @WhaleAlert, an Ethereum whale transferred 2.4 trillion SHIB tokens worth $18.7 million from Binance.US into an unknown wallet. With the price of the token up by 10% since then, the whale&#8217;s SHIB holding is now valued at more than $20 million.  These massive SHIB withdrawals can be traced to the announcement of the Layer 2 blockchain, Shibarium, which is expected to help minimize gas fees and increase the transaction speeds of the blockchain. Token price falls to $0.00000821 &#124; Source: SHIBUSD on Tradingview.com While there&#8217;s still no official launch date for Shibarium yet, the high rate of withdrawals likely signals that SHIB investors are reducing the selling pressure and want to hold their tokens in private wallets in hopes of what the Shibarium launch might bring.  Withdrawals From Exchanges Reduces Selling Pressure On SHIB When SHIB is withdrawn from exchanges, it can’t be readily sold. This reduces the available supply of SHIB for sale, putting upward pressure on the price. When whales transfer such high amounts into self-custody, it frequently results in massive price changes and a rise in interest from other investors. This flurry of withdrawal into self-custody demonstrates the strength of the SHIB community and their faith in SHIB’s future. Related Reading: Is It A Good Idea To Buy Curve Now? Here’s What This Founder Thinks The meme-inspired token has gained quite a lot of community and has led the entire crypto industry in gains for the past two weeks. Shibarium’s launch is anticipated and SHIB holders want to make sure they capitalize on everything the new scaling solution will offer.  At the time of writing, SHIB&#8217;s market cap is nearing $5 billion after it recently retook the 14th position by market cap. The meme coin is trading at $0.000008314 and is up by 7.55% in the past seven days. Featured image from iStock, chart from Tradingview.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Shibarium Layer-2 upgrade is launching any day now, and it looks like some big SHIB players are making moves ahead of the launch. According to on-chain data, over $28 million in SHIB tokens have been withdrawn from major crypto exchanges in the just concluded month of July. </p>
<h2>Massive Withdrawals Signal Investor Interest in Shibarium</h2>
<p>According to <a href="https://twitter.com/ali_charts/status/1686152761505685504?s=20" rel="nofollow">data </a>shared on Twitter by crypto analyst Ali Martinez, backed up by on-chain chart data from IntoTheBlock, around 3.30 trillion SHIB were withdrawn from known crypto exchanges in July, the highest SHIB withdrawal rate in recent months. The chart’s data also shows that the circulating supply of the token within exchanges fell from 86.69 trillion to around 83 trillion by the end of the month.</p>

<p>July 19 saw the most significant withdrawal from exchanges, with more than two trillion tokens going into unknown wallets. According to on-chain <a href="https://twitter.com/whale_alert/status/1681769116049260546?s=20" rel="nofollow">data </a>from @WhaleAlert, an Ethereum whale transferred 2.4 trillion SHIB tokens worth $18.7 million from Binance.US into an unknown wallet. With the price of the token up by 10% since then, the whale&#8217;s SHIB holding is now valued at more than $20 million. </p>
<p>These massive SHIB withdrawals can be traced to the announcement of the Layer 2 blockchain, Shibarium, which is expected to help minimize gas fees and increase the transaction speeds of the blockchain.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/G6KrumpD/" alt="Shiba Inu (SHIB) price chart from Tradingview.com" width="2884" height="1632"/></p>

<p>While there&#8217;s still no official launch date for Shibarium yet, the high rate of withdrawals likely signals that SHIB investors are reducing the selling pressure and want to hold their tokens in private wallets in hopes of what the Shibarium launch might bring. </p>
<h2>Withdrawals From Exchanges Reduces Selling Pressure On SHIB</h2>
<p>When SHIB is withdrawn from exchanges, it can’t be readily sold. This reduces the available supply of SHIB for sale, putting upward pressure on the price. When whales transfer such high amounts into self-custody, it frequently results in massive price changes and a rise in interest from other investors. This flurry of withdrawal into self-custody demonstrates the strength of the SHIB community and their faith in SHIB’s future.</p>

<p>The meme-inspired token has gained quite a lot of community and has led the entire crypto industry in gains for the past two weeks. Shibarium’s launch is anticipated and SHIB holders want to make sure they capitalize on everything the new scaling solution will offer. </p>
<p>At the time of writing, SHIB&#8217;s market cap is nearing $5 billion after it recently retook the 14th position by market cap. The meme coin is trading at $0.000008314 and is up by 7.55% in the past seven days.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/iStock-1362613000.jpg?fit=460%2C307" width="460" height="307" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">545320</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Lightspark CEO Outlines The Challenges Of Building On The Bitcoin Lightning Network</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/challenges-of-bitcoin-lightning-network/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 23:30:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin lightning network]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Lightning network]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Lightspark]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=545322</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The CEO of Lightspark, David Marcus, has come forward to share his experiences on building atop the Bitcoin Lightning Network. Marcus noted the challenges the Lightning Network held for builders, stating that it was incredibly difficult and complex to develop software around the protocol. The Bitcoin Lightning Network And The Challenges It Holds for Builders According to the Lightspark CEO, a firm involved in developing payment solutions on the Lightning Network, a layer-2 scaling platform for Bitcoin, the firm decided to build on the network because of the “unique qualities” Bitcoin provides as the underlying network.  Related Reading: US Presidential Candidate Defends Bitcoin, Calls Out Environmental Critics He explained that Lightspark’s objective is to build a cheap, very open, and interoperable protocol for virtual money/payments, and the Lightning Network is designed to be similar to layer 2 ZK-rollup for Bitcoin.  However, the former president of Paypal and co-creator of Diem noted that building on Lightning and Bitcoin is about five times more difficult than developing on other protocols. This is because the process to create software around the protocol is incredibly difficult and complex to do. Nevertheless, with these objectives in mind, the platform committed to building on the Bitcoin Lightning Network and to do “Whatever it takes to reach their full potential.” But despite having high hopes about the prospects of the network, Marcus’s recent disclosures on Twitter have shown that building on the network was no easy feat.  BTC price trending at $28,879 &#124; Source: BTCUSD on Tradingview.com Moving Forward Despite Difficulties According to Marcus, part of the challenges is attributed to the rigidity of Bitcoin and the difficulties involved in altering its structure to contain new code in its base layers to meet the needs of specific solutions. He pointed out that Bitcoin’s layer 1 is particularly rigid and building a new opcode to mainlet was practically not possible.  However, despite these challenges, Lightspark remains upbeat, and instead of completely abandoning the Lightning Network protocol for other less complex chains, the platform intends to develop a payment solution that would still be applicable “100 years from now.” The firm also intends to reorganize the process enabling crypto market users to connect to the Lightning Network. Although this will depend on their ability to put in place the necessary peer-to-peer payment channels. Related Reading: USDT Issuer Tether Reports A 30% Decline In Profit Apart from Lightspark’s CEO, other players in the sector have also recognized the intricacies and general challenges of building software around the Lightning Network. Popular CEO of Binance Changpeng Zhao has previously pointed out that integrating Lightning Network services on Binance was more complex because of the usage of on-demand invoices, which are different from pre-generated addresses.  Additionally, Fitatjaf, a prominent Bitcoin developer and founder of the decentralized social protocol Nostr, has also offered criticism of the Lightning Network, terming it a pile of complex and ugly hacks.  Featured image from iStock, chart from Tradingview.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The CEO of Lightspark, David Marcus, has come forward to share his experiences on building atop the Bitcoin Lightning Network. Marcus noted the challenges the Lightning Network held for builders, stating that it was incredibly difficult and complex to develop software around the protocol.</p>
<h2>The Bitcoin Lightning Network And The Challenges It Holds for Builders</h2>
<p>According to the Lightspark CEO, a firm involved in developing payment solutions on the Lightning Network, a layer-2 scaling platform for Bitcoin, the firm decided to build on the network because of the “unique qualities” Bitcoin provides as the underlying network. </p>

<p>He explained that Lightspark’s objective is to build a cheap, very open, and interoperable protocol for virtual money/payments, and the Lightning Network is designed to be similar to layer 2 ZK-rollup for Bitcoin. </p>
<p>However, the former president of Paypal and co-creator of Diem <a href="https://twitter.com/davidmarcus/status/1685356197367750656?s=20" rel="nofollow">noted</a> that building on Lightning and Bitcoin is about five times more difficult than developing on other protocols. This is because the process to create software around the protocol is incredibly difficult and complex to do.</p>
<p>Nevertheless, with these objectives in mind, the platform committed to building on the Bitcoin Lightning Network and to do “Whatever it takes to reach their full potential.” But despite having high hopes about the prospects of the network, Marcus’s recent disclosures on Twitter have shown that building on the network was no easy feat. </p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/7h5DcUnI/" alt="Bitcoin (BTC) price chart from Tradingview.com" width="2884" height="1746"/></p>

<h2>Moving Forward Despite Difficulties</h2>
<p>According to Marcus, part of the challenges is attributed to the rigidity of Bitcoin and the difficulties involved in altering its structure to contain new code in its base layers to meet the needs of specific solutions. He pointed out that Bitcoin’s layer 1 is particularly rigid and building a new opcode to mainlet was practically not possible. </p>
<p>However, despite these challenges, Lightspark remains upbeat, and instead of completely abandoning the Lightning Network protocol for other less complex chains, the platform intends to develop a payment solution that would still be applicable “100 years from now.”</p>
<p>The firm also intends to reorganize the process enabling crypto market users to connect to the Lightning Network. Although this will depend on their ability to put in place the necessary peer-to-peer payment channels.</p>

<p>Apart from Lightspark’s CEO, other players in the sector have also recognized the intricacies and general challenges of building software around the Lightning Network. Popular CEO of Binance Changpeng Zhao has previously <a href="https://twitter.com/binance/status/1671042638592589826?s=20" rel="nofollow">pointed out</a> that <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-lightning-network-binance-integration/" rel="nofollow">integrating Lightning Network services on Binance</a> was more complex because of the usage of on-demand invoices, which are different from pre-generated addresses. </p>
<p>Additionally, Fitatjaf, a prominent Bitcoin developer and founder of the decentralized social protocol Nostr, has also offered <a href="https://twitter.com/fiatjaf/status/1679642866484666368?s=20" rel="nofollow">criticism</a> of the Lightning Network, terming it a pile of complex and ugly hacks. </p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/iStock-1383793414.jpg?fit=460%2C298" width="460" height="298" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">545322</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Michael Egorov’s $100 Million Position, A Risk To Curve Finance And DeFi?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/crypto/michael-egorovs-100-million-position-a-risk-to-curve-finance-and-defi/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Opeyemi Sule]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 22:30:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[aave]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CRV]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Curve DAO]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Curve Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Frax Finance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=545334</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Following the recent exploit of Curve Finance pools, there have been genuine concerns about the stability of the decentralized exchange and the Decentralized Finance (DeFi) ecosystem. A new report has emerged, raising questions about Curve founder Michael Egorov&#8217;s $100 million loan positions. These positions have garnered significant interest, as they are backed by about 47% of the entire CRV circulating supply. With the price of CRV dwindling, these debts appear to be at risk of liquidation, putting the Curve protocol, CRV investors, and the overall DeFi space on edge.  Related Reading: Ethereum DeFi Coins Plunge As Curve Concerns Threaten Major Market Crash A Breakdown Of Michael Egorov’s $100 Million Loan On Tuesday, August 1, crypto research firm Delphi Digital released a series of tweets, detailing the loan positions being held by Michael Egorov. According to the report, the Curve Finance founder has around $100 million in loans across various lending protocols backed by 427.5 million CRV tokens. Egorov has a 63.2 million USDT loan backed by 305 million CRV tokens on Aave.  Delphi Digital revealed that the position has a liquidation threshold of 55% and is eligible for liquidation at 0.3767 CRV/USDT. For context, the CRV currently trades at $0.608595, according to CoinGecko data. This means that a 38% price decline will cause a liquidation of Egorov’s position on the Aave protocol. Meanwhile, the Curve founder has 59 million CRV backing a loan of 15.8 million FRAX on Frax Finance. Although this debt is much lower than his Aave position, it poses a much more significant risk to CRV due to Fraxlend’s Time-Weighted Variable Interest Rate. Delphi Digital also noted that liquidation of the Frax loan position can occur regardless of CRV’s price. According to the research firm, the loan is currently at 100% utilization, which allows the interest rate to double every 12 hours. While the interest rate currently stands at 81.20%, Delphi Digital said that it can potentially increase to the maximum of about 10,000% APY in 3.5 days. This high-interest rate could result in the eventual liquidation of the debt. CRVUSDT trading at $0.598 &#124; Source: daily CRVUSDT chart from TradingView How Has The Curve Finance Founder Responded? So far, Michael Egorov has tried to stabilize his positions and the utilization rate twice, repaying a total of 4 million FRAX on July 31st. However, the utilization rate remained at 100%, as users swiftly remove liquidity as soon as he makes the payment. To address this, the Curve founder deployed a new Curve pool on Tuesday, August 1. This pool consists of stablecoin crvUSD and Fraxlend’s CRV/FRAX LP token, seeded with 100,000 CRV rewards.  This is to incentivize liquidity toward the lending market, decrease the utilization rates, and ultimately reduce the liquidation risks. According to Delphi Digital, this pool attracted $2 million in liquidity and lowered the utilization rate to 89% four hours after launch. Related Reading: Is It A Good Idea To Buy Curve Now? Here’s What This Founder Thinks Featured image from Binance Academy, chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Following the recent exploit of Curve Finance pools, there have been genuine concerns about the stability of the decentralized exchange and the Decentralized Finance (DeFi) ecosystem. A new report has emerged, raising questions about Curve founder Michael Egorov&#8217;s $100 million loan positions.</p>
<p>These positions have garnered significant interest, as they are backed by about 47% of the entire CRV circulating supply. With the price of CRV dwindling, these debts appear to be at risk of liquidation, putting the Curve protocol, CRV investors, and the overall DeFi space on edge. </p>

<h2>A Breakdown Of Michael Egorov’s $100 Million Loan</h2>
<p>On Tuesday, August 1, crypto research firm Delphi Digital released a series of <a href="https://twitter.com/Delphi_Digital/status/1686187959303708672?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">tweets</a>, detailing the loan positions being held by Michael Egorov. According to the report, the Curve Finance founder has around $100 million in loans across various lending protocols backed by 427.5 million CRV tokens.</p>
<p>Egorov has a 63.2 million USDT loan backed by 305 million CRV tokens on Aave.  Delphi Digital revealed that the position has a liquidation threshold of 55% and is eligible for liquidation at 0.3767 CRV/USDT.</p>
<p>For context, the CRV currently trades at $0.608595, according to <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/curve-dao-token" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">CoinGecko data</a>. This means that a 38% price decline will cause a liquidation of Egorov’s position on the Aave protocol.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, the Curve founder has 59 million CRV backing a loan of 15.8 million FRAX on Frax Finance. Although this debt is much lower than his Aave position, it poses a much more significant risk to CRV due to Fraxlend’s Time-Weighted Variable Interest Rate.</p>
<p>Delphi Digital also noted that liquidation of the Frax loan position can occur regardless of CRV’s price. According to the research firm, the loan is currently at 100% utilization, which allows the interest rate to double every 12 hours.</p>
<p>While the interest rate currently stands at 81.20%, Delphi Digital said that it can potentially increase to the maximum of about 10,000% APY in 3.5 days. This high-interest rate could result in the eventual liquidation of the debt.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/o70IFcdX/" alt="Curve Finance" width="997" height="586"/></p>

<h2>How Has The Curve Finance Founder Responded?</h2>
<p>So far, Michael Egorov has tried to stabilize his positions and the utilization rate twice, repaying a total of 4 million FRAX on July 31st. However, the utilization rate remained at 100%, as users swiftly remove liquidity as soon as he makes the payment.</p>
<p>To address this, the Curve founder deployed a new Curve pool on Tuesday, August 1. This pool consists of stablecoin crvUSD and Fraxlend’s CRV/FRAX LP token, seeded with 100,000 CRV rewards. </p>
<p>This is to incentivize liquidity toward the lending market, decrease the utilization rates, and ultimately reduce the liquidation risks.</p>
<p>According to Delphi Digital, this pool attracted $2 million in liquidity and lowered the utilization rate to 89% four hours after launch.</p>





]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/04890cb8cf134a4f86b10fca40381ba6.png?fit=460%2C259" width="460" height="259" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">545334</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance To Enter Japan With A Bang, Will List More Tokens Than Any Local Exchange</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/binance/binance-to-enter-japan-with-a-bang/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 21:30:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance Japan]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[japan]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=545321</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[According to Japanese-based crypto media outlet Coinpost, Binance will launch in Japan fully this month and intends to list 34 tokens on its exchange. This means the platform will offer more tokens than its local competitors in Japan, with major domestic exchanges Bitbank, GMO Coin, and Coincheck listing 30, 36, and 22 tokens, respectively.  The largest crypto exchange by trading volume intends to list its native BNB token, making this the first time it will be available in the country. Some of the other tokens expected to be listed include Axie Infinity (AXS), Solana (SOL), and Avalanche (AVAX). A Remarkable Re-entry News of the re-entry into Japan was announced by the CEO of Binance via a Twitter video. According to him, the platform has been making efforts to re-enter the Japanese market for a while now. He was effusive with his praises and noted that since 2017, Japan had established crypto exchange regulations, including the recent stablecoin regulations enacted in June. He also stated it was “fantastic to see Japan being a leader in the Web3 regulatory environment.” Related Reading: USDT Issuer Tether Reports A 30% Decline In Profit He further added that Binance was glad to once again partake in the Japanese market after its purchase of the Sakura Exchange BitCoin (SEBC) platform in November last year. Following the acquisition, SEBC changed its name to Binance Japan Inc.  The purchase of the exchange was instrumental in paving the way for the re-entrance of Binance in Japan. Binance will initially offer sport trading services. However, the exchange will not render leveraged trading services since this will require a Type 1 Financial Instruments Business license, with more restrictive standards.  Additionally, cryptocurrency users in Japan will also be offered access to Binance Earn, a specially designed program that enables participants to earn interest on their cryptocurrency deposits. The exchange will also render Japanese crypto traders an opportunity to trade on its NFT marketplace. BNB coin price sitting at $245 following exchange announcement &#124; Source: BNBUSD on Tradingview.com Major Regulatory Win for Binance This recent announcement marks a major regulatory win for Binance. In the recent past, the platform has faced various regulatory challenges and was recently made to drop its license application in Germany.  Related Reading: US Presidential Candidate Defends Bitcoin, Calls Out Environmental Critics In France, the exchange also faces regulatory investigations, with French authorities accusing Binance of being involved in offering illegal digital assets services and failing to curtail money laundering.  Therefore, this latest announcement of a re-entry into the Japanese market heralds a major regulatory win for the embattled exchange. Featured image from CoinDesk, chart from Tradingview.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>According to Japanese-based crypto media outlet <a href="https://coinpost.jp/?p=475193" rel="nofollow">Coinpost</a>, Binance will launch in Japan fully this month and intends to list 34 tokens on its exchange. This means the platform will offer more tokens than its local competitors in Japan, with major domestic exchanges Bitbank, GMO Coin, and Coincheck listing 30, 36, and 22 tokens, respectively. </p>
<p>The largest crypto exchange by trading volume intends to list its native BNB token, making this the first time it will be available in the country. Some of the other tokens expected to be listed include Axie Infinity (AXS), Solana (SOL), and Avalanche (AVAX).</p>
<h2>A Remarkable Re-entry</h2>
<p>News of the re-entry into Japan was <a href="https://twitter.com/binance/status/1683885315558191113" rel="nofollow">announced</a> by the CEO of Binance via a Twitter video. According to him, the platform has been making efforts to re-enter the Japanese market for a while now. He was effusive with his praises and noted that since 2017, Japan had established crypto exchange regulations, including the recent stablecoin regulations enacted in June. He also stated it was “fantastic to see Japan being a leader in the Web3 regulatory environment.”</p>

<p>He further added that Binance was glad to once again partake in the Japanese market after its <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/binance-japan-to-roll-out-services-by-august/" rel="nofollow">purchase of the Sakura Exchange BitCoin</a> (SEBC) platform in November last year. Following the acquisition, SEBC changed its name to Binance Japan Inc. </p>
<p>The purchase of the exchange was instrumental in paving the way for the re-entrance of Binance in Japan. Binance will initially offer sport trading services. However, the exchange will not render leveraged trading services since this will require a Type 1 Financial Instruments Business license, with more restrictive standards. </p>
<p>Additionally, cryptocurrency users in Japan will also be offered access to Binance Earn, a specially designed program that enables participants to earn interest on their cryptocurrency deposits. The exchange will also render Japanese crypto traders an opportunity to trade on its NFT marketplace.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/zFhoiepi/" alt="Binance Coin (BNB) price chart from Tradingview.com" width="2884" height="1746"/></p>

<h2>Major Regulatory Win for Binance</h2>
<p>This recent announcement marks a major regulatory win for Binance. In the recent past, the platform has faced various regulatory challenges and was recently made to <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/binance-terminates-german-cryptolicense-application/" rel="nofollow">drop its license application in Germany</a>. </p>

<p>In France, the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/binance/binance-rescinds-decision-to-remove-privacy-coins-from-european-market/?swcfpc=1">exchange also faces regulatory investigations</a>, with French authorities accusing Binance of being involved in offering illegal digital assets services and failing to curtail money laundering. </p>
<p>Therefore, this latest announcement of a re-entry into the Japanese market heralds a major regulatory win for the embattled exchange.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Binance-Japan.jpeg?fit=460%2C345" width="460" height="345" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">545321</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Drops Under $29,000, Here&#8217;s Where BTC Could Find Support Next</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-drops-under-29000-btc-find-support-next/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hououin Kyouma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 20:30:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Realized Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin short-term holders]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin support]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=545286</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin has plunged below the $29,000 level during the past day. According to on-chain data, here&#8217;s the next level that could act as major support. Bitcoin Short-Term Holder Realized Price May Be The Next Support Level As pointed out by an analyst in a CryptoQuant post, the realized price of the short-term holders at $28,000 could be an essential level for the asset. The “realized price” here refers to the cost basis (that is, the buying price) of the average investor in the Bitcoin market. Whenever the price of the asset dips below this level, it means that more than 50% of the investors are now underwater. Similarly, a break above the point implies that the overall market has entered into a state of profits. In the context of the current discussion, the realized price of the entire market isn’t of relevance, but rather of a specific segment of it: the “short-term holders” (STHs). This investor group typically only includes holders who bought their BTC within the last six months. Here is a chart that shows the trend in the average cost basis for this Bitcoin cohort over the history of the cryptocurrency: How the realized price of the STHs has shifted throughout history &#124; Source: CryptoQuant Historically, the Bitcoin STH realized price has had some interesting interactions with the spot price of the asset. First is the interactions during bullish periods, which the quant has highlighted in the above graph. It would appear that during these rallies, the price has usually remained above the level. But not just that, the STH realized price has actually actively provided support to it in such periods. In the rally during the past year, too, a similar trend has been seen, as both during the March and June price drawdowns, the cryptocurrency rebounded when it made a retest of this line. Related Reading: Is Another Bitcoin Rally Coming Soon? This Pattern May Say So Psychologically, investors view their cost basis as a profitable buying opportunity during bullish periods, as they believe that the price will only go up from here. So, whenever the asset returns to its cost basis in such periods, they are likely to accumulate again. This extraordinary buying pressure at the level of the STHs could perhaps explain why Bitcoin finds support here. In a similar way, the level acts as resistance during bearish periods, as investors start looking at their acquisition price as the ideal exit opportunity. From the chart, it’s visible that the Bitcoin spot price is approaching the STH realized price once again right now. This level, which is valued at $28,000 currently, could possibly be where Bitcoin can turn around its recent trend of decline. Related Reading: US Presidential Candidate Defends Bitcoin, Calls Out Environmental Critics The analyst warns, however, “if the realized price of short-term holders fails to hold, the bull market may be over.” BTC Price At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading around $28,900, down 1% in the last week. BTC has been going down recently &#124; Source: BTCUSD on Tradingview Featured image from Kanchanara on Unsplash.com, charts from TradingView.com, CryptoQuant.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin has plunged below the $29,000 level during the past day. According to on-chain data, here&#8217;s the next level that could act as major support.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Short-Term Holder Realized Price May Be The Next Support Level</h2>
<p>As pointed out by an analyst in a CryptoQuant <a href="https://cryptoquant.com/insights/quicktake/64c7d442860fe15823fe3e90-The-realized-price-of-Bitcoins-short-term-holders-6M-is-a-very-important-trend-l" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">post</a>, the realized price of the short-term holders at $28,000 could be an essential level for the asset. The “<a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-under-realized-price-163-days/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">realized price</a>” here refers to the cost basis (that is, the buying price) of the average investor in the Bitcoin market.</p>
<p>Whenever the price of the asset dips below this level, it means that more than 50% of the investors are now underwater. Similarly, a break above the point implies that the overall market has entered into a state of profits.</p>
<p>In the context of the current discussion, the realized price of the entire market isn’t of relevance, but rather of a specific segment of it: the “<a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-short-term-holders-exchange-inflows-price/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">short-term holders</a>” (STHs).</p>
<p>This investor group typically only includes holders who bought their BTC within the last six months. Here is a chart that shows the trend in the average cost basis for this Bitcoin cohort over the history of the cryptocurrency:</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone aligncenter" src="https://i0.wp.com/img.cryptoquant.com/50615/quicktake/FjTKpBOxW_8ae2d426cc53e432862018e4e545268ea3907f59f73e35dce5f8c7b877367213.png?resize=1280%2C539&#038;ssl=1" alt="Bitcoin Realized Price" width="1280" height="539"  data-recalc-dims="1"/></p>

<p>Historically, the Bitcoin STH realized price has had some interesting interactions with the spot price of the asset. First is the interactions during <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-rally-may-not-resume-until-this-happens/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">bullish periods</a>, which the quant has highlighted in the above graph.</p>
<p>It would appear that during these rallies, the price has usually remained above the level. But not just that, the STH realized price has actually actively provided support to it in such periods.</p>
<p>In the rally during the past year, too, a similar trend has been seen, as both during the March and June price drawdowns, the cryptocurrency rebounded when it made a retest of this line.</p>

<p>Psychologically, investors view their cost basis as a profitable buying opportunity during bullish periods, as they believe that the price will only go up from here. So, whenever the asset returns to its cost basis in such periods, they are likely to accumulate again.</p>
<p>This extraordinary buying pressure at the level of the STHs could perhaps explain why Bitcoin finds support here. In a similar way, the level acts as resistance during bearish periods, as investors start looking at their acquisition price as the ideal exit opportunity.</p>
<p>From the chart, it’s visible that the Bitcoin spot price is approaching the STH realized price once again right now. This level, which is valued at $28,000 currently, could possibly be where Bitcoin can turn around its recent trend of decline.</p>

<p>The analyst warns, however, “if the realized price of short-term holders fails to hold, the bull market may be over.”</p>
<h2><b>BTC Price</b></h2>
<p>At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading around $28,900, down 1% in the last week.</p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/kanchanara-GnWfl_nnZro-unsplash.jpg?fit=460%2C306" width="460" height="306" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">545286</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Price Forecast: Dark Days Ahead As $29,200 Support Fails</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-price-forecast-dark-days-ahead-as-29200-support-fails/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 19:30:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=545347</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[In his recent report, Charles Edward, a prominent crypto market analyst, released an update on the state of the Bitcoin (BTC) market. The report highlights the continuation of the downtrend for Bitcoin, which has been losing its key support, the 50-day Moving Average (MA).  The bearish trend has been confirmed by technical indicators and the pure fundamental Bitcoin Macro Index algorithm, which has seen an increasing rate of contraction over the last week. Is Bitcoin Headed For $25,000? The report provides insights into both high and low timeframe technicals, with the next support levels for Bitcoin at $28,000, $24,000, and low-$20,000, each offering better relative opportunities.  The low timeframe technicals indicate a breakdown in support at $30,000 and the emergence of a new bearish trend, with a target of circa $25,000. The Capriole Bitcoin Macro Index, which combines over 40 of the most powerful Bitcoin on-chain, macro market, and equities metrics into a single machine learning model, suggests a decent long-term value for multi-year horizon investors, but with decreasing fundamentals over the last week. Related Reading: Litecoin Sharks Buy More Than 200,000 LTC Ahead Of Wednesday’s Halving On the other hand, the Three Factor Model, a new open-source algorithm, values the S&#38;P500 using three fundamental data points only, indicating that the markets are fairly valued today, with room for more upside, despite recent bearish signals. Despite the bearish outlook, the report suggests that the macroeconomic backdrop remains favorable for Bitcoin over the coming years.  The Federal Reserve has paused rate hikes, and the S&#38;P500 has had its longest winning streak in years. However, the technicals and fundamentals are currently showing a &#8220;not yet&#8221; signal, indicating that the market may need to wait for a positive trigger such as the approval of the Blackrock ETF. Overall, the report suggests a long-term bullish outlook for Bitcoin, but with caution in the short term until technicals or fundamentals prove otherwise.  According to Edwards, the nearest points of technical opportunity are $28,000, $25,000, and $21,000, or a daily close back into the $30,000 range. Low Volatility, High Potential Bitcoin&#8217;s price volatility has been at historic lows, with the cryptocurrency experiencing its second-lowest level of yearly volatility ever. This fact has been noted by many in the crypto community, including Crypto Con, who points out that historically, low volatility has been a bullish sign for Bitcoin. Low volatility can be seen as a sign of stability and maturity for a cryptocurrency. It suggests that the market is becoming more efficient and that there is less speculation driving prices up and down. This can be a positive sign for long-term investors, as it suggests that cryptocurrency is becoming more reliable as a store of value. Related Reading: Ethereum DeFi Coins Plunge As Curve Concerns Threaten Major Market Crash Moreover, Bitcoin has historically performed well after periods of low volatility. Every time Bitcoin&#8217;s volatility has dropped to similar levels in the past, it has been followed by a significant price increase.  This suggests that, while the current low volatility may be frustrating for traders looking for quick profits, it could be a positive sign for long-term investors. In conclusion, while the current low volatility in Bitcoin&#8217;s price may not be exciting for traders, it could be a positive sign for long-term investors. Historically, low volatility has been a bullish sign for Bitcoin, and the cryptocurrency&#8217;s current stability comes at a time when several positive macroeconomic factors could drive its price up in the future. As of the time of writing, Bitcoin has lost its crucial support line of $29,000 and is currently trading at $28,900, representing a decline of over 1% in the last 24 hours. Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In his recent <a href="https://capriole.com/update-2/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">report</a>, Charles Edward, a prominent crypto market analyst, released an update on the state of the Bitcoin (BTC) market. The report highlights the continuation of the downtrend for Bitcoin, which has been losing its key support, the 50-day Moving Average (MA). </p>
<p>The bearish trend has been confirmed by technical indicators and the pure fundamental Bitcoin Macro Index algorithm, which has seen an increasing rate of contraction over the last week.</p>
<h2>Is Bitcoin Headed For $25,000?</h2>
<p>The report provides insights into both high and low timeframe technicals, with the next support levels for Bitcoin at $28,000, $24,000, and low-$20,000, each offering better relative opportunities. </p>
<p>The low timeframe technicals indicate a breakdown in support at $30,000 and the emergence of a new bearish trend, with a target of circa $25,000.</p>
<p>The Capriole Bitcoin Macro Index, which combines over 40 of the most powerful Bitcoin on-chain, macro market, and equities metrics into a single machine learning model, suggests a decent long-term value for multi-year horizon investors, but with decreasing fundamentals over the last week.</p>

<p>On the other hand, the Three Factor Model, a new open-source algorithm, values the S&amp;P500 using three fundamental data points only, indicating that the markets are fairly valued today, with room for more upside, despite recent bearish signals.</p>
<p>Despite the bearish outlook, the report suggests that the macroeconomic backdrop remains favorable for Bitcoin over the coming years. </p>
<p>The Federal Reserve has paused rate hikes, and the S&amp;P500 has had its longest winning streak in years. However, the technicals and fundamentals are currently showing a &#8220;not yet&#8221; signal, indicating that the market may need to wait for a positive trigger such as the approval of the Blackrock ETF.</p>
<p>Overall, the report suggests a long-term bullish outlook for Bitcoin, but with caution in the short term until technicals or fundamentals prove otherwise. </p>
<p>According to Edwards, the nearest points of technical opportunity are $28,000, $25,000, and $21,000, or a daily close back into the $30,000 range.</p>
Low Volatility, High Potential
<p>Bitcoin&#8217;s price volatility has been at historic lows, with the cryptocurrency experiencing its second-lowest level of yearly volatility ever. This fact has been noted by many in the crypto community, including Crypto Con, who <a href="https://twitter.com/CryptoCon_/status/1686373259019976705?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">points</a> out that historically, low volatility has been a bullish sign for Bitcoin.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large wp-image-545349" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F2cxl-lWEAAx57l.png?w=860&#038;resize=860%2C450" alt="Bitcoin " width="860" height="450" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F2cxl-lWEAAx57l.png?w=1442 1442w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F2cxl-lWEAAx57l.png?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F2cxl-lWEAAx57l.png?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F2cxl-lWEAAx57l.png?w=860&#038;resize=860%2C450 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F2cxl-lWEAAx57l.png?w=750 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F2cxl-lWEAAx57l.png?w=1140 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" data-recalc-dims="1"/>
<p>Low volatility can be seen as a sign of stability and maturity for a cryptocurrency. It suggests that the market is becoming more efficient and that there is less speculation driving prices up and down. This can be a positive sign for long-term investors, as it suggests that cryptocurrency is becoming more reliable as a store of value.</p>

<p>Moreover, Bitcoin has historically performed well after periods of low volatility. Every time Bitcoin&#8217;s volatility has dropped to similar levels in the past, it has been followed by a significant price increase. </p>
<p>This suggests that, while the current low volatility may be frustrating for traders looking for quick profits, it could be a positive sign for long-term investors.</p>
<p>In conclusion, while the current low volatility in Bitcoin&#8217;s price may not be exciting for traders, it could be a positive sign for long-term investors. Historically, low volatility has been a bullish sign for Bitcoin, and the cryptocurrency&#8217;s current stability comes at a time when several positive macroeconomic factors could drive its price up in the future.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/YbidWM5N/" alt="Bitcoin " width="1814" height="858"/>
<p>As of the time of writing, Bitcoin has lost its crucial support line of $29,000 and is currently trading at $28,900, representing a decline of over 1% in the last 24 hours.</p>
<p>Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/jeremy-vessey-zk7GoKZbBL8-unsplash.jpg?fit=460%2C294" width="460" height="294" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">545347</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Bollinger Bands Are The Tightest Ever, What Happens Next?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-bollinger-bands-are-the-tightest-ever-what-happens-next/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tony "The Bull"]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 19:25:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bollinger bands]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xbt]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xbtusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=545365</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Last week, the 1W Bollinger Bands in Bitcoin reached its tightest level ever. The volatility measuring tool typically doesn’t give any indication of direction, however. Using historical data, we’ve taken all previous instances of extreme lows and the resulting direction — up and down — and discovered the success rate of the signal. Bollinger Band Width Reaches Historical Lows: What Does It Mean? The Bollinger Bands are a complete trading system, designed by John Bollinger in the 1980s — an avid Bitcoin speculator. The tool uses a 20-period simple moving average (SMA) and two bands set at two standard deviations of the SMA. As such, the “Bands” expand and contract based on volatility — a measure of how aggressively price moves within a time period. When the Bands tighten to extremes, it indicates a period of low volatility. This setup is called a Squeeze, which ultimately releases pent up energy and results in a large move. When price action picks up, the bands expand to represent the return of volatility. According to Bollinger Band Width, a related tool designed to tell analysts how tight the bands on an easier to visually compare basis, the Bollinger Bands in BTCUSD are the tightest in the history of crypto. Notably, Ethereum and the TOTAL crypto market cap are also historically tight. The technical indicator, however, doesn’t say anything about direction, only that something big is on the way. In the past, Bitcoin has broken out in either direction. But how many of these times were up? And how far did it climb? When will explosive volatility return? &#124; BTCUSD on TradingView.com Bitcoin Breakout Performance Analyzed: Average 669% ROI When Volatility Returns Past performance is never a guarantee of future results, but from historical price data we can better understand the behavior in BTCUSD after such low volatility phases. Of the nine total instances the Bitcoin weekly Bollinger Bands got this tight, the top cryptocurrency by market cap rallied upward after upon breakout seven times. The average upward movement across all seven times is 872%. In contrast, the two down moves resulted in an average crash of 40%.&#60; Bitcoin falling 40% from here would take it back to $17,500 per coin, while a 872% move higher would take BTCUSD to over $280,000 per coin. The average of up and down moves resulted in a grand total of 669%, which would take the number one cryptocurrency to over $220,000. Considering the rule of diminishing returns, such a strong move is unlikely. However, the data speaks to the magnitude of the move that could occur, once volatility returns. As long as #Bitcoin remains above the weekly Bollinger Band basis –– a 20-period SMA –– I am bullish Lose the mid-BB and then I&#8217;ll talk downside pic.twitter.com/knOo0oMW5M — Tony &#8220;The Bull&#8221; (@tonythebullBTC) July 28, 2023 Tony is the author of the CoinChartist (VIP) newsletter. Sign up for free. Follow @TonyTheBullBTC &#38; @coinchartist_io on Twitter. Or join the TonyTradesBTC Telegram for daily market insights and technical analysis education. Please note: Content is educational and should not be considered investment advice. Featured image from iStockPhoto, Charts from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Last week, the 1W Bollinger Bands in Bitcoin <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-history-making-move-volatility/" rel="nofollow">reached its tightest level ever</a>. The volatility measuring tool typically doesn’t give any indication of direction, however.</p>
<p>Using historical data, we’ve taken all previous instances of extreme lows and the resulting direction — up and down — and discovered the success rate of the signal.</p>
<h2>Bollinger Band Width Reaches Historical Lows: What Does It Mean?</h2>
<p>The <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/topic/bollinger-bands/">Bollinger Bands</a> are a complete trading system, designed by John Bollinger in the 1980s — an avid Bitcoin speculator. The tool uses a 20-period simple moving average (SMA) and two bands set at two standard deviations of the SMA.</p>
<p>As such, the “Bands” expand and contract based on volatility — a measure of how aggressively price moves within a time period. When the Bands tighten to extremes, it indicates a period of low volatility. This setup is called a Squeeze, which ultimately releases pent up energy and results in a large move. When price action picks up, the bands expand to represent the return of volatility.</p>
<p>According to Bollinger Band Width, a related tool designed to tell analysts how tight the bands on an easier to visually compare basis, the Bollinger Bands in BTCUSD are the tightest in the history of crypto. Notably, Ethereum and the TOTAL crypto market cap are also historically tight.</p>
<p>The technical indicator, however, doesn’t say anything about direction, only that something big is on the way. In the past, Bitcoin has broken out in either direction. But how many of these times were up? And how far did it climb?</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large wp-image-545369 aligncenter" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F2CiMJkX0AAxH5q.jpeg?w=860&#038;resize=860%2C414" alt="Bitcoin Bollinger Bands" width="860" height="414" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F2CiMJkX0AAxH5q.jpeg?w=4096 4096w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F2CiMJkX0AAxH5q.jpeg?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F2CiMJkX0AAxH5q.jpeg?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F2CiMJkX0AAxH5q.jpeg?w=860&#038;resize=860%2C414 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F2CiMJkX0AAxH5q.jpeg?w=1536 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F2CiMJkX0AAxH5q.jpeg?w=2048 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F2CiMJkX0AAxH5q.jpeg?w=750 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F2CiMJkX0AAxH5q.jpeg?w=1140 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F2CiMJkX0AAxH5q.jpeg?w=3000 3000w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" data-recalc-dims="1"/></p>

<h2>Bitcoin Breakout Performance Analyzed: Average 669% ROI When Volatility Returns</h2>
<p>Past performance is never a guarantee of future results, but from historical price data we can better understand the behavior in BTCUSD after such low volatility phases.</p>
<p>Of the nine total instances the Bitcoin weekly Bollinger Bands got this tight, the top cryptocurrency by market cap rallied upward after upon breakout seven times. The average upward movement across all seven times is 872%. In contrast, the two down moves resulted in an average crash of 40%.&lt;</p>
<p>Bitcoin falling 40% from here would take it back to $17,500 per coin, while a 872% move higher would take BTCUSD to over $280,000 per coin. The average of up and down moves resulted in a grand total of 669%, which would take the number one cryptocurrency to over $220,000. Considering the rule of diminishing returns, such a strong move is unlikely. However, the data speaks to the magnitude of the move that could occur, once volatility returns.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">As long as <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Bitcoin?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#Bitcoin</a> remains above the weekly Bollinger Band basis –– a 20-period SMA –– I am bullish</p>
<p>Lose the mid-BB and then I&#8217;ll talk downside <a href="https://t.co/knOo0oMW5M" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/knOo0oMW5M</a></p>
<p>— Tony &#8220;The Bull&#8221; (@tonythebullBTC) <a href="https://twitter.com/tonythebullBTC/status/1684958208195010561?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">July 28, 2023</a></p></blockquote>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/iStock-174837577.jpg?fit=460%2C307" width="460" height="307" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">545365</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Why Is Bitcoin Price Down Today?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/why-is-bitcoin-price-down-today-aug-1-2023/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jake Simmons]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 18:24:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[doj]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[kaiko]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=545291</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Today, Bitcoin took another dive, this time to its lowest level since June 21. A check on Bitfinex reveals a BTC price slump to $28,641. Coinbase, America&#8217;s largest crypto exchange, reported an even more drastic drop to $28,478. Although the price bounced back slightly to hover just below $29,000 (-1.4% in the last 24 hours), the downward trend sparks questions. Why Is The Bitcoin Price On The Decline? James V. Straten, a renowned on-chain analyst, recently tweeted: &#8220;Bitcoin drops below $29,000 as open interest spikes while funding rates go lower. As a result of the biggest long liquidation since 24th July.&#8221; As the analyst states, Bitcoin&#8217;s price trend can be majorly attributed to long liquidations. The liquidation data from Coinglass indicates that $23.6 million in BTC longs were liquidated, a relatively small amount but significant considering the market&#8217;s state. In an illiquid market, smaller orders can significantly sway the market. According to data from Kaiko, BTC and ETH have seen a decline in 90-day realized volatility this year, with volatility levels currently hovering around two-year lows. Related Reading: Bitcoin Crucial Moment: Will Resistance At $29,500 Trigger A Sell-Off Or Surge? Moreover, Kaiko&#8217;s data also reveals that Bitcoin&#8217;s correlation with the S&#38;P 500 continued to decline in July, falling to just 3%. The last time it was this low was back in August 2021. This suggests that the traditional financial market&#8217;s influence on Bitcoin&#8217;s price is waning, an impulse much needed at the moment. Analyst @52Skew noted that BTC Spot CVDs &#38; Delta Retrospective were hinting at the downtrend. “There were clear signs of spot supply &#38; sellers, especially on Coinbase. Aggregate Spot CVD indicated heavy supply prior to sell off: Price grinding higher into limit supply &#38; market spot selling.” Meanwhile, renowned trader @exitpumpBTC pointed out on Twitter: &#8220;Someone sitting with 400 BTC buy wall at $28,900 on Binance spot orderbook. Fully closed my short.&#8221; This buy wall might provide some support for Bitcoin&#8217;s price at the current level. Bitcoin Market Sentiment Weighs On Price The Bitcoin Market Sentiment, as represented by the Fear &#38; Greed Index, is presently at 50 &#8211; neutral. However, the sentiment on the Bitcoin and crypto market is lukewarm, despite BTC being up 76% year-to-date. The fading momentum seems to be due to the Bitcoin and crypto market&#8217;s current &#8220;summer slumber.&#8221; The bullish news seems already priced in, and volumes on exchanges are dwindling. Related Reading: US Presidential Candidate Defends Bitcoin, Calls Out Environmental Critics Interestingly, despite some major bullish developments for the broader crypto market, including Blackrock&#8217;s filing for a spot ETF and the victory for XRP and Ripple, the retail and institutional interest remains low. This is reflected in the low liquidity and volatility in the market. Remarkably, the crypto space has been rocked by an array of events recently. From the rise of liquidity absorbing meme coins to scam tokens, the market has seemingly descended into chaos. In the midst of all these, impending events such as the Curve (CRV) hack as well as fears of a potential DOJ action against Binance and Tether, continue to add anxiety to the market. In this uncertain state, there are no new investors to catapult the market upward. At press time, BTC traded at $28,990. Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Today, Bitcoin took another dive, this time to its lowest level since June 21. A check on Bitfinex reveals a BTC price slump to $28,641. Coinbase, America&#8217;s largest crypto exchange, reported an even more drastic drop to $28,478. Although the price bounced back slightly to hover just below $29,000 (-1.4% in the last 24 hours), the downward trend sparks questions.</p>
<h2>Why Is The Bitcoin Price On The Decline?</h2>
<p>James V. Straten, a renowned on-chain analyst, recently <a href="https://twitter.com/jimmyvs24/status/1686296156920238080" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">tweeted</a>: &#8220;Bitcoin drops below $29,000 as open interest spikes while funding rates go lower. As a result of the biggest long liquidation since 24th July.&#8221; As the analyst states, Bitcoin&#8217;s price trend can be majorly attributed to long liquidations. The liquidation data from Coinglass indicates that $23.6 million in BTC longs were liquidated, a relatively small amount but significant considering the market&#8217;s state.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-545350 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot-2023-08-01-190638.png?resize=3455%2C960" alt="Bitcoin liquidations" width="3455" height="960" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot-2023-08-01-190638.png?resize=3455%2C960?w=3455 3455w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot-2023-08-01-190638.png?resize=3455%2C960?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot-2023-08-01-190638.png?resize=3455%2C960?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot-2023-08-01-190638.png?resize=3455%2C960?w=860 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot-2023-08-01-190638.png?resize=3455%2C960?w=1536 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot-2023-08-01-190638.png?resize=3455%2C960?w=2048 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot-2023-08-01-190638.png?resize=3455%2C960?w=750 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot-2023-08-01-190638.png?resize=3455%2C960?w=1140 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot-2023-08-01-190638.png?resize=3455%2C960?w=3000 3000w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" data-recalc-dims="1"/>
<p>In an illiquid market, smaller orders can significantly sway the market. According to data from Kaiko, BTC and ETH have seen a decline in 90-day realized volatility this year, with volatility levels currently hovering around two-year lows.</p>

<p>Moreover, Kaiko&#8217;s data also reveals that Bitcoin&#8217;s correlation with the S&amp;P 500 continued to decline in July, falling to just 3%. The last time it was this low was back in August 2021. This suggests that the traditional financial market&#8217;s influence on Bitcoin&#8217;s price is waning, an impulse much needed at the moment.</p>
<p>Analyst @52Skew <a href="https://twitter.com/52kskew" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">noted</a> that BTC Spot CVDs &amp; Delta Retrospective were hinting at the downtrend. “There were clear signs of spot supply &amp; sellers, especially on Coinbase. Aggregate Spot CVD indicated heavy supply prior to sell off: Price grinding higher into limit supply &amp; market spot selling.”</p>
<p>Meanwhile, renowned trader @exitpumpBTC <a href="https://twitter.com/exitpumpBTC" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">pointed</a> out on Twitter: &#8220;Someone sitting with 400 BTC buy wall at $28,900 on Binance spot orderbook. Fully closed my short.&#8221; This buy wall might provide some support for Bitcoin&#8217;s price at the current level.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Market Sentiment Weighs On Price</h2>
<p>The Bitcoin Market Sentiment, as represented by the Fear &amp; Greed Index, is presently at 50 &#8211; neutral. However, the sentiment on the Bitcoin and crypto market is lukewarm, despite BTC being up 76% year-to-date. The fading momentum seems to be due to the Bitcoin and crypto market&#8217;s current &#8220;summer slumber.&#8221; The bullish news seems already priced in, and volumes on exchanges are dwindling.</p>

<p>Interestingly, despite some major bullish developments for the broader crypto market, including Blackrock&#8217;s <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/coinbase/coinbase-stock-soars-as-blackrock-reveals-partnership/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">filing</a> for a spot ETF and the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/large-exchanges-relist-xrp/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">victory</a> for XRP and Ripple, the retail and institutional interest remains low. This is reflected in the low liquidity and volatility in the market.</p>
<p>Remarkably, the crypto space has been rocked by an array of events recently. From the rise of liquidity absorbing meme coins to scam tokens, the market has seemingly descended into chaos. In the midst of all these, impending events such as the Curve (CRV) <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/ethereum-defi-coins-plunge-curve-concerns-crash/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">hack</a> as well as fears of a potential DOJ action against Binance and Tether, continue to add anxiety to the market. In this uncertain state, there are no new investors to catapult the market upward.</p>
<p>At press time, BTC traded at $28,990.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-545353 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD_2023-08-01_19-22-55.png?resize=3628%2C1672" alt="Bitcoin price" width="3628" height="1672" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD_2023-08-01_19-22-55.png?resize=3628%2C1672?w=3628 3628w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD_2023-08-01_19-22-55.png?resize=3628%2C1672?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD_2023-08-01_19-22-55.png?resize=3628%2C1672?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD_2023-08-01_19-22-55.png?resize=3628%2C1672?w=860 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD_2023-08-01_19-22-55.png?resize=3628%2C1672?w=1536 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD_2023-08-01_19-22-55.png?resize=3628%2C1672?w=2048 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD_2023-08-01_19-22-55.png?resize=3628%2C1672?w=750 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD_2023-08-01_19-22-55.png?resize=3628%2C1672?w=1140 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD_2023-08-01_19-22-55.png?resize=3628%2C1672?w=3000 3000w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" data-recalc-dims="1"/>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/iStock-1403389740.jpg?fit=460%2C259" width="460" height="259" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">545291</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Investor Sentiment Flips Toward Greed Despite Fall Below $29,000</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-investor-sentiment-flips-toward-greed-despite-fall-below-29000/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Best Owie]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 17:01:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=545323</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Amid the turbulence, the Bitcoin price has finally fallen below the $29,000 support. This decline points to the bears taking over the market, but investor sentiment has not swung the way it normally would in such circumstances. Instead of swinging toward bearish momentum, investors are rather leaning toward greed, suggesting that they do not expect this decline to last. Bitcoin Fear &#38; Greed Index Moves Toward Greed The Bitcoin Fear &#38; Greed Index measures investor sentiment toward the market by taking into account things like surveys, social media posts, market volume, and volatility, among others. The aggregate of these metrics is then used to determine if investors are feeling bearish or bullish. Related Reading: Litecoin Sharks Buy More Than 200,000 LTC Ahead Of Wednesday’s Halving The scale goes from 1-100 with 1-25 standing for extreme fear, 26-47 means fear, 54-75 means greed, and 76-100 represents extreme greed. The 48-53 level represents neutral sentiment, which is where the index has been for the last week. The direction in which the index points toward neutral is of interest here. On Monday, the index was sitting at a completely neutral score of 50. However, by Tuesday, the index is now sitting at a neutral score of 53. This move from 50 to 53 indicates that despite the price of BTC falling below $29,000, investors are still viewing it in a positive light. Otherwise, the index would’ve fallen below 50. Fear &#38; Greed Index sitting at 53 &#124; Source: alternative.me Given this, the chances that the current decline will not last long are high. This is because investors being bullish about BTC means they’re likely to put more money into it. Once such buying pressure begins to mount, then BTC could recover above $29,000 once more. Attention Remains On BTC On Monday, Bitcoinist reported an 82% spike in Bitcoin’s daily trading volume, indicating renewed interest in the digital asset. This saw BTC’s trading volume climb to $10.8 billion, but the cryptocurrency has still not slowed down. BTC’s daily trading volume also saw another significant jump on Tuesday, rising 22% in the 24-hour period. This brought the digital asset’s daily volume to $13.4 billion at the time of writing. This continuous rise reiterates the rising interest in the asset, showing that the move in the Fear &#38; Greed Index toward the greed territory is not a fluke. Related Reading: Cardano (ADA) Price Remains Muted Despite Significant Milestones, Why? The volumes could point to accumulation among investors. And if this is the case, then BTC will likely recover over $29,000. A recovery above this mark would put the digital asset back on track to retest the $30,000 resistance before the weekend. BTC price falls below $29,000 support &#124; Source: BTCUSD on Tradingview.com Follow Best Owie on Twitter for market insights, updates, and the occasional funny tweet… Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="p2">Amid the turbulence, the Bitcoin price has finally fallen below the $29,000 support. This decline points to the bears taking over the market, but investor sentiment has not swung the way it normally would in such circumstances. Instead of swinging toward bearish momentum, investors are rather leaning toward greed, suggesting that they do not expect this decline to last.</p>
<h2 class="p2">Bitcoin Fear &amp; Greed Index Moves Toward Greed</h2>
<p class="p2">The Bitcoin <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/crypto/crypto-fear-greed-index-drops-to-one-month-low-heres-what-it-means/?swcfpc=1">Fear &amp; Greed Index</a> measures investor sentiment toward the market by taking into account things like surveys, social media posts, market volume, and volatility, among others. The aggregate of these metrics is then used to determine if investors are feeling bearish or bullish.</p>

<p class="p2">The scale goes from 1-100 with 1-25 standing for extreme fear, 26-47 means fear, 54-75 means greed, and 76-100 represents extreme greed. The 48-53 level represents neutral sentiment, which is where the index has been for the last week. The direction in which the index points toward neutral is of interest here.</p>
<p class="p2">On Monday, the index was sitting at a completely neutral score of 50. However, by Tuesday, the index is now sitting at a neutral score of 53. This move from 50 to 53 indicates that despite the price of BTC falling below $29,000, investors are still viewing it in a positive light. Otherwise, the index would’ve fallen below 50.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-247644 aligncenter" src="https://i0.wp.com/bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot-2023-08-01-at-14.33.50.png?resize=640%2C292&#038;ssl=1" alt="Bitcoin Fear &amp; Greed Index" width="640" height="292"  data-recalc-dims="1"/></p>

<p class="p2">Given this, the chances that the current decline will not last long are high. This is because investors being bullish about BTC means they’re likely to put more money into it. Once such buying pressure begins to mount, then BTC could recover above $29,000 once more.</p>
<h2 class="p2">Attention Remains On BTC</h2>
<p class="p2">On Monday, <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/author/owiebest/" rel="nofollow">Bitcoinist reported </a>an 82% spike in Bitcoin’s daily trading volume, indicating renewed interest in the digital asset. This saw BTC’s trading volume climb to $10.8 billion, but the cryptocurrency has still not slowed down.</p>
<p class="p2"><a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/bitcoin/" rel="nofollow">BTC’s daily trading volume also saw another significant jump on Tuesday</a>, rising 22% in the 24-hour period. This brought the digital asset’s daily volume to $13.4 billion at the time of writing. This continuous rise reiterates the rising interest in the asset, showing that the move in the Fear &amp; Greed Index toward the greed territory is not a fluke.</p>

<p class="p2">The volumes could point to accumulation among investors. And if this is the case, then BTC will likely recover over $29,000. A recovery above this mark would put the digital asset back on track to retest the $30,000 resistance before the weekend.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/7h5DcUnI/" alt="Bitcoin (BTC)  price chart from Tradingview.com" width="2884" height="1746"/></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/iStock-1220738671.jpg?fit=460%2C307" width="460" height="307" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">545323</post-id>	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
