<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
>

<channel>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.newsbtc.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<description>Bitcoin &#38; Cryptocurrency News Today</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 14:48:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>OKX Liquid Marketplace Records Over $3 Billion In Institutional Trade Volume</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/crypto/okx-liquid-marketplace-records-3-billion-in-trade-volume/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Opeyemi Sule]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 16:00:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[futures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[OKB]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[OKX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Perpetuals]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=540581</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Institutional trade volume on the OKX Liquid Marketplace has surpassed $3 billion, the second-largest crypto exchange by trading volume announced on Friday. The Liquid Marketplace is an on-demand liquidity network for professional and institutional traders. This platform allows traders to send requests for quotes (RFQs) to market makers for large digital asset transactions.  OKX Liquid Marketplace Experiences Rapid Growth In Q2 In a press release on Friday, OKX announced that its Liquid Marketplace has now exceeded $3 billion. “This milestone is a testament to the Liquid Marketplace&#8217;s success in providing institutional traders with deep liquidity and reliable execution,” the press statement read. Related Reading: Whales Dive Into XRP, Accumulating $170 Million Worth: What’s Their Game Plan? In April 2023, OKX revealed that the institutional Liquid Marketplace recorded over $1 billion in trading volume in the first quarter of 2023. As of now &#8211; the end of June and 2023 Q2, this figure has more than tripled, surpassing the $3 billion mark. Furthermore, the Liquid Marketplace has been advancing in innovation and product development lately. A few days ago, OKX disclosed the launch of the “Nitro Spreads” feature on the institutional trading platform. Nitro Spreads allows professional and institutional traders to make complex basis trades in a single click. Basis trading refers to trading the difference between an asset’s price on two distinct markets, such as spot vs futures, to generate profits.  This type of trading can be cumbersome, as it usually requires both legs of the trade to be executed simultaneously. However, Nitro Spreads automates this process by executing the two legs of the trade via a central orderbook. On the Liquid Marketplace, traders can use the feature across any combination of the spot, perpetual, and futures markets. OKB Price Slows Down, Makes No Significant Movement In The Past Week While the OKX ecosystem has been surrounded by positivity in recent days, this has not been reflected in the price of OKB, the exchange’s native token. The coin has not registered any loss or gain in the past seven days, according to CoinGecko data. That said, the OKB token appears to be losing the momentum that pushed its price by nearly 13% in the previous week. The cryptocurrency has also not made any significant price movement since then. Related Reading: Bitcoin Price Stalls Below $31,000, Is The Best Time To Buy Next Monday? Price data reveals that OKB has been in a ranging market in the past few months, trading between the $55 and $40 price points. Since reaching a yearly high of $57.98, the cryptocurrency’s price has decreased by roughly 23%. As of this writing, the OKB token changes hands at $44.53, representing a 2.6% price increase in the last 24 hours. Meanwhile, the coin has a 24-hour trading volume of more than $6 million, with a 33.7% increase in the last day. OKBUSD trading at $44.391 &#124; Source: OKBUSD chart from TradingView Featured image from OKX, chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Institutional trade volume on the OKX Liquid Marketplace has surpassed $3 billion, the second-largest crypto exchange by trading volume announced on Friday.</p>
<p>The Liquid Marketplace is an on-demand liquidity network for professional and institutional traders. This platform allows traders to send requests for quotes (RFQs) to market makers for large digital asset transactions. </p>
<h2>OKX Liquid Marketplace Experiences Rapid Growth In Q2</h2>
<p>In a <a href="https://www.globenewswire.com/news-release/2023/06/30/2697553/0/en/Flash-News-OKX-Liquid-Marketplace-Exceeds-Over-USD-3-Billion-in-Institutional-Trading-Volume.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">press release</a> on Friday, OKX announced that its Liquid Marketplace has now exceeded $3 billion. “This milestone is a testament to the Liquid Marketplace&#8217;s success in providing institutional traders with deep liquidity and reliable execution,” the press statement read.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/whales-dive-into-xrp-accumulating-170-million-worth-whats-their-game-plan/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Whales Dive Into XRP, Accumulating $170 Million Worth: What’s Their Game Plan?</a></p>
<p>In April 2023, OKX revealed that the institutional Liquid Marketplace recorded over $1 billion in trading volume in the first quarter of 2023. As of now &#8211; the end of June and 2023 Q2, this figure has more than tripled, surpassing the $3 billion mark.</p>
<p>Furthermore, the Liquid Marketplace has been advancing in innovation and product development lately. A few days ago, OKX disclosed the <a href="https://www.okx.com/learn/okx-liquid-marketplace-launches-nitro-spreads-one-click-basis-trading" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">launch of the “Nitro Spreads”</a> feature on the institutional trading platform.</p>
<p>Nitro Spreads allows professional and institutional traders to make complex basis trades in a single click. Basis trading refers to trading the difference between an asset’s price on two distinct markets, such as spot vs futures, to generate profits. </p>
<p>This type of trading can be cumbersome, as it usually requires both legs of the trade to be executed simultaneously. However, Nitro Spreads automates this process by executing the two legs of the trade via a central orderbook. On the Liquid Marketplace, traders can use the feature across any combination of the spot, perpetual, and futures markets.</p>
<h2>OKB Price Slows Down, Makes No Significant Movement In The Past Week</h2>
<p>While the OKX ecosystem has been surrounded by positivity in recent days, this has not been reflected in the price of OKB, the exchange’s native token. The coin has not registered any loss or gain in the past seven days, according to <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/okb" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">CoinGecko data</a>.</p>
<p>That said, the OKB token appears to be losing the momentum that pushed its price by nearly 13% in the previous week. The cryptocurrency has also not made any significant price movement since then.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-stalls-31000-best-time-to-buy-next-monday/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Bitcoin Price Stalls Below $31,000, Is The Best Time To Buy Next Monday?</a></p>
<p>Price data reveals that OKB has been in a ranging market in the past few months, trading between the $55 and $40 price points. Since reaching a yearly high of $57.98, the cryptocurrency’s price has decreased by roughly 23%.</p>
<p>As of this writing, the OKB token changes hands at $44.53, representing a 2.6% price increase in the last 24 hours. Meanwhile, the coin has a 24-hour trading volume of more than $6 million, with a 33.7% increase in the last day.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/FrqbLgA0/" alt="OKX" width="1009" height="591"/></p>





]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/07104210-2048x1152-1-460x259.jpg" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum Classic (ETC) Resumes Uptrend, Notches 13% In The Last Day</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/etc/ethereum-classic-etc-resumes-uptrend-notches-13-in-the-last-day/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Semilore Faleti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 15:00:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[ETC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum Classic]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=540582</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Ethereum Classic (ETC) is currently experiencing a rise in its market price, gaining 13.99% in the last 24 hours, according to data from CoinMarketCap.  Following the ETC’s dip in the last two days, it appears the bulls have retaken control of the market, pushing the coin to trade above the $20 mark for the first time since April. ETC&#8217;s Price Action In June Ethereum Classic has found a place among the headlines in the last two weeks following its initial bearish form at the start of June.  ETC began the month trading around $18.01 before experiencing a nosedive which saw the token trade as low as $13.99 on June 10. Related Reading: Litecoin Up 18% In Past 24 Hours, Is Halving Rally Here? Thereafter, ETC would rise to $15.03 and hover around this price region for the next few days before embarking on a bullish run that to gain by 28.60% between June 20 and June 24, hitting the price resistance level at $19.33.  The following days would then present a mixed price action before ETC finally retraced to its key support level at $17.64 on June 29. After retesting at this price zone, ETC’s price has resumed its uptrend, climbing higher since then. Ethereum Classic (ETC) remains one of the major projects in the cryptocurrency space. Launched in July 2016, Ethereum Classic is a hard fork of Ethereum created to preserve the purpose and integrity of the original Ethereum network.  At the time of writing, ETC is exchanging hands at  $20.90, with a 1.51% gain in the last hour. The token’s 24-hour trading volume is currently valued at $482 million, having also gone up by 208.92%. ETC Trading At $21.03 On The 1-Hour Chart &#124; Source: ETCUSD Chart On Tradingview.com ETC Price Analysis And Prediction Looking at the ETC’s hourly chart, its Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD) remains well above the signal line indicating the token’s bullish run may still be on.  However, its Relative Strength Index (RSI) is currently in the overbought zone at 89.71, meaning a selling pressure may soon occur, which may drive down the token’s price. Related Reading: Ethereum Continues Uptrend As Staked ETH Soars To New High According to the prediction site, WalletInvestor, if the bulls manage to sustain buying pressure, ETC’s price would experience only a small rise reaching the market value of $21.42 in 14 days. However, if the reverse is the case, and ETC falls under bearish pressure, the team predicts the token to fall to a market price of $18.00.  That said, most of the crypto markets are also on an uptrend alongside Ethereum Classic (ETC). Market leader Bitcoin (BTC) is up by 0.87% in the last day, while other notable coins such as Cardano (ADA) and Solana (SOL) are also gaining by 7.41% and 6.72%, respectively. Featured Image: The Guardian Nigeria, chart from Tradingview.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ethereum Classic (ETC) is currently experiencing a rise in its market price, gaining 13.99% in the last 24 hours, according to <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/ethereum-classic/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">data from CoinMarketCap</a>. </p>
<p>Following the ETC’s dip in the last two days, it appears the bulls have retaken control of the market, pushing the coin to trade above the $20 mark for the first time since April.</p>
<h2>ETC&#8217;s Price Action In June</h2>
<p>Ethereum Classic has found a place among the headlines in the last two weeks following its initial bearish form at the start of June.  ETC began the month trading around $18.01 before experiencing a nosedive which saw the token trade as low as $13.99 on June 10.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/litecoin/litecoin-up-18-in-past-24-hours-is-halving-rally-here/" target="_blank" rel="noopener "> Litecoin Up 18% In Past 24 Hours, Is Halving Rally Here?</a></p>
<p>Thereafter, ETC would rise to $15.03 and hover around this price region for the next few days before embarking on a bullish run that to gain by 28.60% between June 20 and June 24, hitting the price resistance level at $19.33. </p>
<p>The following days would then present a mixed price action before ETC finally retraced to its key support level at $17.64 on June 29. After retesting at this price zone, ETC’s price has resumed its uptrend, climbing higher since then.</p>
<p>Ethereum Classic (ETC) remains one of the major projects in the cryptocurrency space. Launched in July 2016, Ethereum Classic is a hard fork of Ethereum created to preserve the purpose and integrity of the original Ethereum network. </p>
<p>At the time of writing, ETC is exchanging hands at  $20.90, with a 1.51% gain in the last hour. The token’s 24-hour trading volume is currently valued at $482 million, having also gone up by 208.92%.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/rVwqf51d/" alt="ETC" width="1480" height="913"/>

<h2>ETC Price Analysis And Prediction</h2>
<p>Looking at the ETC’s hourly chart, its Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD) remains well above the signal line indicating the token’s bullish run may still be on. </p>
<p>However, its Relative Strength Index (RSI) is currently in the overbought zone at 89.71, meaning a selling pressure may soon occur, which may drive down the token’s price.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/ethereum/ethereum-continues-uptrend-as-staked-eth-soars-to-new-high/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Ethereum Continues Uptrend As Staked ETH Soars To New High</a></p>
<p style="text-align: left">According to the prediction site,<a href="https://walletinvestor.com/forecast/ethereum-classic-prediction" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow"> WalletInvestor</a>, if the bulls manage to sustain buying pressure, ETC’s price would experience only a small rise reaching the market value of $21.42 in 14 days.</p>
<p>However, if the reverse is the case, and ETC falls under bearish pressure, the team predicts the token to fall to a market price of $18.00. </p>
<p>That said, most of the crypto markets are also on an uptrend alongside Ethereum Classic (ETC). Market leader Bitcoin (BTC) is up by 0.87% in the last day, while other notable coins such as Cardano (ADA) and Solana (SOL) are also gaining by 7.41% and 6.72%, respectively.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/stocks-897x598-1-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance Survey Says 88% Of Institutional Users Have a Positive Outlook For Crypto Assets</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/crypto/binance-survey-says-88-of-institutional-users-have-a-positive-outlook-for-crypto-assets/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance survey]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto investment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Institutional Investors]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=540573</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Institutional investors are paying more attention to cryptocurrencies and digital assets. According to a recent survey report by Binance Research and Binance VIP &#38; Institutional, 88% of institutional users have a long-term, optimistic outlook on crypto for the next decade. The crypto market is known for its high volatility, but the majority of big-money players see crypto as an important part of their portfolio for years to come. Institutional Interest In Crypto Assets Is Growing The Institutional Crypto Outlook Survey, which surveyed 208 Binance VIP and Institutional users from 31st March to 15th May 2023, found out that a growing number of institutional crypto investors are in it for the long haul. According to the survey, 63.5% of these users had a positive outlook on digital assets over the next 12 months, while 88% are more positive over the next decade. Related Reading: Ethereum Continues Uptrend As Staked ETH Soars To New High Of the respondents, 50% expect to increase their crypto asset exposure over the next five years. Only 4.3% said they plan to decrease exposure. That signals a lot of confidence and optimism about the future growth and mainstream adoption of cryptocurrencies. Bitcoin remains Most Popular Crypto Asset Among Institutions Bitcoin remains the most popular choice among institutional investors, with a larger proportion of respondents more positive about Bitcoin as compared to the broader crypto sector. This is not surprising given that Bitcoin is the largest crypto by market cap and the most established. Bitcoin is seen as the &#8220;digital gold&#8221; of the crypto world and a store of value and hedge against inflation. BTC crosses $31,000 as institutional interest grows &#124; Source: BTCUSD on TradingView.com 42.8% of investors are more interested in the potential for large investment returns. However, 37.5% are more motivated by the long-term exposure to the technology behind digital assets, with 48.1% and 43.8% of respondents investing in Layer 1 and Layer 2 technologies respectively. Institutional Trade Still Mostly Done On Centralized Exchanges Centralized exchanges remain the most popular platform for institutional trading. While many crypto investors advocate for decentralized exchanges on the rise, centralized exchanges like Binance offer a one-stop shop for institutional traders to easily buy, sell and convert a wide range of cryptocurrencies. The survey found that 90.5% of institutional investors would rather trade on centralized exchanges. Related Reading: Whales Dive Into XRP, Accumulating $170 Million Worth: What’s Their Game Plan? While some institutional investors remain skeptical about cryptocurrency, it&#8217;s clear that mainstream interest in this asset class is building steadily. If institutional adoption continues to rise, it&#8217;s likely to drive broader mainstream acceptance of cryptocurrencies in financial institutions like banks. Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Institutional investors are paying more attention to cryptocurrencies and digital assets. According to a recent survey report by Binance Research and Binance VIP &amp; Institutional, 88% of institutional users have a long-term, optimistic outlook on crypto for the next decade. </p>
<p>The crypto market is known for its high volatility, but the majority of big-money players see crypto as an important part of their portfolio for years to come.</p>
<h2>Institutional Interest In Crypto Assets Is Growing</h2>
<p>The Institutional Crypto Outlook Survey, which surveyed 208 Binance VIP and Institutional users from 31st March to 15th May 2023, found out that a growing number of institutional crypto investors are in it for the long haul. According to the <a href="https://research.binance.com/en/analysis/institutional-crypto-outlook-survey-2023" rel="nofollow">survey</a>, 63.5% of these users had a positive outlook on digital assets over the next 12 months, while 88% are more positive over the next decade.</p>

<p>Of the respondents, 50% expect to increase their crypto asset exposure over the next five years. Only 4.3% said they plan to decrease exposure. That signals a lot of confidence and optimism about the future growth and mainstream adoption of cryptocurrencies.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin remains Most Popular Crypto Asset Among Institutions</h2>
<p>Bitcoin remains the most popular choice among institutional investors, with a larger proportion of respondents more positive about Bitcoin as compared to the broader crypto sector. This is not surprising given that Bitcoin is the largest crypto by market cap and the most established. Bitcoin is seen as the &#8220;digital gold&#8221; of the crypto world and a store of value and hedge against inflation.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/r9xkCXXs/" alt="Bitcoin price chart from TradingView.com (Crypto)" width="2884" height="1724"/></p>

<p>42.8% of investors are more interested in the potential for large investment returns. However, 37.5% are more motivated by the long-term exposure to the technology behind digital assets, with 48.1% and 43.8% of respondents investing in Layer 1 and Layer 2 technologies respectively.</p>
Institutional Trade Still Mostly Done On Centralized Exchanges
<p>Centralized exchanges remain the most popular platform for institutional trading. While many crypto investors advocate for decentralized exchanges on the rise, centralized exchanges like Binance offer a one-stop shop for institutional traders to easily buy, sell and convert a wide range of cryptocurrencies. The survey found that 90.5% of institutional investors would rather trade on centralized exchanges.</p>

<p>While some institutional investors remain skeptical about cryptocurrency, it&#8217;s clear that mainstream interest in this asset class is building steadily. If institutional adoption continues to rise, it&#8217;s likely to drive broader mainstream acceptance of cryptocurrencies in financial institutions like banks.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/sean-pollock-PhYq704ffdA-unsplash-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Litecoin Up 18% In Past 24 Hours, Is Halving Rally Here?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/litecoin/litecoin-up-18-in-past-24-hours-is-halving-rally-here/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hououin Kyouma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 13:05:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Litecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Litecoin Halving]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Litecoin Rally]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ltc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ltc/usd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=540537</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Litecoin has observed a sharp increase of around 18% during the past day as the much-anticipated halving is just over a month away now. Litecoin Outperforms Market With A Strong 18% Surge Like most of the wider cryptocurrency market, LTC had enjoyed a sharp rally a week or so back, which had taken its price above the $90 mark. Unlike coins like Bitcoin, however, the asset had failed to maintain at these post-surge levels, as it slid off during the days that followed, until eventually bottoming out at the low $80 level. In the past day, however, tides seem to have rapidly shifted for Litecoin, as the asset is now trading above $101 after registering a sharp growth of 18% during the last 24 hours. The below chart shows how the cryptocurrency has performed recently. Looks like the coin has observed a sharp uptrend today &#124; Source: LTCUSD on TradingView As you can see in the graph, Litecoin was around the $81 level only a couple of days back. This latest turnaround for the asset has meant that it has now surpassed the high registered around the start of the month. In terms of daily returns, LTC has outperformed almost all the top 20 cryptocurrencies by market cap; Bitcoin Cash (BCH) is the only exception with its whopping 26% gains in the same period. Related Reading: Stablecoin Cap Shows Early Sign Of Reversal, Why This Could Benefit Bitcoin As analyst Tony &#8220;The Bull&#8221; pointed out on Twitter, Litecoin formed a golden cross just before this surge, as its 50-day moving average (MA) has crossed over its 200-day MA. 2020 it is#Litecoin has golden crossed, days after a death cross Does the rest of history repeat? https://t.co/sGlMhgKE0R pic.twitter.com/CRSaqHSbGt — Tony &#8220;The Bull&#8221; (@tonythebullBTC) June 30, 2023 Interestingly, only a few days ago, the same MAs had also formed a cross of the opposite type: the death cross. The bullish cross canceling this bearish one out merely days later is a pattern similar to the one seen back in 2020, which preceded the bull run. LTC Only Has 34 Days To Go For The Next Halving Litecoin also has a strong bullish narrative coming up in the form of its halving. The &#8220;halving&#8221; is an event where the block rewards of the cryptocurrency are permanently cut in half. As the block rewards are the only way to introduce new LTC into the circulating supply, the halving tightens up its production rate. This increased scarcity is why the event has historically been hyped up as a bullish one. Related Reading: Altcoin Whales Show Highly Active Day, Volatility Incoming? Halvings take place roughly every four years, and the next one is estimated to place on August 3, 2023, which is just 34 days away. It now remains to be seen whether the current price surge will be an extended rally that leads to the halving, or if this is another attempt that would run out of steam before long. Featured image from Michael Förtsch on Unsplash.com, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Litecoin has observed a sharp increase of around 18% during the past day as the much-anticipated halving is just over a month away now.</p>
<h2>Litecoin Outperforms Market With A Strong 18% Surge</h2>
<p>Like most of the wider cryptocurrency market, LTC had enjoyed a <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/litecoin-ltc-bulls-charge-past-91-following-20-rally/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">sharp rally</a> a week or so back, which had taken its price above the $90 mark. Unlike coins like Bitcoin, however, the asset had failed to maintain at these post-surge levels, as it slid off during the days that followed, until eventually bottoming out at the low $80 level.</p>
<p>In the past day, however, tides seem to have rapidly shifted for Litecoin, as the asset is now trading above $101 after registering a sharp growth of 18% during the last 24 hours. The below chart shows how the cryptocurrency has performed recently.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium aligncenter" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/hNWWqH48/" alt="Litecoin Price Chart" width="1534" height="911"/></p>

<p>As you can see in the graph, Litecoin was around the $81 level only a couple of days back. This latest turnaround for the asset has meant that it has now surpassed the high registered around the start of the month.</p>
<p>In terms of daily returns, LTC has outperformed almost all the top 20 cryptocurrencies by market cap; <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin-cash/never-skip-korea-pump-bitcoin-cash-soars-168-10-days/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Bitcoin Cash (BCH)</a> is the only exception with its whopping 26% gains in the same period.</p>

<p>As analyst <a href="https://twitter.com/tonythebullbtc/status/1674573433617764357" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Tony &#8220;The Bull&#8221;</a> pointed out on Twitter, Litecoin formed a golden cross just before this surge, as its 50-day moving average (MA) has crossed over its 200-day MA.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">2020 it is<a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Litecoin?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#Litecoin</a> has golden crossed, days after a death cross</p>
<p>Does the rest of history repeat? <a href="https://t.co/sGlMhgKE0R" rel="nofollow">https://t.co/sGlMhgKE0R</a> <a href="https://t.co/CRSaqHSbGt" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/CRSaqHSbGt</a></p>
<p>— Tony &#8220;The Bull&#8221; (@tonythebullBTC) <a href="https://twitter.com/tonythebullBTC/status/1674573433617764357?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">June 30, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p>Interestingly, only a few days ago, the same MAs had also formed a cross of the opposite type: the death cross. The bullish cross canceling this bearish one out merely days later is a pattern similar to the one seen back in 2020, which preceded the bull run.</p>
<h2>LTC Only Has 34 Days To Go For The Next Halving</h2>
<p>Litecoin also has a strong bullish narrative coming up in the form of its halving. The &#8220;<a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/crypto-analyst-says-bitcoin-has-already-bottomed-sets-halving-price/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">halving</a>&#8221; is an event where the block rewards of the cryptocurrency are permanently cut in half.</p>
<p>As the block rewards are the only way to introduce new LTC into the circulating supply, the halving tightens up its production rate. This increased scarcity is why the event has historically been hyped up as a bullish one.</p>

<p>Halvings take place roughly every four years, and the next one is estimated to place on August 3, 2023, which is just 34 days away. It now remains to be seen whether the current price surge will be an extended rally that leads to the halving, or if this is another attempt that would run out of steam before long.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/michael-fortsch-fYSVVQqiqPs-unsplash-1-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum Continues Uptrend As Staked ETH Soars To New High</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/ethereum/ethereum-continues-uptrend-as-staked-eth-soars-to-new-high/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samuel Edyme]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 12:00:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=540556</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Ethereum network is currently witnessing a surge in interest following the recent Shanghai upgrade, which has expanded the options for holders of Ethereum (ETH). This has resulted in an uptick in the number of people staking their ETH in beacon deposit contracts, an indication of the growing confidence in the Ethereum blockchain since the upgrade. Since the Shanghai upgrade, the quantity of staked ETH has been increasing at a swift pace. This growth recently hit a peak, breaking previous records and suggesting that Ethereum&#8217;s transition to proof-of-stake (PoS) has been received positively by the market. New Era For Ethereum The amount of Ethereum staked has now hit an all-time high (ATH), surpassing 25.8 million ETH, equivalent to a value of over $48 billion, according to the latest data shared by blockchain and crypto industry analytics platform, CryptoRank. Related Reading: Ethereum Staking Hits Over $40 Billion After Shanghai Upgrade: What It Means For ETH This development has caused quite a stir in the crypto community and provides insight into the evolving dynamics of the Ethereum blockchain. Just a month earlier, in late May, the Ethereum deposit contract balance had crossed the $40 billion mark. This upward movement underscores the effectiveness of the new features introduced during Ethereum’s transition from the proof-of-work (PoW) to the PoS consensus mechanism after the Merge upgrade. Furthermore, the impact of the Shanghai upgrade on the Ethereum ecosystem has been profound. The surge in the Ethereum staking ratio since the upgrade is indicative of growing interest and faith in the Ethereum blockchain&#8217;s potential.  This, in turn, reflects on the success of the Shanghai upgrade and the Merge in aligning ETH with market expectations and needs. While the influx of staked ETH steadily rises, Ethereum&#8217;s creator, Vitalik Buterin, has recently expressed concerns regarding the potential strain this could put on the network&#8217;s consensus. In a recent blog post, he urged caution, stating, &#8220;Don’t overload Ethereum’s consensus.&#8221; Buterin went on to emphasize that utilizing Ethereum&#8217;s consensus for diverse functions could introduce elevated systemic threats to the ecosystem and should be actively discouraged. Despite this cautionary advice, there has been no decrease in ETH staking activity, only a consistent increase. Related Reading: LSD Tokens Rally As Ethereum Staking Ramps Up, Here Are The Leaders ETH Continous Upward Trend Over the past 24 hours, ETH has seen a slightly bullish trend, up by 1.4%. The second-largest crypto asset by market capitalization has surged from trading below $1,700 earlier this month to trading as high as $1,890, at the time of writing. Notably, the asset tapped and traded above $1,900 earlier today before slightly retracing to a 24-low of $1,843. Meanwhile, ETH has recorded more than $20 billion added to its market cap over the past two weeks. ETH trading volume has also surged over the same period indicating a rising trading activity. Featured image from Shutterstock, Chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Ethereum network is currently witnessing a surge in interest following the recent Shanghai upgrade, which has expanded the options for holders of <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/ethereum/ethereum-staking-reaches-16-million/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Ethereum (ETH)</a>. This has resulted in an uptick in the number of people staking their ETH in beacon deposit contracts, an indication of the growing confidence in the Ethereum blockchain since the upgrade.</p>
<p>Since the Shanghai upgrade, the quantity of <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/ethereum/ethereum-staking-deposit-plummets-as-shanghai-upgrade-near/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">staked ETH</a> has been increasing at a swift pace. This growth recently hit a peak, breaking previous records and suggesting that Ethereum&#8217;s transition to proof-of-stake (PoS) has been received positively by the market.</p>
<h2>New Era For Ethereum</h2>
<p>The amount of Ethereum staked has now hit an all-time high (ATH), surpassing 25.8 million ETH, equivalent to a value of over $48 billion, according to the latest <a href="https://twitter.com/CryptoRank_io/status/1674433238314668033?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">data</a> shared by blockchain and crypto industry analytics platform, CryptoRank.</p>

<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium wp-image-540558" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/FzzDec4aYAUk26a-460x259.jpeg" alt="Ethereum (ETH) deposit contract value hits ATH." width="460" height="259" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/FzzDec4aYAUk26a-460x259.jpeg 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/FzzDec4aYAUk26a-860x484.jpeg 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/FzzDec4aYAUk26a-768x432.jpeg 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/FzzDec4aYAUk26a-750x422.jpeg 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/FzzDec4aYAUk26a-1140x641.jpeg 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/FzzDec4aYAUk26a.jpeg 1200w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px"/>
<p>This development has caused quite a stir in the crypto community and provides insight into the evolving dynamics of the Ethereum blockchain. Just a month earlier, in late May, the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/ethereum/ethereum-staking-hits-over-40-billion-after-shanghai-upgrade/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Ethereum deposit contract balance had crossed the $40 billion mark</a>. </p>
<p>This upward movement underscores the effectiveness of the new features introduced during Ethereum’s transition from the proof-of-work (PoW) to the PoS consensus mechanism after the Merge upgrade.</p>
<p>Furthermore, the impact of the Shanghai upgrade on the Ethereum ecosystem has been profound. The surge in the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/ethereum/ethereum-staking-takes-a-leap-forward-heres-whats-on-the-horizon/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Ethereum staking</a> ratio since the upgrade is indicative of growing interest and faith in the Ethereum blockchain&#8217;s potential. </p>
<p>This, in turn, reflects on the success of the Shanghai upgrade and the Merge in aligning ETH with market expectations and needs.</p>
<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w" dir="ltr">While the influx of staked ETH steadily rises, Ethereum&#8217;s creator, Vitalik Buterin, has recently expressed concerns regarding the potential strain this could put on the network&#8217;s consensus. In a recent <a href="https://vitalik.ca/general/2023/05/21/dont_overload.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">blog post,</a> he urged caution, stating, &#8220;Don’t overload Ethereum’s consensus.&#8221;</p>
<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w" dir="ltr">Buterin went on to emphasize that utilizing Ethereum&#8217;s consensus for diverse functions could introduce elevated systemic threats to the ecosystem and should be actively discouraged. Despite this cautionary advice, there has been no decrease in ETH staking activity, only a consistent increase.</p>

<h2>ETH Continous Upward Trend</h2>
<p>Over the past 24 hours, ETH has seen a slightly bullish trend, up by 1.4%. The second-largest <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-and-ethereum-supply-plummet-to-record-lows/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">crypto asset</a> by market capitalization has surged from trading below $1,700 earlier this month to trading as high as $1,890, at the time of writing.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/AEmeK6FC/" alt="Ethereum (ETH)’s price chart on TradingView" width="2770" height="1556"/>
<p>Notably, the asset tapped and traded above $1,900 earlier today before slightly retracing to a 24-low of $1,843. Meanwhile, ETH has recorded more than $20 billion added to its market cap over the past two weeks. ETH trading volume has also surged over the same period indicating a rising trading activity.</p>
<p>Featured image from Shutterstock, Chart from TradingView</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ETH-460x297.jpg" width="460" height="297" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Whales Dive Into XRP, Accumulating $170 Million Worth: What&#8217;s Their Game Plan?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/whales-dive-into-xrp-accumulating-170-million-worth-whats-their-game-plan/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samuel Edyme]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 10:30:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrp]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=540418</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The recent downturn in the XRP market has not deterred large-scale investors, often referred to as &#8216;whales&#8217;. Amid a 12% drop in XRP&#8217;s price between June 22 and June 28, they instead saw an opportunity rather than a setback, amassing 360 million XRP worth approximately $170 million. This significant investment demonstrates the high-stake moves that define the crypto markets. While such large-scale purchases are not unusual in the volatile world of cryptocurrencies, this particular accumulation of XRP seems to suggest a confident long-term outlook on the asset by these whales, despite the current bearish trend. #Ripple whales bought the dip! While the price of #XRP dropped 12% from June 22 to June 28, whales bought 360 million $XRP worth nearly $170 million. pic.twitter.com/QI0m45cIio — Ali (@ali_charts) June 29, 2023 XRP Whale Movements Amid Market Fluctuations On June 22, XRP&#8217;s price hit a weekly high of $0.52. But this peak didn&#8217;t last long. The subsequent reversal led to a drop, triggering increased profit-taking as many felt the asset was overvalued. Related Reading: ‘Ripple (XRP) Is A Must-Hold For The Next Bull Run,’ Says Bitcoin Maxi Consequently, XRP has been on a downward slope, breaking key support levels, and presently trades below the earlier $0.5 mark. This puts the asset&#8217;s decline at around 4.3% for the past week. However, the picture is not all gloom and doom. The market capitalization of XRP sits at $24.8 billion, making it the fourth-largest cryptocurrency by market cap. This ranking comes even amid the notable downward pressure. Despite the past week&#8217;s bearish trend, the last 24 hours have shown some signs of recovery for XRP. The token has experienced a slight uptick, gaining 2.1% in price. This positive movement has bolstered the asset&#8217;s market cap by over $500 million, pushing it up from just below $24 billion earlier this month to the current $24.8 billion. Even so, XRP&#8217;s daily trading volume has experienced a significant fall, dropping from the $1 billion mark seen earlier this month to below $600 million in the last 24 hours. The token&#8217;s price has remained somewhat stable, with a 24-hour low of $0.46 and a high of $0.47. Effect On The Market While the whales&#8217; massive XRP purchase is newsworthy, it&#8217;s not the only factor at play. The modest price uptrend could be attributed to an overall slight bullish sentiment reverberating throughout the broader cryptocurrency market. Bitcoin, the front-runner in the crypto space, has also displayed a minor upward trend, which typically influences the performance of other digital assets, including XRP. In this volatile world of cryptocurrencies, it&#8217;s crucial to keep an eye on such significant moves as the ones made by the whales. Their actions could set the stage for what&#8217;s next for XRP and other cryptocurrencies in the weeks and months to come. Ripple Labs has actively sought to have the Security and Executive Commission (SEC) lawsuit against it dismissed, asserting that XRP, unlike conventional securities, operates as a digital currency due to its practical use and decentralized features. The company is challenging the SEC&#8217;s authority in this regard and condemns the regulatory body for not offering clear guidance on the status of XRP as a security. Related Reading: XRP Price Topside Bias Vulnerable Unless It Climbs Above $0.50 Ripple claims that the ongoing legal dispute has adversely affected XRP holders and stifled progress in the cryptocurrency sector. The court&#8217;s ruling on Ripple&#8217;s request for dismissal is eagerly awaited, and it could substantially impact the trajectory of the lawsuit. Should the request be granted, it could significantly undermine the SEC&#8217;s case, but if denied, the legal battle will continue with the SEC&#8217;s charges against Ripple remaining active. Featured image from Shutterstock, Chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The recent downturn in the XRP market has not deterred large-scale investors, often referred to as &#8216;whales&#8217;. Amid a 12% drop in XRP&#8217;s price between June 22 and June 28, they instead <a href="https://twitter.com/ali_charts/status/1674366754322104325?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">saw</a> an opportunity rather than a setback, amassing 360 million XRP worth approximately $170 million. This significant investment demonstrates the high-stake moves that define the crypto markets.</p>
<p>While such large-scale purchases are not unusual in the volatile world of cryptocurrencies, this particular accumulation of XRP seems to suggest a confident long-term outlook on the asset by these whales, despite the current bearish trend.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en"><a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Ripple?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#Ripple</a> whales bought the dip!</p>
<p>While the price of <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/XRP?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#XRP</a> dropped 12% from June 22 to June 28, whales bought 360 million <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24XRP&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$XRP</a> worth nearly $170 million. <a href="https://t.co/QI0m45cIio" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/QI0m45cIio</a></p>
<p>— Ali (@ali_charts) <a href="https://twitter.com/ali_charts/status/1674366754322104325?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">June 29, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<h2>XRP Whale Movements Amid Market Fluctuations</h2>
<p>On June 22, <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/xrp-price-vulnerable-0-50/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">XRP&#8217;s price</a> hit a weekly high of $0.52. But this peak didn&#8217;t last long. The subsequent reversal led to a drop, triggering increased profit-taking as many felt the asset was overvalued.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/ripple-xrp-is-a-must-hold-for-the-next-bull-run-says-bitcoin-maxi/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">‘Ripple (XRP) Is A Must-Hold For The Next Bull Run,’ Says Bitcoin Maxi</a></p>
<p>Consequently, XRP has been on a downward slope, breaking key support levels, and presently trades below the earlier $0.5 mark. This puts the asset&#8217;s decline at around 4.3% for the past week.</p>
<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w" dir="ltr">However, the picture is not all gloom and doom. The market capitalization of XRP sits at $24.8 billion, making it the fourth-largest cryptocurrency by market cap. This ranking comes even amid the notable downward pressure.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Despite the past week&#8217;s bearish trend, the last 24 hours have shown some signs of <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/ripple/ripple-thrives-despite-legal-battle-whats-the-market-reaction-of-xrp/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">recovery for XRP</a>. The token has experienced a slight uptick, gaining 2.1% in price. This positive movement has bolstered the asset&#8217;s market cap by over $500 million, pushing it up from just below $24 billion earlier this month to the current $24.8 billion.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/4qBcmQ3P/" alt="Ripple’s XRP price chart on TradingView" width="2770" height="1556"/>
<p dir="ltr">Even so, XRP&#8217;s daily trading volume has experienced a significant fall, dropping from the $1 billion mark seen earlier this month to below $600 million in the last 24 hours. The token&#8217;s price has remained somewhat stable, with a 24-hour low of $0.46 and a high of $0.47.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Effect On The Market</h2>
<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w" dir="ltr">While the whales&#8217; massive XRP purchase is newsworthy, it&#8217;s not the only factor at play. The modest price uptrend could be attributed to an overall slight bullish sentiment reverberating throughout the broader cryptocurrency market. </p>
<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w" dir="ltr">Bitcoin, the front-runner in the crypto space, has also displayed a minor upward trend, which typically influences the performance of other digital assets, <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/ripple-xrp-is-a-must-hold-for-the-next-bull-run-says-bitcoin-maxi/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">including XRP</a>.</p>
<p dir="ltr">In this volatile world of cryptocurrencies, it&#8217;s crucial to keep an eye on such significant moves as the ones made by the whales. Their actions could set the stage for what&#8217;s next for XRP and other cryptocurrencies in the weeks and months to come.</p>
<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w" dir="ltr">Ripple Labs has actively sought to have the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/ripple/ripple-vs-sec-deaton-verdict-date-xrp-loses-steam/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Security and Executive Commission (SEC) lawsuit</a> against it dismissed, asserting that XRP, unlike conventional securities, operates as a digital currency due to its practical use and decentralized features. The company is challenging the SEC&#8217;s authority in this regard and condemns the regulatory body for not offering clear guidance on the status of XRP as a security.</p>

<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w" dir="ltr">Ripple claims that the ongoing legal dispute has adversely affected XRP holders and stifled progress in the cryptocurrency sector. The court&#8217;s ruling on Ripple&#8217;s request for dismissal is eagerly awaited, and it could substantially impact the trajectory of the lawsuit.</p>
<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w" dir="ltr">Should the request be granted, it could significantly undermine the SEC&#8217;s case, but if denied, the legal battle will continue with the SEC&#8217;s charges against Ripple remaining active.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Featured image from Shutterstock, Chart from TradingView</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/todd-cravens-QnBrjY-nFUs-unsplash-2-460x305.jpg" width="460" height="305" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Arbitrum Gains Tempered By Obstacles, Hindering ARB&#8217;s Further Upswing</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/arbitrum-gains-tempered-by-obstacles-hindering-arbs-further-upswing/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 10:00:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ARB price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Arbitrum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price action]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=540519</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Arbitrum (ARB)&#8217;s gains have been tempered by various challenges, hindering its further upswing. The declining inflows of stablecoins on the Arbitrum network have raised concerns among investors and enthusiasts alike, as it signals potential obstacles for the growth and development of the decentralized finance (DeFi) sector.  As a Layer-2 scaling solution for Ethereum, Arbitrum initially garnered significant attention and saw impressive gains, but recent hurdles have dampened the optimism surrounding its future prospects.  While the decline in stablecoin inflows is a cause for worry, there are potential avenues for growth that could help revive Arbitrum&#8217;s momentum.  Source: Coingecko Resilient Growth Amidst Volatility: ARB Performance Despite facing market volatility, both the Arbitrum protocol and its native token, ARB, have demonstrated remarkable growth. CoinGecko reports ARB&#8217;s current price at $1.14, showcasing a 0.9% rally over the past 24 hours and an encouraging seven-day gain of 3.3%. Related Reading: Solana Makes A Comeback: 15% Rally Signals Renewed Momentum However, a recent ARB report highlights a notable decline in stablecoin inflows on the Arbitrum platform, raising concerns about its potential impact on the protocol&#8217;s growth trajectory. The decrease in stablecoin inflows may also impact the protocol&#8217;s overall liquidity. Less stablecoins entering circulation may reduce liquidity in the market. Source: DeFiLlama Such a decline could also indicate a waning demand for stablecoin-based activities within the protocol, potentially affecting its position within the DeFi sector. A Path To Growth For Arbitrum Arbitrum recognizes the potential for expansion by engaging in collaboration within the gaming sector, aiming to attract a larger user base and enhance the Total Value Locked (TVL) on its protocol. Recent developments indicate that Reboot Protocol, in a tweet, has announced its partnership with pixelvaut to launch its flagship game on the Arbitrum network. These strategic alliances have the potential to act as catalysts for growth, offering a promising avenue to counterbalance the decline in stablecoin inflows. Exciting to see the #BattlePlan game on #ArbitrumNova 🧡💙 A launch by @rebootgg_ @pixelvault_ Welcome to the ecosystem 🙌 https://t.co/qCubAO8DYu — Arbitrum (💙,🧡) (@arbitrum) June 28, 2023 By capitalizing on collaborations in the gaming sector, Arbitrum seeks to tap into the ever-growing demand for decentralized applications (dApps) and virtual experiences. Related Reading: Dogecoin Faces Downward Pressure – Will DOGE Bulls Avert A Further Slide? Integrating games and related platforms onto the Arbitrum network could attract a new wave of users, expanding the ecosystem and bolstering the TVL. Moreover, such partnerships can contribute to creating a vibrant and diverse DeFi ecosystem on Arbitrum, offsetting the impact of declining stablecoin inflows. Total market cap of cryptocurrencies nearly unchanged at $1.15 trillion. Chart: TradingView.com Despite facing challenges, Arbitrum remains resilient in its price performance, demonstrating growth in both its protocol and ARB token. The decline in stablecoin inflows serves as a call to action for the platform to explore alternative avenues for growth, such as the collaboration in the gaming sector. (This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk). Featured image from DeFi Pulse]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Arbitrum (ARB)&#8217;s gains have been tempered by various challenges, hindering its further upswing. The declining inflows of stablecoins on the Arbitrum network have raised concerns among investors and enthusiasts alike, as it signals potential obstacles for the growth and development of the decentralized finance (DeFi) sector. </p>
<p>As a Layer-2 scaling solution for Ethereum, Arbitrum initially garnered significant attention and saw impressive gains, but recent hurdles have dampened the optimism surrounding its future prospects. </p>
<p>While the decline in stablecoin inflows is a cause for worry, there are potential avenues for growth that could help revive Arbitrum&#8217;s momentum. </p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-540532" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-164.png" alt="" width="1035" height="77" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-164.png 1035w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-164-460x34.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-164-860x64.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-164-768x57.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-164-750x56.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 1035px) 100vw, 1035px"/></p>

<h2><strong>Resilient Growth Amidst Volatility: ARB Performance</strong></h2>
<p>Despite facing market volatility, both the Arbitrum protocol and its native token, ARB, have demonstrated remarkable growth. <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/arb-protocol" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">CoinGecko</a> reports ARB&#8217;s current price at $1.14, showcasing a 0.9% rally over the past 24 hours and an encouraging seven-day gain of 3.3%.</p>

<p>However, a <a href="https://ambcrypto.com/heres-how-stablecoins-might-hinder-arbitrums-growth/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">recent ARB report</a> highlights a notable decline in stablecoin inflows on the Arbitrum platform, raising concerns about its potential impact on the protocol&#8217;s growth trajectory.</p>
<p>The decrease in stablecoin inflows may also impact the protocol&#8217;s overall liquidity. Less stablecoins entering circulation may reduce liquidity in the market.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-540527" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-163.png" alt="" width="878" height="449" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-163.png 878w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-163-460x235.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-163-860x440.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-163-768x393.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-163-750x384.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 878px) 100vw, 878px"/></p>

<p>Such a decline could also indicate a waning demand for stablecoin-based activities within the protocol, potentially affecting its position within the DeFi sector.</p>
<h2><strong>A Path To Growth For Arbitrum</strong></h2>
<p>Arbitrum recognizes the potential for expansion by engaging in collaboration within the gaming sector, aiming to attract a larger user base and enhance the Total Value Locked (TVL) on its protocol.</p>
<p> Recent developments indicate that Reboot Protocol, <a href="https://twitter.com/arbitrum/status/1674187808901038081" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">in a tweet</a>, has announced its partnership with pixelvaut to launch its flagship game on the Arbitrum network. These strategic alliances have the potential to act as catalysts for growth, offering a promising avenue to counterbalance the decline in stablecoin inflows.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Exciting to see the <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/BattlePlan?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#BattlePlan</a> game on <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/ArbitrumNova?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#ArbitrumNova</a> <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f9e1.png" alt="🧡" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f499.png" alt="💙" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /></p>
<p>A launch by <a href="https://twitter.com/rebootgg_?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">@rebootgg_</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/pixelvault_?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">@pixelvault_</a></p>
<p>Welcome to the ecosystem <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f64c.png" alt="🙌" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> <a href="https://t.co/qCubAO8DYu" rel="nofollow">https://t.co/qCubAO8DYu</a></p>
<p>— Arbitrum (<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f499.png" alt="💙" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />,<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f9e1.png" alt="🧡" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />) (@arbitrum) <a href="https://twitter.com/arbitrum/status/1674187808901038081?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">June 28, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p>By capitalizing on collaborations in the gaming sector, Arbitrum seeks to tap into the ever-growing demand for decentralized applications (dApps) and virtual experiences.</p>

<p>Integrating games and related platforms onto the Arbitrum network could attract a new wave of users, expanding the ecosystem and bolstering the TVL. Moreover, such partnerships can contribute to creating a vibrant and diverse DeFi ecosystem on Arbitrum, offsetting the impact of declining stablecoin inflows.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/MxEesAjR/" width="2315" height="1109"/></p>

<p>Despite facing challenges, Arbitrum remains resilient in its price performance, demonstrating growth in both its protocol and ARB token. </p>
<p>The decline in stablecoin inflows serves as a call to action for the platform to explore alternative avenues for growth, such as the collaboration in the gaming sector. </p>
<p><em>(This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk).</em></p>
<p><em>Featured image from DeFi Pulse</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-165-460x274.png" width="460" height="274" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Price Stalls Below $31,000, Is The Best Time To Buy Next Monday?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-stalls-31000-best-time-to-buy-next-monday/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jake Simmons]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 09:20:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bull Market]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[July]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=540483</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Bitcoin and crypto market eagerly observed the expiry of the quarterly BTC and ETH options today (at 8:00 am UTC / 4:00 am EST). It was the second largest in history with a volume of 159,000 BTC options and 1.25 million ETH options with a total value of almost $7 billion. The market was expecting a sharp increase in volatility, but it failed to materialize. In the run-up, the BTC price briefly spiked as high as $31,300 before seeing a pullback towards $30,700. The event has thus pretty much become a nothing burger. Options analysts at Greeks.Live confirmed a few minutes ago that the quarterly expiration has been completed, with more BTC block calls being traded in the last few days, mainly to close and roll positions at the end of the quarter, with ETH being mainly in the order book, adding: With the quarterly expiry, the market has seen a release of positions that have built up in recent months, and options could see a larger shift if the market supports it in July. Although volatility levels have risen this month and market makers are happy to actively buy positions, the downward trend in major term IV is very much in evidence amidst the strong selling pressure from quarterly delivery. What&#8217;s Next For Bitcoin? Today&#8217;s daily close could become extremely important for the Bitcoin price. Today is month-end, quarter-end and the Personal Consumption Expenditure (PCE) price index, the US Federal Reserve&#8217;s preferred inflation gauge, will be released at 8:30 am EST (12:30 pm CET). On Tuesday, the U.S. market is closed for the Fourth of July, Independence Day. Related Reading: Bitcoin Price Key Indicators Suggest A Strengthening Case For Rally To $32K The Personal Consumption Expenditure (PCE) price index is preferred by the Fed because it provides broader coverage of consumer spending, includes chain weighting to accurately track behavioral changes, accounts for the substitution effect, and uses comprehensive data sources. The PCE is therefore considered a more flexible and representative indicator of inflation compared to other indexes such as the Consumer Price Index (CPI). While headline CPI data have looked extremely good in recent months, core inflation has been shown to be very sticky. A lot of focus today will therefore be on core PCE. The expectation for PCE inflation is 3.9% and for core PCE 4.7% year-over-year. A surprise to the downside has the potential to provide a bullish boost to both the traditional financial market as well as the Bitcoin and crypto markets. Related Reading: Dawn For Bitcoin: $5 Billion In Options Expire And Could Push Price Towards $31,000 As renowned analyst @rektcapital writes via Twitter, BTC is positioning itself for a monthly close above a resistance that had rejected the price for the past three months. Currently, BTC is holding above the same level (black). Thus, the monthly as well as the quarterly close could be an extremely bullish harbinger for July. Is The Best Time To Buy Next Monday? Analyst @tedtalksmacro recently published an analysis about Bitcoin&#8217;s historical performance via Twitter. The result may suggest that the upcoming Monday, July 3, is the best option for a Bitcoin buy, at least historically. As the analyst noted, July has been the best performing month since October 2009. However, the data is skewed due to a 10x in July 2010. Taking only the last five years of data, the best performing month is October, closely followed by July. On a weekly basis, Mondays are the best day to buy and hold BTC. This assumes that buyers do not hold BTC on any day other than the nominated one, as the analyst evaluated. At press time, the Bitcoin price hovered below the $31,000 resistance zone, trading at $30,856. Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Bitcoin and crypto market eagerly <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/dawn-for-bitcoin-5-billion-in-options-expire-and-could-push-price-towards-31000/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">observed</a> the expiry of the quarterly BTC and ETH options today (at 8:00 am UTC / 4:00 am EST). It was the second largest in history with a volume of 159,000 BTC options and 1.25 million ETH options with a total value of almost $7 billion.</p>
<p>The market was expecting a sharp increase in volatility, but it failed to materialize. In the run-up, the BTC price briefly spiked as high as $31,300 before seeing a pullback towards $30,700. The event has thus pretty much become a nothing burger.</p>
<p>Options analysts at Greeks.Live confirmed a few minutes ago that the quarterly expiration has been completed, with more BTC block calls being traded in the last few days, mainly to close and roll positions at the end of the quarter, with ETH being mainly in the order book, <a href="https://twitter.com/GreeksLive/status/1674697279838748673" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">adding</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p><strong>With the quarterly expiry, the market has seen a release of positions that have built up in recent months, and options could see a larger shift if the market supports it in July.</strong></p>
<p><strong>Although volatility levels have risen this month and market makers are happy to actively buy positions, the downward trend in major term IV is very much in evidence amidst the strong selling pressure from quarterly delivery. </strong></p></blockquote>
<h2>What&#8217;s Next For Bitcoin?</h2>
<p>Today&#8217;s daily close could become extremely important for the Bitcoin price. Today is month-end, quarter-end and the Personal Consumption Expenditure (PCE) price index, the US Federal Reserve&#8217;s preferred inflation gauge, will be released at 8:30 am EST (12:30 pm CET). On Tuesday, the U.S. market is closed for the Fourth of July, Independence Day.</p>

<p>The Personal Consumption Expenditure (PCE) price index is preferred by the Fed because it provides broader coverage of consumer spending, includes chain weighting to accurately track behavioral changes, accounts for the substitution effect, and uses comprehensive data sources. The PCE is therefore considered a more flexible and representative indicator of inflation compared to other indexes such as the Consumer Price Index (CPI).</p>
<p>While headline CPI data have looked extremely good in recent months, core inflation has been shown to be very sticky. A lot of focus today will therefore be on core PCE. The expectation for PCE inflation is 3.9% and for core PCE 4.7% year-over-year. A surprise to the downside has the potential to provide a bullish boost to both the traditional financial market as well as the Bitcoin and crypto markets.</p>

<p>As renowned analyst @rektcapital <a href="https://twitter.com/rektcapital/status/1674401122465841155" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">writes</a> via Twitter, BTC is positioning itself for a monthly close above a resistance that had rejected the price for the past three months. Currently, BTC is holding above the same level (black). Thus, the monthly as well as the quarterly close could be an extremely bullish harbinger for July.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-540498 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Fzyq3T2XoAAe5dL.jpg" alt="Bitcoin price monthly close" width="1792" height="1264" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Fzyq3T2XoAAe5dL.jpg 1792w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Fzyq3T2XoAAe5dL-460x324.jpg 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Fzyq3T2XoAAe5dL-860x607.jpg 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Fzyq3T2XoAAe5dL-768x542.jpg 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Fzyq3T2XoAAe5dL-1536x1083.jpg 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Fzyq3T2XoAAe5dL-120x86.jpg 120w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Fzyq3T2XoAAe5dL-750x529.jpg 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Fzyq3T2XoAAe5dL-1140x804.jpg 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1792px) 100vw, 1792px"/>
<h2>Is The Best Time To Buy Next Monday?</h2>
<p>Analyst @tedtalksmacro recently <a href="https://twitter.com/tedtalksmacro" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">published</a> an analysis about Bitcoin&#8217;s historical performance via Twitter. The result may suggest that the upcoming Monday, July 3, is the best option for a Bitcoin buy, at least historically.</p>
<p>As the analyst noted, July has been the best performing month since October 2009. However, the data is skewed due to a 10x in July 2010. Taking only the last five years of data, the best performing month is October, closely followed by July.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-540512 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Fz2RiqtWcAAImdG-scaled.jpg" alt="Average Bitcoin return by calendar month" width="2560" height="1193" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Fz2RiqtWcAAImdG-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Fz2RiqtWcAAImdG-460x214.jpg 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Fz2RiqtWcAAImdG-860x401.jpg 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Fz2RiqtWcAAImdG-768x358.jpg 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Fz2RiqtWcAAImdG-1536x716.jpg 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Fz2RiqtWcAAImdG-2048x954.jpg 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Fz2RiqtWcAAImdG-750x349.jpg 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Fz2RiqtWcAAImdG-1140x531.jpg 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px"/>
<p>On a weekly basis, Mondays are the best day to buy and hold BTC. This assumes that buyers do not hold BTC on any day other than the nominated one, as the analyst evaluated.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-540513 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/FzzesipXsAIPCJ4-scaled.jpg" alt="BTC" width="2560" height="1082" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/FzzesipXsAIPCJ4-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/FzzesipXsAIPCJ4-460x195.jpg 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/FzzesipXsAIPCJ4-860x364.jpg 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/FzzesipXsAIPCJ4-768x325.jpg 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/FzzesipXsAIPCJ4-1536x649.jpg 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/FzzesipXsAIPCJ4-2048x866.jpg 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/FzzesipXsAIPCJ4-750x317.jpg 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/FzzesipXsAIPCJ4-1140x482.jpg 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px"/>
<p>At press time, the Bitcoin price hovered below the $31,000 resistance zone, trading at $30,856.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-540521 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSD_2023-06-30_11-00-59.png" alt="Bitcoin price" width="3628" height="1672" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSD_2023-06-30_11-00-59.png 3628w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSD_2023-06-30_11-00-59-460x212.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSD_2023-06-30_11-00-59-860x396.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSD_2023-06-30_11-00-59-768x354.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSD_2023-06-30_11-00-59-1536x708.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSD_2023-06-30_11-00-59-2048x944.png 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSD_2023-06-30_11-00-59-750x346.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSD_2023-06-30_11-00-59-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 3628px) 100vw, 3628px"/>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/iStock-1424482750-460x248.jpg" width="460" height="248" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Solana Makes A Comeback: 15% Rally Signals Renewed Momentum</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/solana-makes-a-comeback-15-rally/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 07:56:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price action]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SOL Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Solana]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=540465</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Solana (SOL) has staged an impressive comeback, igniting renewed momentum in the crypto space with a decent 15% rally. The blockchain platform has been making significant strides as of late, particularly in the realm of non-fungible tokens (NFTs).  Over the past few weeks, Solana&#8217;s NFT trade counts and trade volume have experienced a notable surge, underlining the platform&#8217;s growing popularity among artists, collectors, and enthusiasts. Adding to the excitement, SOL&#8217;s price witnessed a significant uptick in the last 24 hours, further fueling investor interest and cementing its position as one of the most promising cryptocurrencies in the market. Related Reading: Dogecoin Faces Downward Pressure – Will DOGE Bulls Avert A Further Slide? The recent surge in NFT activity on Solana reflects the platform&#8217;s increasing appeal for digital creators seeking efficient and eco-friendly solutions for tokenizing and trading their unique artworks and digital assets. Top Solana Projects by Active Users (Last 7D)@MagicEden$RARI @rarible$MEAN @meanfinance$GARI @Chingari_IN$SBR @Saber_HQ$GENE @genopets@solincinerator@SharkyFi$RAY @RaydiumProtocol$TFMC @tapfantasy2021@dappradar #Solana $SOL pic.twitter.com/n4HTxmMcjA — Solana Daily (@solana_daily) June 28, 2023 Solana&#8217;s Magic Eden Triggers Active Users Surge In a noteworthy update highlighted by Solana Daily, a renowned Twitter account dedicated to sharing updates about the Solana ecosystem, it was revealed that Magic Eden has emerged as the project with the highest number of active users in the past week. This development showcases the growing popularity and adoption of Magic Eden within the Solana community. The blockchain&#8217;s metrics further substantiate this narrative of growth. According to data from Dune, Solana&#8217;s NFTs have observed a significant increase in the total number of transaction counts over the recent weeks. Source: Dune Analytics The increasing level of transaction activity is matched by a corresponding surge in transaction volume, highlighting the growing enthusiasm and involvement in Solana&#8217;s NFT marketplace. SOL up 15.4% in the last 24 hours. Source: Coingecko As a result of these positive developments, SOL, the native cryptocurrency of Solana, has experienced a substantial surge of 15.4% within the past 24 hours alone. CoinGecko reports that SOL&#8217;s price has reached $18.63, consolidating its upward momentum. This consistent climb has persisted over the past seven days, with SOL climbing 11.0%. SOL market cap currently at $7.3 billion. Chart: TradingView.com Altcoin&#8217;s Popularity On The Rise According to a recent report on SOL&#8217;s price, it is evident that the altcoin experienced an increase in popularity over the course of last week. This rise in popularity was reflected in the surge of social volume surrounding the token. As more users engaged in discussions and shared information about SOL on various social media platforms, it became clear that interest in the altcoin was growing steadily. Moreover, SOL&#8217;s weighted sentiment also witnessed an upward trajectory during the same period. This indicates that the overall sentiment surrounding the token was predominantly positive. Investors and enthusiasts expressed optimism and confidence in SOL, which contributed to the overall positive sentiment observed in discussions and sentiment analysis. (This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk). Featured image from Unsplash]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Solana (SOL) has staged an impressive comeback, igniting renewed momentum in the crypto space with a decent 15% rally. The blockchain platform has been making significant strides as of late, particularly in the realm of non-fungible tokens (NFTs). </p>
<p>Over the past few weeks, Solana&#8217;s NFT trade counts and trade volume have experienced a notable surge, underlining the platform&#8217;s growing popularity among artists, collectors, and enthusiasts. </p>
<p>Adding to the excitement, SOL&#8217;s price witnessed a significant uptick in the last 24 hours, further fueling investor interest and cementing its position as one of the most promising cryptocurrencies in the market.</p>

<p>The recent surge in NFT activity on Solana reflects the platform&#8217;s increasing appeal for digital creators seeking efficient and eco-friendly solutions for tokenizing and trading their unique artworks and digital assets.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Top Solana Projects by Active Users (Last 7D)<a href="https://twitter.com/MagicEden?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">@MagicEden</a><a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24RARI&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$RARI</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/rarible?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">@rarible</a><a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24MEAN&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$MEAN</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/meanfinance?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">@meanfinance</a><a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24GARI&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$GARI</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/Chingari_IN?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">@Chingari_IN</a><a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24SBR&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$SBR</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/Saber_HQ?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">@Saber_HQ</a><a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24GENE&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$GENE</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/genopets?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">@genopets</a><a href="https://twitter.com/solincinerator?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">@solincinerator</a><a href="https://twitter.com/SharkyFi?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">@SharkyFi</a><a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24RAY&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$RAY</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/RaydiumProtocol?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">@RaydiumProtocol</a><a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24TFMC&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$TFMC</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/tapfantasy2021?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">@tapfantasy2021</a><a href="https://twitter.com/DappRadar?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">@dappradar</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Solana?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#Solana</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24SOL&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$SOL</a> <a href="https://t.co/n4HTxmMcjA" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/n4HTxmMcjA</a></p>
<p>— Solana Daily (@solana_daily) <a href="https://twitter.com/solana_daily/status/1674024855866408965?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">June 28, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<h2><strong>Solana&#8217;s Magic Eden Triggers Active Users Surge</strong></h2>
<p>In a <a href="https://twitter.com/solana_daily/status/1674024855866408965" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">noteworthy update</a> highlighted by Solana Daily, a renowned Twitter account dedicated to sharing updates about the Solana ecosystem, it was revealed that Magic Eden has emerged as the project with the highest number of active users in the past week. This development showcases the growing popularity and adoption of Magic Eden within the Solana community.</p>
<p>The blockchain&#8217;s metrics further substantiate this narrative of growth. According to <a href="https://dune.com/chuxin/Solana-NFT-Overview?undefined=" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">data from Dune</a>, Solana&#8217;s NFTs have observed a significant increase in the total number of transaction counts over the recent weeks.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-540466" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-160.png" alt="" width="941" height="399" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-160.png 941w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-160-460x195.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-160-860x365.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-160-768x326.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-160-750x318.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 941px) 100vw, 941px"/></p>

<p>The increasing level of transaction activity is matched by a corresponding surge in transaction volume, highlighting the growing enthusiasm and involvement in Solana&#8217;s NFT marketplace.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-540474" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-161.png" alt="" width="1048" height="74" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-161.png 1048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-161-460x32.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-161-860x61.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-161-768x54.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-161-750x53.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 1048px) 100vw, 1048px"/></p>

<p>As a result of these positive developments, SOL, the native cryptocurrency of Solana, has experienced a substantial surge of 15.4% within the past 24 hours alone. </p>
<p><a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/solana/usd" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">CoinGecko</a> reports that SOL&#8217;s price has reached $18.63, consolidating its upward momentum. This consistent climb has persisted over the past seven days, with SOL climbing 11.0%.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/CLUf7X3A/" width="2315" height="1109"/></p>

<h2><strong>Altcoin&#8217;s Popularity On The Rise</strong></h2>
<p>According to a recent <a href="https://ambcrypto.com/solana-attempts-to-regain-momentum-through-nfts/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">report on SOL&#8217;s price</a>, it is evident that the altcoin experienced an increase in popularity over the course of last week. This rise in popularity was reflected in the surge of social volume surrounding the token. </p>
<p>As more users engaged in discussions and shared information about SOL on various social media platforms, it became clear that interest in the altcoin was growing steadily.</p>
<p>Moreover, SOL&#8217;s weighted sentiment also witnessed an upward trajectory during the same period. This indicates that the overall sentiment surrounding the token was predominantly positive. </p>
<p>Investors and enthusiasts expressed optimism and confidence in SOL, which contributed to the overall positive sentiment observed in discussions and sentiment analysis.</p>
<p><em>(This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk).</em></p>
<p><em>Featured image from Unsplash</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-162-460x231.png" width="460" height="231" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Never Skip A Korea Pump? Bitcoin Cash Soars 168% in 10 Days</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin-cash/never-skip-korea-pump-bitcoin-cash-soars-168-10-days/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jake Simmons]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 07:46:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Cash]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BCH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[korea]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[pump]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Roger Ver]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=540460</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Bitcoin Cash (BCH) price has gone through the roof in recent days. Within the last ten days, the Bitcoin fork has risen by a staggering 168%, temporarily BCH was already up over 200% today. While Bitcoin Cash was still trading at $104 on June 20 and was stuck in a deep bull market that looked bad even compared to other altcoins, a miracle occurred 10 days ago. The price exploded out of nowhere. Why Is Bitcoin Cash Experiencing A Revival? As NewsBTC reported, the reasons for the phenomenal rise in BCH&#8217;s price have already been discussed hotly over the past few days. It was often heard that the listing on the new crypto exchange EDX Markets, which is backed by industry giants Citadel Securities, Charles Schwab Corp. and Fidelity Digital Assets, favored BCH. Furthermore, it has been argued that the price increase is also due to Bitcoin Cash&#8217;s recent &#8220;game-changing&#8221; upgrade. In mid-May, Bitcoin Cash underwent a hard fork that not only improved the network&#8217;s security and privacy measures, but also introduced plans for CashTokens. However, the real reasons for the current Bitcoin Cash pump seem to lie elsewhere: namely in South Korea. Chinese crypto journalist Colin Wu reports today that South Korea could be the reason for the BCH pump, looking at where much of the trading volume originates. Related Reading: Kaching! Bitcoin Cash (BCH) Price Explodes Over 100% – What’s Powering It? In the last 24 hours, the largest exchange in South Korea, Upbit, recorded over $350 million in trading volume for BCH/KRW, accounting for 23.58% of the total trading volume for BCH. Moreover, it is also three times the trading volume of BTC/KRW on Upbit &#8211; an anomaly that has extreme rarity. Renowned crypto whale and trader Andrew Kang agrees, stating that the current BCH rally reminds him of the multi-week Aptos (APT) battle between Korean retailers and &#8220;professional traders.&#8221; Never Skip A Korea Pump? &#8220;Koreans didn&#8217;t need a reason to bid, all that mattered is that it kept going up and early bears got slaughtered,&#8221; Kang said. The trader is alluding to APT&#8217;s 500% rally earlier this year. Related Reading: Bitcoin Cash Surges 20% In One Day As Market Rebounds, What’s Next? South Koreans pumped Aptos because of a joke about housing affordability. APT&#8217;s trading volume on the South Korean crypto exchange UpBit was often higher than the total trading volume on Binance at the time. It was also beneficial that the Aptos Foundation marketed the altcoin to Koreans from day one. According to Alex Shin, co-founder of crypto venture capital firm Hashed, South Korean crypto investors took Aptos&#8217; three-letter ticker &#8220;APT&#8221; and turned it into a meme alluding to how absurdly expensive it is to buy an &#8220;apartment&#8221; in South Korea. Asia expert Wu said at the time that &#8220;pumping altcoins is a tradition in the Korean community.&#8221; Kang concluded: &#8220;People are shorting more BCH than there is liquid supply of it. It’s highly illiquid since most of the supply is dead. Imagine fading the original cartel&#8221; and added &#8220;disbelief pump.&#8221; At press time, BCH changed hands for $300 per coin. Featured image from Binance Academy, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Bitcoin Cash (BCH) price has gone through the roof in recent days. Within the last ten days, the Bitcoin fork has risen by a staggering 168%, temporarily BCH was already up over 200% today. While Bitcoin Cash was still trading at $104 on June 20 and was stuck in a deep bull market that looked bad even compared to other altcoins, a miracle occurred 10 days ago. The price exploded out of nowhere.</p>
<h2>Why Is Bitcoin Cash Experiencing A Revival?</h2>
<p>As NewsBTC reported, the reasons for the phenomenal rise in BCH&#8217;s price have already been <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin-cash/kaching-bitcoin-cash-price-explodes-over-100-whats-powering-it/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">discussed</a> hotly over the past few days. It was often heard that the listing on the new crypto exchange EDX Markets, which is backed by industry giants Citadel Securities, Charles Schwab Corp. and Fidelity Digital Assets, favored BCH.</p>
<p>Furthermore, it has been argued that the price increase is also due to Bitcoin Cash&#8217;s recent &#8220;game-changing&#8221; upgrade. In mid-May, Bitcoin Cash underwent a hard fork that not only improved the network&#8217;s security and privacy measures, but also introduced plans for CashTokens.</p>
<p>However, the real reasons for the current Bitcoin Cash pump seem to lie elsewhere: namely in South Korea. Chinese crypto journalist Colin Wu <a href="https://twitter.com/WuBlockchain/status/1674614453231562755" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">reports</a> today that South Korea could be the reason for the BCH pump, looking at where much of the trading volume originates.</p>

<p>In the last 24 hours, the largest exchange in South Korea, Upbit, recorded over $350 million in trading volume for BCH/KRW, accounting for 23.58% of the total trading volume for BCH. Moreover, it is also three times the trading volume of BTC/KRW on Upbit &#8211; an anomaly that has extreme rarity.</p>
<p>Renowned crypto whale and trader Andrew Kang agrees, <a href="https://twitter.com/Rewkang/status/1674520829244080129" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">stating</a> that the current BCH rally reminds him of the multi-week Aptos (APT) battle between Korean retailers and &#8220;professional traders.&#8221;</p>
<h2>Never Skip A Korea Pump?</h2>
<p>&#8220;Koreans didn&#8217;t need a reason to bid, all that mattered is that it kept going up and early bears got slaughtered,&#8221; Kang said. The trader is alluding to APT&#8217;s 500% rally earlier this year.</p>

<p>South Koreans pumped Aptos because of a joke about housing affordability. APT&#8217;s trading volume on the South Korean crypto exchange UpBit was often higher than the total trading volume on Binance at the time. It was also beneficial that the Aptos Foundation marketed the altcoin to Koreans from day one.</p>
<p>According to Alex Shin, co-founder of crypto venture capital firm Hashed, South Korean crypto investors <a href="https://twitter.com/AlexShin/status/1621926598479073280?lang=en" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">took</a> Aptos&#8217; three-letter ticker &#8220;APT&#8221; and turned it into a meme alluding to how absurdly expensive it is to buy an &#8220;apartment&#8221; in South Korea. Asia expert Wu said at the time that &#8220;pumping altcoins is a tradition in the Korean community.&#8221;</p>
<p>Kang concluded: &#8220;People are shorting more BCH than there is liquid supply of it. It’s highly illiquid since most of the supply is dead. Imagine fading the original cartel&#8221; and added &#8220;disbelief pump.&#8221;</p>
<p>At press time, BCH changed hands for $300 per coin.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-540468 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BCHUSD_2023-06-30_09-29-00.png" alt="Bitcoin Cash price " width="3628" height="1672" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BCHUSD_2023-06-30_09-29-00.png 3628w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BCHUSD_2023-06-30_09-29-00-460x212.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BCHUSD_2023-06-30_09-29-00-860x396.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BCHUSD_2023-06-30_09-29-00-768x354.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BCHUSD_2023-06-30_09-29-00-1536x708.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BCHUSD_2023-06-30_09-29-00-2048x944.png 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BCHUSD_2023-06-30_09-29-00-750x346.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BCHUSD_2023-06-30_09-29-00-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 3628px) 100vw, 3628px"/>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/b52bca2ee4cf4badac52e450703b903c-460x259.png" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
