<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
>

<channel>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.newsbtc.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<description>Bitcoin &#38; Cryptocurrency News Today</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 17:15:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Glassnode Co-Founder Predicts Bull Run For Bitcoin Amidst Sideways Trading</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/glassnode-co-founder-predicts-bull-run-for-bitcoin-amidst-sideways-trading/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 18:30:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=541605</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) has been trading within a narrow range for the past 12 days. Nonetheless, the fact that bulls have held the crucial $30,000 support level is seen as a short-term win for them. Even though BTC has been experiencing sideways trading, there is a growing sense of optimism that it has the potential to break through upper resistance zones and reach new highs.  BTC’s Sideways Trading Sets Stage For Bullish Momentum?  According to Yan Alleman, the co-founder of blockchain analytics firm Glassnode, Bitcoin&#8217;s recent sideways trading has paved the way for potential bullish momentum shortly. BTC&#8217;s current range-bound trading between $31,200 and $29,600 is seen as a consolidation period allowing for a re-establishment of bullish momentum in the market. To assess market sentiment and potential price movements in the Bitcoin market, Glassnode has developed a proprietary metric called the Swissblock Risk Signal. This metric considers various factors, including volatility, on-chain activity, social sentiment, and more. Related Reading: CFTC Investigators Conclude Celsius And Former CEO Violated Rules, Potential Case Looms In the context of Alleman&#8217;s analysis, the Swissblock Risk Signal has remained stable at 0, as seen in the chart below, which suggests that the current market sentiment is neutral, with no clear dominance from either buyers or sellers.  This could indicate that the market is in a consolidation phase, as buyers and sellers are cautious before making any significant moves. Additionally, Alleman predicts that BTC will likely break above $31,200, providing a strong foundation for buyers to target resistance levels at $33,000 and $34,800. However, even if the support at $29,600 were to break, Alleman believes that remaining bullish until the 50% retracement level near $28,200 seems viable. This pullback could represent an opportunity for investors to accumulate BTC for the next leap as the market shows signs of potential growth. As such, Alleman&#8217;s analysis suggests that the current market conditions present a favorable opportunity for those looking to invest in Bitcoin. Bitcoin Faces Critical Moment Bitcoin is facing a critical moment as its price fluctuates within a narrow range, warns market analyst Michael Van de Poppe. With Bitcoin&#8217;s lows being taken again, Van de Poppe believes that if it fails to recover soon, it could test support at $28,500. Adding to Bitcoin&#8217;s challenges is the expectation of a rate hike due to positive unemployment data. This leads to increased speculation that the Federal Reserve will raise interest rates sooner than expected. This could create a more challenging economic environment for cryptocurrencies. If both major resistance lines of $29,600 and $28,500 give in to pressure, a potential bull run in the short term could be in danger, potentially resulting in a retracement down to the $27,500 resistance level. This would represent a 9% pullback from the current level of $30,200. Related Reading: Marathon Digital Reports 21% Decline In Bitcoin Production In June If such a scenario were to occur, it could take time for Bitcoin bulls to regain their current levels. In the past, a period of consolidation has typically followed a pullback before any further continuation to regain lost levels. However, despite Bitcoin&#8217;s challenges, as long as it can hold the $30,000 line, BTC bulls have the upper hand. At the time of writing, BTC is trading at $30,200, down a slight 0.3% in the last 24 hours. Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com ]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin (BTC) has been trading within a narrow range for the past 12 days. Nonetheless, the fact that bulls have held the crucial $30,000 support level is seen as a short-term win for them.</p>
<p>Even though BTC has been experiencing sideways trading, there is a growing sense of optimism that it has the potential to break through upper resistance zones and reach new highs. </p>
<h2>BTC’s Sideways Trading Sets Stage For Bullish Momentum? </h2>
<p><a href="https://twitter.com/Negentropic_/status/1676912618487906304?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">According </a>to Yan Alleman, the co-founder of blockchain analytics firm Glassnode, Bitcoin&#8217;s recent sideways trading has paved the way for potential bullish momentum shortly. BTC&#8217;s current range-bound trading between $31,200 and $29,600 is seen as a consolidation period allowing for a re-establishment of bullish momentum in the market.</p>
<p>To assess market sentiment and potential price movements in the Bitcoin market, Glassnode has developed a proprietary metric called the Swissblock Risk Signal. This metric considers various factors, including volatility, on-chain activity, social sentiment, and more.</p>

<p>In the context of Alleman&#8217;s analysis, the Swissblock Risk Signal has remained stable at 0, as seen in the chart below, which suggests that the current market sentiment is neutral, with no clear dominance from either buyers or sellers. </p>
<img decoding="async" class="size-large wp-image-541606" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/F0WXF49WIAIUjmM-860x352.jpg" alt="Bitcoin " width="860" height="352" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/F0WXF49WIAIUjmM-860x352.jpg 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/F0WXF49WIAIUjmM-460x188.jpg 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/F0WXF49WIAIUjmM-768x314.jpg 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/F0WXF49WIAIUjmM-1536x629.jpg 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/F0WXF49WIAIUjmM-2048x839.jpg 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/F0WXF49WIAIUjmM-750x307.jpg 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/F0WXF49WIAIUjmM-1140x467.jpg 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" loading="lazy"/>
<p>This could indicate that the market is in a consolidation phase, as buyers and sellers are cautious before making any significant moves.</p>
<p>Additionally, Alleman predicts that BTC will likely break above $31,200, providing a strong foundation for buyers to target resistance levels at $33,000 and $34,800. However, even if the support at $29,600 were to break, Alleman believes that remaining bullish until the 50% retracement level near $28,200 seems viable.</p>
<p>This pullback could represent an opportunity for investors to accumulate BTC for the next leap as the market shows signs of potential growth. As such, Alleman&#8217;s analysis suggests that the current market conditions present a favorable opportunity for those looking to invest in Bitcoin.</p>
Bitcoin Faces Critical Moment
<p>Bitcoin is facing a critical moment as its price fluctuates within a narrow range, <a href="https://twitter.com/CryptoMichNL/status/1676960412879953920?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">warns </a>market analyst Michael Van de Poppe. With Bitcoin&#8217;s lows being taken again, Van de Poppe believes that if it fails to recover soon, it could test support at $28,500.</p>
<p>Adding to Bitcoin&#8217;s challenges is the expectation of a rate hike due to positive unemployment data. This leads to increased speculation that the Federal Reserve will raise interest rates sooner than expected. This could create a more challenging economic environment for cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p>If both major resistance lines of $29,600 and $28,500 give in to pressure, a potential bull run in the short term could be in danger, potentially resulting in a retracement down to the $27,500 resistance level. This would represent a 9% pullback from the current level of $30,200.</p>

<p>If such a scenario were to occur, it could take time for Bitcoin bulls to regain their current levels. In the past, a period of consolidation has typically followed a pullback before any further continuation to regain lost levels.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/a9ZhhFex/" alt="Bitcoin " width="1814" height="858"/>
<p>However, despite Bitcoin&#8217;s challenges, as long as it can hold the $30,000 line, BTC bulls have the upper hand. At the time of writing, BTC is trading at $30,200, down a slight 0.3% in the last 24 hours.</p>
<p>Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/iStock-1322509303-3-460x259.jpg" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dormant Bitcoin Supply Peaks As Institutional Investors Show Increased Involvement</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/dormant-bitcoin-supply-peaks-as-institutional-investors/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samuel Edyme]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 17:30:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=541590</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[According to recent hedge fund Ark Invest data, a historical amount of the Bitcoin supply has remained dormant for at least a year, with roughly 70% of the circulating supply unmoved in June 2023. Despite looming economic uncertainty, this dynamic occurs alongside a surge in institutional interest in the cryptocurrency.  In June, several factors contributed to the increased robustness of the Bitcoin price action. Ark Invest, a renowned asset management firm, highlighted this trend in its recent Bitcoin report. Their data sheds light on the risen support from steadfast holders and a noticeable shift in institutional sentiment towards Bitcoin. Bitcoin Holder Base Strength According to Ark Invest&#8217;s analysis, around 70% of Bitcoin&#8217;s circulating supply has not changed hands for at least one year. This statistic signifies an increase in the confidence of long-term Bitcoin investors, contributing to a sturdier holder base.  As seen in the chart below, there has been a spike in Over-the-Counter Transactions (OTC) that hint at growing institutional demand. A one-year high was seen in the balance of BTC held on over-the-counter (OTC) trading desks, typically used as a gauge for institutional activity. The 60% increase in the OTC Bitcoin balance by quarter-end insinuates that institutions and capital allocators are concentrating more on Bitcoin as an investment avenue. The report stated the following: In our view, increased balances on OTC desks suggest that institutions and other large capital allocators are focused increasingly on bitcoin. Meanwhile, diverging trends were noted between USDC and Tether, two prominent stablecoins. While USDC&#8217;s supply shrunk by 37% year-to-date, Tether&#8217;s supply increased by 25%, hitting a record high in June. Ark Invest attributes this divergence to the uncertain U.S. regulatory climate, which might drive some crypto activity overseas. Rising Institutional Activity Amid Market Dynamics An interesting development in June was the Grayscale Bitcoin Trust (GBTC) discount reduction went from 42% to 30% following BlackRock&#8217;s Bitcoin spot Exchange Traded Fund (ETF) filing. According to Ark Invest&#8217;s report, this lower discount implies market anticipation for a Bitcoin spot ETF approval, subsequently enhancing the possibility of GBTC transitioning into an ETF. Ark Invest&#8217;s report cautioned about potential economic challenges despite these positive indications. According to the Purchasing Managers &#8216; Index, manufacturing sector data suggests a plunge in new orders. Concurrently, the U.S. Gross Domestic Income (GDI) shows signs of contraction, indicating the possibility of an impending recession. BTC is trading above $30,000, following its recovery from last month when its value dipped below that. The asset&#8217;s downturn was largely spurred by a legal challenge launched by the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) against Binance and Coinbase, the two foremost crypto exchanges. Related Reading: Analyst’s Forecast: Bitcoin (BTC) To Hit $310,000 If This Happens Nonetheless, Bitcoin&#8217;s recent rally comes on the heels of endorsement from heavyweight financial institutions such as BlackRock. This embrace of the digital currency market has injected a dose of optimism, driving Bitcoin&#8217;s substantial growth. Related Reading: Bitcoin Could Soar To $140,000 In Next Bull Cycle, Crypto Analysis Channel Yesterday, the asset reclaimed its $31,000 mark. However, over the past 24 hours, BTC has retraced and currently trades for $30,400 at the time of writing. Featured image from iStock, Chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>According to recent hedge fund Ark Invest <a href="https://ark-invest.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/The-Bitcoin-Monthly-June-2023.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">data</a>, a historical amount of the Bitcoin supply has remained dormant for at least a year, with roughly 70% of the circulating supply unmoved in June 2023. Despite looming economic uncertainty, this dynamic occurs alongside a surge in institutional interest in the cryptocurrency. </p>
<p>In June, several factors contributed to the increased robustness of the Bitcoin price action. Ark Invest, a renowned asset management firm, highlighted this trend in its recent Bitcoin report. Their data sheds light on the risen support from steadfast holders and a noticeable shift in institutional sentiment towards Bitcoin.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Holder Base Strength</h2>
<p>According to Ark Invest&#8217;s analysis, around 70% of <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-could-soar-in-next-bull-cycle-predicts-crypto/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Bitcoin&#8217;s circulating supply</a> has not changed hands for at least one year. This statistic signifies an increase in the confidence of long-term Bitcoin investors, contributing to a sturdier holder base. </p>
<p>As seen in the chart below, there has been a spike in Over-the-Counter Transactions (OTC) that hint at growing institutional demand. A one-year high was seen in the balance of BTC held on over-the-counter (OTC) trading desks, typically used as a gauge for institutional activity. </p>
<p>The 60% increase in the OTC <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-miners-send-daily-revenue-to-exchanges/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Bitcoin balance</a> by quarter-end insinuates that institutions and capital allocators are concentrating more on Bitcoin as an investment avenue.</p>
<p>The report stated the following:</p>
<blockquote><p>In our view, increased balances on OTC desks suggest that institutions and other large capital allocators are focused increasingly on bitcoin.</p></blockquote>

<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-541604 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-1-860x679.jpg" alt="Bitcoin BTC BTCUSDT Chart 1" width="860" height="679" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-1-860x679.jpg 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-1-460x363.jpg 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-1-768x607.jpg 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-1-750x593.jpg 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-1.jpg 1010w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/>
<p>Meanwhile, diverging trends were noted between USDC and Tether, two prominent stablecoins. While USDC&#8217;s supply shrunk by 37% year-to-date, Tether&#8217;s supply increased by 25%, hitting a record high in June. Ark Invest attributes this divergence to the uncertain U.S. regulatory climate, which might drive some crypto activity overseas.</p>
<h2>Rising Institutional Activity Amid Market Dynamics</h2>
<p>An interesting development in June was the Grayscale Bitcoin Trust (GBTC) discount reduction went from 42% to 30% following BlackRock&#8217;s <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/btc-uptrend-fidelity-to-submit-bitcoin-spot-etf-filing/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Bitcoin spot Exchange Traded Fund (ETF) filing</a>. According to Ark Invest&#8217;s report, this lower discount implies market anticipation for a Bitcoin spot ETF approval, subsequently enhancing the possibility of GBTC transitioning into an ETF.</p>
<p>Ark Invest&#8217;s report cautioned about potential economic challenges despite these positive indications. According to the Purchasing Managers &#8216; Index, manufacturing sector data suggests a plunge in new orders. Concurrently, the U.S. Gross Domestic Income (GDI) shows signs of contraction, indicating the possibility of an impending recession.</p>
<p>BTC is <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/analysts-forecast-bitcoin-btc-to-hit-310000-if-this-happens/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">trading above $30,000</a>, following its recovery from last month when its value dipped below that. The asset&#8217;s downturn was largely spurred by a legal challenge launched by the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) against Binance and Coinbase, the two foremost crypto exchanges.</p>

<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w" dir="ltr">Nonetheless, Bitcoin&#8217;s recent rally comes on the heels of endorsement from <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/blackrock-inches-closer-to-launching-bitcoin-etf-impact-on-btc-price/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">heavyweight financial institutions such as BlackRock</a>. This embrace of the digital currency market has injected a dose of optimism, driving Bitcoin&#8217;s substantial growth.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/ydueGgBM/" alt="Bitcoin (BTC)’s price chart on TradingView" width="2770" height="1556"/>
<p dir="ltr">Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-could-soar-in-next-bull-cycle-predicts-crypto/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Bitcoin Could Soar To $140,000 In Next Bull Cycle, Crypto Analysis Channel</a></p>
<p dir="ltr">Yesterday, the asset reclaimed its $31,000 mark. However, over the past 24 hours, BTC has retraced and currently trades for $30,400 at the time of writing.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Featured image from iStock, Chart from TradingView</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Bitcoin-460x329.jpeg" width="460" height="329" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>CFTC Investigators Conclude Celsius And Former CEO Violated Rules, Potential Case Looms</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/crypto/cftc-investigators-conclude-celsius-violated-rules/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 16:30:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Alex Mashinsky]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[celsius]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Celsius bankruptcy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto regulation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=541589</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) has concluded its investigation into bankrupt crypto lender Celsius and its former CEO, Alex Mashinsky, and found that they violated United States rules, according to sources familiar with the matter.  The investigation, conducted by attorneys in the CFTC&#8217;s enforcement unit, revealed that Celsius misled investors and failed to register with the regulatory body. If the majority of the CFTC&#8217;s commissioners agree with these findings, the agency could file a case in federal court as early as this month. Celsius Reportedly Misled Investors, Lack Of Registration Surfaces  The findings of the investigation shed light on the actions of Celsius and its former CEO, raising questions about their compliance with regulatory requirements. It is alleged that Celsius engaged in deceptive practices and failed to provide accurate information to investors. Related Reading: Valkyrie Follows In BlackRock’s Footsteps, Refiles For Spot Bitcoin ETF By misleading investors, the lending platform potentially put their funds at risk and undermined market transparency. Furthermore, the failure to register with the CFTC raises concerns about the company&#8217;s adherence to regulatory oversight. The independent examiner appointed during Celsius&#8217; bankruptcy case further shed light on the company&#8217;s operations. The examiner found that Celsius had operated in a manner similar to a Ponzi scheme, which raised concerns about the company&#8217;s business practices and its impact on investors. This finding adds weight to the allegations against Celsius and strengthens the case for regulatory action. CEL token struggles at $0.15 &#124; Source: CELUSD on TradingView.com The potential case against Celsius and its ex-CEO has significant implications for the crypto industry and regulatory enforcement. If the CFTC proceeds with the lawsuit, it would signal a strong stance on holding companies accountable for their actions and ensuring investor protection in the cryptocurrency market. When Celsius filed for voluntary bankruptcy in July 2022, the lending company reportedly owed between $1 billion and $10 billion to creditors. The case is currently ongoing at the United States Bankruptcy Court for the Southern District of New York. Implications For The Crypto Industry And Regulatory Enforcement The allegations against Celsius and its former CEO highlight the need for increased regulatory scrutiny and oversight in the crypto sector. As the market continues to grow and attract more participants, it is crucial to establish clear guidelines and enforce compliance to protect investors and maintain market integrity. Related Reading: Analyst Says XRP Will Reach $100, Here’s Why Nevertheless,  the potential case against Celsius demonstrates the commitment of regulatory authorities to uphold these standards and address violations that occur within the industry. This case could serve as a precedent for future enforcement actions, shaping the regulatory landscape for the industry as a whole. Featured image from IQ.Wiki, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) has concluded its investigation into bankrupt crypto lender Celsius and its former CEO, Alex Mashinsky, and found that they violated United States rules, according to sources familiar with the matter. </p>
<p>The investigation, conducted by attorneys in the CFTC&#8217;s enforcement unit, revealed that Celsius misled investors and failed to register with the regulatory body. </p>
<p>If the majority of the CFTC&#8217;s commissioners agree with these findings, the agency could file a case in federal court as early as this month.</p>
<h2>Celsius Reportedly Misled Investors, Lack Of Registration Surfaces </h2>
<p>The <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-07-05/cftc-probe-concludes-crypto-lender-celsius-ex-ceo-mashinsky-broke-rules#xj4y7vzkg" rel="nofollow">findings</a> of the investigation shed light on the actions of Celsius and its former CEO, raising questions about their compliance with regulatory requirements. It is alleged that Celsius engaged in deceptive practices and failed to provide accurate information to investors.</p>

<p>By misleading investors, the lending platform potentially put their funds at risk and undermined market transparency. Furthermore, the failure to register with the CFTC raises concerns about the company&#8217;s adherence to regulatory oversight.</p>
<p>The independent examiner appointed during Celsius&#8217; bankruptcy case further shed light on the company&#8217;s operations. The examiner found that Celsius had operated in a manner similar to a Ponzi scheme, which raised concerns about the company&#8217;s business practices and its impact on investors. This finding adds weight to the allegations against Celsius and strengthens the case for regulatory action.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/kkbXXkMM/" alt="Celsius Token (CEL) price chart from TradingView.com" width="2884" height="1610"/></p>

<p>The potential case against Celsius and its ex-CEO has significant implications for the crypto industry and regulatory enforcement. If the CFTC proceeds with the lawsuit, it would signal a strong stance on holding companies accountable for their actions and ensuring investor protection in the cryptocurrency market.</p>
<p>When Celsius filed for voluntary bankruptcy in July 2022, the lending company reportedly owed between $1 billion and $10 billion to creditors. The case is currently ongoing at the United States Bankruptcy Court for the Southern District of New York.</p>
<h2>Implications For The Crypto Industry And Regulatory Enforcement</h2>
<p>The allegations against Celsius and its former CEO highlight the need for increased regulatory scrutiny and oversight in the crypto sector. As the market continues to grow and attract more participants, it is crucial to establish clear guidelines and enforce compliance to protect investors and maintain market integrity.</p>

<p>Nevertheless,  the potential case against Celsius demonstrates the commitment of regulatory authorities to uphold these standards and address violations that occur within the industry.</p>
<p>This case could serve as a precedent for future enforcement actions, shaping the regulatory landscape for the industry as a whole.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Celsius-network-460x345.jpeg" width="460" height="345" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Marathon Digital Reports 21% Decline In Bitcoin Production In June</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/marathon-digital-reports-21-decline-in-bitcoin-production-in-june/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Semilore Faleti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 15:30:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin hashrate]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Marathon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Marathon Digital]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=541580</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Prominent Bitcoin mining company Marathon Digital Holdings has published its Bitcoin production and mining operation update for June 2023. In the report released yesterday, Marathon revealed that its Bitcoin production decreased by 21% from May due to weather-related issues in Texas and a decline in transaction fees on the Bitcoin network. &#8220;We produced 979 bitcoin in June, down 21% from last month and up 599% from June 2022,” said the Company’s CEO, Fried Theil. “The decreased production relative to last month was due to weather-related curtailment in Texas and a significant decrease in transaction fees, which fell to approximately 5.1% of the total bitcoin we earned in June compared to 11.8% in May,&#8221; Theil added. The Marathon boss noted that the rise of the Bitcoin ordinals contributed to an increase in network fees back in May, and although network congestion decreased in June, he stated that the mining company is quite optimistic about the future of mining economics.  Marathon’s Operational Hash Rate Boosts By 16% Marathon’s monthly report revealed that the mining company’s operational hash rate gained by 16% in June, rising to 17.2 exahashes/second (EH/s). Its installed hash rate also increased to 21.8 EH/a, representing an 8% gain in the last month.  Related Reading: Bitcoin Exchange Supply Continues To Slip, Holders Not Interested In Selling? According to its CEO, Marathon remains committed to its goal of attaining 23 EH/s by boosting its operations in North Dakota and Texas, as emphasized by its CEO.  Theil said: The final steps to achieving our 23 EH/s goal are in Ellendale, ND and Garden City, TX. The final building in Ellendale is expected to come online this month, and final Garden City tie in is also expected within that same period. Theil also announced that the company’s joint venture with Zero Two in Abu Dhabi began operations last week and is expected to achieve a hash rate of 7 EH/s before the end of the year. However, this JV operation does not contribute to the reported operational hash rate of 17.2 EH/s and the mining target of 23 EH/s.  BTC Trading At $30,147 On The Hourly Chart &#124; Source: BTCUSD Chart On Tradingview.com Marathon’s Growth In The Last Year Looking at its Year-Over-Year production rate, Marathon reports that its level of Bitcoin production has gone up by 599% since June 2022, moving from an average daily intake of 4.7 BTC to 32.6 BTC.  Related Reading: Bitcoin Cash Hashrate, Mining Difficulty Skyrockets As Miners Chase BCH Profits Furthermore, the company&#8217;s current operational hash rate of 17.7 EH/s represents a stunning increase of 2,429% compared to last June’s value of 0.7 EH/s. However, its installed hash rate only experienced a percentage gain of 506% moving from 3.6 EH/s to 21.8 EH/s. That said, Marathon stands as a leading mining company with approximately 149,000 Bitcoin miners as of July 1, 2023. Featured Image from Financial Times, chart from Tradingview]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Prominent Bitcoin mining company Marathon Digital Holdings has published its Bitcoin production and mining operation update for June 2023.</p>
<p>In the <a href="https://ir.mara.com/news-events/press-releases/detail/1320/marathon-digital-holdings-announces-bitcoin-production-and" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">report released yesterday</a>, Marathon revealed that its Bitcoin production decreased by 21% from May due to weather-related issues in Texas and a decline in transaction fees on the Bitcoin network.</p>
<p>&#8220;We produced 979 bitcoin in June, down 21% from last month and up 599% from June 2022,” said the Company’s CEO, Fried Theil. “The decreased production relative to last month was due to weather-related curtailment in Texas and a significant decrease in transaction fees, which fell to approximately 5.1% of the total bitcoin we earned in June compared to 11.8% in May,&#8221; Theil added.</p>
<p>The Marathon boss noted that the rise of the Bitcoin ordinals contributed to an increase in network fees back in May, and although network congestion decreased in June, he stated that the mining company is quite optimistic about the future of mining economics. </p>
<h2>Marathon’s Operational Hash Rate Boosts By 16%</h2>
<p>Marathon’s monthly report revealed that the mining company’s operational hash rate gained by 16% in June, rising to 17.2 exahashes/second (EH/s). Its installed hash rate also increased to 21.8 EH/a, representing an 8% gain in the last month. </p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-exchange-supply-slip-holders-interested-selling/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Bitcoin Exchange Supply Continues To Slip, Holders Not Interested In Selling?</a></p>
<p>According to its CEO, Marathon remains committed to its goal of attaining 23 EH/s by boosting its operations in North Dakota and Texas, as emphasized by its CEO.  </p>
<p>Theil said:</p>
<blockquote><p>The final steps to achieving our 23 EH/s goal are in Ellendale, ND and Garden City, TX. The final building in Ellendale is expected to come online this month, and final Garden City tie in is also expected within that same period.
</p></blockquote>
<p>Theil also announced that the<a href="https://www.globenewswire.com/news-release/2023/05/09/2664929/0/en/Marathon-Digital-Holdings-and-Zero-Two-To-Develop-and-Operate-the-First-Large-Scale-Immersion-Bitcoin-Mining-Facilities-in-Abu-Dhabi.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow"> company’s joint venture with Zero Two</a> in Abu Dhabi began operations last week and is expected to achieve a hash rate of 7 EH/s before the end of the year. However, this JV operation does not contribute to the reported operational hash rate of 17.2 EH/s and the mining target of 23 EH/s. </p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/nJ9FLFSE/" alt="Marathon" width="1479" height="913"/>

<h2>Marathon’s Growth In The Last Year</h2>
<p>Looking at its Year-Over-Year production rate, Marathon reports that its level of Bitcoin production has gone up by 599% since June 2022, moving from an average daily intake of 4.7 BTC to 32.6 BTC. </p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin-cash/bitcoin-cash-hashrate-mining-difficulty-skyrockets-as-miners-chase-bch-profits/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Bitcoin Cash Hashrate, Mining Difficulty Skyrockets As Miners Chase BCH Profits</a></p>
<p>Furthermore, the company&#8217;s current operational hash rate of 17.7 EH/s represents a stunning increase of 2,429% compared to last June’s value of 0.7 EH/s. However, its installed hash rate only experienced a percentage gain of 506% moving from 3.6 EH/s to 21.8 EH/s.</p>
<p>That said, Marathon stands as a leading mining company with approximately 149,000 Bitcoin miners as of July 1, 2023.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/e73494ae-4eb3-47d6-884b-2d9deb402463-460x259.jpg" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bittrex Woes Continue: Florida Regulator Says Exchange Violated Multiple Laws</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/crypto/bittrex-woes-continue-florida-regulator-says-exchange-violated-multiple-laws/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[anushsamal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 14:30:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bittrex]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bittrex Bankruptcy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[OFR]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=541544</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[According to court filings, cryptocurrency exchange, Bittrex, has been accused by Florida&#8217;s financial regulator of violating several laws within the state. These violations allegedly occurred prior to Bittrex Inc. filing for Chapter 11 in May. Related Reading: Solana Registers 20% Rise In Past Week, But Can SOL Keep This Up? Bittrex had made a request for an Automatic Stay, which would impede certain creditors from pursuing or continuing legal actions against a bankrupt estate. In response, Brandon Greenberg, Assistant General Counsel to the Florida Office of Financial Regulation (OFR), filed a statement opposing the request. The purpose of Greenberg&#8217;s filing is to challenge the implementation of the Automatic Stay. This would allow creditors to proceed with their actions against Bittrex Inc. as part of the bankruptcy proceedings. Greenberg highlighted in his statement that the financial regulator, the Florida Office of Financial Regulation (OFR), had already provided guidance and advice to Bittrex, regarding potential avenues for resolving the charges brought against them. Accusations Against Bittrex: What Led To The Regulatory Uproar? Bittrex Inc. faces several accusations which included the failure to separate customer assets from the company&#8217;s own capital. Not only that, the exchange, was also accused of inconsistent maintenance of an adequate surety bond. According to the filing, from October 2022 to March 2023, the OFR collaborated with financial regulators in Texas, Maryland, and Michigan to conduct a &#8220;multistate examination&#8221; of Bittrex Inc. This suggests that the regulators from multiple states worked together to assess and investigate the operations of Bittrex Inc. during that period before coming to their present conclusion. After conducting its investigation, the OFR filed a three-count complaint against the exchange platform on April 17, as stated by Greenberg in the filing on Wednesday. On the same day, the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) accused the company of violating federal laws by operating as a securities exchange, broker, and clearing agency. The OFR previously advised the company to engage in administrative procedures. It was suggested in order to help Bittrex to pursue a more substantive discussion and potentially explore options for a settlement. In his filing, Greenberg asserted that the Florida Office of Financial Regulation holds the authority to exercise administrative discretion. It can determine which violations to charge in their Administrative Complaint against the platform. Bittrex Ceased Operations Amidst &#8220;Uncertain Regulatory and Economic Environment&#8221; On March 31, Bittrex Inc. made an announcement stating its intention to wind down its operations in the United States. It cited concerns over the uncertain regulatory and economic environment. According to Greenberg, the company expressed disappointment with the enforcement action taken by the OFR back in April as they had hoped to surrender their license and exit Florida without such action. At that time, Bittrex Inc. did not disclose any plans to file for bankruptcy. However, on April 30, the company surrendered its money transmitter license. Related Reading: Bitcoin Cash (BCH) Registers 28% Gain – How Long Will It Last? Legal representatives for the exchange have combated the allegations. They said that although Bittrex may have faced regulatory issues in the past, they had been in compliance with Florida law since then. On May 8, Bittrex Inc. filed Chapter 11 in the state of Delaware. Featured image from EarthWeb, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>According to<a href="https://casedocs.omniagentsolutions.com/cmsvol2/pub_47475/a9064de6-692c-4960-9f3f-8a02b62d2563_175.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow"> court</a> filings, cryptocurrency exchange, Bittrex, has been accused by Florida&#8217;s financial regulator of violating several laws within the state. These violations allegedly occurred prior to Bittrex Inc. filing for Chapter 11 in May.</p>

<p>Bittrex had made a request for an Automatic Stay, which would impede certain creditors from pursuing or continuing legal actions against a bankrupt estate. In response, Brandon Greenberg, Assistant General Counsel to the Florida Office of Financial Regulation (OFR), filed a statement opposing the request.</p>
<p>The purpose of Greenberg&#8217;s filing is to challenge the implementation of the Automatic Stay. This would allow creditors to proceed with their actions against Bittrex Inc. as part of the bankruptcy proceedings.</p>
<p>Greenberg highlighted in his statement that the financial regulator, the Florida Office of Financial Regulation (OFR), had already provided guidance and advice to Bittrex, regarding potential avenues for resolving the charges brought against them.</p>
<h2>Accusations Against Bittrex: What Led To The Regulatory Uproar?</h2>
<p>Bittrex Inc. faces several accusations which included the failure to separate customer assets from the company&#8217;s own capital. Not only that, the exchange, was also accused of inconsistent maintenance of an adequate surety bond.</p>
<p>According to the filing, from October 2022 to March 2023, the OFR collaborated with financial regulators in Texas, Maryland, and Michigan to conduct a &#8220;multistate examination&#8221; of Bittrex Inc.</p>
<p>This suggests that the regulators from multiple states worked together to assess and investigate the operations of Bittrex Inc. during that period before coming to their present conclusion.</p>
<p>After conducting its investigation, the OFR filed a three-count complaint against the exchange platform on April 17, as stated by Greenberg in the filing on Wednesday.</p>
<p>On the same day, the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) accused the company of violating federal laws by operating as a securities exchange, broker, and clearing agency.</p>
<p>The OFR previously advised the company to engage in administrative procedures. It was suggested in order to help Bittrex to pursue a more substantive discussion and potentially explore options for a settlement.</p>
<p>In his filing, Greenberg asserted that the Florida Office of Financial Regulation holds the authority to exercise administrative discretion. It can determine which violations to charge in their Administrative Complaint against the platform.</p>
<h2>Bittrex Ceased Operations Amidst &#8220;Uncertain Regulatory and Economic Environment&#8221;</h2>
<p>On March 31, Bittrex Inc. made an announcement stating its intention to wind down its operations in the United States. It cited concerns over the uncertain regulatory and economic environment.</p>
<p>According to Greenberg, the company expressed disappointment with the enforcement action taken by the OFR back in April as they had hoped to surrender their license and exit Florida without such action.</p>
<p>At that time, Bittrex Inc. did not disclose any plans to file for bankruptcy. However, on April 30, the company surrendered its money transmitter license.</p>

<p>Legal representatives for the exchange have combated the allegations. They said that although Bittrex may have faced regulatory issues in the past, they had been in compliance with Florida law since then. On May 8, Bittrex Inc. filed Chapter 11 in the state of Delaware.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-541550 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/TOTAL_2023-07-06_17-48-51.png" alt="Bittrex" width="1818" height="830" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/TOTAL_2023-07-06_17-48-51.png 1818w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/TOTAL_2023-07-06_17-48-51-460x210.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/TOTAL_2023-07-06_17-48-51-860x393.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/TOTAL_2023-07-06_17-48-51-768x351.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/TOTAL_2023-07-06_17-48-51-1536x701.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/TOTAL_2023-07-06_17-48-51-750x342.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/TOTAL_2023-07-06_17-48-51-1140x520.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1818px) 100vw, 1818px"/>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bittrex-550-460x259.jpg" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Arbitrage: What Is It and How to Do It</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/learn/how-to-arbitrage-crypto/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[newsbtc]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 14:19:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Learn]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=541575</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[What is arbitrage? Arbitrage, in its simplest form, is the process of buying a stock on one market and selling it on another to take advantage of price listing differences across various markets. For example, a car manufacturer is priced at $45 on the NYSE but is trading at $45.30 on the SSE. A trader purchases these shares on the NYSE and sells them on the SSE to make a 30-cent profit on each share. This is a basic example of arbitrage trading. What is arbitrage trading in crypto? Arbitrage crypto trading works in a similar way to conventional stock market arbitrage trading. In the same way arbitrage traders seek to make gains by buying and selling across markets, crypto arbitrage traders look to profit from the varying list prices on different exchanges. For example, an investor buys 100 Solana coins on the Coinbase crypto exchange at $14 per coin and sells them on the eToro exchange for $14.10 — meaning the investor made 10 cents profit per share by trading them on a new platform. Types of crypto arbitrage The only significant difference between crypto arbitrage trading and stock market arbitration is that there&#8217;s more than one way to do it. Some of the common types of crypto arbitrage trading include: Spatial arbitrage — Also known as geographical arbitrage, spatial arbitrage is when an investor simply buys cryptocurrency on one exchange, sells in another, and collects the profit. Investors can trade crypto between centralized exchanges (CEXs) or Decentralized exchanges (DEXs) and take advantage of an exchange&#8217;s technical inefficiencies — like pricing delays — and listing differences to profit. Spatial arbitrage without transferring — The most common and simple form of arbitrage trading. An investor takes a long position on a cryptocurrency on one exchange and a short position with the same cryptocurrency on another exchange. This means investors can hedge against substantial losses and make small profits on price fluctuations across different exchanges. Triangular arbitrage — The triangle aspect refers to three types of currency involved in a triangular transaction — the two coins and the fiat currency used. Triangular arbitrage works like this: The investor logs on to their crypto exchange or trading account and buys one Bitcoin on their account using their fiat currency — for example, pound sterling or US dollars. The investor transfers that Bitcoin to a different exchange or wallet and purchases 10 Ethereum using that Bitcoin. The investor then sells their current holding of Ethereum — for a higher price than the cost of the original Bitcoin — and buys back the original Bitcoin for the starting price to complete the triangle. Although profitable when done correctly, these opportunities rarely arise, and this isn’t a method commonly used by traders. How to find crypto arbitrage opportunities It&#8217;s all well and good knowing how to put an arbitrage trading plan into action. However, prospective arbitrageurs must know how to spot these opportunities to act on them. To spot a lucrative crypto arbitrage opportunity, investors must: Browse the market for price changes — Whether manually or using a tracking tool to do the heavy lifting, comparing the prices of cryptocurrencies on a range of platforms is essential to know where to buy and sell. Specialist software can help investors scrape this data from various exchanges to highlight potential opportunities. Use trading pairs — Trading helps gauge the comparative value of two cryptocurrencies or between a coin and a fiat currency. For example, an exchange might show that one Bitcoin token is worth X amount of Ethereum on the interface and vice versa. This value can be used to calculate how much a coin is worth when you trade, making it easier to identify if the exchange rate works in your favor. Keep up-to-date with currency exchange rates — Another crucial aspect of arbitraging crypto is tracking the exchange rates of fiat currencies. For investors buying and selling cryptocurrencies across global CEXs and DEXs, understanding how the fiat currencies have moved can affect how much profit they&#8217;ll make when all the assets are sold. Advantages of crypto arbitrage Despite being an uncommon tactic, there are many potential advantages to arbitraging cryptocurrencies. The main advantages of cryptocurrency arbitrage trading include: Low risk — Because crypto arbitrage trading often involves buying and selling simultaneously or on different markets, traders hedge their losses with a counter investment, meaning there is minimal risk for the trade. Potential for quick returns — Arbitrage trading has a quick turnaround — once investors spot an opportunity, they jump at it. The nature of rapid arbitrage trading and currency conversions at a desirable rate means that profits can be realized in a matter of minutes. Industry Volatility — Volatility is usually not associated with positive financial investing, however, it&#8217;s a vital part of arbitrage. Cryptocurrencies are inherently volatile. Because the supply and demand of a coin are largely based on speculation, markets are constantly moving — exposing daily pricing errors and inefficiencies across many crypto exchanges daily. It&#8217;s these inefficiencies that open the door for traders to profit. Works during bull and bear markets — Whether the market is rising or falling, the number of arbitrage opportunities remains the same. Although bull markets are more desirable, traders can hold both long and short positions and make money whether the markets bull or bear. Disadvantages of crypto arbitrage All investment strategies come with a level of risk – cryptocurrency arbitrage is no different. Some of the drawbacks of crypto arbitrage include: Withdrawal limits — Some cryptocurrencies limit the amount you can withdraw at any given time. Investors must understand these limits and select exchanges that offer the cheapest withdrawal fees to maximize profit on short-term trades. Transaction Fees — All trading platforms and cryptocurrency exchanges won&#8217;t let you buy, deposit, or withdraw money or coins from a wallet without charging fees. Investors must factor these fees into account before taking arbitrage trades. Fees for buying, selling, and withdrawing coins or fiat currency can exceed the profit made by performing a successful arbitrage trade — adding extra layers of complexity for novice and experienced investors alike. Slow Transaction Times — As competition for a share of the crypto pie ramps up, so do transaction times, due to the increased volume. Because funds need to be reallocated and withdrawn quickly, these slow wait times can be the difference between an investor profiting, missing out on an opportunity, or losing out entirely. Precision Timing Needed — All trading is relatively time-sensitive, but none more than arbitrage trading. When prices across exchanges don&#8217;t match up, and an opportunity arises, investors have minutes or even seconds to react and turn a profit. Investors need to be quick to reduce the risk of the market turning against them, making it a method that&#8217;s most suitable for more experienced traders. Frequently Asked Questions (FAQs) Which coin is the best for arbitrage? Arbitrage can be done with any crypto coin or token. However, coins with high volatility are most suitable as they open more opportunities for arbitration. Cheaper tokens and meme coins – like Dogecoin, Shiba Inu, and Cardano – offer increased volatility and are also more accessible to investors with smaller portfolios. Can you lose money doing crypto arbitrage? Like any form of trading, if the market doesn&#8217;t fall in your favor — or you make a mistake on your inputs — you can lose money from crypto arbitrage. Unfortunately, trading has real-world consequences, so it&#8217;s critical to be informed and practice on a paper money account before committing personal capital. For more information on how to invest in crypto as a beginner and the potential pros and cons of trading, check out our helpful guide! Is crypto arbitrage legal? Crypto arbitrage trading is not only legal in the majority of countries across the world, but it&#8217;s also encouraged. It helps iron out market inefficiencies by making it easier for centralized and decentralized markets to receive a steady supply of coins to fulfill demand without affecting the market price. How to learn crypto arbitrage? When learning any form of trading, it&#8217;s important to learn from the best and practice the strategy in a safe environment. Most exchanges offer investors the option to set up a paper account. A paper account lets novice investors set up and try different investment strategies — including crypto arbitrage trading – without the risks associated with committing capital straight away.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2>What is arbitrage?</h2>
<p>Arbitrage, in its simplest form, is the process of buying a stock on one market and selling it on another to take advantage of price listing differences across various markets.</p>
<p>For example, a car manufacturer is priced at $45 on the NYSE but is trading at $45.30 on the SSE. A trader purchases these shares on the NYSE and sells them on the SSE to make a 30-cent profit on each share. This is a basic example of arbitrage trading.</p>
<h2>What is arbitrage trading in crypto?</h2>
<p>Arbitrage crypto trading works in a similar way to conventional stock market arbitrage trading.</p>
<p>In the same way arbitrage traders seek to make gains by buying and selling across markets, crypto arbitrage traders look to profit from the varying list prices on different exchanges.</p>
<p>For example, an investor buys 100 <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/solana/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Solana</a> coins on the Coinbase crypto exchange at $14 per coin and sells them on the eToro exchange for $14.10 — meaning the investor made 10 cents profit per share by trading them on a new platform.</p>
<h2>Types of crypto arbitrage</h2>
<p>The only significant difference between crypto arbitrage trading and stock market arbitration is that there&#8217;s more than one way to do it.</p>
<p>Some of the common types of crypto arbitrage trading include:</p>
<p><strong>Spatial arbitrage</strong> — Also known as geographical arbitrage, spatial arbitrage is when an investor simply buys cryptocurrency on one exchange, sells in another, and collects the profit. Investors can trade crypto between centralized exchanges (CEXs) or Decentralized exchanges (DEXs) and take advantage of an exchange&#8217;s technical inefficiencies — like pricing delays — and listing differences to profit.</p>
<p><strong>Spatial arbitrage without transferring</strong> — The most common and simple form of arbitrage trading. An investor takes a long position on a cryptocurrency on one exchange and a short position with the same cryptocurrency on another exchange. This means investors can hedge against substantial losses and make small profits on price fluctuations across different exchanges.</p>
<p><strong>Triangular arbitrage</strong> — The triangle aspect refers to three types of currency involved in a triangular transaction — the two coins and the fiat currency used. Triangular arbitrage works like this:</p>
<ul>
<li>The investor logs on to their crypto exchange or trading account and buys one <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Bitcoin</a> on their account using their fiat currency — for example, pound sterling or US dollars.</li>
<li>The investor transfers that Bitcoin to a different exchange or wallet and purchases 10 <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Ethereum</a> using that Bitcoin.</li>
<li>The investor then sells their current holding of Ethereum — for a higher price than the cost of the original Bitcoin — and buys back the original Bitcoin for the starting price to complete the triangle.</li>
</ul>
<p>Although profitable when done correctly, these opportunities rarely arise, and this isn’t a method commonly used by traders.</p>
<h2>How to find crypto arbitrage opportunities</h2>
<p>It&#8217;s all well and good knowing how to put an arbitrage trading plan into action. However, prospective arbitrageurs must know how to spot these opportunities to act on them.</p>
<p>To spot a lucrative crypto arbitrage opportunity, investors must:</p>
<p><strong>Browse the market for price changes</strong> — Whether manually or using a tracking tool to do the heavy lifting, comparing the prices of cryptocurrencies on a range of platforms is essential to know where to buy and sell. Specialist software can help investors scrape this data from various exchanges to highlight potential opportunities.</p>
<p><strong>Use trading pairs</strong> — Trading helps gauge the comparative value of two cryptocurrencies or between a coin and a fiat currency. For example, an exchange might show that one Bitcoin token is worth X amount of Ethereum on the interface and vice versa. This value can be used to calculate how much a coin is worth when you trade, making it easier to identify if the exchange rate works in your favor.</p>
<p><strong>Keep up-to-date with currency exchange rates</strong> — Another crucial aspect of arbitraging crypto is tracking the exchange rates of fiat currencies. For investors buying and selling cryptocurrencies across global CEXs and DEXs, understanding how the fiat currencies have moved can affect how much profit they&#8217;ll make when all the assets are sold.</p>
<h2>Advantages of crypto arbitrage</h2>
<p>Despite being an uncommon tactic, there are many potential advantages to arbitraging cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p>The main advantages of cryptocurrency arbitrage trading include:</p>
<p><strong>Low risk</strong> — Because crypto arbitrage trading often involves buying and selling simultaneously or on different markets, traders hedge their losses with a counter investment, meaning there is minimal risk for the trade.</p>
<p><strong>Potential for quick returns</strong> — Arbitrage trading has a quick turnaround — once investors spot an opportunity, they jump at it. The nature of rapid arbitrage trading and currency conversions at a desirable rate means that profits can be realized in a matter of minutes.</p>
<p><strong>Industry Volatility</strong> — Volatility is usually not associated with positive financial investing, however, it&#8217;s a vital part of arbitrage. Cryptocurrencies are inherently volatile. Because the supply and demand of a coin are largely based on speculation, markets are constantly moving — exposing daily pricing errors and inefficiencies across many crypto exchanges daily. It&#8217;s these inefficiencies that open the door for traders to profit.</p>
<p><strong>Works during bull and bear markets</strong> — Whether the market is rising or falling, the number of arbitrage opportunities remains the same. Although bull markets are more desirable, traders can hold both long and short positions and make money whether the markets bull or bear.</p>
<h2>Disadvantages of crypto arbitrage</h2>
<p>All investment strategies come with a level of risk – cryptocurrency arbitrage is no different.</p>
<p>Some of the drawbacks of crypto arbitrage include:</p>
<p><strong>Withdrawal limits</strong> — Some cryptocurrencies limit the amount you can withdraw at any given time. Investors must understand these limits and select exchanges that offer the cheapest withdrawal fees to maximize profit on short-term trades.</p>
<p><strong>Transaction Fees</strong> — All trading platforms and cryptocurrency exchanges won&#8217;t let you buy, deposit, or withdraw money or coins from a wallet without charging fees. Investors must factor these fees into account before taking arbitrage trades. Fees for buying, selling, and withdrawing coins or fiat currency can exceed the profit made by performing a successful arbitrage trade — adding extra layers of complexity for novice and experienced investors alike.</p>
<p><strong>Slow Transaction Times</strong> — As competition for a share of the crypto pie ramps up, so do transaction times, due to the increased volume. Because funds need to be reallocated and withdrawn quickly, these slow wait times can be the difference between an investor profiting, missing out on an opportunity, or losing out entirely.</p>
<p><strong>Precision Timing Needed</strong> — All trading is relatively time-sensitive, but none more than arbitrage trading. When prices across exchanges don&#8217;t match up, and an opportunity arises, investors have minutes or even seconds to react and turn a profit. Investors need to be quick to reduce the risk of the market turning against them, making it a method that&#8217;s most suitable for more experienced traders.</p>
<h2>Frequently Asked Questions (FAQs)</h2>
Which coin is the best for arbitrage?
<p>Arbitrage can be done with any crypto coin or token. However, coins with high volatility are most suitable as they open more opportunities for arbitration.</p>
<p>Cheaper tokens and meme coins – like <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/dogecoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Dogecoin</a>, <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Shiba Inu</a>, and <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/cardano/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Cardano</a> – offer increased volatility and are also more accessible to investors with smaller portfolios.</p>
Can you lose money doing crypto arbitrage?
<p>Like any form of trading, if the market doesn&#8217;t fall in your favor — or you make a mistake on your inputs — you can lose money from crypto arbitrage.</p>
<p>Unfortunately, trading has real-world consequences, so it&#8217;s critical to be informed and practice on a paper money account before committing personal capital.</p>
<p>For more information on <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/learn/how-to-invest-in-cryptocurrency/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">how to invest in crypto as a beginner</a> and the potential pros and cons of trading, check out our helpful guide!</p>
Is crypto arbitrage legal?
<p>Crypto arbitrage trading is not only legal in the majority of countries across the world, but it&#8217;s also encouraged.</p>
<p>It helps iron out market inefficiencies by making it easier for centralized and decentralized markets to receive a steady supply of coins to fulfill demand without affecting the market price.</p>
How to learn crypto arbitrage?
<p>When learning any form of trading, it&#8217;s important to learn from the best and practice the strategy in a safe environment.</p>
<p>Most exchanges offer investors the option to set up a paper account. A paper account lets novice investors set up and try different investment strategies — including crypto arbitrage trading – without the risks associated with committing capital straight away.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/NewsBTC-Abitrage-image-460x354.jpg" width="460" height="354" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Under-The-Radar Bullish Bitcoin Moving Average Crossover Looks Imminent</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/under-the-radar-bullish-bitcoin-moving-average-crossover-looks-imminent/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[dbthequant]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 13:14:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin technical analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xbt]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xbtusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=541388</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Many traders and technicians closely follow the well-known &#8220;Golden Cross&#8221; moving average crossover in key liquid markets such as Bitcoin, Gold, and the Nasdaq 100 Index among others. Today, however, we&#8217;ll examine an under-the-radar Bitcoin moving average crossover which looks imminent. Using Bitcoin&#8217;s reliable data from 2011 through today, let&#8217;s find out if this lesser known moving average crossover looks bullish or bearish going forward. This Lesser Known Moving Average Crossover May Soon Hit While the Golden Cross occurs when the 50-day simple moving average crosses above the 200-day simple moving average, Bitcoin&#8217;s 50-day simple moving average (50MA) currently looks poised to cross above its 100-day simple moving average (100MA) within days. Earlier this year, Bitcoin&#8217;s 50MA crossed above its 100MA as the number one crypto by market cap surged in January off of its post-FTX collapse low. Further Bitcoin gains followed from this most recent crossover. Bitcoin Daily Chart  &#124; BTCUSD on TradingView.com Related Reading: Bitcoin Humpback Wallets Reach ATH, Is BlackRock Behind The Surge? Now that Bitcoin has extended its year-to-date gains in recent sessions, its 50MA looks poised to cross back above its 100MA once again. Beyond the signal earlier this year, what&#8217;s happened in the past when Bitcoin&#8217;s 50MA has crossed above its 100MA? Sixty Days And Beyond Looks Bullish To find out, we&#8217;ll look at all signals since 2011, adding an extra condition which better describes current market conditions with respect to Bitcoin. Our extra condition requires that Bitcoin&#8217;s 100MA must be rising, meaning that the average closed at a value greater than the day before when the 50MA crossed above the 100MA. This additional requirement filters out 50MA &#62; 100MA crossovers during periods of downward price momentum and better describes Bitcoin&#8217;s current technical state. While the holding time graphic below illustrates Bitcoin&#8217;s historical tendency for further upside following such signals, hypothetical gains appear unimpressively small with short-term holding times of seven to fifteen days, up only +1.8% and 1.9% respectively. Moving out to a 30-day holding time, the Average Trade of +10.4% looks far more promising. Bitcoin Holding Time Stats  &#124; SOURCE: Tableau From an intermediate-term perspective, however, the Average Trade stats jump significantly higher with hypothetical gains ranging from +45.7% with a 60-day holding time to +170.9% with a 90-day hold. Related Reading: What’s Next For Bitcoin Price? Bulls Aren’t Running Out Of Steam Yet Returning to the early 2023 signal and assuming a 90-day hold (1/25/23 to 4/25/23), Bitcoin&#8217;s recent 50MA &#62;100MA crossover gained a respectable +22.7%. While it&#8217;s clearly below the Average Trade value for the full history of these crossover signals, Bitcoin may be poised for potentially higher prices if it&#8217;s 50MA can once again close above its rising 100MA. DB the Quant is the author of the REKTelligence Report newsletter on Substack. Follow @REKTelligence on Twitter for evidence-based crypto market research and analysis. Important Note: This content is strictly educational in nature and should not be considered investment advice. Featured images created with Tableau. Charts from TradingView.com.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Many traders and technicians closely follow the well-known &#8220;Golden Cross&#8221; moving average crossover in key liquid markets such as Bitcoin, Gold, and the Nasdaq 100 Index among others. Today, however, we&#8217;ll examine an under-the-radar Bitcoin moving average crossover which looks imminent. Using Bitcoin&#8217;s reliable data from 2011 through today, let&#8217;s find out if this lesser known moving average crossover looks bullish or bearish going forward.</p>
<h2>This Lesser Known Moving Average Crossover May Soon Hit</h2>
<p>While the Golden Cross occurs when the 50-day simple moving average crosses above the 200-day simple moving average, Bitcoin&#8217;s 50-day simple moving average (50MA) currently looks poised to cross above its 100-day simple moving average (100MA) within days. Earlier this year, Bitcoin&#8217;s 50MA crossed above its 100MA as the number one crypto by market cap surged in January off of its post-FTX collapse low. Further Bitcoin gains followed from this most recent crossover.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-541392 aligncenter" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/CHART_50-100-Cross-2-460x230.png" alt="" width="460" height="230" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/CHART_50-100-Cross-2-460x230.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/CHART_50-100-Cross-2-860x431.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/CHART_50-100-Cross-2-768x385.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/CHART_50-100-Cross-2-1536x769.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/CHART_50-100-Cross-2-360x180.png 360w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/CHART_50-100-Cross-2-750x376.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/CHART_50-100-Cross-2-1140x571.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/CHART_50-100-Cross-2.png 1559w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px"/></p>
<p style="text-align: center">Bitcoin Daily Chart  | BTCUSD on TradingView.com</p>


<p>Now that Bitcoin has extended its year-to-date gains in recent sessions, its 50MA looks poised to cross back above its 100MA once again. Beyond the signal earlier this year, what&#8217;s happened in the past when Bitcoin&#8217;s 50MA has crossed above its 100MA?</p>
<h2>Sixty Days And Beyond Looks Bullish</h2>
<p>To find out, we&#8217;ll look at all signals since 2011, adding an extra condition which better describes current market conditions with respect to Bitcoin. Our extra condition requires that Bitcoin&#8217;s 100MA must be <em>rising</em>, meaning that the average closed at a value greater than the day before when the 50MA crossed above the 100MA. This additional requirement filters out 50MA &gt; 100MA crossovers during periods of downward price momentum and better describes Bitcoin&#8217;s current technical state.</p>
<p>While the holding time graphic below illustrates Bitcoin&#8217;s historical tendency for further upside following such signals, hypothetical gains appear unimpressively small with short-term holding times of seven to fifteen days, up only +1.8% and 1.9% respectively. Moving out to a 30-day holding time, the Average Trade of +10.4% looks far more promising.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-541394 aligncenter" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/50-100-CROSS-Hold-Times-458x460.png" alt="" width="458" height="460" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/50-100-CROSS-Hold-Times-458x460.png 458w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/50-100-CROSS-Hold-Times-200x200.png 200w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/50-100-CROSS-Hold-Times-42x42.png 42w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/50-100-CROSS-Hold-Times-75x75.png 75w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/50-100-CROSS-Hold-Times.png 738w" sizes="(max-width: 458px) 100vw, 458px"/></p>
<p style="text-align: center">Bitcoin Holding Time Stats  | SOURCE: Tableau</p>
<p>From an intermediate-term perspective, however, the Average Trade stats jump significantly higher with hypothetical gains ranging from +45.7% with a 60-day holding time to +170.9% with a 90-day hold.</p>

<p>Returning to the early 2023 signal and assuming a 90-day hold (1/25/23 to 4/25/23), Bitcoin&#8217;s recent 50MA &gt;100MA crossover gained a respectable +22.7%. While it&#8217;s clearly below the Average Trade value for the full history of these crossover signals, Bitcoin may be poised for potentially higher prices if it&#8217;s 50MA can once again close above its rising 100MA.</p>
<p>DB the Quant is the author of the <a href="https://rektelligence.substack.com/" rel="nofollow">REKTelligence Report</a> newsletter on Substack. Follow <a href="https://twitter.com/rektelligence?s=21&amp;t=MTrDR-nCiRRkbzbRMFRc0Q" rel="nofollow">@REKTelligence</a> on Twitter for evidence-based crypto market research and analysis. Important Note: This content is strictly educational in nature and should not be considered investment advice. Featured images created with Tableau. Charts from TradingView.com.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/iStock-538277295-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Exchange Supply Continues To Slip, Holders Not Interested In Selling?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-exchange-supply-slip-holders-interested-selling/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hououin Kyouma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 12:37:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Exchange Supply]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Selling]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=541540</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[On-chain data shows that the Bitcoin exchange supply has only continued to decline despite the recent rally that the asset has observed. Bitcoin Exchange Supply Continues To Register Net Decline According to data from the on-chain analytics firm Glassnode, exchanges have continued to see withdrawals recently. The indicator of interest here is the &#8220;exchange balance,&#8221; which measures the total amount of Bitcoin that&#8217;s currently sitting in the wallets of all centralized exchanges. When the value of this metric goes up, it means that the investors are depositing a net number of coins to these platforms currently. As one of the main reasons why holders may transfer their BTC to exchanges is for selling-related purposes, this kind of trend can have short-term bearish consequences for the price. On the other hand, decreasing values of the indicator imply a net amount of the supply is leaving from the exchanges. Such a trend, when prolonged, can be a sign that the investors are accumulating at the moment. Naturally, this could be constructive for the cryptocurrency&#8217;s price. Now, here is a chart that shows the trend in the Bitcoin exchange balance over the last few years: The value of the metric seems to have been going downhill in recent days &#124; Source: Glassnode on Twitter As displayed in the above graph, the Bitcoin exchange balance had been in an overall uptrend during 2018 and 2019, but with the COVID crash in March 2020, a shift happened in the market and the indicator started moving in a downward trajectory. There was a break in this trend during the 2021 bull run, as the metric mostly moved sideways, with some increases coming near the top of the rallies. This deviation in the trend was possibly a result of investors depositing to take advantage of the profit-taking opportunity. Related Reading: 75% Of Bitcoin Supply Now In Profit, Will A Drop Happen Here? With the end of the bull market and the transition toward a bearish period, though, the indicator resumed its decline. Events like the 3AC Collapse and the FTX Crash saw the exchange balance dropping especially hard, as these platforms going down made investors more wary of keeping their coins in centralized custody. With the start of the Bitcoin rally this year, however, the metric once again started moving sideways as demand for selling returned. In the leadup to the local top in April, exchanges were receiving net deposits as their supply outright registered an increase. Interestingly, while investors were looking to sell during the price surge back then, the latest uplift in the price above the $30,000 level has actually seen the exchange balance only decline further. This trend of net withdrawals can be a sign that there isn&#8217;t much appetite for selling in the market currently, at least when compared to the demand for taking coins to self-custody. Related Reading: Solana Registers 20% Rise In Past Week, But Can SOL Keep This Up? With the latest drawdown, the Bitcoin exchange balance has dropped to 2.26 million BTC, which is the lowest the indicator has been since way back in March 2018. BTC Price At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading around $30,700, up 1% in the last week. Looks like the asset has gone stale recently &#124; Source: BTCUSD on TradingView Featured image from Kanchanara on Unsplash.com, charts from TradingView.com, Glassnode.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On-chain data shows that the Bitcoin exchange supply has only continued to decline despite the recent rally that the asset has observed.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Exchange Supply Continues To Register Net Decline</h2>
<p>According to data from the on-chain analytics firm <a href="https://twitter.com/glassnode/status/1676613484186935302" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Glassnode</a>, exchanges have continued to see withdrawals recently. The indicator of interest here is the &#8220;<a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/dormant-bitcoin-now-16-higher-than-btc-in-exchange-reserves/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">exchange balance</a>,&#8221; which measures the total amount of Bitcoin that&#8217;s currently sitting in the wallets of all centralized exchanges.</p>
<p>When the value of this metric goes up, it means that the investors are depositing a net number of coins to these platforms currently. As one of the main reasons why holders may transfer their BTC to exchanges is for selling-related purposes, this kind of trend can have short-term bearish consequences for the price.</p>
<p>On the other hand, decreasing values of the indicator imply a net amount of the supply is leaving from the exchanges. Such a trend, when prolonged, can be a sign that the investors are accumulating at the moment. Naturally, this could be constructive for the cryptocurrency&#8217;s price.</p>
<p>Now, here is a chart that shows the trend in the Bitcoin exchange balance over the last few years:</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone aligncenter" src="https://pbs.twimg.com/media/F0SG7AYWcAImzCK?format=jpg&amp;name=4096x4096" alt="Bitcoin Exchange Balance" width="4053" height="2334"/></p>

<p>As displayed in the above graph, the Bitcoin exchange balance had been in an overall uptrend during 2018 and 2019, but with the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-sentiment-social-red-covid-crash-bottom-signal/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">COVID crash</a> in March 2020, a shift happened in the market and the indicator started moving in a downward trajectory.</p>
<p>There was a break in this trend during the 2021 bull run, as the metric mostly moved sideways, with some increases coming near the top of the rallies. This deviation in the trend was possibly a result of investors depositing to take advantage of the profit-taking opportunity.</p>

<p>With the end of the bull market and the transition toward a bearish period, though, the indicator resumed its decline. Events like the 3AC Collapse and the FTX Crash saw the exchange balance dropping especially hard, as these platforms going down made investors more wary of keeping their coins in centralized custody.</p>
<p>With the start of the Bitcoin rally this year, however, the metric once again started moving sideways as demand for selling returned. In the leadup to the local top in April, exchanges were receiving net deposits as their supply outright registered an increase.</p>
<p>Interestingly, while investors were looking to sell during the price surge back then, the latest uplift in the price <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-rejects-31k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">above the $30,000 level</a> has actually seen the exchange balance only decline further.</p>
<p>This trend of net withdrawals can be a sign that there isn&#8217;t much appetite for selling in the market currently, at least when compared to the demand for taking coins to self-custody.</p>

<p>With the latest drawdown, the Bitcoin exchange balance has dropped to 2.26 million BTC, which is the lowest the indicator has been since way back in March 2018.</p>
<h2>BTC Price</h2>
<p>At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading around $30,700, up 1% in the last week.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium aligncenter" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/t7FoJyyQ/" alt="Bitcoin Price Chart" width="1534" height="881"/></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/kanchanara-WrP_TBcstU0-unsplash-460x306.jpg" width="460" height="306" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Solana Registers 20% Rise In Past Week, But Can SOL Keep This Up?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/solana/solana-registers-20-rise-past-week-can-sol-keep-up/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hououin Kyouma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 11:00:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Solana]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sol]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Solana Rally]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SOLUSD]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=541471</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Solana has observed an increase of more than 20% in the past week. Here&#8217;s what on-chain data says regarding whether this is sustainable or not. Solana Trading Volume Has Remained Low Despite Price Rise In its latest insight post, the on-chain analytics firm Santiment has looked at the underlying metrics of Solana to see what has been driving the latest increase in the price. The firm has looked at the &#8220;social volume&#8221; of the cryptocurrency for various social media platforms and has found that the asset has seen elevated interest on Reddit recently. Here, the social volume refers to a metric that measures the total number of unique posts or threads on a given social media platform that is making at least one mention of SOL. This metric can tell us about the degree of discussion that the coin is currently receiving on the website in question. Now, below is a chart that shows the trend in the Solana social volume on four major social media platforms: Telegram, Reddit, Twitter, and 4chan. Looks like the value of the metric has been relatively low for most of these platforms &#124; Source: Santiment As displayed in the above graph, the Solana social volume on Reddit has seen some spikes as the cryptocurrency has risen during the past week or so. The other platforms, however, haven&#8217;t observed that much discussion related to the asset. Related Reading: Blame The “Supermoon” If Bitcoin Crashes Or Rallies Towards $35,000 In July A notable spike in the social volume on Reddit also occurred before the coin&#8217;s 5% surge during the past 24 hours. This may imply that interest from users on the platform could partly be helping fuel the rise. In terms of the actual trading volume, though, SOL has continued to observe muted activity, despite the growth. Here is a chart that displays the trend in this indicator: The value of the metric hasn't been too high recently &#124; Source: Santiment Interestingly, the initial, strong rise that Solana enjoyed was accompanied by elevated volumes, but at the start of this month, the indicator&#8217;s value noted some decline. Since this drop in volume, SOL has mostly moved sideways. Generally, for any price rise to be sustainable, high trading volumes are required. This is due to the fact that participation from a large number of traders is needed to provide enough fuel for any such price move to go on. Related Reading: Bitcoin Cash (BCH) Registers 28% Gain – How Long Will It Last? Despite the sharp growth that Solana has observed today, the trading volume remaining at low values would suggest that the wider market isn&#8217;t finding the rally interesting enough to make moves on the network. Naturally, if the rally has to go on for an extended period, volumes may have to return to the market. There is also the fact that the SOL funding rates (a measure of the periodic fee that futures traders are exchanging between each other) on Binance and DyDx have become quite positive recently. Longs are dominating the market &#124; Source: Santiment From the graph, it&#8217;s visible that the earlier increase in the asset&#8217;s price may have been helped by shorts being liquidated in the market &#8211; as the funding rates had been highly negative then. As long contract holders are the majority force in the futures market now, the chances of a long squeeze taking place are higher now. In this case, if one does take place, the price would feel a bearish effect. SOL Price At the time of writing, Solana is trading around $20, up 20% in the last week. SOL has shot up in the past day &#124; Source: SOLUSD on TradingView Featured image from GuerrillaBuzz on Unsplash.com, charts from TradingView.com, Santiment.net]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Solana has observed an increase of more than 20% in the past week. Here&#8217;s what on-chain data says regarding whether this is sustainable or not.</p>
<h2>Solana Trading Volume Has Remained Low Despite Price Rise</h2>
<p>In its latest insight post, the on-chain analytics firm <a href="https://insights.santiment.net/read/solana-showing-signs-7336?fpr=twitter" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Santiment</a> has looked at the underlying metrics of Solana to see what has been driving the latest increase in the price.</p>
<p>The firm has looked at the &#8220;<a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/dogecoin-2/dogecoin-up-5-but-social-media-talk-remains-low-santiment/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">social volume</a>&#8221; of the cryptocurrency for various social media platforms and has found that the asset has seen elevated interest on Reddit recently.</p>
<p>Here, the social volume refers to a metric that measures the total number of unique posts or threads on a given social media platform that is making at least one mention of SOL. This metric can tell us about the degree of discussion that the coin is currently receiving on the website in question.</p>
<p>Now, below is a chart that shows the trend in the Solana social volume on four major social media platforms: Telegram, Reddit, Twitter, and 4chan.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone aligncenter" src="https://production-sanbase-images.s3.amazonaws.com/uploads/ca84ac009d9b67e9bbf9ee60c4b0881a5af5c5fc3486827b06d5f0028668682a_1688606181708_Screenshot%202023-07-05%20181600.png" alt="Solana Social Volume" width="3079" height="1749"/></p>

<p>As displayed in the above graph, the Solana social volume on Reddit has seen some spikes as the cryptocurrency has risen during the past week or so. The other platforms, however, haven&#8217;t observed that much discussion related to the asset.</p>

<p>A notable spike in the social volume on Reddit also occurred before the coin&#8217;s 5% surge during the past 24 hours. This may imply that interest from users on the platform could partly be helping fuel the rise.</p>
<p>In terms of the actual <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/pepe/pepe-surge-trading-volume-outshines-shib-and-doge-will-this-trend-continue/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">trading volume</a>, though, SOL has continued to observe muted activity, despite the growth.</p>
<p>Here is a chart that displays the trend in this indicator:</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone aligncenter" src="https://production-sanbase-images.s3.amazonaws.com/uploads/c91aa859665a658588d3a38155aaa390961fb2668e1e4412a8a51836731c5d38_1688604861680_Screenshot%202023-07-05%20175138.png" alt="Solana Trading Volume" width="3144" height="1672"/></p>

<p>Interestingly, the initial, strong rise that Solana enjoyed was accompanied by elevated volumes, but at the start of this month, the indicator&#8217;s value noted some decline. Since this drop in volume, SOL has mostly moved sideways.</p>
<p>Generally, for any price rise to be sustainable, high trading volumes are required. This is due to the fact that participation from a large number of traders is needed to provide enough fuel for any such price move to go on.</p>

<p>Despite the sharp growth that Solana has observed today, the trading volume remaining at low values would suggest that the wider market isn&#8217;t finding the rally interesting enough to make moves on the network. Naturally, if the rally has to go on for an extended period, volumes may have to return to the market.</p>
<p>There is also the fact that the SOL <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-funding-rates-bitmex-deep-red-why-bullish/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">funding rates</a> (a measure of the periodic fee that futures traders are exchanging between each other) on Binance and DyDx have become quite positive recently.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone aligncenter" src="https://production-sanbase-images.s3.amazonaws.com/uploads/ef74728f7edffa8e96d05b8a94018489673470699ef380b91e2f4a2b5d36c12c_1688604884219_Screenshot%202023-07-05%20175236.png" alt="Solana Funding Rates" width="3150" height="1672"/></p>

<p>From the graph, it&#8217;s visible that the earlier increase in the asset&#8217;s price may have been helped by shorts being liquidated in the market &#8211; as the funding rates had been highly negative then.</p>
<p>As long contract holders are the majority force in the futures market now, the chances of a long squeeze taking place are higher now. In this case, if one does take place, the price would feel a bearish effect.</p>
<h2>SOL Price</h2>
<p>At the time of writing, Solana is trading around $20, up 20% in the last week.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium aligncenter" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/7n5pw6iD/" alt="Solana Price Chart" width="1534" height="881"/></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/guerrillabuzz-cuK9BLM_mAQ-unsplash-460x259.jpg" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Breaking: Shiba Inu Lead Dev Reveals Shibarium Release Date, SHIB Up 3%</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/shiba-inu-lead-dev-reveals-shibarium-release-date/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jake Simmons]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 09:45:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Shiba Inu]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BONE]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIB]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shibarium]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Treat]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[World Paper]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=541472</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Breaking Shiba Inu news: The highly anticipated layer-2 solution Shibarium, along with other groundbreaking developments, is set to be unveiled at the upcoming Blockchain Futurist Conference and ETHToronto. Shiba Inu&#8217;s lead developer, Shytoshi Kusama, revealed in a new blog post today that these events will serve as platforms for showcasing Shibarium along with the finalized Worldpaper, introducing SHIB-branded projects, and shedding light on Treat. Sweet August For Shiba Inu Army Scheduled for August 15-16, 2023, ETHToronto and the Blockchain Futurist Conference will provide the perfect backdrop for Shiba Inu&#8217;s grand unveiling. ETHToronto is the official hackathon of the Blockchain Futurist Conference and a huge event for the entire Ethereum ecosystem. Related Reading: Recent 800 Billion Shiba Inu Dump Has Short Traders Worried – Here’s Why As the title sponsor, Shiba Inu solidifies its position as &#8220;a major player in the crypto space&#8221;, as emphasized by Kusama in the blog post. Remarkably, the release date aligns with SHIB&#8217;s approximate 3-year anniversary and being the birthplace of Eth. The SHIB community can expect an immersive experience, featuring presentations, demonstrations, and discussions that will reshape the future of Shiba Inu&#8217;s decentralized finance and governance. The highlight of these events will undoubtedly be the introduction of Shibarium, the highly anticipated cornerstone of Shiba Inu&#8217;s ecosystem. Shibarium aims to push the boundaries of scaling Ethereum, providing innovative solutions for the Shiba Inu community. The long-awaited L2 holds immense potential for revolutionizing the Shiba Inu ecosystem. Remarkably, the event is not only about Shibarium. As part of the events, all SHIB-branded projects will be unveiled, showcasing the project&#8217;s commitment to building a diverse and vibrant ecosystem. These projects, including Shib the Metaverse, Shibacals, Shiba Eternity, and Shiboshis, represent the multifaceted nature of Shiba Inu&#8217;s vision. As Kusama writes, there will also be new partnerships announced with Unification and Bad Idea.Ai. Furthermore, all projects that expressed interest in building with Shibarium Tech will be showcased at the conferences. Related Reading: Shiba Inu Records Surge In Daily New Addresses In Q2: A Sign Of Growing Interest? Shiba Inu&#8217;s lead developer also emphasized the significance of Treat, a pivotal component of the project&#8217;s governance framework. At the Blockchain Futurist Conference, Treat will be publicly detailed for the first time. The SHIB army can expect comprehensive insights into Treat&#8217;s functionality and its role in empowering the decentralized ecosystem. Kusama stated: At this venue [Blockchain Futurist Conference]], the finalized Worldpaper will be showcased, all Shib-branded projects will be unveiled, and Treat will be detailed publicly for the first time. Additionally, discussions and potential releases of the long-awaited L2 Shibarium are highly likely. SHIB Is Up 3% With the news, the countdown to the eagerly awaited Blockchain Futurist Conference, where Shiba Inu will take center stage, has begun, and with it, possibly, a renewed SHIB hype. At press time, SHIB was trading at $0.00000758 and has risen around 3% since the publication of Kusama&#8217;s blog post. This puts the SHIB price on the verge of a possible breakout from the downtrend channel that has been in place since early February. A significant rise above $0.000008 towards the 38.2% Fibonacci retracement level ($0.00000831) and a subsequent breakout above this resistance is needed to avoid a fakeout. Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Breaking Shiba Inu news: The highly anticipated layer-2 solution Shibarium, along with other groundbreaking developments, is set to be unveiled at the upcoming Blockchain Futurist Conference and ETHToronto. Shiba Inu&#8217;s lead developer, Shytoshi Kusama, <a href="https://twitter.com/LucieSHIB/status/1676871206555770881" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">revealed</a> in a new blog post today that these events will serve as platforms for showcasing Shibarium along with the finalized Worldpaper, introducing SHIB-branded projects, and shedding light on Treat.</p>
<h2>Sweet August For Shiba Inu Army</h2>
<p>Scheduled for August 15-16, 2023, ETHToronto and the Blockchain Futurist Conference will provide the perfect backdrop for Shiba Inu&#8217;s grand unveiling. ETHToronto is the official hackathon of the Blockchain Futurist Conference and a huge event for the entire Ethereum ecosystem.</p>

<p>As the title sponsor, Shiba Inu solidifies its position as &#8220;a major player in the crypto space&#8221;, as emphasized by Kusama in the blog post. Remarkably, the release date aligns with SHIB&#8217;s approximate 3-year anniversary and being the birthplace of Eth.</p>
<p>The SHIB community can expect an immersive experience, featuring presentations, demonstrations, and discussions that will reshape the future of Shiba Inu&#8217;s decentralized finance and governance. The highlight of these events will undoubtedly be the introduction of Shibarium, the highly anticipated cornerstone of Shiba Inu&#8217;s ecosystem.</p>
<p>Shibarium aims to push the boundaries of scaling Ethereum, providing innovative solutions for the Shiba Inu community. The long-awaited L2 holds immense <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/shibarium-reaches-new-milestones-as-anticipation-builds/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">potential</a> for revolutionizing the Shiba Inu ecosystem.</p>
<p>Remarkably, the event is not only about Shibarium. As part of the events, all SHIB-branded projects will be unveiled, showcasing the project&#8217;s commitment to building a diverse and vibrant ecosystem. These projects, including Shib the Metaverse, <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/shiba-inu-lead-developer-unveils-shibacals-advancing-shibarium-development/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Shibacals</a>, Shiba Eternity, and Shiboshis, represent the multifaceted nature of Shiba Inu&#8217;s vision.</p>
<p>As Kusama writes, there will also be new partnerships announced with Unification and Bad Idea.Ai. Furthermore, all projects that expressed interest in building with Shibarium Tech will be showcased at the conferences.</p>

<p>Shiba Inu&#8217;s lead developer also emphasized the significance of Treat, a pivotal component of the project&#8217;s governance framework. At the Blockchain Futurist Conference, Treat will be publicly detailed for the first time. The SHIB army can expect comprehensive insights into Treat&#8217;s functionality and its role in empowering the decentralized ecosystem. Kusama stated:</p>
<blockquote><p><strong>At this venue [Blockchain Futurist Conference]], the finalized Worldpaper will be showcased, all Shib-branded projects will be unveiled, and Treat will be detailed publicly for the first time. Additionally, discussions and potential releases of the long-awaited L2 Shibarium are highly likely.</strong></p></blockquote>
<h2>SHIB Is Up 3%</h2>
<p>With the news, the countdown to the eagerly awaited Blockchain Futurist Conference, where Shiba Inu will take center stage, has begun, and with it, possibly, a renewed SHIB hype.</p>
<p>At press time, SHIB was trading at $0.00000758 and has risen around 3% since the publication of Kusama&#8217;s blog post. This puts the SHIB price on the verge of a possible breakout from the downtrend channel that has been in place since early February. A significant rise above $0.000008 towards the 38.2% Fibonacci retracement level ($0.00000831) and a subsequent breakout above this resistance is needed to avoid a fakeout.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-541486 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/SHIBUSD_2023-07-06_11-19-18.png" alt="Shiba Inu SHIB price" width="3628" height="1672" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/SHIBUSD_2023-07-06_11-19-18.png 3628w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/SHIBUSD_2023-07-06_11-19-18-460x212.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/SHIBUSD_2023-07-06_11-19-18-860x396.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/SHIBUSD_2023-07-06_11-19-18-768x354.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/SHIBUSD_2023-07-06_11-19-18-1536x708.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/SHIBUSD_2023-07-06_11-19-18-2048x944.png 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/SHIBUSD_2023-07-06_11-19-18-750x346.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/SHIBUSD_2023-07-06_11-19-18-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 3628px) 100vw, 3628px"/>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/iStock-1311148884-460x316.jpg" width="460" height="316" />	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
