<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
>

<channel>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.newsbtc.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<description>Bitcoin &#38; Cryptocurrency News Today</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 03:15:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Price Needs To Clear $31K For Hopes of a Fresh Rally</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-31k-resistance/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 03:15:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xbtusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=540248</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin price is still facing a major hurdle near $31,000. BTC could correct lower below $29,800 if it stays below $31,000 for a long time. Bitcoin is still consolidating below the $31,000 resistance zone. The price is trading below $30,500 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average. There is a key declining channel forming with resistance near $30,200 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Kraken). The pair could correct lower toward the $29,550 support or even $29,000. Bitcoin Price Stuck In A Range Bitcoin price remained in a major range below the $31,000 resistance zone. BTC made another attempt to gain pace above the $31,000 resistance but failed. A high was formed near $31,008 before there was a fresh decline. There was a move below the $30,500 level but the bulls were active above the $29,800 zone. A low is formed near $29,834 and the price is now trading in a range. It is trading near the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the recent decline from the $31,008 swing high to the $29,834 low. Bitcoin price is now trading below $30,500 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average. There is also a key declining channel forming with resistance near $30,200 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair. Immediate resistance is near the $30,200 level. The first major resistance is near the $30,420 level or the 100 hourly Simple moving average. It is close to the 50% Fib retracement level of the recent decline from the $31,008 swing high to the $29,834 low, above which the price might revisit the $31,000 resistance zone. Source: BTCUSD on TradingView.com An upside break above the $31,000 resistance might send BTC toward $31,500. Any more gains could open the doors for a move toward the $32,200 resistance zone. More Losses in BTC? If Bitcoin’s price fails to clear the $30,420 resistance, it could continue to move down. Immediate support on the downside is near the $30,000 level. The next major support is near the $29,850 level, below which there could be a drop toward the $29,550 support. Any more losses might send the price toward the $29,000 zone in the near term. Technical indicators: Hourly MACD – The MACD is now losing pace in the bearish zone. Hourly RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BTC/USD is below the 50 level. Major Support Levels – $30,000, followed by $29,550. Major Resistance Levels – $30,200, $30,420, and $31,000.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>Bitcoin price is still facing a major hurdle near $31,000. BTC could correct lower below $29,800 if it stays below $31,000 for a long time.</em></p>
<ul>
<li>Bitcoin is still consolidating below the $31,000 resistance zone.</li>
<li>The price is trading below $30,500 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average.</li>
<li>There is a key declining channel forming with resistance near $30,200 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could correct lower toward the $29,550 support or even $29,000.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Bitcoin Price Stuck In A Range</h2>
<p>Bitcoin price remained in a major range below the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-consolidates-below-31k/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">$31,000 resistance zone</a>. BTC made another attempt to gain pace above the $31,000 resistance but failed.</p>
<p>A high was formed near $31,008 before there was a fresh decline. There was a move below the $30,500 level but the bulls were active above the $29,800 zone. A low is formed near $29,834 and the price is now trading in a range.</p>
<p>It is trading near the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the recent decline from the $31,008 swing high to the $29,834 low. Bitcoin price is now trading below $30,500 and the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-aims-higher-30500/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">100 hourly Simple moving average</a>. There is also a key declining channel forming with resistance near $30,200 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair.</p>
<p>Immediate resistance is near the $30,200 level. The first major resistance is near the $30,420 level or the 100 hourly Simple moving average. It is close to the 50% Fib retracement level of the recent decline from the $31,008 swing high to the $29,834 low, above which the price might revisit the $31,000 resistance zone.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-540249" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-20.png" alt="Bitcoin Price" width="1835" height="845" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-20.png 1835w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-20-460x212.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-20-860x396.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-20-768x354.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-20-1536x707.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-20-750x345.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-20-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1835px) 100vw, 1835px"/></p>
<p>Source: <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BTCUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">BTCUSD on TradingView.com</a></p>
<p>An upside break above the $31,000 resistance might send BTC toward $31,500. Any more gains could open the doors for a move toward the $32,200 resistance zone.</p>
<h2>More Losses in BTC?</h2>
<p>If Bitcoin’s price fails to clear the $30,420 resistance, it could continue to move down. Immediate support on the downside is near the $30,000 level.</p>
<p>The next major support is near the $29,850 level, below which there could be a drop toward the $29,550 support. Any more losses might send the price toward the $29,000 zone in the near term.</p>
<p>Technical indicators:</p>
<p>Hourly MACD – The MACD is now losing pace in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>Hourly RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BTC/USD is below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Levels – $30,000, followed by $29,550.</p>
<p>Major Resistance Levels – $30,200, $30,420, and $31,000.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/04/shutterstock_786496693-460x325.jpg" width="460" height="325" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>FTT Flies 45% On Rumors Of FTX Planned Relaunch</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/ftx/ftt-flies-45-on-rumors-of-ftx-planned-relaunch/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dalmas Ngetich]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 02:00:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTT bulls]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX bankrupt]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=540232</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[FTT, the native currency of FTX and its ecosystem, is up 45% when writing on June 28. This positive price action follows a report by the Wall Street Journal that the exchange’s new management has started receiving proposals from parties interested in restarting the exchange. The unconfirmed report cited the chief executive officer, John J. Ray III, who took over FTX when it officially filed for bankruptcy in mid-November 2022. Will FTX Be Restarted? Sources report that the management team of the cryptocurrency exchange has been in discussions with investors interested in seeing the platform back up and running.  Different ownership and management structures are being considered as part of this effort. A joint venture is one option, which would involve compensating existing clients affected by the FTX bankruptcy through stakes in the new organization. Additionally, when the exchange is relaunched, it will operate under a new brand name to improve its reputation and regain trust. Related Reading: BNB Market Cap Down By 25% In June Amidst Binance Regulatory Pressure Rumors of this restart are six months after Ray III said he was setting up a task force to explore resuming operations. The CEO also added that despite the alleged illegal activities committed by executives, mainly Sam Bankman-Fried and Alameda Research, the exchange’s business model was feasible. A restructuring and a restart of the exchange, observers note, will be a better outcome for its millions of clients who were adversely affected after the exchange unexpectedly filed for bankruptcy last year. Following the collapse of FTX, the cryptocurrency market tanked, with Bitcoin and Ethereum sinking to new 2022 lows. In a bear market of last year, the FTX collapse forced BTC prices below $16k.  At the same time, FTT, the native currency of FTX, sank 92%. Despite the current expansion, the token is far from its October 2021 highs when each FTT was changing hands at over $69. When writing on June 28, FTT is trading at $1.73 with a market capitalization of $576,331,728. Charges Against Sam Bankman-Fried And Alameda Research Sam Bankman-Fried, the founder of FTX, is charged with wire fraud, commodities fraud, money laundering, and bribery, among others, following an investigation by the United States Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC). The agency sought to discover whether FTX and Alameda Research knowingly engaged in market manipulation and if there was a conflict of interest. The CFTC also alleges that FTX and its trading wing, Alameda Research, failed to disclose their trading activities to clients while using their funds to support FTT prices.  Related Reading: Michael Saylor Doubles Down On Bitcoin, Adds 12,333 BTC To MicroStrategy’s Holdings Amid this, Bankman-Fried is accused of using Alameda funds to cover his expenses, including donating $10 million to a political party. He has pleaded not guilty to all charges, and a trial is planned for October 2023. Feature Image From Canva, Chart From TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>FTT, the native currency of FTX and its ecosystem, is up 45% when writing on June 28. This positive price action follows a <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.wsj.com/amp/articles/ftx-begins-talks-on-reboot-as-managers-uncover-past-misconduct-38ad7e3c" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">report</a> by the Wall Street Journal that the exchange’s new management has started receiving proposals from parties interested in restarting the exchange. </p>
<p>The unconfirmed report cited the chief executive officer, John J. Ray III, who took over FTX when it officially filed for bankruptcy in mid-November 2022.</p>
<h2>Will FTX Be Restarted?</h2>
<p>Sources report that the management team of the cryptocurrency exchange has been in discussions with investors interested in seeing the platform back up and running. </p>
<p>Different ownership and management structures are being considered as part of this effort. A joint venture is one option, which would involve compensating existing clients affected by the FTX bankruptcy through stakes in the new organization. Additionally, when the exchange is relaunched, it will operate under a new brand name to improve its reputation and regain trust.</p>

<p>Rumors of this restart are six months after Ray III said he was setting up a task force to explore resuming operations. The CEO also added that despite the alleged illegal activities committed by executives, mainly Sam Bankman-Fried and Alameda Research, the exchange’s business model was feasible. A restructuring and a restart of the exchange, observers note, will be a better outcome for its millions of clients who were adversely affected after the exchange unexpectedly filed for bankruptcy last year.</p>
<p>Following the collapse of FTX, the cryptocurrency market tanked, with Bitcoin and Ethereum sinking to new 2022 lows. In a bear market of last year, the FTX collapse forced BTC prices below $16k. </p>
<p>At the same time, FTT, the native currency of FTX, sank 92%. Despite the current expansion, the token is far from its October 2021 highs when each FTT was changing hands at over $69. When writing on June 28, FTT is <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.coinlore.com/coin/ftx-token/news" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">trading</a> at $1.73 with a market capitalization of $576,331,728.</p>
<a href="https://www.tradingview.com/x/aKkGqZrg/" rel="nofollow"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/aKkGqZrg/" alt="FTT price on June 28|Source: FTTUSDT on Binance, TradingView" width="1226" height="595"/></a>
<h2>Charges Against Sam Bankman-Fried And Alameda Research</h2>
<p>Sam Bankman-Fried, the founder of FTX, is charged with wire fraud, commodities fraud, money laundering, and bribery, among others, following an investigation by the United States Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC). </p>
<p>The agency sought to discover whether FTX and Alameda Research knowingly engaged in market manipulation and if there was a conflict of interest. The CFTC also alleges that FTX and its trading wing, Alameda Research, failed to disclose their trading activities to clients while using their funds to support FTT prices. </p>

<p>Amid this, Bankman-Fried is accused of using Alameda funds to cover his expenses, including donating $10 million to a political party. He has pleaded not guilty to all charges, and a trial is planned for October 2023.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/FTX-FTT-Rally-460x260.jpg" width="460" height="260" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Takes The Crown: Market Cap Dominance Soars Above 58%, Highest Level Since 2021</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-takes-the-crown-market-cap-dominance-soars-above-58-highest-level-since-2021/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 01:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin dominance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=540221</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) has again taken center stage in the cryptocurrency market as institutional interest surges. This interest has been spurred by major financial giants such as BlackRock, Fidelity, and Ark Invest, who have applied with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) to launch a spot Bitcoin Exchange Traded Fund (ETF).  According to Coin Metrics, BTC&#8217;s market capitalization dominance has reached a new high for 2023, currently at 58%, the highest since April 2021. Bitcoin Rules The Crypto Kingdom BTC has been the leading digital asset and has maintained its position as the top cryptocurrency for a long time. Its market cap of $586 billion is significantly higher than the industry&#8217;s combined market cap, which stands at $425 billion (excluding stablecoins). According to Coin Metrics &#8216; report, BTC&#8217;s dominance fell in the spring of 2021 as traders bid up smaller-cap altcoins, but it never dropped below 40% of the total market. However, with some newer tokens facing intensified regulatory scrutiny in the US, BTC has pulled ahead in 2023. BTC’s weighting in the CMBI 10, index of the 10 largest cryptocurrencies by market capitalization, is also at a 2-year high of 65%. Related Reading: Michael Saylor Doubles Down On Bitcoin, Adds 12,333 BTC To MicroStrategy’s Holdings Looking at a broader basket of assets, BTC&#8217;s 85% return year-to-date outpaces most of the other major digital assets. Per the report, the only two assets with a greater return year-to-date compared to BTC are Bitcoin Cash (BCH) at 102% and Lido (LDO) at 104%. BTC Dominance Rallying Trend Ahead? On the other hand, crypto analyst Michael Van de Poppe recently shared some insights regarding the Bitcoin dominance chart. According to Van de Poppe, &#8220;the chart looks like it wants to continue rallying,&#8221; but there are some key points to remember. One of the most important takeaways is that in September 2019, BTC tested the 200-week moving average (MA) and exponential moving average (EMA) and encountered resistance. This was 10 months before the Bitcoin halving event in May 2020. Van de Poppe notes that the current situation is similar to September 2019. BTC is once again testing the 200-week MA and EMA, and whether it can break through this resistance level remains to be seen. This could be a positive sign for Bitcoin investors, as the halving event was followed by a period of strong price growth for BTC. Related Reading: Radix (XRD) Down By 11% In A Single Day, As Altcoin Market Slows Down Overall, while there are some potential challenges for BTC to overcome in the short term, Van de Poppe&#8217;s analysis suggests that the long-term outlook for Bitcoin remains positive. As of now, Bitcoin trades at $30,100, and it continues to experience a decline in value, representing a 2% drop over the past 24 hours. Additionally, its market dominance, which considers all other cryptocurrencies in the ecosystem, currently stands at 52%. There is a significant contrast between its current dominance and the 72% it achieved in 2021. Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin (BTC) has again taken center stage in the cryptocurrency market as institutional interest surges. This interest has been spurred by major financial giants such as BlackRock, Fidelity, and Ark Invest, who have applied with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) to launch a spot Bitcoin Exchange Traded Fund (ETF). </p>
<p><a href="https://coinmetrics.substack.com/p/state-of-the-network-issue-213" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">According </a>to Coin Metrics, BTC&#8217;s market capitalization dominance has reached a new high for 2023, currently at 58%, the highest since April 2021.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Rules The Crypto Kingdom</h2>
<p>BTC has been the leading digital asset and has maintained its position as the top cryptocurrency for a long time. Its market cap of $586 billion is significantly higher than the industry&#8217;s combined market cap, which stands at $425 billion (excluding stablecoins).</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large wp-image-540224" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/1051ed1c-34e3-4f2e-af33-9e6532cf263e_885x530-860x515.png" alt="Bitcoin " width="860" height="515" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/1051ed1c-34e3-4f2e-af33-9e6532cf263e_885x530-860x515.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/1051ed1c-34e3-4f2e-af33-9e6532cf263e_885x530-460x275.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/1051ed1c-34e3-4f2e-af33-9e6532cf263e_885x530-768x460.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/1051ed1c-34e3-4f2e-af33-9e6532cf263e_885x530-750x449.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/1051ed1c-34e3-4f2e-af33-9e6532cf263e_885x530.png 885w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/>
<p>According to Coin Metrics &#8216; report, BTC&#8217;s dominance fell in the spring of 2021 as traders bid up smaller-cap altcoins, but it never dropped below 40% of the total market.</p>
<p>However, with some newer tokens facing intensified regulatory scrutiny in the US, BTC has pulled ahead in 2023. BTC’s weighting in the CMBI 10, index of the 10 largest cryptocurrencies by market capitalization, is also at a 2-year high of 65%.</p>

<p>Looking at a broader basket of assets, BTC&#8217;s 85% return year-to-date outpaces most of the other major digital assets. Per the report, the only two assets with a greater return year-to-date compared to BTC are Bitcoin Cash (BCH) at 102% and Lido (LDO) at 104%.</p>
BTC Dominance Rallying Trend Ahead?
<p>On the other hand, crypto analyst Michael Van de Poppe recently shared some <a href="https://twitter.com/CryptoMichNL/status/1674077698220539909?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">insights </a>regarding the Bitcoin dominance chart. According to Van de Poppe, &#8220;the chart looks like it wants to continue rallying,&#8221; but there are some key points to remember.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large wp-image-540223" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/FztVzYTWIAAEa7H-860x411.png" alt="Bitcoin " width="860" height="411" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/FztVzYTWIAAEa7H-860x411.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/FztVzYTWIAAEa7H-460x220.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/FztVzYTWIAAEa7H-768x367.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/FztVzYTWIAAEa7H-1536x733.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/FztVzYTWIAAEa7H-750x358.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/FztVzYTWIAAEa7H-1140x544.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/FztVzYTWIAAEa7H.png 1835w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/>
<p>One of the most important takeaways is that in September 2019, BTC tested the 200-week moving average (MA) and exponential moving average (EMA) and encountered resistance. This was 10 months before the Bitcoin halving event in May 2020.</p>
<p>Van de Poppe notes that the current situation is similar to September 2019. BTC is once again testing the 200-week MA and EMA, and whether it can break through this resistance level remains to be seen.</p>
<p>This could be a positive sign for Bitcoin investors, as the halving event was followed by a period of strong price growth for BTC.</p>

<p>Overall, while there are some potential challenges for BTC to overcome in the short term, Van de Poppe&#8217;s analysis suggests that the long-term outlook for Bitcoin remains positive.</p>
<p>As of now, Bitcoin trades at $30,100, and it continues to experience a decline in value, representing a 2% drop over the past 24 hours. Additionally, its market dominance, which considers all other cryptocurrencies in the ecosystem, currently stands at 52%. There is a significant contrast between its current dominance and the 72% it achieved in 2021.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/KktYIhHG/" alt="Bitcoin " width="1814" height="858"/>
<p>Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/roma-kaiuk-O-Cwy6PmG6A-unsplash-340x460.jpg" width="340" height="460" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sui Foundation Refutes Claims Of Dumping Locked Staking Rewards On Binance</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/altcoin/sui-foundation-refutes-claims-of-dumping-locked-staking-rewards-on-binance/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 23:00:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SUI]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SUI Foundation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SUI price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sui token]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SUI tokenomics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SUIUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SUIUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=540209</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The team behind the Sui network and its native SUI token has taken to Twitter to deny allegations of selling locked staking rewards on Binance. Word on the street is that the team moved a huge amount of locked staking rewards and dumped them on Binance to cash in. Sui Foundation Denies Selling Locked Staking Rewards Pump and dump schemes have become very common in the crypto world. According to a report by Chainalysis, 24% of tokens launched in 2022 that were analyzed saw a price decline in the first week indicative of possible pump-and-dump activity.  Related Reading: FTX Puts Sale Of $500 Million Stake In AI Firm Anthropic On Hold According to the foundation, the Sui Foundation has not sold staking rewards or any other tokens from locked and non-circulating staked SUI on Binance or any other exchange. &#8220;All insider token allocations remain subject to and compliant with their lock-ups and other restrictions on transfer,&#8221; said the statement. The Origin Of The Claims A rumor started circulating on Twitter on Thursday that the Sui Foundation was unlocking and dumping locked staking rewards on Binance. According to a Twitter thread by @DefiSquared, a popular crypto trader and commentator, &#8220;locked&#8221; and &#8220;non-circulating&#8221; staked SUI were manipulated by the foundation. The party behind the account claims that the SUI foundation has nearly 3 billion non-circulating and locked SUI staked, which is six times more than the entire circulating supply. DefiSquared also goes on to provide on-chain data showing how millions of SUI rewards were transferred. These tokens were split many times, with most of them ending on Binance. An example was a transfer of 2,500,000 SUI rewards from 0x341f to 0x209f on May 31st. However, The Sui Foundation has since referred to the transaction as a payment subject to a contractual lockup. The specific transaction referenced was a payment subject to a contractual lockup.https://t.co/ViYxQoJMos — Sui Foundation (@SuiFoundation) June 27, 2023 Sui adopts a proof-of-stake consensus mechanism for its blockchain. Its mainnet went officially live on May 3, allowing users to stake their Sui tokens to participate in its proof-of-stake mechanism in exchange for more SUI. Price trending at $0.66 &#124; Source: SUIUSDT on TradingView.com Token Release Schedule The Sui Foundation is yet to publish a token release schedule, more than two months after going live on its mainnet. According to DefiSquared, the supply is actually increasing every day, although the data CoinMarketCap receives shows emissions just once a month. Related Reading: Bitcoin Rally Stalls As Short-Term Holder Exchange Inflows Intensify This comes down to a rough 20% inflation for non-foundation SUI token holders. To address concerns and speculations, the Foundation will publish an official projection of the SUI token vesting and distribution schedule very soon. SUI token is currently down more than 14% in a 7-day timeframe. A subsequent release of 61 million tokens is slated to take place on June 3rd. Featured image from Yahoo Finance, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The team behind the Sui network and its native SUI token has taken to <a href="https://twitter.com/SuiFoundation/status/1673722230596055047?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">Twitter</a> to deny allegations of selling locked staking rewards on Binance. Word on the street is that the team moved a huge amount of locked staking rewards and dumped them on Binance to cash in.</p>
<h2>Sui Foundation Denies Selling Locked Staking Rewards</h2>
<p>Pump and dump schemes have become very common in the crypto world. According to a report by Chainalysis, 24% of tokens launched in 2022 that were analyzed saw a price decline in the first week indicative of possible pump-and-dump activity. </p>

<p>According to the foundation, the Sui Foundation has not sold staking rewards or any other tokens from locked and non-circulating staked SUI on Binance or any other exchange.</p>
<p>&#8220;All insider token allocations remain subject to and compliant with their lock-ups and other restrictions on transfer,&#8221; said the statement.</p>
<h2>The Origin Of The Claims</h2>
<p>A rumor started circulating on Twitter on Thursday that the Sui Foundation was unlocking and dumping locked staking rewards on Binance. According to a Twitter thread by @DefiSquared, a popular crypto trader and commentator, &#8220;locked&#8221; and &#8220;non-circulating&#8221; staked SUI were manipulated by the foundation. The party behind the account claims that the SUI foundation has nearly 3 billion non-circulating and locked SUI staked, which is six times more than the entire circulating supply.</p>
<p>DefiSquared also goes on to provide on-chain data showing how millions of SUI rewards were transferred. These tokens were split many times, with most of them ending on Binance. An example was a transfer of 2,500,000 SUI rewards from 0x341f to 0x209f on May 31st. However, The Sui Foundation has since referred to the transaction as a payment subject to a contractual lockup.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">The specific transaction referenced was a payment subject to a contractual lockup.<a href="https://t.co/ViYxQoJMos" rel="nofollow">https://t.co/ViYxQoJMos</a></p>
<p>— Sui Foundation (@SuiFoundation) <a href="https://twitter.com/SuiFoundation/status/1673722230596055047?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">June 27, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p>Sui adopts a proof-of-stake consensus mechanism for its blockchain. Its mainnet went officially live on May 3, allowing users to stake their Sui tokens to participate in its proof-of-stake mechanism in exchange for more SUI.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/BUAawlIX/" alt="SUI price chart from TradingView.com" width="2884" height="1724"/></p>

Token Release Schedule
<p>The Sui Foundation is yet to publish a token release schedule, more than two months after going live on its mainnet. According to DefiSquared, the supply is actually increasing every day, although the data CoinMarketCap receives shows emissions just once a month.</p>

<p>This comes down to a rough 20% inflation for non-foundation SUI token holders. To address concerns and speculations, the Foundation will publish an official projection of the SUI token vesting and distribution schedule very soon.</p>
<p>SUI token is currently down more than 14% in a 7-day timeframe. A subsequent release of 61 million tokens is slated to take place on June 3rd.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/SUI-token-460x259.jpeg" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Reaches Longest Stretch Ever Without A Bull Run</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-reaches-longest-stretch-ever-without-a-bull-run/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tony "The Bull"]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 22:57:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xbt]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xbtusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=540241</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin is known for its explosive price movements — both bullish and bearish. However, Relative Strength Index data suggests the top cryptocurrency by market cap has gone the longest stretch ever without a bullish impulse. Just how long has it been since the last time BTCUSD was fully bullish? And how does this data compare to past bear markets? Reliving The Thrill Of Past Bitcoin Bull Markets Bitcoin price is retesting $30,000 per coin and bulls are hoping it holds. If it does, yet another higher high could provide further confirmation to onlookers that an uptrend is forming. By definition, an uptrend is a series of higher highs and higher lows — precisely the pattern in BTCUSD since the November 2022 low. But despite this pattern, the crypto market has yet to see a true bull run. Related Reading: Bitcoin Starts To Bite Back Says Reptilian Technical Signal The last major bull market began in late 2020. Prior to that, Bitcoin had a short-lived, 300% rally in 2019. Two years before that in 2017, Bitcoin spent the entire year in a bullish market. This time around, a true bullish impulse is nowhere in sight, and barely in the rear view mirror at this point. It’s been so long since the last bull run, it has now reached the longest stretch ever according to the Relative Strength Index. It’s been a long time since bulls had a turn &#124; BTCUSD on TradingView.com Why The Stampede Is Waiting For An Overbought RSI The Relative Strength Index (RSI) is a momentum measuring tool, which tells an investor if the asset is overbought or oversold. Unlike other assets, the speculative nature of Bitcoin and cryptocurrencies causes them to remain overbought for longer than normal. When this occurs, FOMO fuels a fast and furious price movement higher. Using overbought RSI signals on the weekly BTCUSD chart as a gauge of impulsive behavior, the crypto market has been without a bull market for 973 days. Related Reading: Bitcoin Price Breaks Above $30,000: Is The Bull Run Back On? When compared to past phases of bearishness and boredom, only the 2014 and 2015 bear market comes close. What was once considered the worst bear market on record lasted 959 days before becoming fully overbought on the weekly timeframe. The bull run that followed made Bitcoin a household name and put crypto on the map. Could such a lengthy period of pain and suffering ultimately lead to another epic price increase? For that to happen, BTCUSD must first reach overbought levels on the one week RSI. But considering how long it has been, time is likely ticking away for bears. We are currently in the longest stretch historically without a bullish #Bitcoin impulse, and yet so many still don&#8217;t think there is any chance of another one coming just yet Impulses appear when the weekly RSI reaches overbought pic.twitter.com/r10PjtfBFM — Tony &#8220;The Bull&#8221; (@tonythebullBTC) June 28, 2023 Tony is the author of the CoinChartist (VIP) newsletter. Follow @TonyTheBullBTC &#38; @coinchartist_io on Twitter. Or join the TonyTradesBTC Telegram for daily market insights and technical analysis education. Please note: Content is educational and should not be considered investment advice. Featured image from iStockPhoto, Charts from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin is known for its explosive price movements — both bullish and bearish. However, Relative Strength Index data suggests the top cryptocurrency by market cap has gone the longest stretch ever without a bullish impulse.</p>
<p>Just how long has it been since the last time BTCUSD was fully bullish? And how does this data compare to past bear markets?</p>
<h2>Reliving The Thrill Of Past Bitcoin Bull Markets</h2>
<p>Bitcoin price is retesting $30,000 per coin and bulls are hoping it holds. If it does, yet another higher high could provide further confirmation to onlookers that an uptrend is forming.</p>
<p>By definition, an uptrend is a series of higher highs and higher lows — precisely the pattern in BTCUSD since the November 2022 low. But despite this pattern, the crypto market has yet to see a true bull run.</p>

<p>The last major bull market began in late 2020. Prior to that, Bitcoin had a short-lived, 300% rally in 2019. Two years before that in 2017, Bitcoin spent the entire year in a bullish market.</p>
<p>This time around, a true bullish impulse is nowhere in sight, and barely in the rear view mirror at this point. It’s been so long since the last bull run, it has now reached the longest stretch ever according to the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/topic/relative-strength-index/">Relative Strength Index</a>.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large wp-image-540242 aligncenter" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/8C4A8D93-AD96-4857-B808-B2D5D841B2D9-860x470.jpeg" alt="Bitcoin " width="860" height="470" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/8C4A8D93-AD96-4857-B808-B2D5D841B2D9-860x470.jpeg 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/8C4A8D93-AD96-4857-B808-B2D5D841B2D9-460x251.jpeg 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/8C4A8D93-AD96-4857-B808-B2D5D841B2D9-768x419.jpeg 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/8C4A8D93-AD96-4857-B808-B2D5D841B2D9-750x410.jpeg 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/8C4A8D93-AD96-4857-B808-B2D5D841B2D9-1140x623.jpeg 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/8C4A8D93-AD96-4857-B808-B2D5D841B2D9.jpeg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/></p>

<h2>Why The Stampede Is Waiting For An Overbought RSI</h2>
<p>The Relative Strength Index (RSI) is a momentum measuring tool, which tells an investor if the asset is overbought or oversold. Unlike other assets, the speculative nature of Bitcoin and cryptocurrencies causes them to remain overbought for longer than normal.</p>
<p>When this occurs, FOMO fuels a fast and furious price movement higher. Using overbought RSI signals on the weekly BTCUSD chart as a gauge of impulsive behavior, the crypto market has been without a bull market for 973 days.</p>

<p>When compared to past phases of bearishness and boredom, only the 2014 and 2015 bear market comes close. What was once considered the worst bear market on record lasted 959 days before becoming fully overbought on the weekly timeframe.</p>
<p>The bull run that followed made Bitcoin a household name and put crypto on the map. Could such a lengthy period of pain and suffering ultimately lead to another epic price increase? For that to happen, BTCUSD must first reach overbought levels on the one week RSI. But considering how long it has been, time is likely ticking away for bears.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">We are currently in the longest stretch historically without a bullish <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Bitcoin?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#Bitcoin</a> impulse, and yet so many still don&#8217;t think there is any chance of another one coming just yet</p>
<p>Impulses appear when the weekly RSI reaches overbought <a href="https://t.co/r10PjtfBFM" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/r10PjtfBFM</a></p>
<p>— Tony &#8220;The Bull&#8221; (@tonythebullBTC) <a href="https://twitter.com/tonythebullBTC/status/1674060398184607744?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">June 28, 2023</a></p></blockquote>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/EFD8B4A8-A0C0-478A-82EB-C96D86C18999-460x307.jpeg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Poised For Potential Major Buy Signal In July</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-poised-for-potential-major-buy-signal-in-july/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[dbthequant]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 22:34:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Bullish]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xbtusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=540212</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Spurred by the recent flood of spot Bitcoin ETF applications from Blackrock and Fidelity among others, Bitcoin vaulted impressively up to the $30,000 area where its momentum has stalled in recent sessions. While many analysts and traders routinely acknowledge the significance of the $30,000 level as a key resistance area, Bitcoin&#8217;s move back above its 20-month simple moving average (20-month SMA) may deserve far more attention than it&#8217;s getting. With Bitcoin poised for a potential major buy signal as soon as July 1st, let’s take a closer look at this underappreciated signal. The Simple Line Separating Bull And Bear Phases Bitcoin&#8217;s 20-month SMA currently sits at $29,910 according to the Bitcoin / U.S. Dollar All Time History Index, slightly below Bitcoin&#8217;s current price of just above $30,000. This puts the number one cryptocurrency by market cap barely above its 20-month SMA for the first time since March 2022. What&#8217;s the potential significance? If Bitcoin can end the month of June with a monthly candle close above the 20-month SMA, this will be only the fifth time that this has occurred in all of Bitcoin&#8217;s history, and a signal which has often seen higher prices follow. Bitcoin Monthly Chart with 20-Month SMA  &#124; BTCUSD on TradingView.com Related Reading: Bitcoin Rally Stalls As Short-Term Holder Exchange Inflows Intensify For a clearer picture of the significance of the 20-month SMA, let&#8217;s look at all of Bitcoin&#8217;s monthly closes above the 20-month SMA and below the 20-month SMA. In order to do this, we&#8217;ll create a hypothetical trading system, strictly for analytical purposes, &#8220;buying&#8221; when Bitcoin closes above its 20-month SMA and &#8220;selling&#8221; when Bitcoin closes back below its 20-month SMA. Note that “LE” indicates a buy signal while “LX” indicates a sell signal. The blue highlight shows the periods when the system&#8217;s logic sold Bitcoin following a long exit signal and was out of the market. Bitcoin Monthly Chart with 20-Month SMA  &#124; BTCUSD on TradingView.com What&#8217;s striking in this chart is that 20-month SMA nearly perfectly divides bull phases from bear phases throughout most of Bitcoin’s history from late 2011 to now. For example, exiting once Bitcoin closes below its 20-month SMA sidesteps much of the 2014-2015 bear market, the worst leg down of the 2018-2019 bear market, and so far virtually all of the current 2022-2023 bear market. The early pandemic drop in March of 2020 provides the only exception, with the simple logic getting briefly whipsawed before re-entering at the start of the next month. Bitcoin&#8217;s 20-Month SMA Stats Look Compellingly Bullish Taking our research a step further, let&#8217;s quantify the signals, once again hypothetically &#8220;buying&#8221; when Bitcoin closes above its 20-month SMA and &#8220;selling&#8221; when Bitcoin closes back below its 20-month SMA. From late 2011 to the present, there have been four completed signals with a profitability of 75%, meaning three of the four signals produced a hypothetical gain, and one of the signals produced a loss. Over these four signals, Bitcoin delivered an impressive +2499% hypothetical average trade versus a single worst trade result of -24.8%. While clearly occurrences of these infrequent signals are low (only four to date, and too few to be statistically significant) and the past does not predict the future, we&#8217;ll nevertheless be watching closely to see if Bitcoin can end June with a monthly close above its 20-month SMA. At the moment, sitting just above the key $30,000 level, Bitcoin looks poised for a potential major buy signal in July. DB the Quant is the author of the REKTelligence Report newsletter on Substack. Follow @REKTelligence on Twitter for evidence-based crypto market research and analysis. Important Note: This content is strictly educational in nature and should not be considered investment advice. Featured images created with Tableau. Charts from TradingView.com.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Spurred by the recent flood of spot Bitcoin ETF applications from Blackrock and Fidelity among others, Bitcoin vaulted impressively up to the $30,000 area where its momentum has stalled in recent sessions. While many analysts and traders routinely acknowledge the significance of the $30,000 level as a key resistance area, Bitcoin&#8217;s move back above its 20-month simple moving average (20-month SMA) may deserve far more attention than it&#8217;s getting. With Bitcoin poised for a potential major buy signal as soon as July 1st, let’s take a closer look at this underappreciated signal.</p>
<h2>The Simple Line Separating Bull And Bear Phases</h2>
<p>Bitcoin&#8217;s 20-month SMA currently sits at $29,910 according to the Bitcoin / U.S. Dollar All Time History Index, slightly below Bitcoin&#8217;s current price of just above $30,000. This puts the number one cryptocurrency by market cap barely above its 20-month SMA for the first time since March 2022. What&#8217;s the potential significance? If Bitcoin can end the month of June with a monthly candle close above the 20-month SMA, this will be only the fifth time that this has occurred in all of Bitcoin&#8217;s history, and a signal which has often seen higher prices follow.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium wp-image-540215 aligncenter" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/CHART_BTC-MONTHLY-460x319.png" alt="" width="460" height="319" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/CHART_BTC-MONTHLY-460x319.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/CHART_BTC-MONTHLY-860x597.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/CHART_BTC-MONTHLY-768x533.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/CHART_BTC-MONTHLY-750x520.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/CHART_BTC-MONTHLY-1140x791.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/CHART_BTC-MONTHLY.png 1147w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px"/></p>
<p style="text-align: center">Bitcoin Monthly Chart with 20-Month SMA  | BTCUSD on TradingView.com</p>







For a clearer picture of the significance of the 20-month SMA, let&#8217;s look at all of Bitcoin&#8217;s monthly closes above the 20-month SMA and below the 20-month SMA. In order to do this, we&#8217;ll create a hypothetical trading system, strictly for analytical purposes, &#8220;buying&#8221; when Bitcoin closes above its 20-month SMA and &#8220;selling&#8221; when Bitcoin closes back below its 20-month SMA. Note that “LE” indicates a buy signal while “LX” indicates a sell signal. The blue highlight shows the periods when the system&#8217;s logic sold Bitcoin following a long exit signal and was out of the market.

<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium wp-image-540219 aligncenter" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/CHART_BTC-MONTHLY-SIGNALS-460x233.png" alt="" width="460" height="233" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/CHART_BTC-MONTHLY-SIGNALS-460x233.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/CHART_BTC-MONTHLY-SIGNALS-860x436.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/CHART_BTC-MONTHLY-SIGNALS-768x389.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/CHART_BTC-MONTHLY-SIGNALS-1536x779.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/CHART_BTC-MONTHLY-SIGNALS-750x380.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/CHART_BTC-MONTHLY-SIGNALS-1140x578.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/CHART_BTC-MONTHLY-SIGNALS.png 1566w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px"/></p>
<p style="text-align: center">Bitcoin Monthly Chart with 20-Month SMA  | BTCUSD on TradingView.com</p>
<p>What&#8217;s striking in this chart is that 20-month SMA nearly perfectly divides bull phases from bear phases throughout most of Bitcoin’s history from late 2011 to now. For example, exiting once Bitcoin closes below its 20-month SMA sidesteps much of the 2014-2015 bear market, the worst leg down of the 2018-2019 bear market, and so far virtually all of the current 2022-2023 bear market. The early pandemic drop in March of 2020 provides the only exception, with the simple logic getting briefly whipsawed before re-entering at the start of the next month.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin&#8217;s 20-Month SMA Stats Look Compellingly Bullish</h2>
<p>Taking our research a step further, let&#8217;s quantify the signals, once again hypothetically &#8220;buying&#8221; when Bitcoin closes above its 20-month SMA and &#8220;selling&#8221; when Bitcoin closes back below its 20-month SMA. From late 2011 to the present, there have been four completed signals with a profitability of 75%, meaning three of the four signals produced a hypothetical gain, and one of the signals produced a loss. Over these four signals, Bitcoin delivered an impressive +2499% hypothetical average trade versus a single worst trade result of -24.8%.</p>
<p>While clearly occurrences of these infrequent signals are low (only four to date, and too few to be statistically significant) and the past does not predict the future, we&#8217;ll nevertheless be watching closely to see if Bitcoin can end June with a monthly close above its 20-month SMA. At the moment, sitting just above the key $30,000 level, Bitcoin looks poised for a potential major buy signal in July.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/0195FECF-5AF3-4E5F-BE34-C98D418CD763-460x317.jpeg" width="460" height="317" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Solana Faces Resistance Yet Traders May Find Buying Opportunities Here</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/solana/solana-faces-resistance-yet-traders-may-find-buying-opportunities-here/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[anushsamal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 22:00:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Solana]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sol]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SOLUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SOLUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=540169</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The price of Solana (SOL) has experienced consolidation in recent trading sessions, particularly in light of Bitcoin&#8217;s inability to trade at $31,000. SOL remains below a significant resistance level that the bulls have struggled to overcome for several weeks. Related Reading: Bitcoin Correlation To Gold, Silver Drops To Cyclical Lows: Glassnode On the daily chart, SOL has depreciated by 1.4%. On the weekly chart, the price has slightly declined by just over 2%. The technical outlook appears grim, with limited buying strength indicated by falling demand and accumulation on the daily chart. Solana may require the support of a Bitcoin rally above the $31,000 mark to break past the overhead resistance. This has to be coupled with strength in the broader market. The participation of buyers will be crucial for SOL&#8217;s upward momentum. However, if SOL fails to surpass the immediate ceiling in the upcoming trading sessions, the extended consolidation phase could lead to a price decline. Additionally, the recent decline in market capitalization within the last 24 hours is considered a bearish sign for the altcoin. Solana Price Analysis: One-Day Chart After facing rejection at $17.30, SOL currently trades at $16.30. The coin is encountering overhead resistance at $17. A breakthrough above this level could pave the way for a rally toward $18. Although SOL is currently stuck below the resistance, there may be potential buying opportunities for traders shortly. If consolidation persists, SOL can lose its current price level and decline to $16. Subsequently, it may drop to $15.60, which has served as a Point Of Control (POC) indicated by the red line. The POC represents a significant trading volume, suggesting that it could present a favorable buying opportunity as the coin has historically tended to recover from that point. Technical Analysis Since failing to surpass the $17 mark, SOL has experienced persistently low buying strength. The Relative Strength Index (RSI) has made attempts at recovery, but crossing the 50-mark has proven challenging. As a result, sellers have maintained control of the market. Furthermore, SOL has fallen below the 20-Simple Moving Average, indicating increased downward price action as sellers drove the price momentum. Based on its daily chart, there are promising signs of potential gains for the altcoin. The Moving Average Convergence indicator shows buy signals, as indicated by the formation of green histograms. This suggests a shift in momentum. Related Reading: Cardano Set To Be Delisted On Huobi – Will It Dent ADA Price? Additionally, the Bollinger Bands, which measure price volatility, have converged, indicating that the price is currently constricted. However, this might also imply the possibility of a breakout. If a breakout occurs, SOL could experience a rally of over 10%. Featured image from UnSplash, charts from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The price of Solana (SOL) has experienced consolidation in recent trading sessions, particularly in light of Bitcoin&#8217;s inability to trade at $31,000. SOL remains below a significant resistance level that the bulls have struggled to overcome for several weeks.</p>

<p>On the daily chart, SOL has depreciated by 1.4%. On the weekly chart, the price has slightly declined by just over 2%. The technical outlook appears grim, with limited buying strength indicated by falling demand and accumulation on the daily chart.</p>
<p>Solana may require the support of a Bitcoin rally above the $31,000 mark to break past the overhead resistance. This has to be coupled with strength in the broader market. The participation of buyers will be crucial for SOL&#8217;s upward momentum.</p>
<p>However, if SOL fails to surpass the immediate ceiling in the upcoming trading sessions, the extended consolidation phase could lead to a price decline. Additionally, the recent decline in market capitalization within the last 24 hours is considered a bearish sign for the altcoin.</p>
<h2>Solana Price Analysis: One-Day Chart</h2>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-540172 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/SOLUSD_2023-06-28_20-31-54.png" alt="Solana" width="1817" height="743" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/SOLUSD_2023-06-28_20-31-54.png 1817w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/SOLUSD_2023-06-28_20-31-54-460x188.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/SOLUSD_2023-06-28_20-31-54-860x352.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/SOLUSD_2023-06-28_20-31-54-768x314.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/SOLUSD_2023-06-28_20-31-54-1536x628.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/SOLUSD_2023-06-28_20-31-54-750x307.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/SOLUSD_2023-06-28_20-31-54-1140x466.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1817px) 100vw, 1817px"/>
<p>After facing rejection at $17.30, SOL currently trades at $16.30. The coin is encountering overhead resistance at $17. A breakthrough above this level could pave the way for a rally toward $18.</p>
<p>Although SOL is currently stuck below the resistance, there may be potential buying opportunities for traders shortly. If consolidation persists, SOL can lose its current price level and decline to $16.</p>
<p>Subsequently, it may drop to $15.60, which has served as a Point Of Control (POC) indicated by the red line. The POC represents a significant trading volume, suggesting that it could present a favorable buying opportunity as the coin has historically tended to recover from that point.</p>
<h2>Technical Analysis</h2>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-540175 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/SOLUSD_2023-06-28_20-32-34.png" alt="Solana" width="1817" height="743" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/SOLUSD_2023-06-28_20-32-34.png 1817w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/SOLUSD_2023-06-28_20-32-34-460x188.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/SOLUSD_2023-06-28_20-32-34-860x352.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/SOLUSD_2023-06-28_20-32-34-768x314.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/SOLUSD_2023-06-28_20-32-34-1536x628.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/SOLUSD_2023-06-28_20-32-34-750x307.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/SOLUSD_2023-06-28_20-32-34-1140x466.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1817px) 100vw, 1817px"/>
<p>Since failing to surpass the $17 mark, SOL has experienced persistently low buying strength. The Relative Strength Index (RSI) has made attempts at recovery, but crossing the 50-mark has proven challenging.</p>
<p>As a result, sellers have maintained control of the market. Furthermore, SOL has fallen below the 20-Simple Moving Average, indicating increased downward price action as sellers drove the price momentum.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-540176 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/SOLUSD_2023-06-28_20-33-00.png" alt="Solana" width="1817" height="743" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/SOLUSD_2023-06-28_20-33-00.png 1817w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/SOLUSD_2023-06-28_20-33-00-460x188.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/SOLUSD_2023-06-28_20-33-00-860x352.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/SOLUSD_2023-06-28_20-33-00-768x314.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/SOLUSD_2023-06-28_20-33-00-1536x628.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/SOLUSD_2023-06-28_20-33-00-750x307.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/SOLUSD_2023-06-28_20-33-00-1140x466.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1817px) 100vw, 1817px"/>
<p>Based on its daily chart, there are promising signs of potential gains for the altcoin. The Moving Average Convergence indicator shows buy signals, as indicated by the formation of green histograms. This suggests a shift in momentum.</p>

<p>Additionally, the Bollinger Bands, which measure price volatility, have converged, indicating that the price is currently constricted. However, this might also imply the possibility of a breakout. If a breakout occurs, SOL could experience a rally of over 10%.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/cryptocurrency_Solana_Diamond_Visuals_Alamy-1-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>BNB Market Cap Down By 25% In June Amidst Binance Regulatory Pressure</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/bnb/bnb-market-cap-down-by-25-in-june-amidst-binance-regulatory-pressure/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Semilore Faleti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 21:00:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BNB]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance Coin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=540147</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[BNB, a native token of the Binance exchange, has seen a massive decline in its market shares following the global regulatory pressure on the trading platform.  Binance began experiencing regulatory troubles on June 5, when the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) filed a lawsuit against the exchange on the allegations of fraud and offering of unregistered securities, among others, and this has affected the performance of the cryptocurrency. BNB Loses $10 Billion In Market Cap Following the news of the SEC&#8217;s charges against Binance, its native cryptocurrency BNB, whose market value is tied to the broader performance of the trading platform, saw its market cap drop by 8%, shedding over $4 billion in a single day.  Related Reading: Bitcoin Correlation To Gold, Silver Drops To Cyclical Lows: Glassnode Asides from its struggles on US soil, Binance&#8217;s operations have also suffered some regulatory setbacks in parts of Europe in the last few weeks.  On June 17, the exchange announced the shutdown of its market in the Netherlands due to the inability to obtain a virtual asset service provider (VASP) from the Dutch authorities.  Furthermore, French authorities commenced an investigation into Binance France on the basis of alleged money laundering and illegal canvassing of clients.  Belgium became the latest country to join this growing list of disgruntled nations after its Financial Services and Markets Authorities (FSMA) issued an order directing Binance to cease its operations in the country immediately. Over the last 30 days, all these events have culminated in BNB losing over $12 billion in market shares, representing a staggering 25% decline in the token’s market cap. Moreover, the Binance Coin has also seen its market price fall from $316.56 to trade as low as $223.88 during this period. Although BNB did experience some resurgence in the general market uptrend that occurred last week, it has proven insignificant in turning around the token’s fortunes.  According to data from CoinMarketCap, the coin is exchanging hands at $234.11, with a 2.25% decline in the last 24 hours. Meanwhile, the token market cap now stands at $36 billion, retaining its position as the fourth biggest cryptocurrency in the market.  BNB Market Cap Valued At $36.17 Billion On The 1-Minute Chart &#124; Source: BNB Chart On Tradingview.com What Next For The Cryptocurrency? Following BNB&#8217;s recent negative price movements coupled with its status in the crypto space, there are bound to be high levels of speculation on the token&#8217;s next movements.  According to price prediction site Coincodex, investors&#8217; sentiments surrounding BNB remain bearish, reflecting the present concerns over the token’s fate amidst Binance growing regulatory troubles.  Related Reading: Whale Trades LINK And BNB For PEPE And ETH In High-Value Transaction Coincodex is predicting BNB to maintain its bearish trend, for now, to trade at $226.88 in 5 days, representing a 2.43% gain on the current market price. However, Coincodex is also backing BNB to embark on a market recovery soon as they predict the token to trade by $274.08 in the next 30 days.  That said, predictions are not considered investment advice, and investors are admonished to do their due diligence before engaging the market.  Featured Image: Forbes, chart from Tradingview.com.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>BNB, a native token of the Binance exchange, has seen a massive decline in its market shares following the global regulatory pressure on the trading platform. </p>
<p>Binance began experiencing regulatory troubles on June 5, when the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/sec-sues-binance-and-ceo-for-securities-fraud/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">filed a lawsuit</a> against the exchange on the allegations of fraud and offering of unregistered securities, among others, and this has affected the performance of the cryptocurrency.</p>
<h2>BNB Loses $10 Billion In Market Cap</h2>
<p>Following the news of the SEC&#8217;s charges against Binance, its native cryptocurrency BNB, whose market value is tied to the broader performance of the trading platform, saw its market cap drop by 8%, shedding over $4 billion in a single day. </p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-correlation-gold-silver-drops-cyclical-lows-glassnode/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Bitcoin Correlation To Gold, Silver Drops To Cyclical Lows: Glassnode</a></p>
<p>Asides from its struggles on US soil, Binance&#8217;s operations have also suffered some regulatory setbacks in parts of Europe in the last few weeks. </p>
<p>On June 17, the exchange <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/binance-leave-netherlands-other-eu-countries/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">announced the shutdown</a> of its market in the Netherlands due to the inability to obtain a virtual asset service provider (VASP) from the Dutch authorities. </p>
<p>Furthermore, French authorities <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/binance-allegations-of-aggravated-laundering-france/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">commenced an investigation</a> into Binance France on the basis of alleged money laundering and illegal canvassing of clients. </p>
<p>Belgium became the latest country to join this growing list of disgruntled nations after its Financial Services and Markets Authorities (FSMA) <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/markets-regulator-belgium-binance-suspend-services/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">issued an order</a> directing Binance to cease its operations in the country immediately.</p>
<p>Over the last 30 days, all these events have culminated in BNB losing over $12 billion in market shares, representing a staggering 25% decline in the token’s market cap.</p>
<p>Moreover, the Binance Coin has also seen its market price fall from $316.56 to trade as low as $223.88 during this period.</p>
<p>Although BNB did experience some resurgence in the general market uptrend that occurred last week, it has proven insignificant in turning around the token’s fortunes. </p>
<p>According to data from CoinMarketCap, the coin is exchanging hands at $234.11, with a 2.25% decline in the last 24 hours. Meanwhile, the token market cap now stands at $36 billion, retaining its position as the fourth biggest cryptocurrency in the market. </p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/estuXTI7/" alt="BNB" width="1480" height="913"/></p>

<h2>What Next For The Cryptocurrency?</h2>
<p>Following BNB&#8217;s recent negative price movements coupled with its status in the crypto space, there are bound to be high levels of speculation on the token&#8217;s next movements. </p>
<p>According to price prediction site <a href="https://coincodex.com/crypto/binance-coin/price-prediction/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Coincodex</a>, investors&#8217; sentiments surrounding BNB remain bearish, reflecting the present concerns over the token’s fate amidst Binance growing regulatory troubles. </p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/altcoin/whale-trades-link-and-bnb-for-pepe-and-eth/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Whale Trades LINK And BNB For PEPE And ETH In High-Value Transaction</a></p>
<p>Coincodex is predicting BNB to maintain its bearish trend, for now, to trade at $226.88 in 5 days, representing a 2.43% gain on the current market price.</p>
<p>However, Coincodex is also backing BNB to embark on a market recovery soon as they predict the token to trade by $274.08 in the next 30 days. </p>
<p>That said, predictions are not considered investment advice, and investors are admonished to do their due diligence before engaging the market. </p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/1x-1-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Michael Saylor Doubles Down On Bitcoin, Adds 12,333 BTC To MicroStrategy&#8217;s Holdings</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/michael-saylor-doubles-down-on-bitcoin-adds-12333-btc-to-microstrategys-holdings/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 20:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Microstrategy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=540162</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[MicroStrategy, a publicly traded software company, has once again invested heavily in Bitcoin, adding another 12,333 BTC to its already substantial holdings.  The purchase, which was announced by the company&#8217;s former CEO Michael Saylor, cost around $347 million at an average price of $28,136 per Bitcoin. MicroStrategy Goes All-In On Bitcoin As of June 28th, MicroStrategy now owns a total of 152,333 Bitcoin, which were acquired at an average purchase price of $29,668, for a total cost of approximately $4.52 billion. This latest purchase reaffirms the company&#8217;s bullish stance on BTC, with MicroStrategy now owning one of the largest Bitcoin holdings of any publicly traded company. MicroStrategy has acquired an additional 12,333 BTC for ~$347.0 million at an average price of $28,136 per #bitcoin. As of 6/27/23 @MicroStrategy hodls 152,333 $BTC acquired for ~$4.52 billion at an average price of $29,668 per bitcoin. $MSTR https://t.co/joHo1gEnR0 — Michael Saylor⚡️ (@saylor) June 28, 2023 MicroStrategy&#8217;s decision to invest heavily in Bitcoin has been a topic of discussion and debate within both the traditional financial world and the cryptocurrency community. The company&#8217;s former CEO, Michael Saylor, has been a vocal advocate for BTC, frequently extolling its virtues as a store of value and an inflation hedge. Related Reading: Cardano Set To Be Delisted On Huobi – Will It Dent ADA Price? MicroStrategy&#8217;s initial purchase of Bitcoin in August 2020 was seen as a bold move, given the cryptocurrency&#8217;s reputation for volatility. However, the company&#8217;s investment has paid off handsomely, with the value of its Bitcoin holdings more than doubling in value since its initial purchase. MicroStrategy&#8217;s latest BTC purchase, while significant, is not the first time the company has added to its holdings. In fact, the company has been on a buying spree, having purchased over 100,000 Bitcoin since August 2020. This has made MicroStrategy one of the largest holders of Bitcoin in the world. Nevertheless, the company&#8217;s decision to invest so heavily in BTC has not been without criticism. Some experts have questioned the wisdom of investing such a large amount of capital into a single asset, particularly one as volatile as Bitcoin.  Others have expressed concern over the potential regulatory risks that come with holding such a large amount of cryptocurrency. Despite these concerns, Michael Saylor remains bullish on Bitcoin and continues to advocate for its adoption as a mainstream asset. He has even gone so far as to offer BTC as a form of compensation to MicroStrategy&#8217;s board of directors, demonstrating his commitment to the cryptocurrency&#8217;s long-term prospects. Related Reading: Whale Trades LINK And BNB For PEPE And ETH In High-Value Transaction Overall, MicroStrategy&#8217;s investment in BTC represents a significant shift in the way that traditional companies view cryptocurrencies. While some may view the company&#8217;s actions as risky or imprudent, others see it as a bold and visionary move that could pay off handsomely in the long run. Only time will tell which of these viewpoints proves to be correct. At present, Bitcoin, the leading cryptocurrency in terms of market capitalization, has been experiencing a decline in value but has managed to maintain the $30,000 threshold. As of now, BTC is being traded at $30,100, indicating a 2% decrease in the past 24 hours. Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com ]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MicroStrategy, a publicly traded software company, has once again invested heavily in Bitcoin, adding another 12,333 BTC to its already substantial holdings. </p>
<p>The purchase, which was <a href="https://twitter.com/saylor/status/1674025857063571456?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">announced </a>by the company&#8217;s former CEO Michael Saylor, cost around $347 million at an average price of $28,136 per Bitcoin.</p>
<h2>MicroStrategy Goes All-In On Bitcoin</h2>
<p>As of June 28th, MicroStrategy now owns a total of 152,333 Bitcoin, which were acquired at an average purchase price of $29,668, for a total cost of approximately $4.52 billion. This latest purchase reaffirms the company&#8217;s bullish stance on BTC, with MicroStrategy now owning one of the largest Bitcoin holdings of any publicly traded company.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">MicroStrategy has acquired an additional 12,333 BTC for ~$347.0 million at an average price of $28,136 per <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/bitcoin?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#bitcoin</a>. As of 6/27/23 <a href="https://twitter.com/MicroStrategy?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">@MicroStrategy</a> hodls 152,333 <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24BTC&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$BTC</a> acquired for ~$4.52 billion at an average price of $29,668 per bitcoin. <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24MSTR&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$MSTR</a> <a href="https://t.co/joHo1gEnR0" rel="nofollow">https://t.co/joHo1gEnR0</a></p>
<p>— Michael Saylor<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/26a1.png" alt="⚡" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> (@saylor) <a href="https://twitter.com/saylor/status/1674025857063571456?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">June 28, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p>MicroStrategy&#8217;s decision to invest heavily in Bitcoin has been a topic of discussion and debate within both the traditional financial world and the cryptocurrency community. The company&#8217;s former CEO, Michael Saylor, has been a vocal advocate for BTC, frequently extolling its virtues as a store of value and an inflation hedge.</p>

<p>MicroStrategy&#8217;s initial purchase of Bitcoin in August 2020 was seen as a bold move, given the cryptocurrency&#8217;s reputation for volatility. However, the company&#8217;s investment has paid off handsomely, with the value of its Bitcoin holdings more than doubling in value since its initial purchase.</p>
<p>MicroStrategy&#8217;s latest BTC purchase, while significant, is not the first time the company has added to its holdings. In fact, the company has been on a buying spree, having purchased over 100,000 Bitcoin since August 2020. This has made MicroStrategy one of the largest holders of Bitcoin in the world.</p>
<p>Nevertheless, the company&#8217;s decision to invest so heavily in BTC has not been without criticism. Some experts have questioned the wisdom of investing such a large amount of capital into a single asset, particularly one as volatile as Bitcoin. </p>
<p>Others have expressed concern over the potential regulatory risks that come with holding such a large amount of cryptocurrency.</p>
<p>Despite these concerns, Michael Saylor remains bullish on Bitcoin and continues to advocate for its adoption as a mainstream asset. He has even gone so far as to offer BTC as a form of compensation to MicroStrategy&#8217;s board of directors, demonstrating his commitment to the cryptocurrency&#8217;s long-term prospects.</p>

<p>Overall, MicroStrategy&#8217;s investment in BTC represents a significant shift in the way that traditional companies view cryptocurrencies. While some may view the company&#8217;s actions as risky or imprudent, others see it as a bold and visionary move that could pay off handsomely in the long run. Only time will tell which of these viewpoints proves to be correct.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/NZE2aS1K/" alt="Bitcoin " width="1814" height="858"/>
<p>At present, Bitcoin, the leading cryptocurrency in terms of market capitalization, has been experiencing a decline in value but has managed to maintain the $30,000 threshold. As of now, BTC is being traded at $30,100, indicating a 2% decrease in the past 24 hours.</p>
<p>Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/yigit-ali-atasoy-z1jggXh29_Q-unsplash-460x259.jpg" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Radix (XRD) Down By 11% In A Single Day, As Altcoin Market Slows Down</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/altcoin/radix-down-by-11-in-a-day-as-altcoin-market-slows-down/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Opeyemi Sule]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 19:00:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Radix]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrp]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=540156</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[With decentralized finance (DeFi) gaining more traction, Radix (XRD) is touted to be one of the pioneers of this technological shift. It is a blockchain platform that enables the development of innovative DeFi applications. XRD, Radix’s native token, is one of the worst performers in the market today, recording an 11% loss in the past 24 hours. However, it is worth noting that the general altcoin market is in red today, as most assets are currently in a slight decline.  Radix Experiences Recorrection Following Recent Price Rally The price performance of Radix has been largely positive in 2023. In April, the XRD token reached its yearly peak &#8211; so far &#8211; at $0.139530. However, the cryptocurrency is currently on a 45% price decline, resulting from its slump in April and May. Related Reading: Bitcoin Miners Send 315% Of Daily Revenue To Exchanges Recording High Interaction That said, the Radix market has been showing signs of recovery in June, gaining over 7% in the last 30 days. On June 15, the XRD price found support at the $0.055136 level before commencing its recent bullish run.  According to data from CoinGecko, the token has surged by more than 33% in the past two weeks. However, the token’s price appears to be experiencing a price recorrection at the moment, losing nearly 11% of its value in the past day. As of this writing, the Radix token is trading at $0.076715, with a 24-hour trading volume of over  $5 million. Additionally, the XRD token boasts a market cap of $775.4 million and ranks as the 53rd largest cryptocurrency in the market. XRDUSD trading at $0.075202 &#124; Source: XRDUSD chart from TradingView Whether XRD will resume its bullish trajectory remains to be seen. According to the price prediction site CoinCodex, Radix is expected to rise by more than 31% and cross the $0.1 price point in the next month. The General Altcoin Market Suffers Slight Decline The Radix token is not the only altcoin experiencing a price dip at the moment. Generally, the altcoin market is currently on a decline, with most tokens registering slight losses in the past 24 hours. BNB, for example, has lost 3.2% of its value in the past day. XRP, ADA, and the popular meme coin DOGE are among the other top 10 cryptocurrencies in the red today. As of this writing, the altcoin market cap stands at around $321 billion, representing a nearly 2% drop in the last day. The altcoin market cap at $322.1 billion &#124; Source: TOTAL3 chart from TradingView A broader look at the market shows that altcoins are 20% below their April high. According to crypto analyst Benjamin Cowen, this demonstrates that altcoins (collectively) offer more risk than reward when compared to Bitcoin. That said, some major tokens, such as Stellar (XLM) and Kaspa (KAS) are doing well in the market today, with gains of 5% and 3.5%, respectively. Related Reading: Cardano Set To Be Delisted On Huobi – Will It Dent ADA Price? Featured image from SoFi, charts from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>With decentralized finance (DeFi) gaining more traction, Radix (XRD) is touted to be one of the pioneers of this technological shift. It is a blockchain platform that enables the development of innovative DeFi applications.</p>
<p>XRD, Radix’s native token, is one of the worst performers in the market today, recording an 11% loss in the past 24 hours. However, it is worth noting that the general altcoin market is in red today, as most assets are currently in a slight decline. </p>
<h2>Radix Experiences Recorrection Following Recent Price Rally</h2>
<p>The price performance of Radix has been largely positive in 2023. In April, the XRD token reached its yearly peak &#8211; so far &#8211; at $0.139530. However, the cryptocurrency is currently on a 45% price decline, resulting from its slump in April and May.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-miners-send-daily-revenue-to-exchanges/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Bitcoin Miners Send 315% Of Daily Revenue To Exchanges Recording High Interaction</a></p>
<p>That said, the Radix market has been showing signs of recovery in June, gaining over 7% in the last 30 days. On June 15, the XRD price found support at the $0.055136 level before commencing its recent bullish run. </p>
<p>According to <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/radix" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">data from CoinGecko</a>, the token has surged by more than 33% in the past two weeks. However, the token’s price appears to be experiencing a price recorrection at the moment, losing nearly 11% of its value in the past day.</p>
<p>As of this writing, the Radix token is trading at $0.076715, with a 24-hour trading volume of over  $5 million. Additionally, the XRD token boasts a market cap of $775.4 million and ranks as the 53rd largest cryptocurrency in the market.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/4V2avPg7/" alt="Radix" width="1009" height="591"/></p>

<p>Whether XRD will resume its bullish trajectory remains to be seen. According to the price prediction site <a href="https://coincodex.com/crypto/radix/price-prediction/#:~:text=According%20to%20our%20current%20Radix,0.076794%20by%20July%201%2C%202023." target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">CoinCodex</a>, Radix is expected to rise by more than 31% and cross the $0.1 price point in the next month.</p>
<h2>The General Altcoin Market Suffers Slight Decline</h2>
<p>The Radix token is not the only altcoin experiencing a price dip at the moment. Generally, the altcoin market is currently on a decline, with most tokens registering slight losses in the past 24 hours.</p>
<p>BNB, for example, has lost 3.2% of its value in the past day. XRP, ADA, and the popular meme coin DOGE are among the other top 10 cryptocurrencies in the red today. As of this writing, the altcoin market cap stands at around $321 billion, representing a nearly 2% drop in the last day.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium aligncenter" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/sGB08vBh/" alt="Radix" width="1009" height="591"/></p>

<p>A broader look at the market shows that altcoins are 20% below their April high. According to crypto analyst <a href="https://twitter.com/intocryptoverse/status/1672696669140398081?s=46&amp;t=WkhTj-EULPzEvT2zOAvgfw" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Benjamin Cowen</a>, this demonstrates that altcoins (collectively) offer more risk than reward when compared to Bitcoin.</p>
<p>That said, some major tokens, such as Stellar (XLM) and Kaspa (KAS) are doing well in the market today, with gains of 5% and 3.5%, respectively.</p>





]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/photo_2023-06-28_15-29-03-460x259.jpg" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
