<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
>

<channel>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.newsbtc.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<description>Bitcoin &#38; Cryptocurrency News Today</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 22:13:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Binance Pool&#8217;s Litecoin Hash Rate Falls 50%: What&#8217;s Next?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/litecoin/binance-pool-litecoin-hash-rate-falls-50/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dalmas Ngetich]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 02:00:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Litecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance pool]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cftc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hash rate]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[litecoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[litecoin trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ltc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[viabtc]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=544360</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[As of July 25, on-chain data indicates that the hash rate dedicated to the Litecoin network for mining from Binance Pool, a platform focused on improving miners&#8217; income, is down by over 50% in the past seven months. In crypto mining, hash rate is the cumulative computing power funneled to a proof-of-work network like Bitcoin, Litecoin, or Monero.  These public networks rely on miners distributed across the globe for security, decentralization, and transaction confirmation. Binance Pool Hash Rate To Litecoin Drops By 50% Presently, Binance Pool is allocating approximately 28 TH/s of hash rate to the Litecoin network, a decrease from the average of around 69 TH/s recorded in January 2023. Consequently, Binance Pool has lost its standing as one of the dominant Litecoin mining pools as of July 2023.  As of July 25, Binance Pool is ranked 7th in the Litecoin mining pool scene, accounting for approximately 3.6% of the total hash rate share. In comparison, competitors like Poolin, F2Pool, and viaBTC occupy higher positions, indicating that despite Binance Pool being backed by Binance, the world&#8217;s largest crypto exchange, miners are opting for other pools, some of whom were among the first mining pools in the globe. Related Reading: Ducati Partners With Ripple, Prepares To Launch NFT Collection On XRP Ledger At the moment, it cannot be immediately ascertained as to what the cause can be. However, Binance faces legal challenges in multiple countries, especially in the United States. Two of the country&#8217;s top regulators, the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) and Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), have sued the exchange, accusing them of violating securities laws. Based on the hash rate, viaBTC currently controls the lion&#8217;s share in Litecoin mining, carving out 33% of the total Litecoin network hash rate. F2Pool follows with around 17.2% share, while antpool ranks third with a market share of 13%. Litecoin Pool and Poolin also channel more computing power than Binance Pool. Given the increasingly competitive mining landscape, individual miners must pool their resources and dedicate hash rate through a mining pool. Despite the drop in rankings and hash rate over the last seven months, Binance Pool still plays a critical role in proof-of-work mining networks, including Bitcoin. Halving Incoming, Will LTC Rally? Litecoin currently offers miners 12.5 LTC and transaction fees for each block mined. However, this reward will be halved in the upcoming weeks. The halving even will impact block mining revenue. Nonetheless, a price increase could encourage miners to upgrade their equipment and deploy miners with higher hash rates. Related Reading: Fundstrat Predicts Bitcoin Will Reach $180,000 In 2024, But What’s The Catalyst? Presently, Litecoin has a total hash rate of approximately 780 TH/s, with the network releasing 7,200 LTC to miners daily. However, with the expected supply shock, how Litecoin prices react is yet to be seen. If past cycles guide, Litecoin may rally. According to Litecoin daily price charts, LTC has a resistance at around $115 but is trading below $100. At this level, it is down 23% from July 2023 peaks. Feature image from Canva, chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>As of July 25, on-chain data <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://poolbay.io/crypto/9/litecoin" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">indicates</a> that the hash rate dedicated to the Litecoin network for mining from Binance Pool, a platform focused on improving miners&#8217; income, is down by over 50% in the past seven months. </p>
<p>In crypto mining, hash rate is the cumulative computing power funneled to a proof-of-work network like Bitcoin, Litecoin, or Monero. </p>
<p>These public networks rely on miners distributed across the globe for security, decentralization, and transaction confirmation.</p>
<h2>Binance Pool Hash Rate To Litecoin Drops By 50%</h2>
<p>Presently, Binance Pool is allocating approximately 28 TH/s of hash rate to the Litecoin network, a decrease from the average of around 69 TH/s recorded in January 2023. Consequently, Binance Pool has lost its standing as one of the dominant Litecoin mining pools as of July 2023. </p>
<img decoding="async" class="wp-image-544362 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot366.png" alt="Binance Pool Hash Rate To Litecoin: Pool Bay" width="1217" height="527" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot366.png 1217w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot366-460x199.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot366-860x372.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot366-768x333.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot366-750x325.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot366-1140x494.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1217px) 100vw, 1217px" loading="lazy"/>
<p>As of July 25, Binance Pool is ranked 7th in the Litecoin mining pool scene, accounting for approximately 3.6% of the total hash rate share. </p>
<p>In comparison, competitors like Poolin, F2Pool, and viaBTC occupy higher positions, indicating that despite Binance Pool being backed by Binance, the world&#8217;s largest crypto exchange, miners are opting for other pools, some of whom were among the first mining pools in the globe.</p>

<p>At the moment, it cannot be immediately ascertained as to what the cause can be. However, Binance faces legal challenges in multiple countries, especially in the United States. </p>
<p>Two of the country&#8217;s top regulators, the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) and Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), have sued the exchange, accusing them of violating securities laws.</p>
<p>Based on the hash rate, viaBTC currently controls the lion&#8217;s share in Litecoin mining, carving out 33% of the total Litecoin network hash rate. F2Pool follows with around 17.2% share, while antpool ranks third with a market share of 13%. Litecoin Pool and Poolin also channel more computing power than Binance Pool.</p>
<p>Given the increasingly competitive mining landscape, individual miners must pool their resources and dedicate hash rate through a mining pool. </p>
<p>Despite the drop in rankings and hash rate over the last seven months, Binance Pool still plays a critical role in proof-of-work mining networks, including Bitcoin.</p>
<h2>Halving Incoming, Will LTC Rally?</h2>
<p>Litecoin currently offers miners 12.5 LTC and transaction fees for each block mined. However, this reward will be halved in the upcoming weeks. </p>
<p>The halving even will impact block mining revenue. Nonetheless, a price increase could encourage miners to upgrade their equipment and deploy miners with higher hash rates.</p>

<p>Presently, Litecoin has a total hash rate of approximately 780 TH/s, with the network releasing 7,200 LTC to miners daily. However, with the expected supply shock, how Litecoin prices react is yet to be seen. If past cycles guide, Litecoin may rally. </p>
<p>According to Litecoin daily price charts, LTC has a resistance at around $115 but is trading below $100. At this level, it is down 23% from July 2023 peaks.</p>
<a href="https://www.tradingview.com/x/Ze1VPTqr/" rel="nofollow"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/Ze1VPTqr/" alt="LTC price on July 26| Source: LTCUSDT on Binance, TradingView" width="1226" height="595"/></a>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Binance-Pool-Litecoin-Mining-Hash-Rate-460x260.jpg" width="460" height="260" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tezos (XTZ) Loses Steam In Q2, Market Cap Drops 30% Following SEC Crackdown</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/xtz/tezos-xtz-loses-steam-in-q2-market-cap-drops-30-following-sec-crackdown/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 01:00:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[XTZ]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tezos]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tezos price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XTZ Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XTZUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=544348</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[According to a recent report by crypto research firm Messari, Tezos has been progressing in its roadmap development, with several new features and upgrades being introduced to the network.  The platform&#8217;s core developers have announced a strategic shift to hybrid optimistic/zk rollups, with multiple teams committed to building rollups that will enable the platform to process more transactions per second (TPS) and enhance scalability. Tezos DeFi Ecosystem Booms Per the report, the recent launch of the 14th network upgrade, Nairobi, has brought improvements to the platform, new rollup functionality, and enhanced attestations.  In addition, Tezos core developers have unveiled the Data Availability Layer (DAL), which operates in parallel with Tezos Layer-1 and ensures data availability while scaling bandwidth and storage capacity. Tezos has also been experiencing growing traction in the Decentralized Finance (DeFi) space, with the Total Value Locked (TVL) nearly doubling in the past year. The platform is seeing the launch of several new DeFi protocols, including novel DEXs, lending protocols, and perps protocols. To further support the growth of the Tezos ecosystem, the XTZ Ecosystem DAO has been introduced to manage and distribute XTZ, Tezos’ native token, to support community initiatives.  Nevertheless, despite experiencing a strong Q1 2023, with market capitalization surging from $0.66 billion to $1.03 billion (+55%), outperforming the broader market by 9%, the platform saw a 30% Quarter-over Quarter (QoQ) drop in Q2, ending the quarter with a market capitalization of $0.72 billion, primarily following the SEC&#8217;s complaints against Binance and Coinbase. Related Reading: Here’s How Crypto Offers A Lifeline For This Bahamian Payment Company Furthermore, the total crypto market capitalization during Q2 increased by 2%, driven by Bitcoin and Ethereum, which saw a 7% and 6% rise, respectively, propelled by the introduction of Bitcoin Spot Exchange-Traded Funds (ETFs).  On the other hand, Tezos&#8217; revenue, measured by total gas fees spent (excluding storage costs), experienced an 82% QoQ decrease in Q2, primarily influenced by a 79% decrease in the average transaction fee.  The reduction in the average transaction fee was attributed to the decline of the XTZ price and a slowdown in NFT front-running bidding activities. Fixed Inflation Rate And Burn Mechanisms  Tezos&#8217; native token, XTZ, serves multiple functions within the network, including staking, governance, and payment for gas fees.  The token has a fixed annual inflation rate of 4.4%, with a total supply of 965 million XTZ. The report notes that Tezos has implemented burn mechanisms by creating new accounts or smart contracts and imposing penalties on misbehaving validators.  Moreover, During Q2, Tezos displayed consistent usage levels compared to previous quarters. The network recorded an average of 53,000 daily smart contract calls and 41,000 daily transactions, indicating a 7% decrease and a 1% decline in QoQ, respectively.  However, NFTs remain the key driver of activity on Tezos, while DeFi applications continue to see greater adoption. Related Reading: Bitcoin Coinbase Premium Turns Red, US Institutions Disinterested? Conversely, Tezos&#8217; ecosystem experienced mixed activity, with NFTs and gaming remaining relatively flat, while DeFi continues to see increased activity. Regarding decentralization and staking, Tezos has a globally distributed validator set with a high staking rate relative to other base-layer protocols. Looking ahead, Tezos&#8217; strategic shift in its roll-up roadmap, continued developments in the Data Availability Layer, and the anticipated activation of the Hybrid Optimistic/ZK Rollup hold promise for further growth and innovation on the network.  Overall, Tezos remains a promising player in the blockchain space, with a robust ecosystem and a growing community of developers and users. Currently, the price of XTZ is $0.810801, representing a 0.41% price decline in the last 24 hours and a 2.06% price decline in the past 7 days.  The 24-hour trading volume for XTZ is $15,383,765.48, indicating significant trading activity on the Tezos network.  Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>According to a recent <a href="https://messari.io/report/state-of-tezos-q2-2023" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">report </a>by crypto research firm Messari, Tezos has been progressing in its roadmap development, with several new features and upgrades being introduced to the network. </p>
<p>The platform&#8217;s core developers have announced a strategic shift to hybrid optimistic/zk rollups, with multiple teams committed to building rollups that will enable the platform to process more transactions per second (TPS) and enhance scalability.</p>
<h2>Tezos DeFi Ecosystem Booms</h2>
<p>Per the report, the recent launch of the 14th network upgrade, Nairobi, has brought improvements to the platform, new rollup functionality, and enhanced attestations. </p>
<p>In addition, Tezos core developers have unveiled the Data Availability Layer (DAL), which operates in parallel with Tezos Layer-1 and ensures data availability while scaling bandwidth and storage capacity.</p>
<p>Tezos has also been experiencing growing traction in the Decentralized Finance (DeFi) space, with the Total Value Locked (TVL) nearly doubling in the past year. The platform is seeing the launch of several new DeFi protocols, including novel DEXs, lending protocols, and perps protocols.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-544350" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot_32.jpg" alt="Tezos" width="858" height="425" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot_32.jpg 858w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot_32-460x228.jpg 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot_32-768x380.jpg 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot_32-750x372.jpg 750w" sizes="(max-width: 858px) 100vw, 858px"/>
<p>To further support the growth of the Tezos ecosystem, the XTZ Ecosystem DAO has been introduced to manage and distribute XTZ, Tezos’ native token, to support community initiatives. </p>
<p>Nevertheless, despite experiencing a strong Q1 2023, with market capitalization surging from $0.66 billion to $1.03 billion (+55%), outperforming the broader market by 9%, the platform saw a 30% Quarter-over Quarter (QoQ) drop in Q2, ending the quarter with a market capitalization of $0.72 billion, primarily following the SEC&#8217;s complaints against Binance and Coinbase.</p>

<p>Furthermore, the total crypto market capitalization during Q2 increased by 2%, driven by Bitcoin and Ethereum, which saw a 7% and 6% rise, respectively, propelled by the introduction of Bitcoin Spot Exchange-Traded Funds (ETFs). </p>
<p>On the other hand, Tezos&#8217; revenue, measured by total gas fees spent (excluding storage costs), experienced an 82% QoQ decrease in Q2, primarily influenced by a 79% decrease in the average transaction fee. </p>
<p>The reduction in the average transaction fee was attributed to the decline of the XTZ price and a slowdown in NFT front-running bidding activities.</p>
Fixed Inflation Rate And Burn Mechanisms 
<p>Tezos&#8217; native token, XTZ, serves multiple functions within the network, including staking, governance, and payment for gas fees. </p>
<p>The token has a fixed annual inflation rate of 4.4%, with a total supply of 965 million XTZ. The report notes that Tezos has implemented burn mechanisms by creating new accounts or smart contracts and imposing penalties on misbehaving validators. </p>
<p>Moreover, During Q2, Tezos displayed consistent usage levels compared to previous quarters. The network recorded an average of 53,000 daily smart contract calls and 41,000 daily transactions, indicating a 7% decrease and a 1% decline in QoQ, respectively. </p>
<p>However, NFTs remain the key driver of activity on Tezos, while DeFi applications continue to see greater adoption.</p>

<p>Conversely, Tezos&#8217; ecosystem experienced mixed activity, with NFTs and gaming remaining relatively flat, while DeFi continues to see increased activity. Regarding decentralization and staking, Tezos has a globally distributed validator set with a high staking rate relative to other base-layer protocols.</p>
<p>Looking ahead, Tezos&#8217; strategic shift in its roll-up roadmap, continued developments in the Data Availability Layer, and the anticipated activation of the Hybrid Optimistic/ZK Rollup hold promise for further growth and innovation on the network. </p>
<p>Overall, Tezos remains a promising player in the blockchain space, with a robust ecosystem and a growing community of developers and users.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/26WOGEEF/" alt="Tezos" width="1814" height="858"/>
<p>Currently, the price of XTZ is $0.810801, representing a 0.41% price decline in the last 24 hours and a 2.06% price decline in the past 7 days. </p>
<p>The 24-hour trading volume for XTZ is $15,383,765.48, indicating significant trading activity on the Tezos network. </p>
<p>Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/rodion-kutsaiev-yG9XXLhyyZs-unsplash-460x460.jpg" width="460" height="460" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Analyst Says It’s Time To Buy Dogecoin, Here’s Why</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/dogecoin/analyst-says-its-time-to-buy-dogecoin/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Best Owie]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[doge]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DOGE payments]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dogeusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dogeusdt]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[twitter]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=544296</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Dogecoin remains one of the popular coins despite the crypto bear market and its resilience has seen it garner a significant following. And now, after a long and stretched-out downtrend, a crypto analyst has sounded the buy alarm for the meme coin, giving reasons for this. Time To Buy Dogecoin? According to a crypto analyst known as Kaleo on Twitter, Dogecoin’s current range is a good place to buy. The reasoning for this revolves around expectations that billionaire Elon Musk will integrate the meme coin as a payment method for Twitter. Related Reading: Ethereum Whale Transfers To Exchanges Suggest More Selling Pressure For ETH This comes after the billionaire recently incorporated the infamous DOGE logo on his Twitter profile, placing it next to X, the new symbol for the social media platform. And as Kaleo points out, “There’s a solid chance he actually does something this time though, and him including it in his bio at the same time as the X rebrand isn’t just a coincidence.” However, the analyst also points to the fact that this may not be a completely smooth ride for the altcoin. For example, Kaleo explains that Dogecoin’s current rally could reach a cool-off period where it falls in line with the general crypto market trend. But he added that it would be a good idea to “accumulate on any dips we get from here.” DOGE surges 9% to $0.077 &#124; Source: DOGEUSD on Tradingview.com What Happens To DOGE If It Is A Payment Method On Twitter? Dogecoin becoming a payment method on the Twitter platform (now X) has been long-awaited by not just the DOGE community but the broader crypto market. This is because such an integration will give the cryptocurrency its most significant use case to date, while also exposing it to the hundreds of millions of users of the social media platform. Historically, whenever Elon Musk has tweeted about the meme coin, it has led to a rapid increase in price. So it is expected that such an announcement of Dogecoin being a verified payment method on Twitter will lead to an at least 100% rally for the digital asset. Related Reading: Bullish Signal: Whales Accumulate Massive Amounts Of ARB If DOGE were to be integrated as an accepted form of payment on Twitter, it is possible that the price of the meme coin will rally toward $0.2. However, “it’ll happen fast, and the entire timeline will say it was obvious in retrospect,” Kaleo explains. For now, DOGE’s price is still trending at  $0.077, a 9% increase from its Monday price, according to data from Coinmarketcap. Nevertheless, DOGE remains the 7th-largest cryptocurrency with a market cap of $10.89 billion. Follow Best Owie on Twitter for market insights, updates, and the occasional funny tweet… Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="p2">Dogecoin remains one of the popular coins despite the crypto bear market and its resilience has seen it garner a significant following. And now, after a long and stretched-out downtrend, a crypto analyst has sounded the buy alarm for the meme coin, giving reasons for this.</p>
<h2 class="p2">Time To Buy Dogecoin?</h2>
<p class="p2">According to a crypto analyst known as Kaleo on Twitter, Dogecoin’s <a href="https://twitter.com/CryptoKaleo/status/1683685219134496774?s=20" rel="nofollow">current range is a good place to buy</a>. The reasoning for this revolves around expectations that billionaire Elon Musk will integrate the meme coin as a payment method for Twitter.</p>

<p class="p2">This comes after the billionaire recently incorporated the infamous DOGE logo on his Twitter profile, placing it next to X, the new symbol for the social media platform. And as Kaleo <a href="https://twitter.com/CryptoKaleo/status/1683703702392111105?s=20" rel="nofollow">points out</a>, “There’s a solid chance he actually does something this time though, and him including it in his bio at the same time as the X rebrand isn’t just a coincidence.”</p>
<p class="p2">However, the analyst also points to the fact that this may not be a completely smooth ride for the altcoin. For example, Kaleo explains that Dogecoin’s current rally could reach a cool-off period where it falls in line with the general crypto market trend. But he added that it would be a good idea to “accumulate on any dips we get from here.”</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/poRDeO3U/" alt="Dogecoin (DOGE) price chart from Tradingview.com" width="2884" height="1758"/></p>

<h2 class="p2">What Happens To DOGE If It Is A Payment Method On Twitter?</h2>
<p class="p2">Dogecoin becoming a payment method on the Twitter platform (now X) has been long-awaited by not just the DOGE community but the broader crypto market. This is because such an integration will give the cryptocurrency its most significant use case to date, while also exposing it to the hundreds of millions of users of the social media platform.</p>
<p class="p2">Historically, whenever Elon Musk has tweeted about the meme coin, it has led to a rapid increase in price. So it is expected that such an announcement of Dogecoin being a verified payment method on Twitter will lead to an at least 100% rally for the digital asset.</p>

<p class="p2">If DOGE were to be integrated as an accepted form of payment on Twitter, it is possible that the price of the meme coin will rally toward $0.2. However, “it’ll happen fast, and the entire timeline will say it was obvious in retrospect,” Kaleo explains.</p>
<p class="p2">For now, DOGE’s price is still trending at  $0.077, a 9% increase from its Monday price, according to data from Coinmarketcap. Nevertheless, DOGE remains the 7th-largest cryptocurrency with a market cap of $10.89 billion.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/iStock-1318513754-460x243.jpg" width="460" height="243" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ducati Partners With Ripple, Prepares To Launch NFT Collection On XRP Ledger</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/ducati-partners-with-ripple-prepares-to-launch-nft-collection-on-xrp-ledger/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Opeyemi Sule]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 21:00:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ducati]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrp]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP Ledger]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrpusdt]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=544335</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Following a long-term interest in Web3, Ducati partnered with payment company Ripple and is set to launch its first non-fungible token (NFT) collection on the XRP Ledger this week. This step is the motorcycle company&#8217;s first venture into the Web3 space and blockchain technology. Related Reading: Cardano TVL – A Crucial Factor For ADA Price Revival? Ducati Delves Into Web3; Prepares To Launch First NFT Collection Ducati, a renowned motorcycle manufacturer established in 1926, is set to enter the world of Web3 by launching its first-ever digital collectibles on the XRP Ledger. The Bologna-based firm believes this step is essential to strengthen its relationship with its global community. Claudia Domenicali, CEO of Ducati, commented on the Web3 move: Entering WEB 3.0 is another way to get closer to the Ducatisti community by further extending the number of services offered to them. It also represents an opportunity to meet and make ourselves known to a new community of NFT enthusiasts, giving them the opportunity to live unique Ducati-style experiences and collect the digital assets that we will develop exclusively for this new dimension of the brand. Ducati claims the digital collectible will consist of a video sequence of Ducati logos on tanks of motorcycles manufactured from 1946 to date. This NFT collection is set to go live on the XRP Ledger on July 26, 2023.  Collectibles. Community. Experiences. Ducati enters the #Web3 world with @Web3Pro_ &#38; @Ripple, showcasing Ducati&#8217;s past, present and future. Registration goes live July 26. Join the waitlist now to stay in the know at https://t.co/eFRTFwdvWT pic.twitter.com/IWAHbM1Wfy — Ducati (@DucatiMotor) July 20, 2023 Users who sign up within the first week after launch will receive the Ducati NFT “as a gift.” In addition, these users can access future releases by the motorcycle manufacturer.  It is worth mentioning that Ducati also collaborated with Web3 Pro, a white-label Software-as-a-Service (SaaS) platform, in the execution of this NFT project. A Win For Ripple And XRP Ledger? The XRP Ledger is a public, decentralized blockchain designed by Ripple, the company behind the XRP token. Blockchain technology allows for the creation of tokens, which are IOUs representing any currency value, and the production of NFTs. Indeed, XRP Ledger is not the most popular choice amongst enthusiasts regarding non-fungible tokens. However, the blockchain has been experiencing significant activity recently, with more than 1 million non-fungible tokens minted in the first quarter of 2023. With Ducati set to launch its first-ever NFT collection, XRPL may likely enjoy increased adoption and on-chain activity in the coming months. Moreover, Ripple has been in the spotlight following its victory over the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) on July 13. Related Reading: Ripple’s XRP Sales Jump Significantly In 2023, But Is This Bearish For The Altcoin? It is worth pointing out the timing of Ducati’s NFT rollout on the XRP Ledger. Although it remains unclear whether Ripple&#8217;s recent win is integral to the NFT launch, one cannot deny the positive impact this ruling has had on Ripple’s payment technology lately. Today, July 25, 2023, the Republic of Palau unveiled its collaboration with Ripple Labs to mint its stablecoin. Expectedly, this Palau stablecoin is deployed on the XRP Ledger. XRPUSD trading at $0.69835 &#124; Source: XRPUSD daily chart on TradingView Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Following a long-term interest in Web3, Ducati partnered with payment company Ripple and is set to launch its first non-fungible token (NFT) collection on the XRP Ledger this week. This step is the motorcycle company&#8217;s first venture into the Web3 space and blockchain technology.</p>

<h2>Ducati Delves Into Web3; Prepares To Launch First NFT Collection</h2>
<p>Ducati, a renowned motorcycle manufacturer established in 1926, is set to enter the world of Web3 by launching its first-ever digital collectibles on the XRP Ledger. The Bologna-based firm <a href="https://www.ducati.com/ww/en/news/ducati-announces-its-entry-into-the-world-of-web-3-0-in-partnership-with-nft-pro" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">believes this step</a> is essential to strengthen its relationship with its global community.</p>
<p>Claudia Domenicali, CEO of Ducati, commented on the Web3 move:</p>
<blockquote><p>Entering WEB 3.0 is another way to get closer to the Ducatisti community by further extending the number of services offered to them. It also represents an opportunity to meet and make ourselves known to a new community of NFT enthusiasts, giving them the opportunity to live unique Ducati-style experiences and collect the digital assets that we will develop exclusively for this new dimension of the brand.</p></blockquote>
<p>Ducati claims the digital collectible will consist of a video sequence of Ducati logos on tanks of motorcycles manufactured from 1946 to date. This NFT collection is set to go live on the XRP Ledger on July 26, 2023. </p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Collectibles. Community. Experiences. Ducati enters the <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Web3?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#Web3</a> world with <a href="https://twitter.com/Web3Pro_?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">@Web3Pro_</a> &amp; <a href="https://twitter.com/Ripple?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">@Ripple</a>, showcasing Ducati&#8217;s past, present and future.</p>
<p>Registration goes live July 26. Join the waitlist now to stay in the know at <a href="https://t.co/eFRTFwdvWT" rel="nofollow">https://t.co/eFRTFwdvWT</a> <a href="https://t.co/IWAHbM1Wfy" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/IWAHbM1Wfy</a></p>
<p>— Ducati (@DucatiMotor) <a href="https://twitter.com/DucatiMotor/status/1682087851641454592?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">July 20, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p>Users who <a href="https://t.co/eFRTFwdvWT" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">sign up</a> within the first week after launch will receive the Ducati NFT “as a gift.” In addition, these users can access future releases by the motorcycle manufacturer. </p>
<p>It is worth mentioning that Ducati also collaborated with Web3 Pro, a white-label Software-as-a-Service (SaaS) platform, in the execution of this NFT project.</p>
<h2>A Win For Ripple And XRP Ledger?</h2>
<p>The XRP Ledger is a public, decentralized blockchain designed by Ripple, the company behind the XRP token. Blockchain technology allows for the creation of tokens, which are IOUs representing any currency value, and the production of NFTs.</p>
<p>Indeed, XRP Ledger is not the most popular choice amongst enthusiasts regarding non-fungible tokens. However, the blockchain has been experiencing significant activity recently, with more than 1 million non-fungible tokens minted in the first quarter of 2023.</p>
<p>With Ducati set to launch its first-ever NFT collection, XRPL may likely enjoy increased adoption and on-chain activity in the coming months. Moreover, Ripple has been in the spotlight following<a href="https://bitcoinist.com/ripple-judge-deems-xrp-sale-non-investment-contract/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow"> its victory</a> over the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) on July 13.</p>

<p>It is worth pointing out the timing of Ducati’s NFT rollout on the XRP Ledger. Although it remains unclear whether Ripple&#8217;s recent win is integral to the NFT launch, one cannot deny the positive impact this ruling has had on Ripple’s payment technology lately.</p>
<p>Today, July 25, 2023, the Republic of Palau <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/republic-palau-ripple-labs-mint-first-stablecoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">unveiled its collaboration</a> with Ripple Labs to mint its stablecoin. Expectedly, this Palau stablecoin is deployed on the XRP Ledger.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/OYQP7Bri/" alt="XRP" width="997" height="586"/></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/photo-1615172282427-9a57ef2d142e-2-460x294.jpeg" width="460" height="294" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fundstrat Predicts Bitcoin Will Reach $180,000 In 2024, But What&#8217;s The Catalyst?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-will-reach-180000-in-2024/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 20:00:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin prediction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fundstrat]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=544332</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin has been on the lips of many crypto investors and news outlets for the past few months as major investment companies like BlackRock look to bring on Spot Bitcoin ETFs. The world&#8217;s largest digital currency has also seen an increase in price in the past few months as a result of this, ranging around $30,000 for almost a month.  Now, Fundstrat, an equity research firm based in New York City, has made a daring bullish prediction on the price of BTC. According to the investment research firm, the price of the cryptocurrency could reach $180,000 before its April 2024 halving. Fundstrat Makes Bullish Bitcoin Prediction In a Monday note to its clients, the firm put forward that BTC&#8217;s price could be on the verge of skyrocketing in the next year. A big part of their prediction revolves around the possibility of the trading of Spot Bitcoin ETFs by investment firms spearheaded by BlackRock, the world’s largest asset manager with over $9 trillion in assets. If approved, Spot Bitcoin ETFs could open the gates for mainstream investors and institutions to pour billions of dollars into Bitcoin. Related Reading: Elon Musk Incorporates Dogecoin Symbol In Twitter Bio, Triggering 5% Increase In Price The investment research firm said that the current daily demand for BTC currently at $25 million could skyrocket to $100 million with Spot Bitcoin ETFs. This would put bitcoin ETFs in direct rivalry with the market for precious metals ETFs, which currently has a total market capitalization of approximately $230 billion. &#8220;This [bitcoin ETF launch] would bring daily demand to $125 million, while daily supply is only $25 million. The implied equilibrium price would need to rise so daily supply matches daily demand,” Fundstrat said in the research note. Fundstrat&#8217;s head of digital asset strategy, Sean Farrell, also added: &#8220;We anticipate [a bitcoin ETF] would attract new investors and generate increased demand for bitcoin.&#8221; BTC price recovers slightly to $29,227 &#124; Source: BTCUSD on Tradingview.com  Upcoming BTC Halving Another thing the research note mentions is the influence of the upcoming Bitcoin halving. Done once approximately every four years, the Bitcoin halving cuts in half the reward given to miners for mining a block on the blockchain. Past halvings have been known to reduce inflationary pressure on BTC, thereby steadily increasing its price.  According to Fundstrat, the impending reduction of the daily mining incentive to $6 million from its current $12 million would result in a sizeable increase in the price of Bitcoin in order to achieve a state of equilibrium between buyers and sellers. The effect of the halving is then expected to compound with the Spot Bitcoin ETFs, leading to a greater price increase. Related Reading: Ripple’s XRP Sales Jump Significantly In 2023, But Is This Bearish For The Altcoin? Coincidentally, Fundstrat is not the only firm anticipating BTC reaching the $100,000 mark in the near future. In April, Standard Chartered predicted that a unit of Bitcoin would go for more than $100,000 by the end of 2024. Featured image from iStock, chart from Tradingview.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin has been on the lips of many crypto investors and news outlets for the past few months as major investment companies like BlackRock look to bring on Spot Bitcoin ETFs. The world&#8217;s largest digital currency has also seen an increase in price in the past few months as a result of this, ranging around $30,000 for almost a month. </p>
<p>Now, Fundstrat, an equity research firm based in New York City, has made a daring bullish prediction on the price of BTC. According to the investment research firm, the price of the cryptocurrency could reach $180,000 before its April 2024 halving.</p>
<h2>Fundstrat Makes Bullish Bitcoin Prediction</h2>
<p>In a Monday <a href="https://fsinsight.com/" rel="nofollow">note</a> to its clients, the firm put forward that BTC&#8217;s price could be on the verge of skyrocketing in the next year. A big part of their prediction revolves around the possibility of the trading of Spot Bitcoin ETFs by investment firms spearheaded by BlackRock, the world’s largest asset manager with over $9 trillion in assets. If approved, Spot Bitcoin ETFs could open the gates for mainstream investors and institutions to pour billions of dollars into Bitcoin.</p>

<p>The investment research firm said that the current daily demand for BTC currently at $25 million could skyrocket to $100 million with Spot Bitcoin ETFs. This would put bitcoin ETFs in direct rivalry with the market for precious metals ETFs, which currently has a total market capitalization of approximately $230 billion.</p>
<p>&#8220;This [bitcoin ETF launch] would bring daily demand to $125 million, while daily supply is only $25 million. The implied equilibrium price would need to rise so daily supply matches daily demand,” Fundstrat said in the research note.</p>
<p>Fundstrat&#8217;s head of digital asset strategy, Sean Farrell, also added: &#8220;We anticipate [a bitcoin ETF] would attract new investors and generate increased demand for bitcoin.&#8221;</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/qdfK1Dfg/" alt="Bitcoin (BTC) price chart from Tradingview.com" width="2884" height="1758"/></p>

<h2>Upcoming BTC Halving</h2>
<p>Another thing the research note mentions is the influence of the upcoming Bitcoin halving. Done once approximately every four years, the Bitcoin halving cuts in half the reward given to miners for mining a block on the blockchain. Past halvings have been known to reduce inflationary pressure on BTC, thereby steadily increasing its price. </p>
<p>According to Fundstrat, the impending reduction of the daily mining incentive to $6 million from its current $12 million would result in a sizeable increase in the price of Bitcoin in order to achieve a state of equilibrium between buyers and sellers. The effect of the halving is then expected to compound with the Spot Bitcoin ETFs, leading to a greater price increase.</p>

<p>Coincidentally, Fundstrat is not the only firm anticipating BTC reaching the $100,000 mark in the near future. In April, Standard Chartered predicted that a unit of Bitcoin would go for more than $100,000 by the end of 2024.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/iStock-1356848899-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>UK Regulator To Enquire About Worldcoin, As WLD Declines By 17% One Day Post-Launch</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/altcoin/uk-regulator-to-enquire-about-worldcoin-as-wld-declines-by-17-one-day-post-launch/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Semilore Faleti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 19:00:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Privacy concerns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[uk]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[WLD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[WorldCoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=544309</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[UK data regulator, the Information Commissioner Office (ICO), has laid out intentions to probe the newly launched crypto project Worldcoin.  According to a report by Reuters on July 25, the ICO has taken notice of WorldCoin’s launch in the UK and will now proceed to “making further inquiries.” Launched on Monday, Worldcoin is an Ethereum-based project founded by the CEO of OpenAI, Sam Altman. On the protocol’s official website, it states that Worldcoin aims to be “the world&#8217;s largest identity and financial public network.” To achieve its aim, the network utilizes a digital identification system known as “World ID,” designed to differentiate humans from artificial intelligence online.  Interested Worldcoin users are required to undergo a physical iris scan process at one of the project’s “Orb” locations before being granted a WorldID, prompting much concern over the user’s privacy. Currently, there are three Worldcoin Orb locations in the UK, all of which are based in London. Globally, the crypto project has already managed to establish 125 orbs locations in 20 countries across 5 continents.  Related Reading: Binance Announces Listing Of Sam Altman’s Worldcoin, Opens Deposits Worldcoin Under Criticism Over Privacy Concerns. Although the launch of Worldcoin was greeted with much anticipation and goodwill, the project has also received heavy criticism, especially in relation to its World ID system, which requires users to undergo an in-person iris scan procedure.  Popular crypto lawyer John Deaton, along with many others, believes the process is a threat to users&#8217; freedom and privacy, terming it as “Orwellian.”  In addition, Ethereum Founder Vitalik Buterin also highlighted concerns about the World ID system. In a recent blog post, he stated that an iris scan is likely to reveal more information about users than originally designed.  WLD Declines By 17% A Day After Launch  Following the launch of Worldcoin on Monday, its native token, WLD, had an impressive debut in the market, rising by 88% and hitting a peak price of $3.31. However, the WLD token has since then recorded an overall negative price movement. Based on data from CoinMarketCap, WLD is currently down by 16.76% in the last 24 hours, trading as low as $1.92 within this period.  According to Worldcoin’s whitepaper, WLD is primarily designed as a utility token for network governance. However, the token also serves as a payment medium for specific services in the World App or other crypto wallets.  Related Reading: Countdown To FOMC: What Bitcoin And Crypto Traders Must Brace For At the time of writing, WLD is exchanging hands at $2.13, with a 0.57% gain in the last hour. The token’s 24-hour trading volume is also up by 34.56% and is valued at $403.35 million. With a market cap of $231.09 million, WLD ranks as the 124th largest cryptocurrency in the market.  WLD Trading At $2.2432 On The Hourly Chart &#124; Source: WLDUSDT Chart On Tradingview.com Featured Image From Worldcoin, Chart From Tradingview]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>UK data regulator, the Information Commissioner Office (ICO), has laid out intentions to probe the newly launched crypto project Worldcoin. </p>
<p>According to a<a href="https://www.reuters.com/technology/uk-data-watchdog-make-enquiries-worldcoin-crypto-project-2023-07-25/#:~:text=REUTERS%2FIssei%20Kato%2F%20LONDON%2C%20July%2025%20%28Reuters%29%20-%20Britain%27s,exchange%20for%20a%20digital%20identification%20and%20free%20cryptocurrency." target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow"> report by Reuters</a> on July 25, the ICO has taken notice of WorldCoin’s launch in the UK and will now proceed to “making further inquiries.”</p>
<p>Launched on Monday, Worldcoin is an Ethereum-based project founded by the CEO of OpenAI, Sam Altman. On the protocol’s official website, it states that Worldcoin aims to be “the world&#8217;s largest identity and financial public network.”</p>
<p>To achieve its aim, the network utilizes a digital identification system known as “World ID,” designed to differentiate humans from artificial intelligence online. </p>
<p>Interested Worldcoin users are required to undergo a physical iris scan process at one of the project’s “Orb” locations before being granted a WorldID, prompting much concern over the user’s privacy.</p>
<p>Currently, there are three Worldcoin Orb locations in the UK, all of which are based in London. Globally, the crypto project has already managed to establish 125 orbs locations in 20 countries across 5 continents. </p>

<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/altcoin/binance-announces-listing-worldcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Binance Announces Listing Of Sam Altman’s Worldcoin, Opens Deposits</a></p>
<h2>Worldcoin Under Criticism Over Privacy Concerns.</h2>
<p>Although the launch of Worldcoin was greeted with much anticipation and goodwill, the project has also received heavy criticism, especially in relation to its World ID system, which requires users to undergo an in-person iris scan procedure. </p>
<p>Popular crypto lawyer John Deaton, along with many others,<a href="https://twitter.com/JohnEDeaton1/status/1683573312964685824?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow"> believes</a> the process is a threat to users&#8217; freedom and privacy, terming it as “Orwellian.” </p>
<p>In addition, Ethereum Founder Vitalik Buterin also highlighted concerns about the World ID system. In a recent <a href="https://vitalik.eth.limo/general/2023/07/24/biometric.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">blog post</a>, he stated that an iris scan is likely to reveal more information about users than originally designed. </p>
<p>WLD Declines By 17% A Day After Launch </p>

<p>Following the launch of Worldcoin on Monday, its native token, WLD, had an impressive debut in the market, rising by 88% and hitting a peak price of $3.31. However, the WLD token has since then recorded an overall negative price movement.</p>
<p>Based on <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/worldcoin-org/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">data from CoinMarketCap</a>, WLD is currently down by 16.76% in the last 24 hours, trading as low as $1.92 within this period. </p>
<p>According to <a href="https://whitepaper.worldcoin.org/tokenomics#introducing-wld" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Worldcoin’s whitepaper</a>, WLD is primarily designed as a utility token for network governance. However, the token also serves as a payment medium for specific services in the World App or other crypto wallets. </p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/countdown-fomc-bitcoin-crypto-must-brace-for/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Countdown To FOMC: What Bitcoin And Crypto Traders Must Brace For</a></p>
<p>At the time of writing, WLD is exchanging hands at $2.13, with a 0.57% gain in the last hour. The token’s 24-hour trading volume is also up by 34.56% and is valued at $403.35 million. With a market cap of $231.09 million, WLD ranks as the 124th largest cryptocurrency in the market. </p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/J5zCOyTZ/" alt="Worldcoin" width="1480" height="913"/></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/6cd19b69-82d1-4a78-96ca-44b49d86eaf5-460x259.jpg" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Coinbase Premium Turns Red, US Institutions Disinterested?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-coinbase-premium-red-institutionals-disinterested/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hououin Kyouma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 18:50:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Coinbase Premium]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=544290</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Data shows the Bitcoin Coinbase Premium Gap has turned negative recently, a sign that large US-based investors may be selling currently. Bitcoin Coinbase Premium Gap Has Remained Near Neutral For A While Now As pointed out by an analyst in a CryptoQuant post, the interest from US investors in the asset has declined during the last couple of months. The indicator of interest here is the &#8220;Coinbase Premium Gap,&#8221; which keeps track of the difference between the Bitcoin price listed on Coinbase (USD pair) and that on Binance (USDT pair). The Coinbase exchange is popularly known to be used by US-based investors (especially large institutions), while the Binance platform has a more global audience. Thus, the Coinbase Premium Gap can provide us with hints about the buying or selling pressure differences between these two user bases. When the value of this indicator is positive, it means that the price listed on Coinbase is more than that on Binance. This suggests that American users are potentially participating in a higher amount of buying than global investors currently. On the other hand, negative values of the metric suggest the US-based holders may be doing a higher amount of selling than the worldwide users (or alternatively, they are just buying less of the asset). Related Reading: Will Bitcoin Rebound? This Metric May Be The One To Watch Now, here is a chart that shows the trend in the Bitcoin Coinbase Premium Gap over the last few months: The value of the metric seems to have been around the neutral line in recent days &#124; Source: CryptoQuant As displayed in the above graph, the Bitcoin Coinbase Premium Gap has turned slightly red recently, implying that the price on Coinbase has become lesser than on Binance. This discount implies that the US-based institutional investors have been participating in a heavier amount of selling than the global users during the latest downward move in the cryptocurrency&#8217;s price. Even before this shift towards the small negative values, the indicator&#8217;s value had been mostly around the neutral mark during the last few months, meaning that American investors didn&#8217;t have any interest in accumulating the asset any more than the rest of the world. Related Reading: Bitcoin Sharks Continue Accumulation, But Whales Stagnate Back during the selloff in June, the US-based holders had even been applying notable selling pressure, as the metric&#8217;s value had been negative. This selloff was due to US-focused FUD from the SEC cases against Binance and Coinbase, so it makes sense that this side of the market was selling to a higher degree. Earlier during the year, though, the US institutional investors had seemed very much interested in the asset, as they had been participating in a high amount of accumulation, which had resulted in the metric turning highly positive. At present, however, it would appear that large American investors continue to be disinterested in Bitcoin, considering that the Premium Gap is still floating near the neutral line. This low level of interest could translate to further downward movement for the digital asset as it struggles to hold above $29,000. BTC Price At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading around $29,200, down 3% in the last week. BTC has observed a plunge recently &#124; Source: BTCUSD on TradingView Featured image from Kanchanara on Unsplash.com, charts from TradingView.com, CryptoQuant.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Data shows the Bitcoin Coinbase Premium Gap has turned negative recently, a sign that large US-based investors may be selling currently.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Coinbase Premium Gap Has Remained Near Neutral For A While Now</h2>
<p>As pointed out by an analyst in a CryptoQuant <a href="https://cryptoquant.com/insights/quicktake/64beb75580aa183d1d9cb514-The-Coinbase-Premium-Gap-signals-the-weak-mood-of-US-institutional-investors" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">post</a>, the interest from US investors in the asset has declined during the last couple of months. The indicator of interest here is the &#8220;<a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-coinbase-premium-buying-ending/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Coinbase Premium Gap</a>,&#8221; which keeps track of the difference between the Bitcoin price listed on Coinbase (USD pair) and that on Binance (USDT pair).</p>
<p>The Coinbase exchange is popularly known to be used by US-based investors (especially large institutions), while the Binance platform has a more global audience. Thus, the Coinbase Premium Gap can provide us with hints about the buying or selling pressure differences between these two user bases.</p>
<p>When the value of this indicator is positive, it means that the price listed on Coinbase is more than that on Binance. This suggests that American users are potentially participating in a higher amount of buying than global investors currently.</p>
<p>On the other hand, negative values of the metric suggest the US-based holders may be doing a higher amount of selling than the worldwide users (or alternatively, they are just buying less of the asset).</p>

<p>Now, here is a chart that shows the trend in the Bitcoin Coinbase Premium Gap over the last few months:</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone aligncenter" src="https://img.cryptoquant.com/35304/quicktake/BTE4f0Lm9_c8d15a8f4e22daad095b3f2aa5dcadf2f3b499286842fcfc91cf00bc64db68cb.png" alt="Bitcoin Coinbase Premium" width="1192" height="505"/></p>

<p>As displayed in the above graph, the Bitcoin Coinbase Premium Gap has turned slightly red recently, implying that the price on Coinbase has become lesser than on Binance.</p>
<p>This discount implies that the US-based institutional investors have been participating in a heavier amount of selling than the global users during the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-plunge-to-29200-sends-5-9-of-supply-into-loss/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">latest downward move</a> in the cryptocurrency&#8217;s price.</p>
<p>Even before this shift towards the small negative values, the indicator&#8217;s value had been mostly around the neutral mark during the last few months, meaning that American investors didn&#8217;t have any interest in accumulating the asset any more than the rest of the world.</p>

<p>Back during the selloff in June, the US-based holders had even been applying notable selling pressure, as the metric&#8217;s value had been negative. This selloff was due to US-focused FUD from the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin-price-hammered-below-25000-amid-the-feds-hawkish-tone-sec-lawsuits/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">SEC cases</a> against Binance and Coinbase, so it makes sense that this side of the market was selling to a higher degree.</p>
<p>Earlier during the year, though, the US institutional investors had seemed very much interested in the asset, as they had been participating in a high amount of accumulation, which had resulted in the metric turning highly positive.</p>
<p>At present, however, it would appear that large American investors continue to be disinterested in Bitcoin, considering that the Premium Gap is still floating near the neutral line.</p>
<p>This low level of interest could translate to further downward movement for the digital asset as it struggles to hold above $29,000.</p>
<h2>BTC Price</h2>
<p>At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading around $29,200, down 3% in the last week.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium aligncenter" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/33sf4ktY/" alt="Bitcoin Price Chart" width="1534" height="877"/></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/kanchanara-Lta5b8mPytw-unsplash-1-460x306.jpg" width="460" height="306" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Worldcoin Founder’s Refusal To Answer Token Distribution Question Sparks Controversy</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/altcoin/worldcoin-founders-token-distribution/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 16:30:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tokenomics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[WLD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[WLD tokenomics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[WorldCoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=544295</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Worldcoin co-founder Alex Blania&#8217;s recent refusal to disclose the token’s distribution model has raised some eyebrows, including that of John Deaton, who has expressed his dismay at his action. Something Fishy With Worldcoin? A video surfaced on Twitter in which Alex Blania, during a recent Bankless interview alongside fellow co-founder Sam Altman, refused to respond to the host’s question on Worldcoin’s token distribution, citing the regulatory uncertainty in the US as why he couldn’t answer the question.  Related Reading: Binance Announces Listing Of Sam Altman’s Worldcoin, Opens Deposits The Twitter user (@Pledditor) posted the video with the caption: “When a crypto founder refuses to answer questions about token distribution🚩🚩🚩” In the video, the host asks Blania to explain the distribution of the WLD token and Blania is quoted as saying: “Look, many of the details we can’t talk about here for the regulatory uncertainty in the United States.”  The video quickly went viral and sparked controversy as to whether Worldcoin was just another ‘ponzinomics’ or, indeed, Alex Blania was honest about why he couldn’t answer the question.  However, renowned crypto lawyer John Deaton, who represents some XRP holders, quickly reacted to the video in a tweet. Deaton’s tweet read: Wtf did this dude just say?  Did he literally say that he can’t talk about how WorldCoin is distributed “because of the regulatory uncertainty” in the United States? 🤦‍♂️  If there was ever a signal to RUN AWAY as fast as you can from a project, HERE IT IS. Is he saying he can’t tell you how to acquire it or what you’re acquiring because he might get sued? 🤷‍♂️  Now that I think of it, is he being smart and just following legal advice or is he a moron. 🤷‍♂️  Deaton stated that Blania’s action was enough reason for investors to run away from the project. However, the SEC and its Chair Gary Gensler weren’t spared from Deaton’s wrath as he also slammed them for their role in creating a state of turmoil regarding the regulatory environment in the crypto space.  “But this is an example of the chaos caused when you have bad faith regulators like @GaryGensler intentionally keeping the regulatory environment as unknowable,” Deaton said. A Bad Start For WLD? This development comes less than 48 hours after the launch of Worldcoin’s highly-anticipated WLD token. There were, however, some positives for the token as leading crypto exchanges like Binance, Gate.io, and KuCoin were quick to list it upon launch.  WLD price recovers above $2.2 &#124; Source: WLDUSD on Tradingview.com Founded by OpenAI’s CEO Altman, Worldcoin aims to solve the problem of differentiating between humans and bot-related projects. This problem has stemmed from the growing use of artificial intelligence in almost all spheres of life. The team plans to resolve this by giving humans unique digital identities to differentiate them from artificial intelligence algorithms.  Related Reading: Elon Musk Incorporates Dogecoin Symbol In Twitter Bio, Triggering 5% Increase In Price The WLD token spiked to as high as $3.30 upon launch. However, it seems the token’s price has negatively reacted to the issue of its token distribution and other privacy concerns as it dumped to as low as $1.66 on Monday, according to data from CoinGeko. WLD is currently trading at around $2.12 at the time of writing, with a 16% decrease in the last 24 hours. Featured image from Altcoin Buzz, chart from Tradingview.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Worldcoin co-founder Alex Blania&#8217;s recent refusal to disclose the token’s distribution model has raised some eyebrows, including that of John Deaton, who has expressed his dismay at his action.</p>
<h2>Something Fishy With Worldcoin?</h2>
<p>A <a href="https://twitter.com/Pledditor/status/1683388758933098496?s=20" rel="nofollow">video</a> surfaced on Twitter in which Alex Blania, during a recent Bankless interview alongside fellow co-founder Sam Altman, refused to respond to the host’s question on Worldcoin’s token distribution, citing the regulatory uncertainty in the US as why he couldn’t answer the question. </p>

<p>The Twitter user (@Pledditor) posted the video with the <a href="https://twitter.com/Pledditor/status/1683388758933098496?s=20" rel="nofollow">caption</a>:</p>
<p><i>“When a crypto founder refuses to answer questions about token distribution<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f6a9.png" alt="🚩" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f6a9.png" alt="🚩" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f6a9.png" alt="🚩" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />”</i></p>
<p>In the video, the host asks Blania to explain the distribution of the WLD token and Blania is quoted as saying: “Look, many of the details we can’t talk about here for the regulatory uncertainty in the United States.” </p>
<p>The video quickly went viral and sparked controversy as to whether Worldcoin was just another ‘ponzinomics’ or, indeed, Alex Blania was honest about why he couldn’t answer the question. </p>
<p>However, renowned crypto lawyer John Deaton, who represents some XRP holders, quickly reacted to the video in a tweet.</p>
<p>Deaton’s <a href="https://twitter.com/JohnEDeaton1/status/1683550906615316480?s=20" rel="nofollow">tweet</a> read:</p>
<blockquote><p>Wtf did this dude just say?  Did he literally say that he can’t talk about how WorldCoin is distributed “because of the regulatory uncertainty” in the United States? <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f926-200d-2642-fe0f.png" alt="🤦‍♂️" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> </p>
<p>If there was ever a signal to RUN AWAY as fast as you can from a project, HERE IT IS. Is he saying he can’t tell you how to acquire it or what you’re acquiring because he might get sued? <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f937-200d-2642-fe0f.png" alt="🤷‍♂️" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> </p>
<p>Now that I think of it, is he being smart and just following legal advice or is he a moron. <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f937-200d-2642-fe0f.png" alt="🤷‍♂️" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> </p></blockquote>
<p>Deaton stated that Blania’s action was enough reason for investors to run away from the project. However, the SEC and its Chair Gary Gensler weren’t spared from Deaton’s wrath as he also slammed them for their role in creating a state of turmoil regarding the regulatory environment in the crypto space. </p>
<p>“But this is an example of the chaos caused when you have bad faith regulators like @GaryGensler intentionally keeping the regulatory environment as unknowable,” Deaton said.</p>
<h2>A Bad Start For WLD?</h2>
<p>This development comes less than 48 hours after the launch of Worldcoin’s highly-anticipated WLD token. There were, however, some positives for the token as leading crypto exchanges like Binance, Gate.io, and KuCoin were quick to list it upon launch. </p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/EnKCY55C/" alt="Worldcoin (WLD) price chart from Tradingview.com" width="2884" height="1758"/></p>

<p>Founded by OpenAI’s CEO Altman, Worldcoin aims to solve the problem of differentiating between humans and bot-related projects. This problem has stemmed from the growing use of artificial intelligence in almost all spheres of life. The team plans to resolve this by giving humans unique digital identities to differentiate them from artificial intelligence algorithms. </p>

<p>The WLD token spiked to as high as $3.30 upon launch. However, it seems the token’s price has negatively reacted to the issue of its token distribution and other privacy concerns as it dumped to as low as $1.66 on Monday, according to data from <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/worldcoin" rel="nofollow">CoinGeko</a>. WLD is currently trading at around $2.12 at the time of writing, with a 16% decrease in the last 24 hours.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Worldcoin-WLD-1.jpeg" width="310" height="163" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Here’s How Crypto Offers A Lifeline For This Bahamian Payment Company</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/crypto-payments-by-bahamian-payment-company/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[anushsamal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 15:30:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[circle]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto remittances]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Island Pay]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LATAM]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Rifos]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[The World Bank]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USDC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=544279</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Latin American region faces high costs and challenges of traditional settlements, as people sending money to their close ones have to deal with high rates of transfer, and a portion of the population still remains unbanked. However, in a recent development, the Bahamas payment company, Island Pay, is now incorporating cryptocurrency for remittance transactions to make it a smoother and cheaper process. Island Pay is set to introduce crypto wallets that utilize the stablecoin USDC as the medium of exchange. The payment firm plans to roll out the CiNKO wallet in more than 30 countries. The wallet which caters to users in the Caribbean and LATAM regions will enable individuals to conduct transactions with vendors, make payments to others (including those without bank accounts), and fund pre-paid cards. Island Pay CEO Richard Douglas stated: Our goal is to continuously look for ways to advance financial inclusion in the region and enhance financial experiences for both the unbanked and banked populations. Related Reading: Will Bitcoin Rebound? This Metric May Be The One To Watch Crypto Revolutionizes Remittance Landscape, Advancing Financial Inclusion By integrating crypto for remittance, Island Pay demonstrates its commitment to fostering financial inclusion and enriching monetary experiences for both banked and unbanked individuals in the region. The incorporation of this technology will lead to significant reductions in international money transfer fees. When receiving USDC stablecoins on CiNKO, users will not be charged. They may, however, encounter gas fees, depending on the blockchain network used for the transaction. The demand for crypto transactions has surged due to the existing challenges in conventional remittance methods. According to the World Bank, the average cost of sending $200 can be as high as 6.2%. Additionally, these transactions often take several days to process through traditional financial intermediaries. As pointed out in Circle&#8217;s recent report, the technology has the potential to slash the cost of sending money abroad by a substantial 80%. This report predicts that Blockchain&#8217;s capacity to enhance cost savings for financial institutions engaged in cross-border transactions will reach a market cap of $10 billion by the year 2030. Even before this, the Bahamas boasted a well-established presence in the fintech sector, with various global payment platforms and crypto wallets operating in the region. Rifos disclosed that the remittance and payments sectors are currently the fastest-growing fintech segments in LATAM. The surge in smartphone adoption and connectivity has also played a crucial role in fostering innovation and advancements in these areas. Related Reading: Aave May Rally 20% Supported by Historical Levels, But Crucial Resistance Remains Despite the high fees with traditional channels, remittances to Latin America and the Caribbean witnessed remarkable growth. There has been a 27% increase in 2021 and an 11% increase in 2022, with a total of $145 billion in 2017. The region&#8217;s GDP is expected to slow down to 3.3% this year, but remittances are expected to reach an all-time high. Featured image from Freeman Law, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Latin American region faces high costs and challenges of traditional settlements, as people sending money to their close ones have to deal with high rates of transfer, and a portion of the population still remains unbanked.</p>
<p>However, in a recent<a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-07-25/bahamas-payment-platform-island-pay-is-latest-to-offer-crypto-remittance?leadSource=uverify%20wall" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow"> development</a>, the Bahamas payment company, Island Pay, is now incorporating cryptocurrency for remittance transactions to make it a smoother and cheaper process.</p>
<p>Island Pay is set to introduce crypto wallets that utilize the stablecoin USDC as the medium of exchange. The payment firm plans to roll out the CiNKO wallet in more than 30 countries.</p>
<p>The wallet which caters to users in the Caribbean and LATAM regions will enable individuals to conduct transactions with vendors, make payments to others (including those without bank accounts), and fund pre-paid cards.</p>
<p>Island Pay CEO Richard Douglas stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>Our goal is to continuously look for ways to advance financial inclusion in the region and enhance financial experiences for both the unbanked and banked populations.</p></blockquote>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/will-bitcoin-rebound-this-metric-may-be-the-one-to-watch/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Will Bitcoin Rebound? This Metric May Be The One To Watch</a></p>
<h2>Crypto Revolutionizes Remittance Landscape, Advancing Financial Inclusion</h2>
<p>By integrating crypto for remittance, Island Pay demonstrates its commitment to fostering financial inclusion and enriching monetary experiences for both banked and unbanked individuals in the region.</p>
<p>The incorporation of this technology will lead to significant reductions in international money transfer fees. When receiving USDC stablecoins on CiNKO, users will not be charged. They may, however, encounter gas fees, depending on the blockchain network used for the transaction.</p>
<p>The demand for crypto transactions has surged due to the existing challenges in conventional remittance methods.<a href="https://www.worldbank.org/en/news/press-release/2023/06/13/remittances-remain-resilient-likely-to-slow#:~:text=The%20top%20five%20recipient%20countries,and%20Pakistan%20(%2430%20billion)." target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow"> According</a> to the World Bank, the average cost of sending $200 can be as high as 6.2%. Additionally, these transactions often take several days to process through traditional financial intermediaries.</p>
<p>As pointed out in Circle&#8217;s recent report, the technology has the potential to slash the cost of sending money abroad by a substantial 80%. This report predicts that Blockchain&#8217;s capacity to enhance cost savings for financial institutions engaged in cross-border transactions will reach a market cap of $10 billion by the year 2030.</p>
<p>Even before this, the Bahamas boasted a well-established presence in the fintech sector, with various global payment platforms and crypto wallets operating in the region.</p>
<p>Rifos<a href="https://www.rifos.org/remittance-report/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow"> disclosed</a> that the remittance and payments sectors are currently the fastest-growing fintech segments in LATAM. The surge in smartphone adoption and connectivity has also played a crucial role in fostering innovation and advancements in these areas.</p>

<p>Despite the high fees with traditional channels, remittances to Latin America and the Caribbean witnessed remarkable growth. There has been a 27% increase in 2021 and an 11% increase in 2022, with a total of $145 billion in 2017.</p>
<p>The region&#8217;s GDP is expected to slow down to 3.3% this year, but remittances are expected to reach an all-time high.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-544300 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/TOTAL_2023-07-25_16-41-38.png" alt="Crypto" width="1818" height="830" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/TOTAL_2023-07-25_16-41-38.png 1818w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/TOTAL_2023-07-25_16-41-38-460x210.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/TOTAL_2023-07-25_16-41-38-860x393.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/TOTAL_2023-07-25_16-41-38-768x351.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/TOTAL_2023-07-25_16-41-38-1536x701.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/TOTAL_2023-07-25_16-41-38-750x342.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/TOTAL_2023-07-25_16-41-38-1140x520.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1818px) 100vw, 1818px"/>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/AdobeStock_419491555-scaled-1-460x307.jpeg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ripple&#8217;s XRP Sales Jump Significantly In 2023, But Is This Bearish For The Altcoin?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/ripple-xrp-sales-jump-in-2023/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 14:33:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple holdings]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrp]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrpusdt]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=544266</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Ripple’s sales in 2023 have caused mixed feelings for members of the Ripple community, with many considering it bullish for the network while others see it as detrimental to XRP’s price action.  What Has Happened With Ripple’s Sales? Compared to 2022, Ripple sold 37% more XRP per month in 2023, and a recent tweet by Mr. Huber, an influencer in the XRP community, drew many’s attention to this development.  Related Reading: Elon Musk Incorporates Dogecoin Symbol In Twitter Bio, Triggering 5% Increase In Price &#8220;Ripple sold 2.22 billion XRP since 2023 started. That&#8217;s about 315 million per month. About 50% more than the usual 200 million in 2022. Now the crying is about to start. But I can reassure you. It is not XRP Tards who have bought these 2.2 billion XRP and XRP has outperformed anyway. No matter what you feel,&#8221; Huber said. It is important to mention that Mr. Huber initially made a mistake regarding the percentage increase in monthly sales from last year, which stands at 37% against the 50% he initially tweeted. He, however, quickly corrected it in a follow-up tweet. Despite this, 37% remains a lot, and these figures will undoubtedly raise eyebrows about what is going on with Ripple and how XRP’s price will react to these sales, whether it will bring about a massive rise in XRP’s price or a steady decline.  XRP’s circulation does justice to these claims, as the number of XRPs in circulation has grown exponentially. XRP’s circulating supply was 50.334 billion at the beginning of the year but now stands at 52.554 billion after Ripple&#8217;s sales and monthly escrow releases. That is an additional 2.2 billion XRPs put in circulation since January and a 4.4% increase, and the year is far from over.  In 2021, Ripple sold 2 billion XRPs, amounting to 166 million XRPs being sold on an average monthly basis. In 2022, it sold 2.75 billion XRPs, an average of 230 million tokens sold monthly.  XRP holding steady above $0.7 &#124; Source: XRPUSD on Tradingview.com In 2023, Ripple has sold 2.22 billion XRPs since the start of the year, amounting to an average of 315 million tokens sold monthly since January. That proves that Ripple has increased XRP sales massively since 2021. What Does This Mean For Ripple And Its Community? These figures could be both good and bad news for XRP and its community. On the positive side, it shows that there has been a greater demand for the token over the years, which signifies growth and wider adoption of the token.  This demand may mainly be coming from institutional investors, which could undoubtedly expand the use cases of XRP beyond the cryptocurrency space. While on the negative side, having so much XRP in circulation without a deflationary mechanism could reduce the token’s value. Related Reading: Binance Announces Listing Of Sam Altman’s Worldcoin, Opens Deposits For now, XRP’s price seems to be feeling the heat as the altcoin’s price is down 4.89% in the last 24 hours to trade at $0.688. Nevertheless, its daily volume is up 8.69%, pointing to a rise in trading activity.  Featured image from Analytics Insight, chart from Tradingview.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ripple’s sales in 2023 have caused mixed feelings for members of the Ripple community, with many considering it bullish for the network while others see it as detrimental to XRP’s price action. </p>
<h2>What Has Happened With Ripple’s Sales?</h2>
<p>Compared to 2022, Ripple sold 37% more XRP per month in 2023, and a recent <a href="https://twitter.com/Leerzeit/status/1683556697640402946?s=20" rel="nofollow">tweet</a> by Mr. Huber, an influencer in the XRP community, drew many’s attention to this development. </p>

<p>&#8220;Ripple sold 2.22 billion XRP since 2023 started. That&#8217;s about 315 million per month. About 50% more than the usual 200 million in 2022. Now the crying is about to start. But I can reassure you. It is not XRP Tards who have bought these 2.2 billion XRP and XRP has outperformed anyway. No matter what you feel,&#8221; Huber said.</p>
<p>It is important to mention that Mr. Huber initially made a mistake regarding the percentage increase in monthly sales from last year, which stands at 37% against the 50% he initially tweeted. He, however, quickly corrected it in a follow-up tweet.</p>
<p>Despite this, 37% remains a lot, and these figures will undoubtedly raise eyebrows about what is going on with Ripple and how XRP’s price will react to these sales, whether it will bring about a massive rise in XRP’s price or a steady decline. </p>
<p>XRP’s circulation does justice to these claims, as the number of XRPs in circulation has grown exponentially. XRP’s circulating supply was 50.334 billion at the beginning of the year but now stands at 52.554 billion after Ripple&#8217;s sales and monthly escrow releases. That is an additional 2.2 billion XRPs put in circulation since January and a 4.4% increase, and the year is far from over. </p>
<p>In 2021, Ripple sold 2 billion XRPs, amounting to 166 million XRPs being sold on an average monthly basis. In 2022, it sold 2.75 billion XRPs, an average of 230 million tokens sold monthly. </p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/UMrSoXRL/" alt="Ripple ( XRP) price chart from Tradingview.com" width="2884" height="1758"/></p>

<p>In 2023, Ripple has sold 2.22 billion XRPs since the start of the year, amounting to an average of 315 million tokens sold monthly since January. That proves that Ripple has increased XRP sales massively since 2021.</p>
<h2>What Does This Mean For Ripple And Its Community?</h2>
<p>These figures could be both good and bad news for XRP and its community. On the positive side, it shows that there has been a greater demand for the token over the years, which signifies growth and wider adoption of the token. </p>
<p>This demand may mainly be coming from institutional investors, which could undoubtedly expand the use cases of XRP beyond the cryptocurrency space. While on the negative side, having so much XRP in circulation without a deflationary mechanism could reduce the token’s value.</p>

<p>For now, XRP’s price seems to be feeling the heat as the altcoin’s price is down 4.89% in the last 24 hours to trade at $0.688. Nevertheless, its daily volume is up 8.69%, pointing to a rise in trading activity. </p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ripple-XRP-460x307.png" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
