<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
>

<channel>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.newsbtc.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<description>Bitcoin &#38; Cryptocurrency News Today</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 03:00:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Price Extends Recovery But Lack of Momentum Remains A Concern</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-extends-recovery-27k/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 03:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xbtusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=538653</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin price is rising above the $26,500 resistance. BTC could gain bullish momentum if it settles above the $27,200 and $27,500 resistance levels. Bitcoin is slowly moving higher above the $26,500 resistance. The price is trading above $26,500 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average. There is a key bullish trend line forming with support near $26,600 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Kraken). The pair could rise further if it clears the $27,200 and $27,500 resistance levels. Bitcoin Price Eyes Sustained Upward Move Bitcoin price managed to settle above the $26,000 resistance zone. BTC climbed higher steadily above the $26,200 and $26,500 resistance levels. It even spiked above the $27,000 level but there was a lack of bullish momentum. A high is formed near $27,184 and the price is now correcting gains. There was a move below the $27,000 support. It is now trading below the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the recent increase from the $26,253 swing low to the $27,184 high. Bitcoin price is now trading above $26,500 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average. Besides, there is a key bullish trend line forming with support near $26,600 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair. Source: BTCUSD on TradingView.com On the upside, the price is facing resistance near the $27,200 level. The next major resistance is near the $27,500 level. A close above the $27,500 resistance might spark bullish moves in the near term. The next major resistance is near the $28,500 level, above which the bulls might send BTC toward the $29,200 resistance zone. Are Dips Supported in BTC? If Bitcoin’s price fails to clear the $27,200 resistance, it could continue to move down. Immediate support on the downside is near the $26,700 level. The next major support is near the $26,600 level and the trend line. It is close to the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the recent increase from the $26,253 swing low to the $27,184 high. The main support is now near $26,250, below which the price might gain bearish momentum toward $25,750. Any more losses might send the price toward $25,200 in the near term. Technical indicators: Hourly MACD – The MACD is now losing pace in the bullish zone. Hourly RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BTC/USD is above the 50 level. Major Support Levels – $26,600, followed by $26,250. Major Resistance Levels – $27,200, $27,500, and $28,500.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>Bitcoin price is rising above the $26,500 resistance. BTC could gain bullish momentum if it settles above the $27,200 and $27,500 resistance levels.</em></p>
<ul>
<li>Bitcoin is slowly moving higher above the $26,500 resistance.</li>
<li>The price is trading above $26,500 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average.</li>
<li>There is a key bullish trend line forming with support near $26,600 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could rise further if it clears the $27,200 and $27,500 resistance levels.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Bitcoin Price Eyes Sustained Upward Move</h2>
<p>Bitcoin price managed to settle above the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-steadies-above-26k/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">$26,000 resistance zone</a>. BTC climbed higher steadily above the $26,200 and $26,500 resistance levels. It even spiked above the $27,000 level but there was a lack of bullish momentum.</p>
<p>A high is formed near $27,184 and the price is now correcting gains. There was a move below the $27,000 support. It is now trading below the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the recent increase from the $26,253 swing low to the $27,184 high.</p>
<p>Bitcoin price is now trading above $26,500 and the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-aims-26200/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">100 hourly Simple moving average</a>. Besides, there is a key bullish trend line forming with support near $26,600 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-538654" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-13.png" alt="Bitcoin Price" width="1835" height="845" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-13.png 1835w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-13-460x212.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-13-860x396.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-13-768x354.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-13-1536x707.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-13-750x345.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-13-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1835px) 100vw, 1835px"/></p>
<p>Source: <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BTCUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">BTCUSD on TradingView.com</a></p>
<p>On the upside, the price is facing resistance near the $27,200 level. The next major resistance is near the $27,500 level. A close above the $27,500 resistance might spark bullish moves in the near term. The next major resistance is near the $28,500 level, above which the bulls might send BTC toward the $29,200 resistance zone.</p>
<h2>Are Dips Supported in BTC?</h2>
<p>If Bitcoin’s price fails to clear the $27,200 resistance, it could continue to move down. Immediate support on the downside is near the $26,700 level.</p>
<p>The next major support is near the $26,600 level and the trend line. It is close to the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the recent increase from the $26,253 swing low to the $27,184 high. The main support is now near $26,250, below which the price might gain bearish momentum toward $25,750. Any more losses might send the price toward $25,200 in the near term.</p>
<p>Technical indicators:</p>
<p>Hourly MACD – The MACD is now losing pace in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>Hourly RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BTC/USD is above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Levels – $26,600, followed by $26,250.</p>
<p>Major Resistance Levels – $27,200, $27,500, and $28,500.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/shutterstock_1724354728-460x230.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance Faces Regulatory Headwinds: UK Registration Canceled, Exits Netherlands, Cyprus</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/binance/binance-faces-regulatory-headwinds-uk-registration-canceled-exits-netherlands-cyprus/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 00:30:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance Markets Limited]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance UK]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BNB]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[regulation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=538643</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[In the latest development surrounding Binance, the world&#8217;s largest cryptocurrency exchange, the company has officially canceled its registration in the United Kingdom. The UK Financial Conduct Authority (FCA) approved Binance&#8217;s request to deregister Binance Markets Limited (BML) (BML) on May 30, 2023, effectively ending its authorization to provide regulated services in the country. While the termination of Binance&#8217;s registration with the FCA may seem significant, it will not impact the exchange&#8217;s operations as BML never conducted any business or had users in the UK. Ilir Laro, Binance&#8217;s sub-regional manager for growth in the UK and Europe, clarified that BML had remained dormant since its acquisition by Binance Group in 2020 and had not engaged in any regulated activities. Related Reading: Report: Do Kwon Refutes Passport Forgery Claims, Shifts Blame To ‘Chinese’ Agency In March, Binance halted the process of allowing UK customers to withdraw or deposit funds in British Pounds following the termination of its operational agreements with local partner Paysafe. According to data from Kaiko, the exchange previously held a dominant position in terms of cryptocurrency trading volume denominated in Sterling until it lost its banking partner. Laro stated, &#8220;BML was successfully acquired back in 2020 by Binance Group, intended to launch a regulated business in the UK. This attempt was not successful, however, and has since then remained dormant since its acquisition.&#8221; Cryptocurrency Exchange Binance Faces Regulatory Hurdles Binance&#8217;s decision to exit the UK comes amid a series of regulatory challenges faced by the cryptocurrency exchange. The US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) and the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) have both filed lawsuits against Binance, alleging various violations, including misleading practices and manipulative trading. The company&#8217;s move to withdraw from the Netherlands was prompted by its failure to meet the registration requirements, while in Cyprus, Binance is preparing for the implementation of the Markets in Crypto-assets (MiCA) framework. BNB price struggles as exchange battles regulatory headwinds &#124; Source: BNBUSD on TradingView.com With the upcoming enforcement of MiCA in 2024, Binance aims to focus on obtaining permits to operate in key European Union (EU) countries. Binance&#8217;s sub-regional development manager in the UK and Europe, Ilir Laro, mentioned that the exchange still holds regulated organizations in Poland, Sweden, France, Italy, and Spain. Laro emphasized, &#8220;Because MiCA, the European law on the regulation of cryptocurrencies, will come into force in 2024, the company will focus on obtaining permits to operate in EU countries.&#8221; Binance&#8217;s exit from multiple markets and ongoing regulatory challenges highlight the intensifying scrutiny faced by the cryptocurrency exchange. However, Binance&#8217;s strategy director, Patrick Hillmann, expressed the company&#8217;s commitment to regulation in the UK despite the difficulties it is encountering in the United States. Related Reading: Stablecoins Supply Finally Shows Rise, Here’s Why This Is Bullish For Bitcoin Hillmann stated, &#8220;We are committed to working constructively with regulators in the UK to develop and promote responsible crypto adoption and innovation.&#8221; As Binance navigates through these challenges, it remains to be seen how the exchange will adapt to regulatory frameworks and maintain its position as a leading player in the cryptocurrency industry. Featured image from Reuters, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In the latest development surrounding Binance, the world&#8217;s largest cryptocurrency exchange, the company has officially <a href="https://register.fca.org.uk/s/firm?id=001b000000nojfNAAQ" rel="nofollow">canceled</a> its registration in the United Kingdom. The UK Financial Conduct Authority (FCA) approved Binance&#8217;s request to deregister Binance Markets Limited (BML) (BML) on May 30, 2023, effectively ending its authorization to provide regulated services in the country.</p>
<p>While the termination of Binance&#8217;s registration with the FCA may seem significant, it will not impact the exchange&#8217;s operations as BML never conducted any business or had users in the UK. </p>
<p>Ilir Laro, Binance&#8217;s sub-regional manager for growth in the UK and Europe, clarified that BML had remained dormant since its acquisition by Binance Group in 2020 and had not engaged in any regulated activities.</p>

<p>In March, Binance halted the process of allowing UK customers to withdraw or deposit funds in British Pounds following the termination of its operational agreements with local partner Paysafe. According to data from <a href="https://twitter.com/KaikoData/status/1670767740951445507" rel="nofollow">Kaiko</a>, the exchange previously held a dominant position in terms of cryptocurrency trading volume denominated in Sterling until it lost its banking partner.</p>
<p>Laro stated, &#8220;BML was successfully acquired back in 2020 by Binance Group, intended to launch a regulated business in the UK. This attempt was not successful, however, and has since then remained dormant since its acquisition.&#8221;</p>
<h2>Cryptocurrency Exchange Binance Faces Regulatory Hurdles</h2>
<p>Binance&#8217;s decision to exit the UK comes amid a series of regulatory challenges faced by the cryptocurrency exchange. The US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) and the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) have both filed lawsuits against Binance, alleging various violations, including misleading practices and manipulative trading.</p>
<p>The company&#8217;s move to withdraw from the Netherlands was prompted by its failure to meet the registration requirements, while in Cyprus, Binance is preparing for the implementation of the Markets in Crypto-assets (MiCA) framework.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/sStQpxqK/" alt="Binance Coin (BNB) price chart from TradingView.com" width="2884" height="1724"/></p>

<p>With the upcoming enforcement of MiCA in 2024, Binance aims to focus on obtaining permits to operate in key European Union (EU) countries. Binance&#8217;s sub-regional development manager in the UK and Europe, Ilir Laro, mentioned that the exchange still holds regulated organizations in Poland, Sweden, France, Italy, and Spain.</p>
<p>Laro emphasized, &#8220;Because MiCA, the European law on the regulation of cryptocurrencies, will come into force in 2024, the company will focus on obtaining permits to operate in EU countries.&#8221;</p>
<p>Binance&#8217;s exit from multiple markets and ongoing regulatory challenges highlight the intensifying scrutiny faced by the cryptocurrency exchange. However, Binance&#8217;s strategy director, Patrick Hillmann, expressed the company&#8217;s commitment to regulation in the UK despite the difficulties it is encountering in the United States.</p>

<p>Hillmann stated, &#8220;We are committed to working constructively with regulators in the UK to develop and promote responsible crypto adoption and innovation.&#8221;</p>
<p>As Binance navigates through these challenges, it remains to be seen how the exchange will adapt to regulatory frameworks and maintain its position as a leading player in the cryptocurrency industry.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Binance-1-460x319.jpeg" width="460" height="319" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>PEPE Down 78% From May Peaks But Holder Count Rising</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/pepe-down-78-from-may-peaks-but-holder-count-rising/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dalmas Ngetich]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 00:30:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PEPE]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PEPEUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=538638</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[While PEPE is down 78% from its May 2023 peaks, token holders continue to rise. As of June 19, there are now 119,229 unique addresses holding the token, an increase from early June, Etherscan data shows.   The meme token is based on Pepe the Frog meme, created by Matt Furie in 2005.  Falling Prices, Rising Token Holder Count The token gained substantial recognition as a meme coin and enjoyed exponential price growth a month after launching in late April 2023.  With surging prices and the meme coin culture providing tailwinds, the token soon rose higher in the market cap ranking, securing a position in the top 100.  Related Reading: Stablecoins Supply Finally Shows Rise, Here’s Why This Is Bullish For Bitcoin As of June 19, PEPE is perched at 89th position with a market cap of $364,936,703, according to CoinMarketCap. PEPE is down 78% from May 2023 peaks, and prices remain fragile.  Despite falling prices, PEPE holders continue to maintain an upward trend. With over 119,000 holders, users appear keen on accumulating. In crypto circles, token holder count can be used to measure interest and adoption. Projects with a higher token holder count can be used to indicate strong community support, which can translate to success. It can also indicate the level of utility and adoption. Tokens like USDT, a stablecoin, have high token holder counts considering their role in decentralized finance (DeFi), remittance, and more.  In the case of PEPE, token holders are mostly speculating because the coin has no utility but is deflationary. An extract from their homepage reads:  PEPE is a meme coin with no intrinsic value or expectation of financial return. There is no formal team or roadmap. The coin is completely useless and for entertainment purposes only. PEPE is an ERC-20 token on Ethereum and can be bought on platforms like Binance, KuCoin, Uniswap, a decentralized exchange, and others. At the same time, the token’s derivatives have been listed on several cryptocurrency exchanges, including Binance, which began supporting the token on its Innovation Zone while listing PEPE’s perpetual futures in early May 2023. Binance To Delist PEPE From Flexible Loan Program Following increasing regulatory scrutiny, Binance announced plans to delist PEPE as a borrowable asset from their Flexible Loan program. The delisting would take effect on June 21 and also coincide with the cancellation of any open PEPE loan holdings. Related Reading: Report: Do Kwon Refutes Passport Forgery Claims, Shifts Blame To ‘Chinese’ Agency Binance strongly encourages its users to settle any outstanding debts related to PEPE. Accounts that face liquidation will incur a 2% charge, where applicable. The exchange has assured borrowers that it will accept repayment in the same currency.  Feature Image From Canva, Chart From TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>While PEPE is down 78% from its May 2023 peaks, token holders continue to rise. As of June 19, there are now 119,229 unique addresses holding the token, an increase from early June, Etherscan data <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://etherscan.io/token/0x6982508145454ce325ddbe47a25d4ec3d2311933?a=0x1497ebd1ed721dd7b2dc12768545558933df82fd" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">shows</a>.  </p>
<p>The meme token is based on Pepe the Frog meme, created by Matt Furie in 2005. </p>
<h2><strong>Falling Prices, Rising Token Holder Count</strong></h2>
<p>The token gained substantial recognition as a meme coin and enjoyed exponential price growth a month after launching in late April 2023. </p>
<p>With surging prices and the meme coin culture providing tailwinds, the token soon rose higher in the market cap ranking, securing a position in the top 100. </p>

<p>As of June 19, PEPE is <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/pepe/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">perched</a> at 89th position with a market cap of $364,936,703, according to CoinMarketCap. PEPE is down 78% from May 2023 peaks, and prices remain fragile. </p>
<a href="https://www.tradingview.com/x/vMLbtQIw/" rel="nofollow"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/vMLbtQIw/" alt="PEPE price on June 19| OKXUSDT on OKX, TradingView" width="1226" height="595"/></a>
<p>Despite falling prices, PEPE holders continue to maintain an upward trend. With over 119,000 holders, users appear keen on accumulating.</p>
<p>In crypto circles, token holder count can be used to measure interest and adoption. Projects with a higher token holder count can be used to indicate strong community support, which can translate to success.</p>
<p>It can also indicate the level of utility and adoption. Tokens like USDT, a stablecoin, have high token holder counts considering their role in decentralized finance (DeFi), remittance, and more. </p>
<p>In the case of PEPE, token holders are mostly speculating because the coin has no utility but is deflationary. An extract from their homepage<a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.pepe.vip/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow"> reads</a>: </p>
<blockquote><p>PEPE is a meme coin with no intrinsic value or expectation of financial return. There is no formal team or roadmap. The coin is completely useless and for entertainment purposes only.</p></blockquote>
<p>PEPE is an ERC-20 token on Ethereum and can be bought on platforms like Binance, KuCoin, Uniswap, a decentralized exchange, and others.</p>
<p>At the same time, the token’s derivatives have been listed on several cryptocurrency exchanges, including Binance, which began supporting the token on its Innovation Zone while listing PEPE’s perpetual futures in early May 2023.</p>
<h2><strong>Binance To Delist PEPE From Flexible Loan Program</strong></h2>
<p>Following increasing regulatory scrutiny, Binance <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.binance.com/en/support/announcement/binance-flexible-loan-has-delisted-pepe-as-a-borrowable-asset-edebf68609a6495886c349fe7cbc355f" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">announced</a> plans to delist PEPE as a borrowable asset from their Flexible Loan program. The delisting would take effect on June 21 and also coincide with the cancellation of any open PEPE loan holdings.</p>

<p>Binance strongly encourages its users to settle any outstanding debts related to PEPE. Accounts that face liquidation will incur a 2% charge, where applicable. The exchange has assured borrowers that it will accept repayment in the same currency. </p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Crypto-news-Template21-460x260.jpg" width="460" height="260" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum Eyes Dramatic Shift: Proposes Validator Limit Increase From 32 To 2048 ETH</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/ethereum/ethereum-eyes-dramatic-shift-proposes-validator-limit/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samuel Edyme]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 23:00:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=538586</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Ethereum, the second-largest blockchain by market capitalization, could be on the cusp of a significant operational shift. In the latest Ethereum core developer consensus meeting, a key agenda item under discussion was a proposed increase in the maximum validator limit. If implemented, this adjustment would see the limit skyrocket from the current 32 ETH to 2,048 ETH per validator. Currently, validators in Ethereum&#8217;s network maintain a balance cap set at both the minimum and maximum of 32 ETH. Those managing large-scale staking operations, consequently, must establish multiple validators to earn yield beyond this limit. As such, the result is a significant growth in the number of validators, with the current count reaching 600,000 active validators and an additional 90,000 on standby. Streamlining For Optimization Michael Neuder, an Ethereum Foundation researcher and a primary advocate of this change, argues that the proposed increase would alleviate the pressures caused by the expanding validator set size. Related Reading: Ethereum Cancun Upgrade: Why Arbitrum, Optimism Will Profit Massively Neuder highlighted that the current validator cap does support decentralization, but it simultaneously leads to an inflation of the validator set size. This increasing size eventually enhances the system&#8217;s performance by expediting the conclusion within a solitary Ethereum slot. In addition, Neuder pointed out the prospect of auto-compounding validator rewards brought on by this change. Given the current restrictions, any rewards earned beyond the 32 ETH cap must be averted to other places to generate any staking yield. With a raised cap, these rewards could be compounded instantaneously, enabling validators to reap greater benefits from their staked ETH. Impact On Large-Scale Operators And Associated Risks The proposal also aims to address the procedural challenges encountered by major node managers, such as exchanges like Coinbase, that presently supervise multitudes of validators due to the standing 32 ETH constraint per validator. If the cap were to be elevated, such operators could manage fewer validators with higher stakes, which could potentially simplify operations. However, Neuder cautioned about the risks tied to this proposed change. For instance, the increase could potentially lead to steeper penalties for inadvertent double attestations or proposals, also known as &#8220;slashing.&#8221; This highlights the importance of considering all possible implications in the path toward improving network efficiency and validator rewards. Notably, as Ethereum continues to evolve, this potential change in the validator limit serves as a critical discussion point in the broader conversation about the platform&#8217;s future. Related Reading: Ethereum Price Prints Bullish Technical Pattern, Why Close Above $1,780 Is Critical Meanwhile, Ethereum is down 1% in the past week amid the industry&#8217;s current condition. The second-largest crypto asset by market capitalization has recorded a downward movement, also falling by 1.1% in the past 24 hours. At the time of writing, ETH trades above $1,700 after moving below that price range to trade at the $1,600 region last week. ETH&#8217;s trading volume has plummeted over the past 7 days from above $7 billion last Monday to below $4 billion in the past 24 hours, indicating a decline in trading activity. Featured image from Shutterstock, chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w" dir="ltr">Ethereum, the second-largest blockchain by market capitalization, could be on the cusp of a significant operational shift. In the latest Ethereum core developer consensus <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ybgQuRcz9sg" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">meeting</a>, a key agenda item under discussion was a <a href="https://ethresear.ch/t/increase-the-max-effective-balance-a-modest-proposal/15801" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">proposed</a> increase in the maximum validator limit. </p>
<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w" dir="ltr">If implemented, this adjustment would see the limit skyrocket from the current 32 ETH to 2,048 ETH per validator. Currently, validators in <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/ethereum-cancun-upgrade-arbitrum-optimism-will-profit/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Ethereum&#8217;s network</a> maintain a balance cap set at both the minimum and maximum of 32 ETH. </p>
<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w" dir="ltr">Those managing large-scale staking operations, consequently, must establish multiple validators to earn yield beyond this limit. As such, the result is a significant growth in the number of validators, with the current count reaching 600,000 active validators and an additional 90,000 on standby.</p>
<h2 class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w" dir="ltr">Streamlining For Optimization</h2>
<p>Michael Neuder, an Ethereum Foundation researcher and a primary advocate of this change, argues that the proposed increase would alleviate the pressures caused by the expanding validator set size.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/ethereum-cancun-upgrade-arbitrum-optimism-will-profit/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Ethereum Cancun Upgrade: Why Arbitrum, Optimism Will Profit Massively</a></p>
<p>Neuder highlighted that the current validator cap does support decentralization, but it simultaneously leads to an inflation of the validator set size. This increasing size eventually enhances the system&#8217;s performance by expediting the conclusion within a solitary <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-consolidates-1720/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Ethereum</a> slot.</p>
<p>In addition, Neuder pointed out the prospect of auto-compounding validator rewards brought on by this change. Given the current restrictions, any rewards earned beyond the 32 ETH cap must be averted to other places to generate any staking yield. </p>
<p>With a raised cap, these rewards could be compounded instantaneously, enabling validators to reap greater benefits from their staked ETH.</p>
<h2>Impact On Large-Scale Operators And Associated Risks</h2>
<p>The proposal also aims to address the procedural challenges encountered by major node managers, such as exchanges like Coinbase, that presently supervise multitudes of validators due to the standing 32 ETH constraint per validator.</p>
<p>If the cap were to be elevated, such operators could manage fewer validators with higher stakes, which could potentially simplify operations. However, Neuder cautioned about the risks tied to this proposed change. </p>
<p>For instance, the increase could potentially lead to steeper penalties for inadvertent double attestations or proposals, also known as &#8220;slashing.&#8221; This highlights the importance of considering all possible implications in the path toward improving network efficiency and validator rewards.</p>
<p>Notably, as Ethereum continues to evolve, this potential change in the validator limit serves as a critical discussion point in the broader conversation about the platform&#8217;s future. </p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-bullish-above-1780/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Ethereum Price Prints Bullish Technical Pattern, Why Close Above $1,780 Is Critical</a></p>
<p>Meanwhile, Ethereum is down 1% in the past week amid the industry&#8217;s current condition. The second-largest crypto asset by market capitalization has recorded a downward movement, also falling by 1.1% in the past 24 hours. </p>
<p>At the time of writing, <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-bullish-above-1780/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">ETH trades above $1,700</a> after moving below that price range to trade at the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/ethereum/ethereum-plunges-1700-metric-signaled-in-advance/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">$1,600 region</a> last week. ETH&#8217;s trading volume has plummeted over the past 7 days from above $7 billion last Monday to below $4 billion in the past 24 hours, indicating a decline in trading activity.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/2bpVHbWq/" alt="Ethereum (ETH)’s price chart on TradingView" width="2770" height="1556"/>
<p>Featured image from Shutterstock, chart from TradingView</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ethereum-ETH-Block-Size-Surges.png" width="350" height="250" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Is It Lights Out For Litecoin As A Daily Death Cross Approaches?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/litecoin/litecoin-daily-death-cross-crypto-halving/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tony "The Bull"]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 22:18:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Litecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[death cross]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ltc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ltc/usd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ltcbtc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ltceth]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LTCUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=538609</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Litecoin price has sank recently along with the greater crypto market, despite not being named a security by the US SEC. The downward pressure has the altcoin at risk of forming a death cross on the daily timeframe. Although the signal sounds ominous and often indicates a downtrend is coming, it might not be lights out for LTC after all. Let&#8217;s take a look. Lackluster Litecoin Performance Ahead of Halving Attributed to SEC With Litecoin&#8217;s halving just weeks away, the currently eleventh-ranked cryptocurrency by market cap was expected to perform better than it has. Fundamental and technical signals both point to LTC being undervalued, yet the coin has suffered alongside other altcoins from SEC-related sell pressure. Related Reading: Why Litecoin Could Be Gearing Up For Its Greatest Rally Since 2017 The US SEC is trying to kill the crypto industry, and its causing LTCUSD daily charts to inch closer to an ominous death cross. Its this a valid breakout of the downtrend line? &#124; LTCUSD on TradingView.com Doing A Double-Take On The Daily LTCUSD Death Cross A death cross occurs when the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average from above. This is considered a sell signal in a moving average-based trading system, and often precedes a negative trend change. But not always. A closer look at the 2020 death cross into golden cross &#124; LTCUSD on TradingView.com The chart above shows an example of a previous death cross from late 2020, which immediately rolled into a golden cross as soon as Litecoin found some support and started rising again. LTCUSD went on a massive rally lasting several weeks of upside. For this situation to repeat, Litecoin absolutely has to recover from current levels and resume its formerly bullish momentum. Otherwise, a death cross could lead to renewed selling from investors who expected more out of the halving. Related Reading: Litecoin Attempts To Revitalize The Crypto Market With Bullish Breakout Death cross and golden crosses can sometimes trigger back and forth in a choppy market, which is a drawback of using moving averages as trading signals. This is due to volatile price action pulling the faster moving average back and forth through the slower moving average. Furthermore, as an average of price action, moving averages are lagging indicators in general. A golden cross must be left on the chart when the all the consolidation ends, otherwise the looming death cross signal could have truly deadly implications. With Litecoin&#8217;s halving scheduled for under 45 days from now, anything is possible. Tony is the author of the CoinChartist (VIP) newsletter. Follow @TonyTheBullBTC &#38; @coinchartist_io on Twitter. Or join the TonyTradesBTC Telegram for daily market insights and technical analysis education. Please note: Content is educational and should not be considered investment advice. Featured image from iStockPhoto, Charts from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Litecoin price has sank recently along with the greater crypto market, despite not being named a security by the US SEC.</p>
<p>The downward pressure has the altcoin at risk of forming a death cross on the daily timeframe. Although the signal sounds ominous and often indicates a downtrend is coming, it might not be lights out for LTC after all. Let&#8217;s take a look.</p>
<h2>Lackluster Litecoin Performance Ahead of Halving Attributed to SEC</h2>
<p>With Litecoin&#8217;s halving just weeks away, the currently eleventh-ranked cryptocurrency by market cap was <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/ltc/why-litecoin-greatest-rally-since-2017/?swcfpc=1">expected to perform better than it has</a>.</p>
<p>Fundamental and technical signals both point to LTC being undervalued, yet the coin has suffered alongside other altcoins from SEC-related sell pressure.</p>

<p>The US SEC is trying to kill the crypto industry, and its causing LTCUSD daily charts to inch closer to an ominous death cross.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large wp-image-538620 aligncenter" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/LTCUSD_2023-06-19_12-11-41-860x469.png" alt="litecoin death cross" width="860" height="469" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/LTCUSD_2023-06-19_12-11-41-860x469.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/LTCUSD_2023-06-19_12-11-41-460x251.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/LTCUSD_2023-06-19_12-11-41-768x419.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/LTCUSD_2023-06-19_12-11-41-1536x838.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/LTCUSD_2023-06-19_12-11-41-2048x1118.png 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/LTCUSD_2023-06-19_12-11-41-750x409.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/LTCUSD_2023-06-19_12-11-41-1140x622.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/></p>

<h2>Doing A Double-Take On The Daily LTCUSD Death Cross</h2>
<p>A death cross occurs when the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average from above. This is considered a sell signal in a moving average-based trading system, and often precedes a negative trend change. But not always.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-large wp-image-538619 aligncenter" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/LTCUSD_2023-06-19_12-01-17-860x493.png" alt="LTCUSD_2023-06-19_12-01-17" width="860" height="493" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/LTCUSD_2023-06-19_12-01-17-860x493.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/LTCUSD_2023-06-19_12-01-17-460x264.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/LTCUSD_2023-06-19_12-01-17-768x440.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/LTCUSD_2023-06-19_12-01-17-1536x881.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/LTCUSD_2023-06-19_12-01-17-2048x1175.png 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/LTCUSD_2023-06-19_12-01-17-750x430.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/LTCUSD_2023-06-19_12-01-17-1140x654.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/></p>
<p style="text-align: center">A closer look at the 2020 death cross into golden cross | <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/LTCUSD/?aff_id=118619" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">LTCUSD on TradingView.com</a></p>
<p>The chart above shows an example of a previous death cross from late 2020, which immediately rolled into a golden cross as soon as Litecoin found some support and started rising again.</p>
<p>LTCUSD went on a massive rally lasting several weeks of upside. For this situation to repeat, Litecoin absolutely has to recover from current levels and resume its formerly bullish momentum. Otherwise, a death cross could lead to renewed selling from investors who expected more out of the halving.</p>

<p>Death cross and golden crosses can sometimes trigger back and forth in a choppy market, which is a drawback of using moving averages as trading signals. This is due to volatile price action pulling the faster moving average back and forth through the slower moving average. Furthermore, as an average of price action, moving averages are lagging indicators in general.</p>
<p>A golden cross must be left on the chart when the all the consolidation ends, otherwise the looming death cross signal could have truly deadly implications. With Litecoin&#8217;s halving scheduled for under 45 days from now, anything is possible.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/iStock-648636254-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Resistance At $26,600: A Make Or Break Moment For Bulls</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-resistance-at-26600-a-make-or-break-moment-for-bulls/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 21:00:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=538606</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) is currently consolidating above the crucial $26,000 level, a key threshold for the world&#8217;s largest cryptocurrency to continue its upward momentum and reach higher levels.  The recovery of this price mark on June 15th has given BTC holders renewed confidence, with the highly anticipated news of Blackrock, the largest fund manager in the world with over $10 trillion under its management, announcing a formal application for a new spot Bitcoin Exchange-Traded Fund (ETF) has further boosted their optimism. Despite this positive news, Bitcoin still faces significant resistance ahead if it is to recover previously lost territories and solidify a bull run. Related Reading: Crypto Analyst Says Bitcoin Has Already Bottomed, Sets Halving Price Higher Low At $25,800 Before Upside Breakout? Crypto analyst WoeToe has recently shared his thoughts on the current state of the Bitcoin market, highlighting a crucial level that bulls should keep an eye on. According to WoeToe, Bitcoin has failed to break its resistance level at $26,600, indicating that the market may be experiencing a period of consolidation before making its next move. WoeToe believes that BTC may set a higher low around the $25,800 level before breaking out of its current channel to the upside, as indicated by the yellow lines on the chart. This means that if Bitcoin were to drop to $25,800, it would be a critical level for bulls to defend to maintain bullish momentum. Therefore, bulls must hold the $25,800 mark and prevent a drop below it. If Bitcoin successfully sets a higher low at this level and breaks out of its current channel, it could potentially open up new resistance levels and lead to a bullish trend in the market. However, if bulls fail to defend the potential higher low at $25,800, Bitcoin could experience a further downtrend. In this scenario, the cryptocurrency may test its strongest support floor, indicated by its 200-day Moving Average (MA), currently at $25,200.  The 200-day MA has previously prevented Bitcoin from extending its downtrend since last week&#8217;s weekly opening. Bitcoin Downside Risk Increases Cryptocurrency trader Rekt Capital has warned Bitcoin investors, stating that the leading cryptocurrency has rallied straight into the 200-week Moving Average, which could act as new resistance and potentially trigger a two-step breakdown confirmation. This, in turn, could lead to further downside for Bitcoin shortly. The 200-week MA is a widely-watched technical indicator that reflects the average price of Bitcoin over the past 200 weeks. It is considered a significant support level and has historically acted as a key price point for the cryptocurrency. Related Reading: Stablecoins Supply Finally Shows Rise, Here’s Why This Is Bullish For Bitcoin However, if BCT fails to break through the 200-week MA and instead turns it into new resistance, it could lead to a two-step breakdown confirmation. This would mean that the cryptocurrency would break through two key support levels quickly, potentially signaling a significant shift in market sentiment and leading to further downside. Bitcoin has made multiple attempts to break through the $26,600 resistance level but has been unsuccessful. The cryptocurrency is trading at $26,400 and has yet to surpass the critical resistance mark. Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com ]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin (BTC) is currently consolidating above the crucial $26,000 level, a key threshold for the world&#8217;s largest cryptocurrency to continue its upward momentum and reach higher levels. </p>
<p>The recovery of this price mark on June 15th has given BTC holders renewed confidence, with the highly anticipated news of Blackrock, the largest fund manager in the world with over $10 trillion under its management, announcing a formal application for a new spot Bitcoin Exchange-Traded Fund (ETF) has further boosted their optimism.</p>
<p>Despite this positive news, Bitcoin still faces significant resistance ahead if it is to recover previously lost territories and solidify a bull run.</p>

<h2>Higher Low At $25,800 Before Upside Breakout?</h2>
<p>Crypto analyst WoeToe has recently <a href="https://twitter.com/cryptowoetoe/status/1670717873700974601?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">shared </a>his thoughts on the current state of the Bitcoin market, highlighting a crucial level that bulls should keep an eye on. According to WoeToe, Bitcoin has failed to break its resistance level at $26,600, indicating that the market may be experiencing a period of consolidation before making its next move.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large wp-image-538614" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Screenshot_57-860x472.jpg" alt="Bitcoin " width="860" height="472" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Screenshot_57-860x472.jpg 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Screenshot_57-460x253.jpg 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Screenshot_57-768x422.jpg 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Screenshot_57-750x412.jpg 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Screenshot_57.jpg 949w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/>
<p>WoeToe believes that BTC may set a higher low around the $25,800 level before breaking out of its current channel to the upside, as indicated by the yellow lines on the chart. This means that if Bitcoin were to drop to $25,800, it would be a critical level for bulls to defend to maintain bullish momentum.</p>
<p>Therefore, bulls must hold the $25,800 mark and prevent a drop below it. If Bitcoin successfully sets a higher low at this level and breaks out of its current channel, it could potentially open up new resistance levels and lead to a bullish trend in the market.</p>
<p>However, if bulls fail to defend the potential higher low at $25,800, Bitcoin could experience a further downtrend. In this scenario, the cryptocurrency may test its strongest support floor, indicated by its 200-day Moving Average (MA), currently at $25,200. </p>
<p>The 200-day MA has previously prevented Bitcoin from extending its downtrend since last week&#8217;s weekly opening.</p>
Bitcoin Downside Risk Increases
<p>Cryptocurrency trader Rekt Capital has <a href="https://twitter.com/rektcapital/status/1670490269878239232?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">warned</a><a href="https://twitter.com/rektcapital/status/1670490269878239232?s=20" rel="nofollow"> </a>Bitcoin investors, stating that the leading cryptocurrency has rallied straight into the 200-week Moving Average, which could act as new resistance and potentially trigger a two-step breakdown confirmation. This, in turn, could lead to further downside for Bitcoin shortly.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large wp-image-538615" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Fy7F1CQWwAAJ7t8-860x609.jpg" alt="Bitcoin " width="860" height="609" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Fy7F1CQWwAAJ7t8-860x609.jpg 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Fy7F1CQWwAAJ7t8-460x326.jpg 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Fy7F1CQWwAAJ7t8-768x544.jpg 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Fy7F1CQWwAAJ7t8-1536x1088.jpg 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Fy7F1CQWwAAJ7t8-120x86.jpg 120w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Fy7F1CQWwAAJ7t8-750x531.jpg 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Fy7F1CQWwAAJ7t8-1140x807.jpg 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Fy7F1CQWwAAJ7t8.jpg 1788w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/>
<p>The 200-week MA is a widely-watched technical indicator that reflects the average price of Bitcoin over the past 200 weeks. It is considered a significant support level and has historically acted as a key price point for the cryptocurrency.</p>

<p>However, if BCT fails to break through the 200-week MA and instead turns it into new resistance, it could lead to a two-step breakdown confirmation. This would mean that the cryptocurrency would break through two key support levels quickly, potentially signaling a significant shift in market sentiment and leading to further downside.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/57KuzSgc/" alt="Bitcoin " width="1814" height="858"/>
<p>Bitcoin has made multiple attempts to break through the $26,600 resistance level but has been unsuccessful. The cryptocurrency is trading at $26,400 and has yet to surpass the critical resistance mark.</p>
<p>Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/andrea-seiler-qQXlEM55L5M-unsplash-345x460.jpg" width="345" height="460" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Whale Removes Nearly $400 million In BTC From Binance</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/btc-whale-removes-nearly-400-million-in-bitcoin-from-binance/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 20:00:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Whale]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=538599</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A massive Bitcoin transaction was spotted on the blockchain recently, indicating a whale may be moving their funds into self-custody. Data shows a Bitcoin whale has withdrawn $395.8 million from Binance to an unknown wallet, a sign that may be bullish for the cryptocurrency&#8217;s price.  Massive Bitcoin Transaction Spotted on the Blockchain According to the data provided by Whale Alert, a cryptocurrency transaction tracker, a whale recently transferred 15,000 BTC away from Binance, the world&#8217;s largest cryptocurrency exchange by volume. At the current market price, these Bitcoins are worth around $395.878 million. 🚨 🚨 🚨 🚨 🚨 🚨 🚨 🚨 🚨 🚨 15,000 #BTC (395,878,446 USD) transferred from #Binance to unknown wallethttps://t.co/PyhE6gBozq — Whale Alert (@whale_alert) June 19, 2023 Related Reading: Crypto Analyst Says Bitcoin Has Already Bottomed, Sets Halving Price This is one of the largest single transactions involving Bitcoin that has been reported so far this year. Although the recipient address is unknown, the amount of the transaction suggests that it was likely an institutional investor or high net worth individual also known as a &#8220;whale&#8221; who wanted complete control of their digital assets. How Self-Custody Is Good For The Price Of Bitcoin It is no new revelation that when dealing with digital assets, self-custody is the best way, especially on a large scale. By transferring from an exchange wallet into a private wallet, the whale now has sole control and responsibility over the private keys that can move the funds.  For many long term holders, this is a safer option than keeping large amounts of crypto on an exchange which could be at higher risk of hacks or scams. BTC recovers above $26,000 resistance &#124; Source: BTCUSD on TradingView.com When whales make significant transactions, it can frequently cause price volatility. If this whale plans to hold their BTC long-term, it could signal confidence in Bitcoin’s future value. On the other hand, if they were to sell a significant percentage of it, there would be an oversupply on the market, which would bring the price down, at least temporarily. Related Reading: Trust Wallet Token (TWT) Tallies 22% In Last Week, Will It Test $1 Mark? Also, when big players move their BTC off exchanges into self-custody wallets, it&#8217;s usually a good sign for Bitcoin&#8217;s price. Removing hundreds of millions of dollars of Bitcoin from exchanges means less supply available for trading. This increases scarcity on exchanges, thereby increasing the price of Bitcoin.  Bitcoin is now trading above $26,000 after breaking the $26,000 resistance during the weekend. With the next Bitcoin halving less than a year away, whales moving their assets into self-custody may send some ripples of bullish sentiment into the wider crypto industry.  Featured image from Coingape, chart from Tradingview.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p style="font-weight: 400">A massive Bitcoin transaction was spotted on the blockchain recently, indicating a whale may be moving their funds into self-custody. Data shows a Bitcoin whale has withdrawn $395.8 million from Binance to an unknown wallet, a sign that may be bullish for the cryptocurrency&#8217;s price. </p>
<h2 style="font-weight: 400">Massive Bitcoin Transaction Spotted on the Blockchain</h2>
<p style="font-weight: 400">According to the <a href="https://twitter.com/whale_alert/status/1670732027069358080?s=20" rel="nofollow">data </a>provided by Whale Alert, a cryptocurrency transaction tracker, a whale recently transferred 15,000 BTC away from Binance, the world&#8217;s largest cryptocurrency exchange by volume. At the current market price, these Bitcoins are worth around $395.878 million.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en"><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f6a8.png" alt="🚨" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f6a8.png" alt="🚨" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f6a8.png" alt="🚨" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f6a8.png" alt="🚨" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f6a8.png" alt="🚨" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f6a8.png" alt="🚨" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f6a8.png" alt="🚨" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f6a8.png" alt="🚨" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f6a8.png" alt="🚨" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f6a8.png" alt="🚨" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> 15,000 <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/BTC?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#BTC</a> (395,878,446 USD) transferred from <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Binance?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#Binance</a> to unknown wallet<a href="https://t.co/PyhE6gBozq" rel="nofollow">https://t.co/PyhE6gBozq</a></p>
<p>— Whale Alert (@whale_alert) <a href="https://twitter.com/whale_alert/status/1670732027069358080?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">June 19, 2023</a></p></blockquote>

<p style="font-weight: 400">This is one of the largest single transactions involving Bitcoin that has been reported so far this year. Although the recipient address is unknown, the amount of the transaction suggests that it was likely an institutional investor or high net worth individual also known as a &#8220;whale&#8221; who wanted complete control of their digital assets.</p>
<h2 style="font-weight: 400">How Self-Custody Is Good For The Price Of Bitcoin</h2>
<p style="font-weight: 400">It is no new revelation that when dealing with digital assets, self-custody is the best way, especially on a large scale. By transferring from an exchange wallet into a private wallet, the whale now has sole control and responsibility over the private keys that can move the funds. </p>
<p style="font-weight: 400">For many long term holders, this is a safer option than keeping large amounts of crypto on an exchange which could be at higher risk of hacks or scams.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/kLKUenvF/" alt="Bitcoin (BTC) price chart from TradingView.com" width="2160" height="1686"/></p>

<p style="font-weight: 400">When whales make significant transactions, it can frequently cause price volatility. If this whale plans to hold their BTC long-term, it could signal confidence in Bitcoin’s future value. On the other hand, if they were to sell a significant percentage of it, there would be an oversupply on the market, which would bring the price down, at least temporarily.</p>

<p style="font-weight: 400">Also, when big players move their BTC off exchanges into self-custody wallets, it&#8217;s usually a good sign for Bitcoin&#8217;s price. Removing hundreds of millions of dollars of Bitcoin from exchanges means less supply available for trading. This increases scarcity on exchanges, thereby increasing the price of Bitcoin. </p>
<p style="font-weight: 400">Bitcoin is now trading above $26,000 after breaking the $26,000 resistance during the weekend. With the next Bitcoin halving less than a year away, whales moving their assets into self-custody may send some ripples of bullish sentiment into the wider crypto industry. </p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/IMG_0015-460x240.jpeg" width="460" height="240" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Short-Term Holders Still Bullish, Will Rally Restart?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-short-term-holders-still-bullish-will-rally-restart/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hououin Kyouma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 19:00:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Bullish]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin rally]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin short-term holders]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=538550</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[On-chain data shows that Bitcoin short-term holders have participated in buying recently despite the price briefly dropping below their cost basis. Bitcoin Has Rebounded Back Above Short-Term Holder Realized Price As pointed out by an analyst in a CryptoQuant post, the BTC price had recently fallen below the realized price of the short-term holders. The &#8220;realized price&#8221; here refers to a metric that&#8217;s derived from the &#8220;realized cap.&#8221; The realized cap is a popular capitalization model for Bitcoin that assumes that the true value of each coin in circulation is not the current spot price, but the price at which it was last moved/sold on the blockchain. When this cap is divided by the total number of coins in circulation, the &#8220;realized price&#8221; emerges. The significance of this indicator is that it represents the cost basis of the average investor in the market. In the context of the current discussion, the average acquisition price of the entire market isn&#8217;t of interest, however; the realized price for only a segment of the market is relevant: the short-term holders. The &#8220;short-term holders&#8221; (STHs) here refer to investors who bought their coins less than 155 days ago. These investors are generally fickle and their behavior has historically been relevant to the trend BTC has followed. Now, here is a chart that shows the trend in the Bitcoin STH realized price over the past year: The value of the metric seems to have been near the spot price recently &#124; Source: CryptoQuant The STH realized price has historically displayed some interesting interactions with the spot price of Bitcoin. During bearish periods, the metric has provided resistance to the price, while in bullish trends, it has switched its role to being a support level. Both these patterns are also visible in the above graph, where the cryptocurrency saw a negative reaction to the line around the time of the November 2022 FTX collapse, while it found support at it when the rally had taken a step back in March 2023. As for why this pattern exists at all, the reason likely lies in the fact that the STHs look at their cost basis differently depending on the wider trend being followed in the market at the time. During bear markets, the investors look at their acquisition price as a chance to escape. They believe that selling at their cost basis would at least mean that they can avoid taking losses. It&#8217;s this selling that becomes the source of resistance at the line. Related Reading: Ethereum Cancun Upgrade: Why Arbitrum, Optimism Will Profit Massively In rallies, on the other hand, the STHs generally hold a bullish sentiment. They look at their cost basis as a profitable buying opportunity, as they think that the price would go up in the near future. The mass buying when the price touches the line may explain why the asset has observed rebounds here. From the chart, it&#8217;s visible that Bitcoin had recently dipped slightly under this line, raising concerns about whether the bullish regime had come to an end. In the past few days, however, the asset has been able to regain itself back above the level. Related Reading: Bitcoin Price Steadies Above $26K, Can Bulls Pump It Further? Since the STHs didn&#8217;t participate in selling at the level when the asset retested the line from below, it&#8217;s looking likely that they still lean towards a bullish sentiment. Naturally, this could suggest that the Bitcoin rally not be over yet after all. BTC Price At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading around $26,400, up 2% in the last week. BTC has recovered back above $26,000 &#124; Source: BTCUSD on TradingView Featured image from Kanchanara on Unsplash.com, charts from TradingView.com, CryptoQuant.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On-chain data shows that Bitcoin short-term holders have participated in buying recently despite the price briefly dropping below their cost basis.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Has Rebounded Back Above Short-Term Holder Realized Price</h2>
<p>As pointed out by an analyst in a CryptoQuant <a href="https://cryptoquant.com/insights/quicktake/648f65652ec8802caad3ec5f-Short-Term-Holders-Are-Not-Done-With-This-Bitcoin-Rally" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">post</a>, the BTC price had recently fallen below the realized price of the short-term holders. The &#8220;<a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-under-realized-price-163-days/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">realized price</a>&#8221; here refers to a metric that&#8217;s derived from the &#8220;realized cap.&#8221;</p>
<p>The realized cap is a popular capitalization model for Bitcoin that assumes that the true value of each coin in circulation is not the current spot price, but the price at which it was last moved/sold on the blockchain.</p>
<p>When this cap is divided by the total number of coins in circulation, the &#8220;realized price&#8221; emerges. The significance of this indicator is that it represents the cost basis of the average investor in the market.</p>
<p>In the context of the current discussion, the average acquisition price of the entire market isn&#8217;t of interest, however; the realized price for only a segment of the market is relevant: the short-term holders.</p>
<p>The &#8220;<a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/data-reveals-short-term-bitcoin-holders-refuse-to-sell/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">short-term holders</a>&#8221; (STHs) here refer to investors who bought their coins less than 155 days ago. These investors are generally fickle and their behavior has historically been relevant to the trend BTC has followed.</p>
<p>Now, here is a chart that shows the trend in the Bitcoin STH realized price over the past year:</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone aligncenter" src="https://img.cryptoquant.com/2008/quicktake/9LlsDJ_6aed1a0f6d765ec84b9df2597487323ec386493869d9961b3fcd3328d2430070.png" alt="Bitcoin Short-Term Holder Realized Price" width="1280" height="806"/></p>

<p>The STH realized price has historically displayed some interesting interactions with the spot price of Bitcoin. During bearish periods, the metric has provided resistance to the price, while in bullish trends, it has switched its role to being a support level.</p>
<p>Both these patterns are also visible in the above graph, where the cryptocurrency saw a negative reaction to the line around the time of the November 2022 <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-price-touches-20000-for-first-time-post-ftx-collapse/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">FTX collapse</a>, while it found support at it when the rally had taken a step back in March 2023.</p>
<p>As for why this pattern exists at all, the reason likely lies in the fact that the STHs look at their cost basis differently depending on the wider trend being followed in the market at the time.</p>
<p>During bear markets, the investors look at their acquisition price as a chance to escape. They believe that selling at their cost basis would at least mean that they can avoid taking losses. It&#8217;s this selling that becomes the source of resistance at the line.</p>

<p>In rallies, on the other hand, the STHs generally hold a bullish sentiment. They look at their cost basis as a profitable buying opportunity, as they think that the price would go up in the near future. The mass buying when the price touches the line may explain why the asset has observed rebounds here.</p>
<p>From the chart, it&#8217;s visible that Bitcoin had recently dipped slightly under this line, raising concerns about whether the bullish regime had come to an end. In the past few days, however, the asset has been able to regain itself back above the level.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-steadies-above-26k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Bitcoin Price Steadies Above $26K, Can Bulls Pump It Further?</a></p>
<p>Since the STHs didn&#8217;t participate in selling at the level when the asset retested the line from below, it&#8217;s looking likely that they still lean towards a bullish sentiment. Naturally, this could suggest that the Bitcoin rally not be over yet after all.</p>
<h2>BTC Price</h2>
<p>At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading around $26,400, up 2% in the last week.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium aligncenter" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/oPKgpQX6/" alt="Bitcoin Price Chart" width="1534" height="911"/></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/kanchanara-rhm7H8X5J98-unsplash-1-460x306.jpg" width="460" height="306" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto King Do Kwon Behind Bars: Sentenced To 4 Months In Montenegrin Jail</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/breaking-news-ticker/crypto-king-do-kwon-behind-bars-sentenced-to-4-months-in-montenegrin-jail/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 18:00:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Breaking News Ticker]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DeFi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Terraform Labs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=538563</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[According to a Reuters report, Crypto entrepreneur Do Kwon, the former CEO of Terraform Labs, has been sentenced to four months in prison by a court in Montenegro for allegedly using forged passports.  Crypto Mogul Faces Jail Time For Passport Forgery Kwon, who is charged with multibillion-dollar fraud in the United States and is wanted by South Korean authorities on similar charges, was detained in March along with Han Chang-Joon, the former finance officer of Terraform Labs, as they attempted to board a flight to Dubai at the airport in Montenegro&#8217;s capital, Podgorica. Both men were charged with forging official documents. Related Reading: Trust Wallet Token (TWT) Tallies 22% In Last Week, Will It Test $1 Mark? Kwon had argued that he believed the Costa Rican passport was a legitimate &#8220;golden passport&#8221; available to wealthy applicants seeking fast-track citizenship in certain countries. However, the court rejected this explanation and handed down the prison sentences. The case has attracted widespread media attention, as Kwon is wanted by US and South Korean authorities on fraud charges related to the collapse of Terra last May. The company&#8217;s collapse led to over $60 billion in losses and sparked investigations into Kwon&#8217;s activities. As Bloomberg reported on June 8th, Terraform Labs co-founder Do Kwon may face multiple jail terms in different countries, according to senior South Korean prosecutor Dan Sunghan.  During an interaction with Bloomberg, Sunghan stated that South Korea had conducted most of the foundational investigation into the collapse of the Terra ecosystem and had more evidence on the matter than US authorities. Related Reading: US Politician Cheers Shiba Inu Price Surge, But Trend Reversal Still Pending Sunghan believes that carrying out the investigation and trial of Kwon in South Korea is the most efficient approach to getting justice. He also suggested that Kwon could face jail sentences for different charges in two separate countries, in addition to the recent decision by Montenegro&#8217;s court.  Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>According to a Reuters <a href="https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/montenegro-court-jails-cryptocurrency-king-do-kwon-four-months-media-2023-06-19/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">report</a>, Crypto entrepreneur Do Kwon, the former CEO of Terraform Labs, has been sentenced to four months in prison by a court in Montenegro for allegedly using forged passports. </p>

<h2>Crypto Mogul Faces Jail Time For Passport Forgery</h2>
<p>Kwon, who is charged with multibillion-dollar fraud in the United States and is wanted by South Korean authorities on similar charges, was detained in March along with Han Chang-Joon, the former finance officer of Terraform Labs, as they attempted to board a flight to Dubai at the airport in Montenegro&#8217;s capital, Podgorica. Both men were charged with forging official documents.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/trust-wallet-token-twt/trust-wallet-token-twt-tallies-22-in-last-week-will-it-test-1-mark/">Trust Wallet Token (TWT) Tallies 22% In Last Week, Will It Test $1 Mark?</a></p>
<p>Kwon had argued that he believed the Costa Rican passport was a legitimate &#8220;golden passport&#8221; available to wealthy applicants seeking fast-track citizenship in certain countries. However, the court rejected this explanation and handed down the prison sentences.</p>
<p>The case has attracted widespread media attention, as Kwon is wanted by US and South Korean authorities on fraud charges related to the collapse of Terra last May. The company&#8217;s collapse led to over $60 billion in losses and sparked investigations into Kwon&#8217;s activities.</p>
<p>As Bloomberg <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-06-08/fallen-crypto-mogul-kwon-could-face-jail-in-south-korea-and-us-prosecutor-says" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">reported </a>on June 8th, Terraform Labs co-founder Do Kwon may face multiple jail terms in different countries, according to senior South Korean prosecutor Dan Sunghan. </p>
<p>During an interaction with Bloomberg, Sunghan stated that South Korea had conducted most of the foundational investigation into the collapse of the Terra ecosystem and had more evidence on the matter than US authorities.</p>



<p>Sunghan believes that carrying out the investigation and trial of Kwon in South Korea is the most efficient approach to getting justice. He also suggested that Kwon could face jail sentences for different charges in two separate countries, in addition to the recent decision by Montenegro&#8217;s court. </p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/EDNVJ0ql/" alt="Crypto" width="1814" height="858"/>
<p>Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/saad-chaudhry-AqHIWSsF24I-unsplash-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Report: Do Kwon Refutes Passport Forgery Claims, Shifts Blame To &#8216;Chinese&#8217; Agency</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/crypto/report-do-kwon-refutes-passport-forgery-claims-shifts-blame-to-chinese-agency/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Eli Dambel]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 17:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[arrest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Do Kwon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[terra luna]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=538536</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Terraform founder Do Kwon, facing eight count charges in the United States for the ecosystem crash, recently denied two allegations against him. Do Kwon was accused of traveling with forged documents and sending financial donations to a former Montenegro minister. But according to a South Korean media, Segye’s report, Do Kwon told the Montenegrin Basic Court that he received his travel documents from a Chinese agency and wasn’t aware they were forged. Kwon also denies sending financial donations to the current leader of the Europe Now party Milojko Spajic, during his tenure as the Montenegro finance minister.  Do Kwon Denies Forging Documents During his arrest in March 2023, the Montenegro authorities announced that Do Kwon was traveling with fake documents. A Twitter account of the European country&#8217;s Interior Minister, Filip Adzic, wrote;  The person is suspected of being one of the most wanted fugitives, South Korean national Do Kwon, a co-founder and CEO of the Singapore-based Terraform Labs. Related Reading: Shiba Inu (SHIB) Burn Rate Suffers 87% Decline In Single Week Adzic also added: The former cryptocurrency king, who is behind losses of over $40 billion, has been apprehended at the Podgorica airport with forged documents. However, Do Kwon has denied forging his traveling documents and passports, including his Costa Rican passport.  Instead, he blamed a Singaporean agency stating: I received my Costa Rica passport after filling in the documents required by a Singaporean agency that was recommended to me by a friend. I received my Belgian passport through another agency. Do Kwon also stated that he hadn&#8217;t doubted the authenticity of his travel documents since they’d been with him for many years. Regarding the Singaporean agency that supposedly issued the document, the Terraform founder stated he couldn&#8217;t remember the exact name but only knew it was written &#8220;in Chinese.&#8221;  Terraform Founder Denies Sending Funds to Montenegro&#8217;s Former Finance Minister The second allegation Do Kwon denied was about sending payments to the former finance minister of Montenegro, Milojko Spajic, the current Europe Now party leader.  On June 17, a Radio Free Europe regional arm reported that Do Kwon allegedly contacted Spajic through a letter he sent to many officials in Montenegro before the country&#8217;s last elections. But during the court hearing, Do Kwon&#8217;s lawyers stated this is categorically denied and it is not true. Apart from Do Kwon’s lawyers, the former finance minister also denied having anything to do with the Terraform founder. However, on June 6, a Montenegro news outlet Balkinsight reported that the country’s outgoing prime minister urged the prosecutors to investigate the relationship between Kwon and Spajic.  Also, on June 9, a Twitter account FatMan, dedicated to updating the crypto community about Terra issues, shared an update about Do Kwon’s financial donations to Spajic. The Terraform founder has, however, denied the ties in the recent hearing. Following the court session, the presiding judge Ivana Becic announced that June 19 would be the date for a verdict on the forgery charges.  Meanwhile, Do Kwon will remain in extradition custody for six months waiting for the court to grant or reject the South Korean extradition request. Featured image from Pixabay and chart from Tradingview.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Terraform founder Do Kwon, facing eight count charges in the United States for the ecosystem crash, recently denied two allegations against him. </p>
<p>Do Kwon was accused of traveling with forged documents and sending financial donations to a former Montenegro minister. But according to a South Korean media, Segye’s <a href="https://www.segye.com/newsView/20230616521002" rel="nofollow">report</a>, Do Kwon told the Montenegrin Basic Court that he received his travel documents from a Chinese agency and wasn’t aware they were forged.</p>
<p>Kwon also denies sending financial donations to the current leader of the Europe Now party Milojko Spajic, during his tenure as the Montenegro finance minister. </p>
<h2>Do Kwon Denies Forging Documents</h2>
<p>During his arrest in March 2023, the Montenegro authorities announced that Do Kwon was traveling with fake documents. A Twitter account of the European country&#8217;s Interior Minister, Filip Adzic, wrote; </p>
<blockquote><p>The person is suspected of being one of the most wanted fugitives, South Korean national Do Kwon, a co-founder and CEO of the Singapore-based Terraform Labs.</p></blockquote>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/shiba-inu-shib-burn-rate-suffers-87-decline-in-single-week/?swcfpc=1">Shiba Inu (SHIB) Burn Rate Suffers 87% Decline In Single Week</a></p>
<p>Adzic also added:</p>
<blockquote><p>The former cryptocurrency king, who is behind losses of over $40 billion, has been apprehended at the Podgorica airport with forged documents.</p></blockquote>
<p>However, Do Kwon has denied forging his traveling documents and passports, including his Costa Rican passport. </p>
<p>Instead, he blamed a Singaporean agency stating:</p>
<blockquote><p>I received my Costa Rica passport after filling in the documents required by a Singaporean agency that was recommended to me by a friend. I received my Belgian passport through another agency.</p></blockquote>
<p>Do Kwon also stated that he hadn&#8217;t doubted the authenticity of his travel documents since they’d been with him for many years. Regarding the Singaporean agency that supposedly issued the document, the Terraform founder stated he couldn&#8217;t remember the exact name but only knew it was written &#8220;in Chinese.&#8221; </p>
<h2>Terraform Founder Denies Sending Funds to Montenegro&#8217;s Former Finance Minister</h2>
<p>The second allegation Do Kwon denied was about sending payments to the former finance minister of Montenegro, Milojko Spajic, the current Europe Now party leader. </p>
<p>On June 17, a Radio Free Europe <a href="https://www.slobodnaevropa.org/a/kralj-kriptovaluta-izborne--kampanje-u-crnoj-gori/32463516.html" rel="nofollow">regional arm reported that</a> Do Kwon allegedly contacted Spajic through a letter he sent to many officials in Montenegro before the country&#8217;s last elections. But during the court hearing, Do Kwon&#8217;s lawyers stated this is categorically denied and it is not true.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-538545 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/LUNAUSDT_2023-06-19_18-19-51-860x454.png" alt="Report: Do Kwon Refutes Passport Forgery Claims, Shifts Blame to &#039;Chinese&#039; Agency" width="860" height="454" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/LUNAUSDT_2023-06-19_18-19-51-860x454.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/LUNAUSDT_2023-06-19_18-19-51-460x243.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/LUNAUSDT_2023-06-19_18-19-51-768x406.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/LUNAUSDT_2023-06-19_18-19-51-1536x811.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/LUNAUSDT_2023-06-19_18-19-51-2048x1082.png 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/LUNAUSDT_2023-06-19_18-19-51-750x396.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/LUNAUSDT_2023-06-19_18-19-51-1140x602.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/>
<p>Apart from Do Kwon’s lawyers, the former finance minister also denied having anything to do with the Terraform founder. However, on June 6, a Montenegro news outlet Balkinsight <a href="https://balkaninsight.com/2023/06/06/montenegro-urged-to-probe-crypto-fugitives-ties-with-party-leader/" rel="nofollow">reported that</a> the country’s outgoing prime minister urged the prosecutors to investigate the relationship between Kwon and Spajic. </p>
<p>Also, on June 9, a Twitter account FatMan, dedicated to updating the crypto community about Terra issues, <a href="https://twitter.com/FatManTerra/status/1667078961501700098?" rel="nofollow">shared an update</a> about Do Kwon’s financial donations to Spajic. The Terraform founder has, however, denied the ties in the recent hearing. </p>
<p>Following the court session, the presiding judge Ivana Becic announced that June 19 would be the date for a verdict on the forgery charges. </p>
<p>Meanwhile, Do Kwon will remain in extradition custody for six months waiting for the court to grant or reject the South Korean extradition request.</p>
<p>Featured image from Pixabay and chart from Tradingview.com</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/arrest-460x307.jpeg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
