<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
>

<channel>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.newsbtc.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<description>Bitcoin &#38; Cryptocurrency News Today</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 06:17:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Stellar (XLM) Takes Investors By Surprise With 23% Rally</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/stellar-surprises-with-41-rally/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 06:17:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price action]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[stellar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XLM Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=540663</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Stellar (XLM), the decentralized blockchain platform aiming to revolutionize the world of cross-border transactions and digital asset transfers, has emerged as one of the most promising cryptocurrencies in today&#8217;s market.  With its recent surge, Stellar has garnered significant attention and is rapidly becoming one of the biggest gainers of the day. As Bitcoin&#8217;s price continues to climb, it has sparked renewed interest and enthusiasm in the overall cryptocurrency market, benefiting altcoins like Stellar. Related Reading: Solana Makes A Comeback: 15% Rally Signals Renewed Momentum This bullish momentum is not only a testament to the platform&#8217;s technological advancements but also to the growing recognition of its potential to disrupt traditional financial systems. XLM Shows Strong Rally, But Traders Should Watch Out XLM has recently witnessed a notable rally of 4.6% within a 24-hour period, propelling its price to $0.109, as reported by CoinGecko. Moreover, over the past seven days, XLM has demonstrated a significant surge of 22.6%. These positive price movements have captured the attention of investors and traders alike, signaling a bullish sentiment in the market. XLM up 4.6 in the last 24 hours. Source: Coingecko Despite the encouraging rally, a new XLM price report advises higher timeframe traders to remain prepared for a possible range rather than a breakout beyond a crucial resistance level. On the 1-day price chart, the $0.0935 level represents the previous lower high for XLM. Related Reading: Arbitrum Gains Tempered By Obstacles, Hindering ARB’s Further Upswing However, on June 27, the price successfully broke past this resistance level with substantial trading volume. This breakout was followed by consecutive days of upward movement, without any significant retracement, indicating a strong bullish trend in the market. XLM price trajectory in the last week. Source: CoinMarketCap Looking ahead, if XLM experiences a dip in the coming days, the $0.1 level could potentially serve as a support level for the cryptocurrency. This implies that if the price retraces, there may be a higher chance of finding support around the $0.1 mark, offering some stability to XLM&#8217;s price action. Correlation Between Bitcoin And Altcoins Historically, Bitcoin has exhibited a positive correlation with many altcoins. This means that when Bitcoin&#8217;s price surges, altcoins tend to follow suit, amplifying the overall bullish sentiment in the market. The recent rally in Bitcoin has likely created a favorable environment for altcoins, including XLM, leading to their upward price movements. XLM market cap currently at $3 billion on the weekly chart: TradingView.com However, it&#8217;s essential to note that while altcoins often experience a positive correlation with Bitcoin during bullish phases, their performance can vary. Some altcoins may outperform Bitcoin, while others may underperform. Therefore, it&#8217;s crucial for investors and traders to conduct thorough research and analyze the specific factors influencing each altcoin&#8217;s price trajectory. (This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk). Featured image from Forex Academy]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Stellar (XLM), the decentralized blockchain platform aiming to revolutionize the world of cross-border transactions and digital asset transfers, has emerged as one of the most promising cryptocurrencies in today&#8217;s market. </p>
<p>With its recent surge, Stellar has garnered significant attention and is rapidly becoming one of the biggest gainers of the day. As Bitcoin&#8217;s price continues to climb, it has sparked renewed interest and enthusiasm in the overall cryptocurrency market, benefiting altcoins like Stellar.</p>

<p>This bullish momentum is not only a testament to the platform&#8217;s technological advancements but also to the growing recognition of its potential to disrupt traditional financial systems.</p>
<h2><strong>XLM Shows Strong Rally, But Traders Should Watch Out</strong></h2>
<p>XLM has recently witnessed a notable rally of 4.6% within a 24-hour period, propelling its price to $0.109, as reported by <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/stellar" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">CoinGecko</a>. Moreover, over the past seven days, XLM has demonstrated a significant surge of 22.6%. These positive price movements have captured the attention of investors and traders alike, signaling a bullish sentiment in the market.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-540665" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a.png" alt="" width="1045" height="75" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a.png 1045w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-460x33.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-860x62.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-768x55.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-750x54.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 1045px) 100vw, 1045px"/></p>

<p>Despite the encouraging rally, a new <a href="https://ambcrypto.com/xlm-turns-bullish-gains-41-in-two-weeks/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">XLM price report</a> advises higher timeframe traders to remain prepared for a possible range rather than a breakout beyond a crucial resistance level. On the 1-day price chart, the $0.0935 level represents the previous lower high for XLM.</p>

<p>However, on June 27, the price successfully broke past this resistance level with substantial trading volume. This breakout was followed by consecutive days of upward movement, without any significant retracement, indicating a strong bullish trend in the market.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-540666" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-1.png" alt="" width="1041" height="462" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-1.png 1041w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-1-460x204.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-1-860x382.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-1-768x341.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-1-750x333.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 1041px) 100vw, 1041px"/></p>

<p>Looking ahead, if XLM experiences a dip in the coming days, the $0.1 level could potentially serve as a support level for the cryptocurrency. This implies that if the price retraces, there may be a higher chance of finding support around the $0.1 mark, offering some stability to XLM&#8217;s price action.</p>
<h2><strong>Correlation Between Bitcoin And Altcoins</strong></h2>
<p>Historically, Bitcoin has exhibited a positive correlation with many altcoins. This means that when <a href="https://www.afr.com/markets/currencies/blackrock-s-bitcoin-ambitions-driving-price-higher-20230629-p5dke2" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Bitcoin&#8217;s price surges</a>, altcoins tend to follow suit, amplifying the overall bullish sentiment in the market. The recent rally in Bitcoin has likely created a favorable environment for altcoins, including XLM, leading to their upward price movements.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/4044QwWl/" width="2315" height="1109"/></p>

<p>However, it&#8217;s essential to note that while altcoins often experience a positive correlation with Bitcoin during bullish phases, their performance can vary. Some altcoins may outperform Bitcoin, while others may underperform. Therefore, it&#8217;s crucial for investors and traders to conduct thorough research and analyze the specific factors influencing each altcoin&#8217;s price trajectory.</p>
<p><em>(This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk).</em></p>
<p><em>Featured image from Forex Academy</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-2-460x269.png" width="460" height="269" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Here’s What Caused Bitcoin’s Flash Crash To $29,000</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/heres-what-caused-bitcoins-flash-crash-to-29000/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Best Owie]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 23:00:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=540611</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin had been trending over $31,000 for the better part of Friday after reclaiming this support level from the bears. However, this did not last long as the digital asset saw a flash crash that sent its price spiraling toward the $29,000 level. SEC Says ETF Filings Are Inadequate On Friday, the Wall Street Journal released a report that negatively impacted the market. The report revealed that the United States Securities and Exchange Commission thought that the recent barrage of Bitcoin ETH filings that it had received was inadequate in their filings. Related Reading: Litecoin Bull Case Grows Stronger As Hashrate Touches New All Time-High This follows a two-week stretch of positivity after heavy hitters such as BlackRock, WisdomTree, and Fidelity, among others, filed requests for Bitcoin Spot ETFs with the SEC. Following the news of the filings, the price of Bitcoin rallied tremendously, crossing $31,000 for the first time in over one month. However, with the news of the SEC saying that the filings are inadequate, it has quickly eroded investor sentiment. The price of BTC fell to $29,200 on Friday afternoon, before recovering quickly. Although the damage was already done and BTC bulls are now struggling to maintain support at $30,000. Bitcoin In Freefall Bitcoin had been able to establish a reasonably bullish trend over the last couple of weeks. But that did not last long as the SEC came to burst the bubble for investors. As a result, Bitcoin seems to be in freefall with no reasonable support to keep the price from falling lower. BTC struggles to hold $30,000 &#124; Source: BTCUSD on TradingView.com In a matter of hours, the digital asset has lost about $1,000 of its value, turning a previously good day into a bloody day for investors. This rapid decline has shoved the cryptocurrency below its 5-day moving average, which could see BTC become bearish over the weekend. However, in the mid and long-term, the digital asset remains as bullish as ever, ranging above both its 50-day and 100-day moving averages. Both of these levels signal that while bears may have gained temporary control of the price, bulls remain largely in control. And as long as sell pressure remains low, then BTC could recover back above $31,000 over the next couple of days. Related Reading: The Blessing Of July: Can Bitcoin Climb To $36,000 In The Coming Month? At the time of writing, BTC is down 1.59% in the last 24 hours to be trading slightly above $30,000. Although it is currently struggling, its trading volume is sitting above $23.5 billion, showing a significant amount of demand for the digital asset as well. Follow Best Owie on Twitter for market insights, updates, and the occasional funny tweet… Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="p2">Bitcoin had been trending over $31,000 for the better part of Friday after reclaiming this support level from the bears. However, this did not last long as the digital asset saw a flash crash that sent its price spiraling toward the $29,000 level.</p>
<h2 class="p2">SEC Says ETF Filings Are Inadequate</h2>
<p class="p2">On Friday, the Wall Street Journal released a <a href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/sec-says-spot-bitcoin-etf-filings-are-inadequate-390336e8" rel="nofollow">report</a> that negatively impacted the market. The report revealed that the United States Securities and Exchange Commission thought that the recent barrage of Bitcoin ETH filings that it had received was inadequate in their filings.</p>

<p class="p2">This follows a two-week stretch of positivity after heavy hitters such as BlackRock, WisdomTree, and Fidelity, among others, filed requests for Bitcoin Spot ETFs with the SEC. Following the news of the filings, the price of Bitcoin rallied tremendously, crossing $31,000 for the first time in over one month.</p>
<p class="p2">However, with the news of the SEC saying that the filings are inadequate, it has quickly eroded investor sentiment. The price of BTC fell to $29,200 on Friday afternoon, before recovering quickly. Although the damage was already done and BTC bulls are now struggling to maintain support at $30,000.</p>
<h2 class="p2">Bitcoin In Freefall</h2>
<p class="p2">Bitcoin had been able to establish a reasonably bullish trend over the last couple of weeks. But that did not last long as the SEC came to burst the bubble for investors. As a result, Bitcoin seems to be in freefall with no reasonable support to keep the price from falling lower.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/0qDjwsC1/" alt="Bitcoin (BTC) price chart from TradingView.com" width="2884" height="1724"/></p>

<p class="p2">In a matter of hours, the digital asset has lost about $1,000 of its value, turning a previously good day into a bloody day for investors. This rapid decline has shoved the cryptocurrency below its 5-day moving average, which could see BTC become bearish over the weekend.</p>
<p class="p2">However, in the mid and long-term, the digital asset remains as bullish as ever, ranging above both its 50-day and 100-day moving averages. Both of these levels signal that while bears may have gained temporary control of the price, bulls remain largely in control. And as long as sell pressure remains low, then BTC could recover back above $31,000 over the next couple of days.</p>

<p class="p2">At the time of writing, BTC is down 1.59% in the last 24 hours to be trading slightly above $30,000. Although it is currently struggling, its trading volume is sitting above $23.5 billion, showing a significant amount of demand for the digital asset as well.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/iStock-1212035447-1-460x345.jpg" width="460" height="345" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Compound (COMP) Blasts Off With 113% Rise In Two-Week Rally, What&#8217;s Behind The Surge?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/altcoin/compound-comp-blasts-off-with-113-rise-in-two-week-rally-whats-behind-the-surge/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 20:00:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[compound]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Compound (COMP)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[compusdt]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DeFi]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=540625</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Compound (COMP) has recently surged with a staggering 113% rise in just two weeks, and the reason behind the rally has been the talk of the crypto community. DeFi Ignas, a decentralized finance (DeFi) researcher, has analyzed the recent developments surrounding Compound and provided insights into the potential factors contributing to the surge. Compound Takes The Lead With Triple-Digit Growth In June This remarkable growth has been fueled by a range of factors, including the recent announcement of the launch of Superstate Funds by Compound&#8217;s founder, which aims to bridge traditional markets with blockchain ecosystems. One of the major challenges facing DeFi is the lack of integration with traditional financial markets. While the DeFi space has grown rapidly over the past few years, it is still relatively small compared to the traditional financial system.  Related Reading: XRP Dips After SEC’s ETF Blow But A Rebound Looks Likely By bridging these two worlds, Superstate could help to bring more institutional investors into the DeFi space and increase the overall liquidity and stability of DeFi protocols. Furthermore, Superstate&#8217;s focus on creating regulated financial products could help address some of the regulatory concerns raised about DeFi. While DeFi protocols are decentralized and operate on blockchain networks, they still fall under the jurisdiction of various regulatory bodies.  By creating regulated financial products that comply with existing regulations, Superstate could help to mitigate some of the risks associated with DeFi and pave the way for more widespread adoption of these protocols. Superstate aims to bridge traditional markets with blockchain ecosystems by buying short-term government debt and tokenizing it on blockchains. While it is unclear whether the tokenization will include COMP holders or lead to an airdrop, this announcement has generated excitement and speculation among the crypto community. Jump Crypto Whale Responsible For COMP Rally? While new governance proposals have been introduced, none have been significant enough to account for the sudden price increase. However, there has been a significant balance change among various Jump Crypto wallets. Jump Crypto wallets are a group of cryptocurrency wallets associated with Jump Trading, a Chicago-based trading firm specializing in high-frequency trading strategies. The wallets have been identified as significant players in the cryptocurrency market, particularly in the DeFi space, where they have been involved in market making and liquidity provision. These wallets have emerged as major players in the COMP market. One of these wallets holds many COMP tokens and has been involved in significant balance changes, including the recent withdrawal of 170,000 COMP tokens from Binance. This withdrawal amounts to $9.7 million and represents 1.7% of the total supply of COMP. Related Reading: OKX Liquid Marketplace Records Over $3 Billion In Institutional Trade Volume The actions of this particular wallet appear to be the primary reason for the recent surge in the COMP price. The withdrawal of such a large amount of tokens from Binance has significantly increased demand for COMP, driving up its price. As a result, this wallet now ranks as the ninth-largest holder of COMP tokens. Compound&#8217;s native token, COMP, is trading at $58, following its uptrend that began on June 16th. In the last 24 hours, COMP has continued to soar with a 14% gain and is currently attempting to break through the $60 level to surpass its yearly high of $64 achieved in February. Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com ]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Compound (COMP) has recently surged with a staggering 113% rise in just two weeks, and the reason behind the rally has been the talk of the crypto community. DeFi Ignas, a decentralized finance (DeFi) researcher, has <a href="https://twitter.com/DefiIgnas/status/1674758284816031746?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">analyzed </a>the recent developments surrounding Compound and provided insights into the potential factors contributing to the surge.</p>
<h2>Compound Takes The Lead With Triple-Digit Growth In June</h2>
<p>This remarkable growth has been fueled by a range of factors, including the recent announcement of the launch of Superstate Funds by Compound&#8217;s founder, which aims to bridge traditional markets with blockchain ecosystems.</p>
<p>One of the major challenges facing DeFi is the lack of integration with traditional financial markets. While the DeFi space has grown rapidly over the past few years, it is still relatively small compared to the traditional financial system. </p>

<p>By bridging these two worlds, Superstate could help to bring more institutional investors into the DeFi space and increase the overall liquidity and stability of DeFi protocols.</p>
<p>Furthermore, Superstate&#8217;s focus on creating regulated financial products could help address some of the regulatory concerns raised about DeFi. While DeFi protocols are decentralized and operate on blockchain networks, they still fall under the jurisdiction of various regulatory bodies. </p>
<p>By creating regulated financial products that comply with existing regulations, Superstate could help to mitigate some of the risks associated with DeFi and pave the way for more widespread adoption of these protocols.</p>
<p>Superstate aims to bridge traditional markets with blockchain ecosystems by buying short-term government debt and tokenizing it on blockchains. While it is unclear whether the tokenization will include COMP holders or lead to an airdrop, this announcement has generated excitement and speculation among the crypto community.</p>
Jump Crypto Whale Responsible For COMP Rally?
<p>While new governance proposals have been introduced, none have been significant enough to account for the sudden price increase. However, there has been a significant balance change among various Jump Crypto wallets.</p>
<p>Jump Crypto wallets are a group of cryptocurrency wallets associated with Jump Trading, a Chicago-based trading firm specializing in high-frequency trading strategies. The wallets have been identified as significant players in the cryptocurrency market, particularly in the DeFi space, where they have been involved in market making and liquidity provision.</p>
<p>These wallets have emerged as major players in the COMP market. One of these wallets holds many COMP tokens and has been involved in significant balance changes, including the recent withdrawal of 170,000 COMP tokens from Binance. This withdrawal amounts to $9.7 million and represents 1.7% of the total supply of COMP.</p>

<p>The actions of this particular wallet appear to be the primary reason for the recent surge in the COMP price. The withdrawal of such a large amount of tokens from Binance has significantly increased demand for COMP, driving up its price. As a result, this wallet now ranks as the ninth-largest holder of COMP tokens.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/Rm4ONpM3/" alt="Compound " width="1815" height="858"/>
<p>Compound&#8217;s native token, COMP, is trading at $58, following its uptrend that began on June 16th. In the last 24 hours, COMP has continued to soar with a 14% gain and is currently attempting to break through the $60 level to surpass its yearly high of $64 achieved in February.</p>
<p>Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/iStock-1369021012-460x300.jpg" width="460" height="300" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Litecoin Breaks Psychological Barrier But Remains in Bearish Territory: What Lies Ahead?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/litecoin/litecoin-breaks-psychological-barrier-but-remains-in-bearish-territory-what-lies-ahead/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[anushsamal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 19:00:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Litecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ltc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ltc/usd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LTCUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=540617</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The recent surge in Litecoin (LTC) price propelled it to reach a significant psychological level of $100. This upward movement has provided a bullish boost and allowed the altcoin to register gains in recent trading sessions. However, despite this bullishness, the price of LTC remains within bearish territory, indicating ongoing downward pressure. Reclaiming the $100 price mark is crucial for sustaining a bullish trend. Related Reading: XRP Dips After SEC’s ETF Blow But A Rebound Looks Likely In the past 24 hours, LTC has experienced a rally of nearly 17%. On the weekly chart, the altcoin has maintained double-digit gains, reflecting its positive performance over a longer period. It&#8217;s worth noting that Litecoin&#8217;s halving event is just a little over a month away. Historically, the price of the asset tends to increase before this event. However, due to the fluctuating nature of Bitcoin, which often influences major altcoins, LTC might experience slight depreciation. Significant depreciation is less likely as long as LTC maintains its price above the local support level. A sustained increase in demand for the altcoin is necessary to ensure continued gains on the daily chart. The market capitalization of LTC has also increased, indicating bullish momentum in the market. Litecoin Price Analysis: One-Day Chart When writing, Litecoin (LTC) was trading at $97.81. After reaching the $100 mark, LTC has been steadily gaining in price. However, despite the bullish momentum, Litecoin remains within a crucial zone that is bearish and could potentially reverse the gains. This bearish zone, indicated in red, extends from $94 to $103. In previous trading sessions, LTC has retraced when attempting to revisit the $103 level. The $94 mark has also been a reversal point over the past few months. Moreover, Litecoin entered the excess selling zone the maximum number of times, where the price fluctuated between the two (upper and lower) bands of the bearish region. The overhead resistance levels are $100 and $103. In case of a decline from these levels, the price could drop to $94 initially, followed by a potential further decline to $90. Technical Analysis Regarding demand, Litecoin (LTC) was approaching overbought conditions. The Relative Strength Index (RSI) was above the 60 mark, indicating buyers had gained market control. This suggests a higher demand for LTC compared to selling pressure. The increased demand was also reflected in the price, as it climbed above the 20-Simple Moving Average (SMA) line. This signifies that buyers were driving the price momentum in the market, pushing it higher. As long as Litecoin (LTC) maintains its price above the 20-Simple Moving Average (SMA), indicated by the red line on the chart, specifically around the $87 level, the bullish sentiment is expected to persist. Litecoin (LTC) formed a strong buy signal in line with increased demand. The Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD) indicator showed a green histogram, indicating a fresh buy signal. This suggests a strong bullish momentum and strength in the LTC market. Related Reading: Litecoin Up 18% In Past 24 Hours, Is Halving Rally Here? Furthermore, the Chaikin Money Flow (CMF) indicator displayed capital inflows outweighing outflows. The indicator was above the half-line, indicating more capital inflows than outflows at the given time. Featured image from UnSplash, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The recent surge in Litecoin (LTC) price propelled it to reach a significant psychological level of $100. This upward movement has provided a bullish boost and allowed the altcoin to register gains in recent trading sessions.</p>
<p>However, despite this bullishness, the price of LTC remains within bearish territory, indicating ongoing downward pressure. Reclaiming the $100 price mark is crucial for sustaining a bullish trend.</p>

<p>In the past 24 hours, LTC has experienced a rally of nearly 17%. On the weekly chart, the altcoin has maintained double-digit gains, reflecting its positive performance over a longer period.</p>
<p>It&#8217;s worth noting that Litecoin&#8217;s halving event is just a little over a month away. Historically, the price of the asset tends to increase before this event.</p>
<p>However, due to the fluctuating nature of Bitcoin, which often influences major altcoins, LTC might experience slight depreciation.</p>
<p>Significant depreciation is less likely as long as LTC maintains its price above the local support level. A sustained increase in demand for the altcoin is necessary to ensure continued gains on the daily chart. The market capitalization of LTC has also increased, indicating bullish momentum in the market.</p>
<h2>Litecoin Price Analysis: One-Day Chart</h2>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-540619 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/LTCUSDT_2023-06-30_21-49-25.png" alt="Litecoin" width="1817" height="743" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/LTCUSDT_2023-06-30_21-49-25.png 1817w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/LTCUSDT_2023-06-30_21-49-25-460x188.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/LTCUSDT_2023-06-30_21-49-25-860x352.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/LTCUSDT_2023-06-30_21-49-25-768x314.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/LTCUSDT_2023-06-30_21-49-25-1536x628.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/LTCUSDT_2023-06-30_21-49-25-750x307.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/LTCUSDT_2023-06-30_21-49-25-1140x466.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1817px) 100vw, 1817px"/>
<p>When writing, Litecoin (LTC) was trading at $97.81. After reaching the $100 mark, LTC has been steadily gaining in price. However, despite the bullish momentum, Litecoin remains within a crucial zone that is bearish and could potentially reverse the gains.</p>
<p>This bearish zone, indicated in red, extends from $94 to $103. In previous trading sessions, LTC has retraced when attempting to revisit the $103 level. The $94 mark has also been a reversal point over the past few months.</p>
<p>Moreover, Litecoin entered the excess selling zone the maximum number of times, where the price fluctuated between the two (upper and lower) bands of the bearish region.</p>
<p>The overhead resistance levels are $100 and $103. In case of a decline from these levels, the price could drop to $94 initially, followed by a potential further decline to $90.</p>
<h2>Technical Analysis</h2>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-540620 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/LTCUSDT_2023-06-30_21-45-56.png" alt="Litecoin" width="1817" height="743" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/LTCUSDT_2023-06-30_21-45-56.png 1817w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/LTCUSDT_2023-06-30_21-45-56-460x188.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/LTCUSDT_2023-06-30_21-45-56-860x352.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/LTCUSDT_2023-06-30_21-45-56-768x314.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/LTCUSDT_2023-06-30_21-45-56-1536x628.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/LTCUSDT_2023-06-30_21-45-56-750x307.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/LTCUSDT_2023-06-30_21-45-56-1140x466.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1817px) 100vw, 1817px"/>
<p>Regarding demand, Litecoin (LTC) was approaching overbought conditions. The Relative Strength Index (RSI) was above the 60 mark, indicating buyers had gained market control. This suggests a higher demand for LTC compared to selling pressure.</p>
<p>The increased demand was also reflected in the price, as it climbed above the 20-Simple Moving Average (SMA) line. This signifies that buyers were driving the price momentum in the market, pushing it higher.</p>
<p>As long as Litecoin (LTC) maintains its price above the 20-Simple Moving Average (SMA), indicated by the red line on the chart, specifically around the $87 level, the bullish sentiment is expected to persist.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-540621 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/LTCUSDT_2023-06-30_21-46-24.png" alt="Litecoin" width="1817" height="743" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/LTCUSDT_2023-06-30_21-46-24.png 1817w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/LTCUSDT_2023-06-30_21-46-24-460x188.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/LTCUSDT_2023-06-30_21-46-24-860x352.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/LTCUSDT_2023-06-30_21-46-24-768x314.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/LTCUSDT_2023-06-30_21-46-24-1536x628.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/LTCUSDT_2023-06-30_21-46-24-750x307.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/LTCUSDT_2023-06-30_21-46-24-1140x466.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1817px) 100vw, 1817px"/>
<p>Litecoin (LTC) formed a strong buy signal in line with increased demand. The Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD) indicator showed a green histogram, indicating a fresh buy signal. This suggests a strong bullish momentum and strength in the LTC market.</p>

<p>Furthermore, the Chaikin Money Flow (CMF) indicator displayed capital inflows outweighing outflows. The indicator was above the half-line, indicating more capital inflows than outflows at the given time.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/kanchanara-_m8pHtTykMs-unsplash-460x306.jpg" width="460" height="306" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Price Takes A Hit As SEC Deems Spot ETF Filings &#8216;Inadequate&#8217;</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-price-takes-a-hit-as-sec-deems-spot-etf-filings-inadequate/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 18:00:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=540607</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has reportedly told exchanges Nasdaq and Cboe that recent filings for spot Bitcoin (BTC) exchange-traded funds (ETFs) from asset managers including BlackRock and Fidelity were not “clear and comprehensive” enough. Bitcoin ETFs In Jeopardy? The SEC has rejected several Bitcoin ETF filings in recent years due to concerns over potential fraudulent and manipulative practices associated with the cryptocurrency market.  The agency has stated that the filings do not meet the standards designed to protect investors and the public interest. In particular, the SEC has expressed concerns about the lack of regulation and oversight in the cryptocurrency market, which could make it easier for bad actors to manipulate the price of Bitcoin and other cryptocurrencies.  Related Reading: Litecoin Up 18% In Past 24 Hours, Is Halving Rally Here? The SEC has also expressed concerns about custody and liquidity issues related to cryptocurrency. While some asset managers have attempted to address these concerns in their filings, the SEC has continued to reject them as inadequate. However, Several proposed solutions have been put forward to address the SEC&#8217;s concerns around Bitcoin ETFs.  One potential solution is the use of regulated custodians to hold the Bitcoin backing the ETF, which would provide greater oversight and security for investors. Some asset managers have also proposed using futures contracts to track the price of Bitcoin, rather than holding the actual cryptocurrency, which could help address liquidity concerns.  In addition, some have suggested that the SEC could work with industry participants to establish best practices and guidelines for the cryptocurrency market, which could help mitigate risks associated with fraudulent and manipulative practices.  Despite these proposals, the SEC has continued to scrutinize Bitcoin ETF filings, indicating that more work may need to be done to address the agency&#8217;s concerns. The SEC declined to comment on the Wall Street Journal report, while Nasdaq and Cboe were not available for immediate comment. The decision is a blow to asset managers&#8217; attempts to launch Bitcoin ETFs, which have been repeatedly blocked by regulators in the US. BTC’s Price Tumbles, Signaling The End Of The Bull Run?  The latest criticism by the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) on filings for spot Bitcoin exchange-traded funds has caused BTC’s price to drop from over $31,000 to $29,800.  Although Bitcoin is currently trading above the $30,000 line, there is uncertainty around the ETF filings by BlackRock and other major financial players, which could lead to another downtrend and a test of lower support. If this were to happen, Bitcoin bulls must hold the $29,500 line, which is the next support below $30,000. Additionally, Bitcoin&#8217;s 50-day moving average (MA) on the daily chart could provide strong support for the cryptocurrency, currently placed at $28,100. Related Reading: Ethereum Classic (ETC) Resumes Uptrend, Notches 13% In The Last Day Nevertheless, as reported on June 29th by NewsBTC, Bitcoin is likely to enter a 10-day period of downtrend due to the loss of the strength of the current uptrend, as noted by the Average Directional Index (ADX) on the 1-day chart. The ADX is a technical indicator that measures the strength of a trend and is used by traders to identify potential price movements. Bitcoin&#8217;s ADX is already spiking down, which suggests a potential shift in trend. Additionally, the squeeze momentum indicator also reflects the downtrend that Bitcoin could be poised to experience in the coming week and a half. Overall, the recent criticism by the US SEC of the filings for spot BTC ETFs by BlackRock and Fidelity adds to the uncertainty surrounding the cryptocurrency&#8217;s future price movements. If the asset managers cannot find common ground with the SEC&#8217;s expectations, their ETF applications could be in jeopardy. Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com ]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has <a href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/sec-says-spot-bitcoin-etf-filings-are-inadequate-390336e8" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">reportedly </a>told exchanges Nasdaq and Cboe that recent filings for spot Bitcoin (BTC) exchange-traded funds (ETFs) from asset managers including BlackRock and Fidelity were not “clear and comprehensive” enough.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin ETFs In Jeopardy?</h2>
<p>The SEC has rejected several Bitcoin ETF filings in recent years due to concerns over potential fraudulent and manipulative practices associated with the cryptocurrency market. </p>
<p>The agency has stated that the filings do not meet the standards designed to protect investors and the public interest. In particular, the SEC has expressed concerns about the lack of regulation and oversight in the cryptocurrency market, which could make it easier for bad actors to manipulate the price of Bitcoin and other cryptocurrencies. </p>

<p>The SEC has also expressed concerns about custody and liquidity issues related to cryptocurrency. While some asset managers have attempted to address these concerns in their filings, the SEC has continued to reject them as inadequate. However, Several proposed solutions have been put forward to address the SEC&#8217;s concerns around Bitcoin ETFs. </p>
<p>One potential solution is the use of regulated custodians to hold the Bitcoin backing the ETF, which would provide greater oversight and security for investors. Some asset managers have also proposed using futures contracts to track the price of Bitcoin, rather than holding the actual cryptocurrency, which could help address liquidity concerns. </p>
<p>In addition, some have suggested that the SEC could work with industry participants to establish best practices and guidelines for the cryptocurrency market, which could help mitigate risks associated with fraudulent and manipulative practices. </p>
<p>Despite these proposals, the SEC has continued to scrutinize Bitcoin ETF filings, indicating that more work may need to be done to address the agency&#8217;s concerns.</p>
<p>The SEC declined to comment on the Wall Street Journal report, while Nasdaq and Cboe were not available for immediate comment. The decision is a blow to asset managers&#8217; attempts to launch Bitcoin ETFs, which have been repeatedly blocked by regulators in the US.</p>
BTC’s Price Tumbles, Signaling The End Of The Bull Run? 
<p>The latest criticism by the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) on filings for spot Bitcoin exchange-traded funds has caused BTC’s price to drop from over $31,000 to $29,800. </p>
<p>Although Bitcoin is currently trading above the $30,000 line, there is uncertainty around the ETF filings by BlackRock and other major financial players, which could lead to another downtrend and a test of lower support.</p>
<p>If this were to happen, Bitcoin bulls must hold the $29,500 line, which is the next support below $30,000. Additionally, Bitcoin&#8217;s 50-day moving average (MA) on the daily chart could provide strong support for the cryptocurrency, currently placed at $28,100.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/etc/ethereum-classic-etc-resumes-uptrend-notches-13-in-the-last-day/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Ethereum Classic (ETC) Resumes Uptrend, Notches 13% In The Last Day</a></p>
<p>Nevertheless, as reported on June 29th by <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-bulls-battle-against-miners-128-million-move-is-the-bull-run-in-danger/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">NewsBTC</a>, Bitcoin is likely to enter a 10-day period of downtrend due to the loss of the strength of the current uptrend, as noted by the Average Directional Index (ADX) on the 1-day chart.</p>
<p>The ADX is a technical indicator that measures the strength of a trend and is used by traders to identify potential price movements. Bitcoin&#8217;s ADX is already spiking down, which suggests a potential shift in trend. Additionally, the squeeze momentum indicator also reflects the downtrend that Bitcoin could be poised to experience in the coming week and a half.</p>
<p>Overall, the recent criticism by the US SEC of the filings for spot BTC ETFs by BlackRock and Fidelity adds to the uncertainty surrounding the cryptocurrency&#8217;s future price movements. </p>
<p>If the asset managers cannot find common ground with the SEC&#8217;s expectations, their ETF applications could be in jeopardy.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/Y74gTsm1/" alt="Bitcoin " width="1814" height="858"/>
<p>Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/iStock-1472939339-460x264.jpg" width="460" height="264" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>XRP Dips After SEC’s ETF Blow But A Rebound Looks Likely</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/xrp-dips-after-secs-etf-blow-but-a-rebound-looks-likely/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[anushsamal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 17:00:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrp]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrpusdt]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=540585</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has raised concerns about the recent filings for spot Bitcoin exchange-traded funds (ETFs), stating that they are insufficient. This comes after asset management giants BlackRock and Fidelity submitted their applications to launch spot Bitcoin ETFs. Related Reading: Cardano Shows Signs of Recovery: When Will it Reach $0.30? The Wall Street Journal reported that the SEC shared its perspective on the filings with Nasdaq and Cboe. Specifically, the agency expressed that the filings lacked clarity and comprehensiveness. Following the release of this news, Bitcoin experienced a drop of nearly 2% in its value. Similarly, other altcoins, including XRP, also saw a decline in their respective charts. Over the past 24 hours, XRP witnessed a decrease of approximately 1%, while on the weekly chart, it recorded a loss of more than 4%. As a result, the technical outlook turned bearish, leading to a decrease in investor interest. The charts reflected a decline in both demand and accumulation. Currently, XRP is hovering around a crucial support level, and a breach of this level may potentially trigger an upward movement for XRP. The market capitalization of XRP decreased, indicating that sellers had a stronger grip on the market. XRP Price Analysis: One-Day Chart As of the time of writing, the altcoin XRP was trading at $0.46. Currently, XRP has reached its lowest level since the end of May. This level has historically acted as a significant support level for the coin. This level is often referred to as a bullish order block, and it has the potential to drive price recovery. Looking ahead, the first hurdle for XRP would be the resistance at $0.48, followed by a potential move above the $0.50 mark. However, if XRP faces another rejection at $0.50, it could lead to a return to trading at $0.46 and possibly even a further decline to $0.43. Technical Analysis Due to low demand, there has been a decline in buying interest. The Relative Strength Index (RSI) is currently below the half-line and close to the 40-mark, suggesting that buyers have lost their influence and sellers have gained control. Similarly, XRP has dropped below the 20-Simple Moving Average line. This indicates a weakening demand and implies that sellers are currently driving the price momentum in the market As demand for the altcoin decreased, the altcoin generated sell signals, although these signals were diminishing in size. This indicates that the bearish momentum might be subsiding. The Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD) showed red histograms associated with the sell signals, but their size was decreasing. This suggests that while bearish sentiment still existed, the price could potentially experience a rebound in the near future. Related Reading: Slovakian Lawmakers Pass Amendment Lowering Cryptocurrency Taxation When considering volatility, the Bollinger Bands are used. In this case, the bands were wide and parallel, indicating a range for the altcoin. The upper band, which aligned with the $0.52 price level, is expected to serve as a significant resistance level. Featured image from Unsplash, charts from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has raised concerns about the recent filings for spot Bitcoin exchange-traded funds (ETFs), stating that they are insufficient. This comes after asset management giants BlackRock and Fidelity submitted their applications to launch spot Bitcoin ETFs.</p>

<p>The Wall Street Journal reported that the SEC shared its perspective on the filings with Nasdaq and Cboe. Specifically, the agency expressed that the filings lacked clarity and comprehensiveness.</p>
<p>Following the release of this news, Bitcoin experienced a drop of nearly 2% in its value. Similarly, other altcoins, including XRP, also saw a decline in their respective charts.</p>
<p>Over the past 24 hours, XRP witnessed a decrease of approximately 1%, while on the weekly chart, it recorded a loss of more than 4%. As a result, the technical outlook turned bearish, leading to a decrease in investor interest.</p>
<p>The charts reflected a decline in both demand and accumulation. Currently, XRP is hovering around a crucial support level, and a breach of this level may potentially trigger an upward movement for XRP. The market capitalization of XRP decreased, indicating that sellers had a stronger grip on the market.</p>
<h2>XRP Price Analysis: One-Day Chart</h2>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-540594 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPUSD_2023-06-30_19-53-03.png" alt="XRP" width="1817" height="743" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPUSD_2023-06-30_19-53-03.png 1817w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPUSD_2023-06-30_19-53-03-460x188.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPUSD_2023-06-30_19-53-03-860x352.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPUSD_2023-06-30_19-53-03-768x314.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPUSD_2023-06-30_19-53-03-1536x628.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPUSD_2023-06-30_19-53-03-750x307.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPUSD_2023-06-30_19-53-03-1140x466.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1817px) 100vw, 1817px"/>
<p>As of the time of writing, the altcoin XRP was trading at $0.46. Currently, XRP has reached its lowest level since the end of May. This level has historically acted as a significant support level for the coin. This level is often referred to as a bullish order block, and it has the potential to drive price recovery.</p>
<p>Looking ahead, the first hurdle for XRP would be the resistance at $0.48, followed by a potential move above the $0.50 mark. However, if XRP faces another rejection at $0.50, it could lead to a return to trading at $0.46 and possibly even a further decline to $0.43.</p>
<h2>Technical Analysis</h2>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-540597 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPUSD_2023-06-30_20-23-33.png" alt="XRP" width="1817" height="743" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPUSD_2023-06-30_20-23-33.png 1817w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPUSD_2023-06-30_20-23-33-460x188.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPUSD_2023-06-30_20-23-33-860x352.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPUSD_2023-06-30_20-23-33-768x314.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPUSD_2023-06-30_20-23-33-1536x628.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPUSD_2023-06-30_20-23-33-750x307.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPUSD_2023-06-30_20-23-33-1140x466.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1817px) 100vw, 1817px"/>
<p>Due to low demand, there has been a decline in buying interest. The Relative Strength Index (RSI) is currently below the half-line and close to the 40-mark, suggesting that buyers have lost their influence and sellers have gained control.</p>
<p>Similarly, XRP has dropped below the 20-Simple Moving Average line. This indicates a weakening demand and implies that sellers are currently driving the price momentum in the market</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-540599 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPUSD_2023-06-30_20-23-55.png" alt="XRP" width="1818" height="743" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPUSD_2023-06-30_20-23-55.png 1818w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPUSD_2023-06-30_20-23-55-460x188.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPUSD_2023-06-30_20-23-55-860x351.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPUSD_2023-06-30_20-23-55-768x314.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPUSD_2023-06-30_20-23-55-1536x628.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPUSD_2023-06-30_20-23-55-750x307.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPUSD_2023-06-30_20-23-55-1140x466.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1818px) 100vw, 1818px"/>
<p>As demand for the altcoin decreased, the altcoin generated sell signals, although these signals were diminishing in size. This indicates that the bearish momentum might be subsiding.</p>
<p>The Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD) showed red histograms associated with the sell signals, but their size was decreasing. This suggests that while bearish sentiment still existed, the price could potentially experience a rebound in the near future.</p>

<p>When considering volatility, the Bollinger Bands are used. In this case, the bands were wide and parallel, indicating a range for the altcoin. The upper band, which aligned with the $0.52 price level, is expected to serve as a significant resistance level.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/kanchanara-0kRsP5iRZI4-unsplash-7-460x306.jpg" width="460" height="306" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>OKX Liquid Marketplace Records Over $3 Billion In Institutional Trade Volume</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/crypto/okx-liquid-marketplace-records-3-billion-in-trade-volume/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Opeyemi Sule]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 16:00:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[futures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[OKB]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[OKX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Perpetuals]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=540581</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Institutional trade volume on the OKX Liquid Marketplace has surpassed $3 billion, the second-largest crypto exchange by trading volume announced on Friday. The Liquid Marketplace is an on-demand liquidity network for professional and institutional traders. This platform allows traders to send requests for quotes (RFQs) to market makers for large digital asset transactions.  OKX Liquid Marketplace Experiences Rapid Growth In Q2 In a press release on Friday, OKX announced that its Liquid Marketplace has now exceeded $3 billion. “This milestone is a testament to the Liquid Marketplace&#8217;s success in providing institutional traders with deep liquidity and reliable execution,” the press statement read. Related Reading: Whales Dive Into XRP, Accumulating $170 Million Worth: What’s Their Game Plan? In April 2023, OKX revealed that the institutional Liquid Marketplace recorded over $1 billion in trading volume in the first quarter of 2023. As of now &#8211; the end of June and 2023 Q2, this figure has more than tripled, surpassing the $3 billion mark. Furthermore, the Liquid Marketplace has been advancing in innovation and product development lately. A few days ago, OKX disclosed the launch of the “Nitro Spreads” feature on the institutional trading platform. Nitro Spreads allows professional and institutional traders to make complex basis trades in a single click. Basis trading refers to trading the difference between an asset’s price on two distinct markets, such as spot vs futures, to generate profits.  This type of trading can be cumbersome, as it usually requires both legs of the trade to be executed simultaneously. However, Nitro Spreads automates this process by executing the two legs of the trade via a central orderbook. On the Liquid Marketplace, traders can use the feature across any combination of the spot, perpetual, and futures markets. OKB Price Slows Down, Makes No Significant Movement In The Past Week While the OKX ecosystem has been surrounded by positivity in recent days, this has not been reflected in the price of OKB, the exchange’s native token. The coin has not registered any loss or gain in the past seven days, according to CoinGecko data. That said, the OKB token appears to be losing the momentum that pushed its price by nearly 13% in the previous week. The cryptocurrency has also not made any significant price movement since then. Related Reading: Bitcoin Price Stalls Below $31,000, Is The Best Time To Buy Next Monday? Price data reveals that OKB has been in a ranging market in the past few months, trading between the $55 and $40 price points. Since reaching a yearly high of $57.98, the cryptocurrency’s price has decreased by roughly 23%. As of this writing, the OKB token changes hands at $44.53, representing a 2.6% price increase in the last 24 hours. Meanwhile, the coin has a 24-hour trading volume of more than $6 million, with a 33.7% increase in the last day. OKBUSD trading at $44.391 &#124; Source: OKBUSD chart from TradingView Featured image from OKX, chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Institutional trade volume on the OKX Liquid Marketplace has surpassed $3 billion, the second-largest crypto exchange by trading volume announced on Friday.</p>
<p>The Liquid Marketplace is an on-demand liquidity network for professional and institutional traders. This platform allows traders to send requests for quotes (RFQs) to market makers for large digital asset transactions. </p>
<h2>OKX Liquid Marketplace Experiences Rapid Growth In Q2</h2>
<p>In a <a href="https://www.globenewswire.com/news-release/2023/06/30/2697553/0/en/Flash-News-OKX-Liquid-Marketplace-Exceeds-Over-USD-3-Billion-in-Institutional-Trading-Volume.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">press release</a> on Friday, OKX announced that its Liquid Marketplace has now exceeded $3 billion. “This milestone is a testament to the Liquid Marketplace&#8217;s success in providing institutional traders with deep liquidity and reliable execution,” the press statement read.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/whales-dive-into-xrp-accumulating-170-million-worth-whats-their-game-plan/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Whales Dive Into XRP, Accumulating $170 Million Worth: What’s Their Game Plan?</a></p>
<p>In April 2023, OKX revealed that the institutional Liquid Marketplace recorded over $1 billion in trading volume in the first quarter of 2023. As of now &#8211; the end of June and 2023 Q2, this figure has more than tripled, surpassing the $3 billion mark.</p>
<p>Furthermore, the Liquid Marketplace has been advancing in innovation and product development lately. A few days ago, OKX disclosed the <a href="https://www.okx.com/learn/okx-liquid-marketplace-launches-nitro-spreads-one-click-basis-trading" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">launch of the “Nitro Spreads”</a> feature on the institutional trading platform.</p>
<p>Nitro Spreads allows professional and institutional traders to make complex basis trades in a single click. Basis trading refers to trading the difference between an asset’s price on two distinct markets, such as spot vs futures, to generate profits. </p>
<p>This type of trading can be cumbersome, as it usually requires both legs of the trade to be executed simultaneously. However, Nitro Spreads automates this process by executing the two legs of the trade via a central orderbook. On the Liquid Marketplace, traders can use the feature across any combination of the spot, perpetual, and futures markets.</p>
<h2>OKB Price Slows Down, Makes No Significant Movement In The Past Week</h2>
<p>While the OKX ecosystem has been surrounded by positivity in recent days, this has not been reflected in the price of OKB, the exchange’s native token. The coin has not registered any loss or gain in the past seven days, according to <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/okb" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">CoinGecko data</a>.</p>
<p>That said, the OKB token appears to be losing the momentum that pushed its price by nearly 13% in the previous week. The cryptocurrency has also not made any significant price movement since then.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-stalls-31000-best-time-to-buy-next-monday/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Bitcoin Price Stalls Below $31,000, Is The Best Time To Buy Next Monday?</a></p>
<p>Price data reveals that OKB has been in a ranging market in the past few months, trading between the $55 and $40 price points. Since reaching a yearly high of $57.98, the cryptocurrency’s price has decreased by roughly 23%.</p>
<p>As of this writing, the OKB token changes hands at $44.53, representing a 2.6% price increase in the last 24 hours. Meanwhile, the coin has a 24-hour trading volume of more than $6 million, with a 33.7% increase in the last day.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/FrqbLgA0/" alt="OKX" width="1009" height="591"/></p>





]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/07104210-2048x1152-1-460x259.jpg" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum Classic (ETC) Resumes Uptrend, Notches 13% In The Last Day</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/etc/ethereum-classic-etc-resumes-uptrend-notches-13-in-the-last-day/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Semilore Faleti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 15:00:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[ETC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum Classic]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=540582</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Ethereum Classic (ETC) is currently experiencing a rise in its market price, gaining 13.99% in the last 24 hours, according to data from CoinMarketCap.  Following the ETC’s dip in the last two days, it appears the bulls have retaken control of the market, pushing the coin to trade above the $20 mark for the first time since April. ETC&#8217;s Price Action In June Ethereum Classic has found a place among the headlines in the last two weeks following its initial bearish form at the start of June.  ETC began the month trading around $18.01 before experiencing a nosedive which saw the token trade as low as $13.99 on June 10. Related Reading: Litecoin Up 18% In Past 24 Hours, Is Halving Rally Here? Thereafter, ETC would rise to $15.03 and hover around this price region for the next few days before embarking on a bullish run that to gain by 28.60% between June 20 and June 24, hitting the price resistance level at $19.33.  The following days would then present a mixed price action before ETC finally retraced to its key support level at $17.64 on June 29. After retesting at this price zone, ETC’s price has resumed its uptrend, climbing higher since then. Ethereum Classic (ETC) remains one of the major projects in the cryptocurrency space. Launched in July 2016, Ethereum Classic is a hard fork of Ethereum created to preserve the purpose and integrity of the original Ethereum network.  At the time of writing, ETC is exchanging hands at  $20.90, with a 1.51% gain in the last hour. The token’s 24-hour trading volume is currently valued at $482 million, having also gone up by 208.92%. ETC Trading At $21.03 On The 1-Hour Chart &#124; Source: ETCUSD Chart On Tradingview.com ETC Price Analysis And Prediction Looking at the ETC’s hourly chart, its Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD) remains well above the signal line indicating the token’s bullish run may still be on.  However, its Relative Strength Index (RSI) is currently in the overbought zone at 89.71, meaning a selling pressure may soon occur, which may drive down the token’s price. Related Reading: Ethereum Continues Uptrend As Staked ETH Soars To New High According to the prediction site, WalletInvestor, if the bulls manage to sustain buying pressure, ETC’s price would experience only a small rise reaching the market value of $21.42 in 14 days. However, if the reverse is the case, and ETC falls under bearish pressure, the team predicts the token to fall to a market price of $18.00.  That said, most of the crypto markets are also on an uptrend alongside Ethereum Classic (ETC). Market leader Bitcoin (BTC) is up by 0.87% in the last day, while other notable coins such as Cardano (ADA) and Solana (SOL) are also gaining by 7.41% and 6.72%, respectively. Featured Image: The Guardian Nigeria, chart from Tradingview.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ethereum Classic (ETC) is currently experiencing a rise in its market price, gaining 13.99% in the last 24 hours, according to <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/ethereum-classic/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">data from CoinMarketCap</a>. </p>
<p>Following the ETC’s dip in the last two days, it appears the bulls have retaken control of the market, pushing the coin to trade above the $20 mark for the first time since April.</p>
<h2>ETC&#8217;s Price Action In June</h2>
<p>Ethereum Classic has found a place among the headlines in the last two weeks following its initial bearish form at the start of June.  ETC began the month trading around $18.01 before experiencing a nosedive which saw the token trade as low as $13.99 on June 10.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/litecoin/litecoin-up-18-in-past-24-hours-is-halving-rally-here/" target="_blank" rel="noopener "> Litecoin Up 18% In Past 24 Hours, Is Halving Rally Here?</a></p>
<p>Thereafter, ETC would rise to $15.03 and hover around this price region for the next few days before embarking on a bullish run that to gain by 28.60% between June 20 and June 24, hitting the price resistance level at $19.33. </p>
<p>The following days would then present a mixed price action before ETC finally retraced to its key support level at $17.64 on June 29. After retesting at this price zone, ETC’s price has resumed its uptrend, climbing higher since then.</p>
<p>Ethereum Classic (ETC) remains one of the major projects in the cryptocurrency space. Launched in July 2016, Ethereum Classic is a hard fork of Ethereum created to preserve the purpose and integrity of the original Ethereum network. </p>
<p>At the time of writing, ETC is exchanging hands at  $20.90, with a 1.51% gain in the last hour. The token’s 24-hour trading volume is currently valued at $482 million, having also gone up by 208.92%.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/rVwqf51d/" alt="ETC" width="1480" height="913"/>

<h2>ETC Price Analysis And Prediction</h2>
<p>Looking at the ETC’s hourly chart, its Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD) remains well above the signal line indicating the token’s bullish run may still be on. </p>
<p>However, its Relative Strength Index (RSI) is currently in the overbought zone at 89.71, meaning a selling pressure may soon occur, which may drive down the token’s price.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/ethereum/ethereum-continues-uptrend-as-staked-eth-soars-to-new-high/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Ethereum Continues Uptrend As Staked ETH Soars To New High</a></p>
<p style="text-align: left">According to the prediction site,<a href="https://walletinvestor.com/forecast/ethereum-classic-prediction" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow"> WalletInvestor</a>, if the bulls manage to sustain buying pressure, ETC’s price would experience only a small rise reaching the market value of $21.42 in 14 days.</p>
<p>However, if the reverse is the case, and ETC falls under bearish pressure, the team predicts the token to fall to a market price of $18.00. </p>
<p>That said, most of the crypto markets are also on an uptrend alongside Ethereum Classic (ETC). Market leader Bitcoin (BTC) is up by 0.87% in the last day, while other notable coins such as Cardano (ADA) and Solana (SOL) are also gaining by 7.41% and 6.72%, respectively.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/stocks-897x598-1-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance Survey Says 88% Of Institutional Users Have a Positive Outlook For Crypto Assets</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/crypto/binance-survey-says-88-of-institutional-users-have-a-positive-outlook-for-crypto-assets/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance survey]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto investment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Institutional Investors]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=540573</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Institutional investors are paying more attention to cryptocurrencies and digital assets. According to a recent survey report by Binance Research and Binance VIP &#38; Institutional, 88% of institutional users have a long-term, optimistic outlook on crypto for the next decade. The crypto market is known for its high volatility, but the majority of big-money players see crypto as an important part of their portfolio for years to come. Institutional Interest In Crypto Assets Is Growing The Institutional Crypto Outlook Survey, which surveyed 208 Binance VIP and Institutional users from 31st March to 15th May 2023, found out that a growing number of institutional crypto investors are in it for the long haul. According to the survey, 63.5% of these users had a positive outlook on digital assets over the next 12 months, while 88% are more positive over the next decade. Related Reading: Ethereum Continues Uptrend As Staked ETH Soars To New High Of the respondents, 50% expect to increase their crypto asset exposure over the next five years. Only 4.3% said they plan to decrease exposure. That signals a lot of confidence and optimism about the future growth and mainstream adoption of cryptocurrencies. Bitcoin remains Most Popular Crypto Asset Among Institutions Bitcoin remains the most popular choice among institutional investors, with a larger proportion of respondents more positive about Bitcoin as compared to the broader crypto sector. This is not surprising given that Bitcoin is the largest crypto by market cap and the most established. Bitcoin is seen as the &#8220;digital gold&#8221; of the crypto world and a store of value and hedge against inflation. BTC crosses $31,000 as institutional interest grows &#124; Source: BTCUSD on TradingView.com 42.8% of investors are more interested in the potential for large investment returns. However, 37.5% are more motivated by the long-term exposure to the technology behind digital assets, with 48.1% and 43.8% of respondents investing in Layer 1 and Layer 2 technologies respectively. Institutional Trade Still Mostly Done On Centralized Exchanges Centralized exchanges remain the most popular platform for institutional trading. While many crypto investors advocate for decentralized exchanges on the rise, centralized exchanges like Binance offer a one-stop shop for institutional traders to easily buy, sell and convert a wide range of cryptocurrencies. The survey found that 90.5% of institutional investors would rather trade on centralized exchanges. Related Reading: Whales Dive Into XRP, Accumulating $170 Million Worth: What’s Their Game Plan? While some institutional investors remain skeptical about cryptocurrency, it&#8217;s clear that mainstream interest in this asset class is building steadily. If institutional adoption continues to rise, it&#8217;s likely to drive broader mainstream acceptance of cryptocurrencies in financial institutions like banks. Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Institutional investors are paying more attention to cryptocurrencies and digital assets. According to a recent survey report by Binance Research and Binance VIP &amp; Institutional, 88% of institutional users have a long-term, optimistic outlook on crypto for the next decade. </p>
<p>The crypto market is known for its high volatility, but the majority of big-money players see crypto as an important part of their portfolio for years to come.</p>
<h2>Institutional Interest In Crypto Assets Is Growing</h2>
<p>The Institutional Crypto Outlook Survey, which surveyed 208 Binance VIP and Institutional users from 31st March to 15th May 2023, found out that a growing number of institutional crypto investors are in it for the long haul. According to the <a href="https://research.binance.com/en/analysis/institutional-crypto-outlook-survey-2023" rel="nofollow">survey</a>, 63.5% of these users had a positive outlook on digital assets over the next 12 months, while 88% are more positive over the next decade.</p>

<p>Of the respondents, 50% expect to increase their crypto asset exposure over the next five years. Only 4.3% said they plan to decrease exposure. That signals a lot of confidence and optimism about the future growth and mainstream adoption of cryptocurrencies.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin remains Most Popular Crypto Asset Among Institutions</h2>
<p>Bitcoin remains the most popular choice among institutional investors, with a larger proportion of respondents more positive about Bitcoin as compared to the broader crypto sector. This is not surprising given that Bitcoin is the largest crypto by market cap and the most established. Bitcoin is seen as the &#8220;digital gold&#8221; of the crypto world and a store of value and hedge against inflation.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/r9xkCXXs/" alt="Bitcoin price chart from TradingView.com (Crypto)" width="2884" height="1724"/></p>

<p>42.8% of investors are more interested in the potential for large investment returns. However, 37.5% are more motivated by the long-term exposure to the technology behind digital assets, with 48.1% and 43.8% of respondents investing in Layer 1 and Layer 2 technologies respectively.</p>
Institutional Trade Still Mostly Done On Centralized Exchanges
<p>Centralized exchanges remain the most popular platform for institutional trading. While many crypto investors advocate for decentralized exchanges on the rise, centralized exchanges like Binance offer a one-stop shop for institutional traders to easily buy, sell and convert a wide range of cryptocurrencies. The survey found that 90.5% of institutional investors would rather trade on centralized exchanges.</p>

<p>While some institutional investors remain skeptical about cryptocurrency, it&#8217;s clear that mainstream interest in this asset class is building steadily. If institutional adoption continues to rise, it&#8217;s likely to drive broader mainstream acceptance of cryptocurrencies in financial institutions like banks.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/sean-pollock-PhYq704ffdA-unsplash-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Litecoin Up 18% In Past 24 Hours, Is Halving Rally Here?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/litecoin/litecoin-up-18-in-past-24-hours-is-halving-rally-here/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hououin Kyouma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 13:05:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Litecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Litecoin Halving]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Litecoin Rally]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ltc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ltc/usd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=540537</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Litecoin has observed a sharp increase of around 18% during the past day as the much-anticipated halving is just over a month away now. Litecoin Outperforms Market With A Strong 18% Surge Like most of the wider cryptocurrency market, LTC had enjoyed a sharp rally a week or so back, which had taken its price above the $90 mark. Unlike coins like Bitcoin, however, the asset had failed to maintain at these post-surge levels, as it slid off during the days that followed, until eventually bottoming out at the low $80 level. In the past day, however, tides seem to have rapidly shifted for Litecoin, as the asset is now trading above $101 after registering a sharp growth of 18% during the last 24 hours. The below chart shows how the cryptocurrency has performed recently. Looks like the coin has observed a sharp uptrend today &#124; Source: LTCUSD on TradingView As you can see in the graph, Litecoin was around the $81 level only a couple of days back. This latest turnaround for the asset has meant that it has now surpassed the high registered around the start of the month. In terms of daily returns, LTC has outperformed almost all the top 20 cryptocurrencies by market cap; Bitcoin Cash (BCH) is the only exception with its whopping 26% gains in the same period. Related Reading: Stablecoin Cap Shows Early Sign Of Reversal, Why This Could Benefit Bitcoin As analyst Tony &#8220;The Bull&#8221; pointed out on Twitter, Litecoin formed a golden cross just before this surge, as its 50-day moving average (MA) has crossed over its 200-day MA. 2020 it is#Litecoin has golden crossed, days after a death cross Does the rest of history repeat? https://t.co/sGlMhgKE0R pic.twitter.com/CRSaqHSbGt — Tony &#8220;The Bull&#8221; (@tonythebullBTC) June 30, 2023 Interestingly, only a few days ago, the same MAs had also formed a cross of the opposite type: the death cross. The bullish cross canceling this bearish one out merely days later is a pattern similar to the one seen back in 2020, which preceded the bull run. LTC Only Has 34 Days To Go For The Next Halving Litecoin also has a strong bullish narrative coming up in the form of its halving. The &#8220;halving&#8221; is an event where the block rewards of the cryptocurrency are permanently cut in half. As the block rewards are the only way to introduce new LTC into the circulating supply, the halving tightens up its production rate. This increased scarcity is why the event has historically been hyped up as a bullish one. Related Reading: Altcoin Whales Show Highly Active Day, Volatility Incoming? Halvings take place roughly every four years, and the next one is estimated to place on August 3, 2023, which is just 34 days away. It now remains to be seen whether the current price surge will be an extended rally that leads to the halving, or if this is another attempt that would run out of steam before long. Featured image from Michael Förtsch on Unsplash.com, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Litecoin has observed a sharp increase of around 18% during the past day as the much-anticipated halving is just over a month away now.</p>
<h2>Litecoin Outperforms Market With A Strong 18% Surge</h2>
<p>Like most of the wider cryptocurrency market, LTC had enjoyed a <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/litecoin-ltc-bulls-charge-past-91-following-20-rally/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">sharp rally</a> a week or so back, which had taken its price above the $90 mark. Unlike coins like Bitcoin, however, the asset had failed to maintain at these post-surge levels, as it slid off during the days that followed, until eventually bottoming out at the low $80 level.</p>
<p>In the past day, however, tides seem to have rapidly shifted for Litecoin, as the asset is now trading above $101 after registering a sharp growth of 18% during the last 24 hours. The below chart shows how the cryptocurrency has performed recently.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium aligncenter" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/hNWWqH48/" alt="Litecoin Price Chart" width="1534" height="911"/></p>

<p>As you can see in the graph, Litecoin was around the $81 level only a couple of days back. This latest turnaround for the asset has meant that it has now surpassed the high registered around the start of the month.</p>
<p>In terms of daily returns, LTC has outperformed almost all the top 20 cryptocurrencies by market cap; <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin-cash/never-skip-korea-pump-bitcoin-cash-soars-168-10-days/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Bitcoin Cash (BCH)</a> is the only exception with its whopping 26% gains in the same period.</p>

<p>As analyst <a href="https://twitter.com/tonythebullbtc/status/1674573433617764357" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Tony &#8220;The Bull&#8221;</a> pointed out on Twitter, Litecoin formed a golden cross just before this surge, as its 50-day moving average (MA) has crossed over its 200-day MA.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">2020 it is<a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Litecoin?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#Litecoin</a> has golden crossed, days after a death cross</p>
<p>Does the rest of history repeat? <a href="https://t.co/sGlMhgKE0R" rel="nofollow">https://t.co/sGlMhgKE0R</a> <a href="https://t.co/CRSaqHSbGt" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/CRSaqHSbGt</a></p>
<p>— Tony &#8220;The Bull&#8221; (@tonythebullBTC) <a href="https://twitter.com/tonythebullBTC/status/1674573433617764357?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">June 30, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p>Interestingly, only a few days ago, the same MAs had also formed a cross of the opposite type: the death cross. The bullish cross canceling this bearish one out merely days later is a pattern similar to the one seen back in 2020, which preceded the bull run.</p>
<h2>LTC Only Has 34 Days To Go For The Next Halving</h2>
<p>Litecoin also has a strong bullish narrative coming up in the form of its halving. The &#8220;<a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/crypto-analyst-says-bitcoin-has-already-bottomed-sets-halving-price/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">halving</a>&#8221; is an event where the block rewards of the cryptocurrency are permanently cut in half.</p>
<p>As the block rewards are the only way to introduce new LTC into the circulating supply, the halving tightens up its production rate. This increased scarcity is why the event has historically been hyped up as a bullish one.</p>

<p>Halvings take place roughly every four years, and the next one is estimated to place on August 3, 2023, which is just 34 days away. It now remains to be seen whether the current price surge will be an extended rally that leads to the halving, or if this is another attempt that would run out of steam before long.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/michael-fortsch-fYSVVQqiqPs-unsplash-1-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
