<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
>

<channel>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.newsbtc.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<description>Bitcoin &#38; Cryptocurrency News Today</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 22:34:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Ripple vs SEC: No Money For Years, XRP Holders Lose If SEC Wins, Says John Deaton</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/ripple-vs-sec-no-money-for-years-xrp-holders-lose-if-sec-wins-says-john-deaton/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 01:00:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple VS SEC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ripple xrp]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrpusdt]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=541632</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[John Deaton, a pro-XRP lawyer, recently made some statements regarding the ongoing legal battle between Ripple and the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). Deaton believes that if Ripple loses to the SEC, no money may be collected for years, and only if Ripple loses on appeal.  However, he also believes that if the Supreme Court takes on the appeal, which he thinks they will if Congress hasn&#8217;t acted by then, Ripple will win hands down. Ripple Legal Troubles Could Linger For Years Deaton&#8217;s view is that if the SEC wins, Ripple will appeal, and the current status quo will continue for the next 2-5 years. Deaton emphasized: Assuming the SEC wins and the civil case lawyers get a win because the judge in California follows Judge Torres&#8217; ruling, Ripple will appeal that case as well, and there will be no money for years, if ever.  In such a scenario, if Ripple loses all the appeals, the SEC would collect the money, not the civil plaintiffs. The SEC would then offer a payback fund for XRP holders to sell their XRP, as in Veritaseum. The Veritaseum and the ongoing Ripple cases are similar in that they both involve allegations of unregistered securities offerings in the cryptocurrency industry.  Related Reading: Glassnode Co-Founder Predicts Bull Run For Bitcoin Amidst Sideways Trading In the Veritaseum case, the SEC alleged that Veritaseum and its founder, Reginald Middleton, conducted an unregistered initial coin offering (ICO) that raised approximately $14.8 million. Similarly, in the Ripple case, the SEC alleged that Ripple conducted an unregistered securities offering by selling XRP to investors. After the Veritaseum case was concluded, the SEC set up a Fair Fund to distribute the funds collected from the defendants to investors harmed by the unregistered securities offering. The Fair Fund enabled investors who participated in the Veritaseum ICO to apply for a refund of their investment. This development could serve as a precedent for how the SEC may proceed with the Ripple case if it successfully proves that XRP constitutes a security. In such a scenario, the SEC may similarly establish a Fair Fund to compensate investors who purchased XRP during the unregistered securities offering.  XRP Holders Can Continue To Believe Their Assets Are Not Securities Furthermore, Deaton argued that being on the “75K list”- a list of over 75,000 XRP holders named as potential &#8220;intervenors&#8221; &#8211; is a good thing because a massive putative class of XRP holders is easily identifiable.  By joining the class list he put out, no one waived anything whatsoever, and if there were ever any money for XRP holders from the civil case or the SEC case, he would likely be contacted because he has the list of the &#8220;75K.&#8221; The list&#8217;s purpose is to allow these XRP holders to potentially seek reimbursement or other relief if the SEC&#8217;s case against Ripple results in a judgment or settlement that impacts the value of XRP. By joining the list, these individuals are indicating that they believe XRP is not a security and that they should be allowed to participate in any proceedings related to the case. Additionally, Deaton advises ignoring the people who claim that joining the 75K list and arguing XRP isn&#8217;t a security is a bad thing if there is one day a monetary recovery for XRP holders.  Related Reading: Ethereum Whale Transfers Over 25,000 ETH To Exchange: Massive Dip On The Horizon? Overall, Deaton believes that the civil case may not lead to anything. If the SEC wins, it would collect the most money and offer the best option, “ironically.”  Also, if Ripple loses and Congress fixes this regulatory mess during the 5 years of appeals, it all “goes away anyway”, according to the pro-XRP Lawyer.  Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com ]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>John Deaton, a pro-XRP lawyer, recently made some <a href="https://twitter.com/JohnEDeaton1/status/1676952467060428802?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">statements </a>regarding the ongoing legal battle between Ripple and the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). Deaton believes that if Ripple loses to the SEC, no money may be collected for years, and only if Ripple loses on appeal. </p>
<p>However, he also believes that if the Supreme Court takes on the appeal, which he thinks they will if Congress hasn&#8217;t acted by then, Ripple will win hands down.</p>
<h2>Ripple Legal Troubles Could Linger For Years</h2>
<p>Deaton&#8217;s view is that if the SEC wins, Ripple will appeal, and the current status quo will continue for the next 2-5 years. Deaton emphasized:</p>
<p>Assuming the SEC wins and the civil case lawyers get a win because the judge in California follows Judge Torres&#8217; ruling, Ripple will appeal that case as well, and there will be no money for years, if ever. </p>
<p>In such a scenario, if Ripple loses all the appeals, the SEC would collect the money, not the civil plaintiffs. The SEC would then offer a payback fund for XRP holders to sell their XRP, as in Veritaseum.</p>
<p>The Veritaseum and the ongoing Ripple cases are similar in that they both involve allegations of unregistered securities offerings in the cryptocurrency industry. </p>

<p>In the Veritaseum case, the SEC alleged that Veritaseum and its founder, Reginald Middleton, conducted an unregistered initial coin offering (ICO) that raised approximately $14.8 million. Similarly, in the Ripple case, the SEC alleged that Ripple conducted an unregistered securities offering by selling XRP to investors.</p>
<p>After the Veritaseum case was concluded, the SEC set up a Fair Fund to distribute the funds collected from the defendants to investors harmed by the unregistered securities offering. The Fair Fund enabled investors who participated in the Veritaseum ICO to apply for a refund of their investment.</p>
<p>This development could serve as a precedent for how the SEC may proceed with the Ripple case if it successfully proves that XRP constitutes a security. In such a scenario, the SEC may similarly establish a Fair Fund to compensate investors who purchased XRP during the unregistered securities offering. </p>
XRP Holders Can Continue To Believe Their Assets Are Not Securities
<p>Furthermore, Deaton argued that being on the “75K list”- a list of over 75,000 XRP holders named as potential &#8220;intervenors&#8221; &#8211; is a good thing because a massive putative class of XRP holders is easily identifiable. </p>
<p>By joining the class list he put out, no one waived anything whatsoever, and if there were ever any money for XRP holders from the civil case or the SEC case, he would likely be contacted because he has the list of the &#8220;75K.&#8221;</p>
<p>The list&#8217;s purpose is to allow these XRP holders to potentially seek reimbursement or other relief if the SEC&#8217;s case against Ripple results in a judgment or settlement that impacts the value of XRP. By joining the list, these individuals are indicating that they believe XRP is not a security and that they should be allowed to participate in any proceedings related to the case.</p>
<p>Additionally, Deaton advises ignoring the people who claim that joining the 75K list and arguing XRP isn&#8217;t a security is a bad thing if there is one day a monetary recovery for XRP holders. </p>

<p>Overall, Deaton believes that the civil case may not lead to anything. If the SEC wins, it would collect the most money and offer the best option, “ironically.” </p>
<p>Also, if Ripple loses and Congress fixes this regulatory mess during the 5 years of appeals, it all “goes away anyway”, according to the pro-XRP Lawyer. </p>
<img decoding="async" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/h36Dfun9/" alt="Ripple" width="1815" height="858" loading="lazy"/>
<p>Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/jp-valery-9BatP4ovW2I-unsplash-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>BlackRock CEO Larry Fink Says Bitcoin Is Digital Gold, So What’s The Digital Silver?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/blackrock-ceo-larry-fink-says-bitcoin-is-digital-gold-so-whats-the-digital-silver/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Best Owie]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 23:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BlackRock]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[digital gold]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[digital silver]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Litecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ltc]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=541549</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[On Wednesday, an interview with BlackRock CEO Larry Fink went viral in which the CEO called Bitcoin an international asset. Not only that, Fink also pointed toward digital assets such as Bitcoin as being a way to digitize gold on the blockchain. This statement from the CEO has since been interpreted in various ways to mean that Fink referred to BTC as digital gold. So the question now remains, if Bitcoin is digital gold, which cryptocurrency is digital silver? ETH Is Digital Silver? The digital gold argument for Bitcoin continues but with Ethereum being the second-largest and most popular cryptocurrency in the market, it has often been dubbed the ‘Digital Silver’. Over the last seven years, its performance has also solidified claims that Ethereum is silver to Bitcoin’s gold. Related Reading: Rapid Rise In Cardano’s TVL Points Toward Bullish Sentiment Around ADA There have previously been claims that Litecoin qualifies to be referred to as the digital silver. Most of these claims were rooted in the fact that Litecoin’s mechanism is basically identical to that of BTC. However, performance-wise, it has fallen short compared to ETH, which is now BTC’s largest rival. One area where Litecoin tends to outshine Ethereum though is when it comes to supply. While Litecoin undergoes halving events every four years like BTC to reduce its block rewards and has a maximum supply, Ethereum has none of these things. ETH’s unlimited supply has usually been a concern as this means the digital asset could be a perpetually inflationary asset. That is, until the implementation of the ETH burn, aimed at reducing the rate at which new coins are being brought into circulation. Data from Ultrasound Money, a website that tracks the ETH burn and issuance rate, shows that instead of increasing, the ETH supply is now decreasing at a rate of 0.33% per year. This development eliminates the concerns about inflation for ETH, further giving credence to the fact that Ethereum is the digital silver. ETH price resting above $1,900 &#124; Source: ETHUSD on Tradingview.com Bitcoin Vs Ethereum, Which Is Better? The argument about the better option between Bitcoin and Ethereum continues to wax strong, especially on social media platforms. However, both of these digital assets are unique in their own way and serve different functions in the market. While Bitcoin continues to hold the torch as the pioneer cryptocurrency, garnering massive support over the last decade, Ethereum, in its own right, has propelled the concept of decentralized finance (DeFi). Related Reading: Shiba Inu Records Accelerated Burn Rate, But Price Fails To Respond The use of smart contracts on the latter has helped developers to create financial products investors can leverage to manage their own wealth without the need for an intermediary. Although this capability is gradually being developed on Bitcoin as well. For now, both digital assets serve different sides of the market. However, this could easily change in the future. Follow Best Owie on Twitter for market insights, updates, and the occasional funny tweet… Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="p2">On Wednesday, an <a href="https://twitter.com/saylor/status/1676687611379826688?s=20" rel="nofollow">interview</a> with BlackRock CEO Larry Fink went viral in which the CEO called Bitcoin an international asset. Not only that, Fink also pointed toward digital assets such as Bitcoin as being a way to digitize gold on the blockchain. This statement from the CEO has since been interpreted in various ways to mean that Fink referred to BTC as digital gold. So the question now remains, if Bitcoin is digital gold, which cryptocurrency is digital silver?</p>
<h2 class="p2">ETH Is Digital Silver?</h2>
<p class="p2">The digital gold argument for Bitcoin continues but with Ethereum being the second-largest and most popular cryptocurrency in the market, it has often been dubbed the ‘Digital Silver’. Over the last seven years, its performance has also solidified claims that Ethereum is silver to Bitcoin’s gold.</p>

<p class="p2">There have previously been <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/ethereum/entrepreneur-calls-ethereum-silver-to-bitcoin-as-digital-gold-not-litecoin/">claims</a> that Litecoin qualifies to be referred to as the digital silver. Most of these claims were rooted in the fact that Litecoin’s mechanism is basically identical to that of BTC. However, performance-wise, it has fallen short compared to ETH, which is now BTC’s largest rival.</p>
<p class="p2">One area where Litecoin tends to outshine Ethereum though is when it comes to supply. While Litecoin undergoes halving events every four years like BTC to reduce its block rewards and has a maximum supply, Ethereum has none of these things. ETH’s unlimited supply has usually been a concern as this means the digital asset could be a perpetually inflationary asset. That is, until the implementation of the ETH burn, aimed at reducing the rate at which new coins are being brought into circulation.</p>
<p class="p2">Data from <a href="https://ultrasound.money/" rel="nofollow">Ultrasound Money</a>, a website that tracks the ETH burn and issuance rate, shows that instead of increasing, the ETH supply is now decreasing at a rate of 0.33% per year. This development eliminates the concerns about inflation for ETH, further giving credence to the fact that Ethereum is the digital silver.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/1B4YtxRt/" alt="Ethereum (ETH) price chart from Tradingview.com (Digital silver)" width="2884" height="1724"/></p>

<h2 class="p2">Bitcoin Vs Ethereum, Which Is Better?</h2>
<p class="p2">The argument about the better option between Bitcoin and Ethereum continues to wax strong, especially on social media platforms. However, both of these digital assets are unique in their own way and serve different functions in the market.</p>
<p class="p2">While Bitcoin continues to hold the torch as the pioneer cryptocurrency, garnering massive support over the last decade, Ethereum, in its own right, has propelled the concept of decentralized finance (DeFi).</p>

<p class="p2">The use of smart contracts on the latter has helped developers to create financial products investors can leverage to manage their own wealth without the need for an intermediary. Although this capability is gradually being developed on Bitcoin as well.</p>
<p class="p2">For now, both digital assets serve different sides of the market. However, this could easily change in the future.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/iStock-877508312-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Chainlink (LINK) Signal Returns That Prompted 14,000% Surge</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/link/chainlink-link-signal-returns-that-prompted-14000-surge/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tony "The Bull"]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 22:39:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[LINK]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[chainlink]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Link]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LINKUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[linkusdt]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=541631</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Chainlink (LINK) was among a subset of cryptocurrencies that made a lower low on daily timeframes recently. A lower low is indicative of a continued downtrend and weakness at support. However, on higher timeframes, technical tell a very different story — one of possible strength building. In fact, a signal has appeared that the last time around prompted a 14,000% rally in LINKUSD. High Timeframe Bullish Confluence Hints At Surprise Chainlink Recovery Chainlink (LINKUSD) remains down more than 80% from its former all-time highs. Worse yet, after a full year at bear market lows, the range broke down temporarily forming a lower low on daily charts. In technical analysis, higher timeframes provide more dominant signals. And although there was a lower low made on the daily, the monthly timeframe did not make a lower low on a closing basis. Related Reading: GM: How A Morning Star Pattern Could Awaken Altcoins On top of being a possible range deviation and reclaim, the monthly candlestick formed a dragonfly doji. A dragonfly doji In Japanese candlestick analysis represents a possible bullish reversal pattern. Within even lower timeframes, Chainlink was among a slew of altcoins they formed a different bullish Japanese candlesticks reversal pattern on weekly timeframes, called the morning star pattern. Will a similar trend follow? &#124; LINKUSD on TradingView.com A LINK To The Past: Oversold Stochastic No More If bullish range reclaim on low timeframes, and a pair of higher timeframe Japanese candlestick reversal patterns aren’t enough confluence for you, there’s more. The one-month Stochastic has left oversold territory for the first time since late 2021. The indicator spent all of 2022 oversold, and halfway through 2023. Related Reading: Why Bitcoin Dominance Hints At A Surprise Altcoin Season Ahead Prior to that, the last time Chainlink left oversold conditions was back in early 2019, before going on an over 14,000% run. The signal is back and in alignment with the potential reversal patterns from above. Meanwhile, Bitcoin and other cryptocurrencies have enjoyed much more of a recovery by comparison. The broader trend turning around more clearly could remove whatever doubt is remaining surrounding LINK, allowing the altcoin to return to its former glory days. This chart originally appeared in Issue #10 of CoinChartist (VIP). Sign up for a free subscription. Tony is the author of the CoinChartist (VIP) newsletter. Follow @TonyTheBullBTC &#38; @coinchartist_io on Twitter. Or join the TonyTradesBTC Telegram for daily market insights and technical analysis education. Please note: Content is educational and should not be considered investment advice. Featured image from iStockPhoto, Charts from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Chainlink (LINK) was among a subset of cryptocurrencies that made a lower low on daily timeframes recently. A lower low is indicative of a continued downtrend and weakness at support.</p>
<p>However, on higher timeframes, technical tell a very different story — one of possible strength building. In fact, a signal has appeared that the last time around prompted a 14,000% rally in LINKUSD.</p>
<h2>High Timeframe Bullish Confluence Hints At Surprise Chainlink Recovery</h2>
<p>Chainlink (LINKUSD) remains down more than 80% from its former all-time highs. Worse yet, after a full year at bear market lows, the range broke down temporarily forming a lower low on daily charts.</p>
<p>In technical analysis, higher timeframes provide more dominant signals. And although there was a lower low made on the daily, the monthly timeframe did not make a lower low on a closing basis.</p>

<p>On top of being a possible range deviation and reclaim, the monthly candlestick formed a dragonfly doji. A <a href="https://coinchartist.io/dragonfly-doji/education/japanese-candlesticks/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">dragonfly doji</a> In Japanese candlestick analysis represents a possible bullish reversal pattern.</p>
<p>Within even lower timeframes, Chainlink was among a slew of altcoins they formed a different bullish Japanese candlesticks reversal pattern on weekly timeframes, called the morning star pattern.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large wp-image-541637 aligncenter" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/5B32754E-998C-4464-9B36-BAFEEF454E58-860x535.png" alt="Chainlink" width="860" height="535" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/5B32754E-998C-4464-9B36-BAFEEF454E58-860x535.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/5B32754E-998C-4464-9B36-BAFEEF454E58-460x286.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/5B32754E-998C-4464-9B36-BAFEEF454E58-768x478.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/5B32754E-998C-4464-9B36-BAFEEF454E58-1536x955.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/5B32754E-998C-4464-9B36-BAFEEF454E58-2048x1274.png 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/5B32754E-998C-4464-9B36-BAFEEF454E58-750x466.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/5B32754E-998C-4464-9B36-BAFEEF454E58-1140x709.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/></p>

<h2>A LINK To The Past: Oversold Stochastic No More</h2>
<p>If bullish range reclaim on low timeframes, and a pair of higher timeframe Japanese candlestick reversal patterns aren’t enough confluence for you, there’s more.</p>
<p>The one-month Stochastic has left oversold territory for the first time since late 2021. The indicator spent all of 2022 oversold, and halfway through 2023.</p>

<p>Prior to that, the last time Chainlink left oversold conditions was back in early 2019, before going on an over 14,000% run. The signal is back and in alignment with the potential reversal patterns from above.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, Bitcoin and other cryptocurrencies have enjoyed much more of a recovery by comparison. The broader trend turning around more clearly could remove whatever doubt is remaining surrounding LINK, allowing the altcoin to return to its former glory days.</p>
<p>This chart originally appeared in <a href="https://coinchartist.substack.com/p/special-issue-time-for-fireworks?utm_source=profile&amp;utm_medium=reader2" rel="nofollow">Issue #10 of CoinChartist (VIP)</a>. Sign up for a free subscription.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/240B6161-65C9-4250-9F43-BBF3D12BA565-460x314.jpeg" width="460" height="314" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Volumes Cross $4.2 Trillion in H1 2023, What Does The Second Half Of The Year Hold?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-volumes-cross-4-2-trillion-in-h1-2023/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 21:30:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin trading volumes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=541624</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Institutional interest in cryptocurrencies such as Bitcoin has been increasing in the past few months, with mainstream interest in the cryptocurrency industry. As a result, the largest crypto, Bitcoin, exploded in the first half of 2023, as its trading volume on various exchanges crossed $4.2 trillion.  Bitcoin Sees Highest Trading Volume In March According to data from bitcoinity.org, BTC trading volume on exchanges during this whole first half of the year eventually exceeded $4.2 trillion, with March recording the highest monthly BTC trading volume of $1.2 trillion.  Related Reading: CFTC Investigators Conclude Celsius And Former CEO Violated Rules, Potential Case Looms Last year was a tough year for Bitcoin, which was mirrored by the rest of the cryptocurrency industry, as it appeared to be caught in a bear market season. Market analysts had initially projected a further decline for BTC, however, the price started to rebound in April this year, crossing $30,000 for the first time this year.  This was Bitcoin&#8217;s first highest price in 12 months, signaling renewed vigor in the bullish market. Although this bullish sentiment was a little short-lived, with BTC dipping back down to $28,000. Statistics show that Bitcoin trading volume went back down to $492.9 billion during this period, However, things started to change in June, as news came out that several investment companies like BlackRock, Fidelity, and Invesco were filing Bitcoin spot ETF applications with the SEC. This sparked hope that mainstream investors will soon gain access to Bitcoin exposure, propelling the price of BTC back over $30,000 in late June and a 13-month high of $31,500 in July. BTC price holding above $30,000 &#124; Source: BTCUSD on TradingView.com Volatility And Price Action: What To Expect In H2 2023 The second half of 2023 is expected to be a wild ride in the world of crypto and Bitcoin. With BTC volumes crossing $4.2 trillion in the first half of 2023, it’s clear that mainstream interest in the cryptocurrency is surging. While investment companies like BlackRock have updated their filings with the SEC for spot Bitcoin EFTs, investors wait to see what comes next. If approved, spot Bitcoin ETFs will be a major turning point for the crypto, as Bitcoin currently holds 49% dominance in the industry. Bitcoin&#8217;s price has already increased by more than 50% since the beginning of the year and is presently trading at over $30,300 following the news of the ETF filings. Related Reading: Valkyrie Follows In BlackRock’s Footsteps, Refiles For Spot Bitcoin ETF According to data from the on-chain analytics firm Glassnode, the 1+ years old supply HODLers of BTC is now at a new all-time high of 13.4 million BTC as more investors opt to hold for the long-term. Also, as expectations around the ETFs rise, prices are expected to rise. If this happens, this will lead to increased participation from investors, translating to possibly higher trading volumes for Bitcoin. Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Institutional interest in cryptocurrencies such as Bitcoin has been increasing in the past few months, with mainstream interest in the cryptocurrency industry. As a result, the largest crypto, Bitcoin, exploded in the first half of 2023, as its trading volume on various exchanges crossed $4.2 trillion. </p>
<h2>Bitcoin Sees Highest Trading Volume In March</h2>
<p>According to <a href="http://data.bitcoinity.org/markets/volume/6m?c=e&amp;t=b" rel="nofollow">data</a> from bitcoinity.org, BTC trading volume on exchanges during this whole first half of the year eventually exceeded $4.2 trillion, with March recording the highest monthly BTC trading volume of $1.2 trillion. </p>

<p>Last year was a tough year for Bitcoin, which was mirrored by the rest of the cryptocurrency industry, as it appeared to be caught in a bear market season. Market analysts had initially projected a further decline for BTC, however, the price started to rebound in April this year, crossing $30,000 for the first time this year. </p>
<p>This was Bitcoin&#8217;s first highest price in 12 months, signaling renewed vigor in the bullish market. Although this bullish sentiment was a little short-lived, with BTC dipping back down to $28,000. Statistics show that Bitcoin trading volume went back down to $492.9 billion during this period,</p>
<p>However, things started to change in June, as news came out that several investment companies like BlackRock, Fidelity, and Invesco were filing Bitcoin spot ETF applications with the SEC. This sparked hope that mainstream investors will soon gain access to Bitcoin exposure, propelling the price of BTC back over $30,000 in late June and a 13-month high of $31,500 in July.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/3wW572Yc/" alt="Bitcoin (BTC) price chart from TradingView.com" width="2884" height="1642"/></p>

<h2>Volatility And Price Action: What To Expect In H2 2023</h2>
<p>The second half of 2023 is expected to be a wild ride in the world of crypto and Bitcoin. With BTC volumes crossing $4.2 trillion in the first half of 2023, it’s clear that mainstream interest in the cryptocurrency is surging. While investment companies like BlackRock have updated their filings with the SEC for spot Bitcoin EFTs, investors wait to see what comes next. If approved, spot Bitcoin ETFs will be a major turning point for the crypto, as Bitcoin currently holds 49% dominance in the industry.</p>
<p>Bitcoin&#8217;s price has already increased by more than 50% since the beginning of the year and is presently trading at over $30,300 following the news of the ETF filings.</p>

<p>According to <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-hodling-continues-1-years-old-supply-ath/" rel="nofollow">data</a> from the on-chain analytics firm Glassnode, the 1+ years old supply HODLers of BTC is now at a new all-time high of 13.4 million BTC as more investors opt to hold for the long-term.</p>
<p>Also, as expectations around the ETFs rise, prices are expected to rise. If this happens, this will lead to increased participation from investors, translating to possibly higher trading volumes for Bitcoin.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/iStock-1255216496-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>UAE Share In Global Mining Activity Grows, Accounts For 3.7% Of Mined Bitcoin</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/uae-accounts-for-3-7-of-mined-bitcoin/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 20:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[uae]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=541623</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[According to the latest report by Hashrate Index, a website for Bitcoin mining data and metrics, the UAE is now becoming a growing destination for Bitcoin miners, especially in the Middle East.  Bitcoin Miners Look For Greener Pastures Bitcoin miners have faced issues in popular Bitcoin mining countries like China and Kazakhstan in recent years. As a result, many of these miners have been forced to look for new operational hubs.  Related Reading: Analyst Says XRP Will Reach $100, Here’s Why Mining Bitcoin is a difficult process, both financially and in terms of the amount of electricity required. It involves using powerful computers to solve complex math problems in order to get rewarded with BTC. This energy requirement is part of the reason why miners have run into problems in various jurisdictions over the years. However, the Middle East is now emerging as a prime destination for Bitcoin miners, and the UAE is leading the charge among these energy-rich countries. The United Arab Emirates is helping to pave the path for the future of Bitcoin mining with its increased availability of affordable electricity, favorable access to funding, and politically stable and business-friendly climate. During the past year-and-a-half, some major mining companies signed agreements and entered partnerships with the digital asset arm of Abu Dhabi&#8217;s sovereign wealth fund (Zero Two) to create two giga projects that put the UAE on the global bitcoin mining map. As a result, the biggest amount was spent on a single Bitcoin mining site, with an investment totaling $2 billion. Now, it seems these large-scale projects are starting to cement the UAE as a serious player in the Bitcoin mining niche. According to the data provided by the Hashrate Index, bitcoin miners in the UAE should produce approximately 13 EH/s, which is equivalent to 3.7% of the total Bitcoin hash rate at an assumed average energy efficiency of 30 J/TH.  BTC price recovers from Thursday crash &#124; Source: BTCUSD on TradingView.com UAE Aims To Become A Global Crypto Hub The UAE government aims to establish the country as a global hub for cryptocurrency and blockchain innovation. Several recent initiatives show the country is serious about becoming a leader in this emerging industry. With government backing, relaxed rules, and major companies setting up offices, the building blocks are in place.  Earlier this year, the country announced that it is launching a ‘free zone’ for crypto firms called the RAK Digital Assets Oasis (RAK DAO), allowing them to own 100% of their companies.  Related Reading: Ethereum Whale Transactions Jump Over 50% As ETH Eyes $2,000 The future looks bright for Bitcoin mining in the UAE. The country&#8217;s share in the global Bitcoin mining metric should continue to grow as more mining firms are drawn to the region. However, considering the hot climate of the region when compared to big Bitcoin mining regions like Texas and Russia, the temperature could be challenging for mining.  Also, the report shows that the only way to mine Bitcoin in a scalable and legally sustainable way in the country is by partnering with a government entity. Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>According to the latest <a href="https://hashrateindex.com/blog/bitcoin-mining-around-the-world-united-arab-emirates/" rel="nofollow">report</a> by Hashrate Index, a website for Bitcoin mining data and metrics, the UAE is now becoming a growing destination for Bitcoin miners, especially in the Middle East. </p>
<h2>Bitcoin Miners Look For Greener Pastures</h2>
<p>Bitcoin miners have faced issues in popular Bitcoin mining countries like China and Kazakhstan in recent years. As a result, many of these miners have been forced to look for new operational hubs. </p>

<p>Mining Bitcoin is a difficult process, both financially and in terms of the amount of electricity required. It involves using powerful computers to solve complex math problems in order to get rewarded with BTC. This energy requirement is part of the reason why miners have run into problems in various jurisdictions over the years.</p>
<p>However, the Middle East is now emerging as a prime destination for Bitcoin miners, and the UAE is leading the charge among these energy-rich countries. The United Arab Emirates is helping to pave the path for the future of Bitcoin mining with its increased availability of affordable electricity, favorable access to funding, and politically stable and business-friendly climate.</p>
<p>During the past year-and-a-half, some major mining companies signed agreements and entered partnerships with the digital asset arm of Abu Dhabi&#8217;s sovereign wealth fund (Zero Two) to create two giga projects that put the UAE on the global bitcoin mining map. As a result, the biggest amount was spent on a single Bitcoin mining site, with an investment totaling $2 billion.</p>
<p>Now, it seems these large-scale projects are starting to cement the UAE as a serious player in the Bitcoin mining niche. According to the data provided by the Hashrate Index, bitcoin miners in the UAE should produce approximately 13 EH/s, which is equivalent to 3.7% of the total Bitcoin hash rate at an assumed average energy efficiency of 30 J/TH. </p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/3wW572Yc/" alt="Bitcoin (BTC) price chart from TradingView.com (UAE)" width="2884" height="1642"/></p>

<h2>UAE Aims To Become A Global Crypto Hub</h2>
<p>The UAE government aims to establish the country as a global hub for cryptocurrency and blockchain innovation. Several recent initiatives show the country is serious about becoming a leader in this emerging industry. With government backing, relaxed rules, and major companies setting up offices, the building blocks are in place. </p>
<p>Earlier this year, the country announced that it is launching a ‘free zone’ for crypto firms called the RAK Digital Assets Oasis (RAK DAO), allowing them to own 100% of their companies. </p>

<p>The future looks bright for Bitcoin mining in the UAE. The country&#8217;s share in the global Bitcoin mining metric should continue to grow as more mining firms are drawn to the region. However, considering the hot climate of the region when compared to big Bitcoin mining regions like Texas and Russia, the temperature could be challenging for mining. </p>
<p>Also, the report shows that the only way to mine Bitcoin in a scalable and legally sustainable way in the country is by partnering with a government entity.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/iStock-921980584-460x250.jpg" width="460" height="250" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum Whale Transfers Over 25,000 ETH To Exchange: Massive Dip On The Horizon?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/ethereum/ethereum-whale-transfers-to-exchange/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samuel Edyme]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 19:30:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=541612</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Ethereum&#8217;s price seems to have been following Bitcoin&#8217;s, but recent large transactions suggest it may soon move independently. Whale Alert reported a sum of 25,264 ETH, roughly valued at around $48 million, was moved from an unidentified wallet to the leading cryptocurrency exchange, Coinbase. 🚨 🚨 25,264 #ETH (48,302,924 USD) transferred from unknown wallet to #Coinbasehttps://t.co/ViF7z23ixe — Whale Alert (@whale_alert) July 6, 2023 Analyzing The Potential Impact While these large transfers can, on occasion, herald an upcoming uptrend, they can also imply a short-term surge in volatility. Particularly, such movements can be used to discern possible price sentiment changes. Related Reading: Ethereum Continues Uptrend As Staked ETH Soars To New High In addition to the 25,264 ETH transferred, another substantial transaction of 30,000 ETH was also noted. This amount was relocated from an anonymous wallet to OKEX, another prominent crypto exchange.  🚨 🚨 🚨 30,000 #ETH (57,687,950 USD) transferred from unknown wallet to #OKExhttps://t.co/ENxRwsJMLh — Whale Alert (@whale_alert) July 6, 2023 Notably, as with any financial market, the crypto industry is impacted by many factors, with &#8216;whale&#8217; movements being just one of them. While they can potentially influence price sentiment, other elements, such as broader market trends, global economic indicators, and investor sentiment, should also be considered for a holistic market understanding. Ethereum Latest Price Action Thiese Ethereum transactions come at a time when ETH has been trading between an intra-day high of $1,957.35 and an intra-day low of $1,872.94. At the time of writing, Ethereum has only seen a slight decline of 1.4% in the past day, with a market price of $1,884. This modest plunge indicates whales might not have moved or sold just a small amount of the ETH deposited. Notably, a &#8216;whale&#8217; in cryptocurrency refers to an individual or entity holding a large amount of a cryptocurrency. This individual or entity has the potential to influence the market due to the sizeable volume of its holdings. When such transfers occur, they can create waves in the market and often signal potential price shifts. Related Reading: Ethereum Price Retests Uptrend Support But Can Bulls Save The Day Over the past week, Ethereum has seen more than a $3 billion surge in its market capitalization. The second largest asset by market cap has surged from the $223 billion seen last Thursday to $226 billion. ETH&#8217;s daily trading volume has also surged significantly in the same period. Ethereum&#8217;s daily trading volume has soared from $6 billion last week to above $12 billion over the past 24 hours. Featured image from Shutterstock, Chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ethereum&#8217;s price seems to have been following Bitcoin&#8217;s, but recent large transactions suggest it may soon move independently.</p>
<p>Whale Alert <a href="https://twitter.com/whale_alert/status/1676786014868631553?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">reported</a> a sum of 25,264 ETH, roughly valued at around $48 million, was moved from an unidentified wallet to the leading cryptocurrency exchange, Coinbase.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en"><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f6a8.png" alt="🚨" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f6a8.png" alt="🚨" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> 25,264 <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/ETH?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#ETH</a> (48,302,924 USD) transferred from unknown wallet to <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Coinbase?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#Coinbase</a><a href="https://t.co/ViF7z23ixe" rel="nofollow">https://t.co/ViF7z23ixe</a></p>
<p>— Whale Alert (@whale_alert) <a href="https://twitter.com/whale_alert/status/1676786014868631553?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">July 6, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<h2>Analyzing The Potential Impact</h2>
<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w" dir="ltr">While these large transfers can, on occasion, herald an upcoming uptrend, they can also imply a short-term surge in volatility. Particularly, such movements can be used to discern possible price sentiment changes.</p>

<p dir="ltr">In addition to the 25,264 ETH transferred, another substantial transaction of 30,000 ETH was also <a href="https://twitter.com/whale_alert/status/1676842449241554944?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">noted</a>. This amount was relocated from an anonymous wallet to OKEX, another prominent crypto exchange. </p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en"><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f6a8.png" alt="🚨" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f6a8.png" alt="🚨" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f6a8.png" alt="🚨" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> 30,000 <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/ETH?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#ETH</a> (57,687,950 USD) transferred from unknown wallet to <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/OKEx?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#OKEx</a><a href="https://t.co/ENxRwsJMLh" rel="nofollow">https://t.co/ENxRwsJMLh</a></p>
<p>— Whale Alert (@whale_alert) <a href="https://twitter.com/whale_alert/status/1676842449241554944?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">July 6, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p dir="ltr">Notably, as with any financial market, the crypto industry is impacted by many factors, with &#8216;whale&#8217; movements being just one of them. While they can potentially influence price sentiment, other elements, such as broader market trends, global economic indicators, and investor sentiment, should also be considered for a holistic market understanding.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Ethereum Latest Price Action</h2>
<p>Thiese Ethereum <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/ethereum/ethereum-starknet-launches-testnet-for-quantum-leap-upgrade/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">transactions</a> come at a time when ETH has been trading between an<a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-lacks-momentum-1950/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener "> intra-day high of $1,957.35</a> and an intra-day low of $1,872.94. At the time of writing, <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-retests-1900/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Ethereum has only seen a slight decline</a> of 1.4% in the past day, with a market price of $1,884.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/bqpuPH8s/" alt="Ethereum (ETH)’s price chart on TradingView" width="2770" height="1556"/>
<p>This modest plunge indicates whales might not have moved or sold just a small amount of the ETH deposited. Notably, a &#8216;whale&#8217; in cryptocurrency refers to an individual or entity holding a large amount of a cryptocurrency.</p>
<p>This individual or entity has the potential to influence the market due to the sizeable volume of its holdings. When such transfers occur, they can create waves in the market and often signal potential price shifts.</p>

<p>Over the past week, Ethereum has seen more than a $3 billion surge in its market capitalization. The second largest asset by <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/ethereum/ethereum-continues-uptrend-as-staked-eth-soars-to-new-high/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">market cap has surged</a> from the $223 billion seen last Thursday to $226 billion. ETH&#8217;s daily trading volume has also surged significantly in the same period.</p>
<p>Ethereum&#8217;s daily trading volume has soared from $6 billion last week to above $12 billion over the past 24 hours.</p>
<p>Featured image from Shutterstock, Chart from TradingView</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/todd-cravens-QnBrjY-nFUs-unsplash-2-460x305.jpg" width="460" height="305" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Glassnode Co-Founder Predicts Bull Run For Bitcoin Amidst Sideways Trading</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/glassnode-co-founder-predicts-bull-run-for-bitcoin-amidst-sideways-trading/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 18:30:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=541605</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) has been trading within a narrow range for the past 12 days. Nonetheless, the fact that bulls have held the crucial $30,000 support level is seen as a short-term win for them. Even though BTC has been experiencing sideways trading, there is a growing sense of optimism that it has the potential to break through upper resistance zones and reach new highs.  BTC’s Sideways Trading Sets Stage For Bullish Momentum?  According to Yan Alleman, the co-founder of blockchain analytics firm Glassnode, Bitcoin&#8217;s recent sideways trading has paved the way for potential bullish momentum shortly. BTC&#8217;s current range-bound trading between $31,200 and $29,600 is seen as a consolidation period allowing for a re-establishment of bullish momentum in the market. To assess market sentiment and potential price movements in the Bitcoin market, Glassnode has developed a proprietary metric called the Swissblock Risk Signal. This metric considers various factors, including volatility, on-chain activity, social sentiment, and more. Related Reading: CFTC Investigators Conclude Celsius And Former CEO Violated Rules, Potential Case Looms In the context of Alleman&#8217;s analysis, the Swissblock Risk Signal has remained stable at 0, as seen in the chart below, which suggests that the current market sentiment is neutral, with no clear dominance from either buyers or sellers.  This could indicate that the market is in a consolidation phase, as buyers and sellers are cautious before making any significant moves. Additionally, Alleman predicts that BTC will likely break above $31,200, providing a strong foundation for buyers to target resistance levels at $33,000 and $34,800. However, even if the support at $29,600 were to break, Alleman believes that remaining bullish until the 50% retracement level near $28,200 seems viable. This pullback could represent an opportunity for investors to accumulate BTC for the next leap as the market shows signs of potential growth. As such, Alleman&#8217;s analysis suggests that the current market conditions present a favorable opportunity for those looking to invest in Bitcoin. Bitcoin Faces Critical Moment Bitcoin is facing a critical moment as its price fluctuates within a narrow range, warns market analyst Michael Van de Poppe. With Bitcoin&#8217;s lows being taken again, Van de Poppe believes that if it fails to recover soon, it could test support at $28,500. Adding to Bitcoin&#8217;s challenges is the expectation of a rate hike due to positive unemployment data. This leads to increased speculation that the Federal Reserve will raise interest rates sooner than expected. This could create a more challenging economic environment for cryptocurrencies. If both major resistance lines of $29,600 and $28,500 give in to pressure, a potential bull run in the short term could be in danger, potentially resulting in a retracement down to the $27,500 resistance level. This would represent a 9% pullback from the current level of $30,200. Related Reading: Marathon Digital Reports 21% Decline In Bitcoin Production In June If such a scenario were to occur, it could take time for Bitcoin bulls to regain their current levels. In the past, a period of consolidation has typically followed a pullback before any further continuation to regain lost levels. However, despite Bitcoin&#8217;s challenges, as long as it can hold the $30,000 line, BTC bulls have the upper hand. At the time of writing, BTC is trading at $30,200, down a slight 0.3% in the last 24 hours. Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com ]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin (BTC) has been trading within a narrow range for the past 12 days. Nonetheless, the fact that bulls have held the crucial $30,000 support level is seen as a short-term win for them.</p>
<p>Even though BTC has been experiencing sideways trading, there is a growing sense of optimism that it has the potential to break through upper resistance zones and reach new highs. </p>
<h2>BTC’s Sideways Trading Sets Stage For Bullish Momentum? </h2>
<p><a href="https://twitter.com/Negentropic_/status/1676912618487906304?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">According </a>to Yan Alleman, the co-founder of blockchain analytics firm Glassnode, Bitcoin&#8217;s recent sideways trading has paved the way for potential bullish momentum shortly. BTC&#8217;s current range-bound trading between $31,200 and $29,600 is seen as a consolidation period allowing for a re-establishment of bullish momentum in the market.</p>
<p>To assess market sentiment and potential price movements in the Bitcoin market, Glassnode has developed a proprietary metric called the Swissblock Risk Signal. This metric considers various factors, including volatility, on-chain activity, social sentiment, and more.</p>

<p>In the context of Alleman&#8217;s analysis, the Swissblock Risk Signal has remained stable at 0, as seen in the chart below, which suggests that the current market sentiment is neutral, with no clear dominance from either buyers or sellers. </p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large wp-image-541606" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/F0WXF49WIAIUjmM-860x352.jpg" alt="Bitcoin " width="860" height="352" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/F0WXF49WIAIUjmM-860x352.jpg 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/F0WXF49WIAIUjmM-460x188.jpg 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/F0WXF49WIAIUjmM-768x314.jpg 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/F0WXF49WIAIUjmM-1536x629.jpg 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/F0WXF49WIAIUjmM-2048x839.jpg 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/F0WXF49WIAIUjmM-750x307.jpg 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/F0WXF49WIAIUjmM-1140x467.jpg 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/>
<p>This could indicate that the market is in a consolidation phase, as buyers and sellers are cautious before making any significant moves.</p>
<p>Additionally, Alleman predicts that BTC will likely break above $31,200, providing a strong foundation for buyers to target resistance levels at $33,000 and $34,800. However, even if the support at $29,600 were to break, Alleman believes that remaining bullish until the 50% retracement level near $28,200 seems viable.</p>
<p>This pullback could represent an opportunity for investors to accumulate BTC for the next leap as the market shows signs of potential growth. As such, Alleman&#8217;s analysis suggests that the current market conditions present a favorable opportunity for those looking to invest in Bitcoin.</p>
Bitcoin Faces Critical Moment
<p>Bitcoin is facing a critical moment as its price fluctuates within a narrow range, <a href="https://twitter.com/CryptoMichNL/status/1676960412879953920?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">warns </a>market analyst Michael Van de Poppe. With Bitcoin&#8217;s lows being taken again, Van de Poppe believes that if it fails to recover soon, it could test support at $28,500.</p>
<p>Adding to Bitcoin&#8217;s challenges is the expectation of a rate hike due to positive unemployment data. This leads to increased speculation that the Federal Reserve will raise interest rates sooner than expected. This could create a more challenging economic environment for cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p>If both major resistance lines of $29,600 and $28,500 give in to pressure, a potential bull run in the short term could be in danger, potentially resulting in a retracement down to the $27,500 resistance level. This would represent a 9% pullback from the current level of $30,200.</p>

<p>If such a scenario were to occur, it could take time for Bitcoin bulls to regain their current levels. In the past, a period of consolidation has typically followed a pullback before any further continuation to regain lost levels.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/a9ZhhFex/" alt="Bitcoin " width="1814" height="858"/>
<p>However, despite Bitcoin&#8217;s challenges, as long as it can hold the $30,000 line, BTC bulls have the upper hand. At the time of writing, BTC is trading at $30,200, down a slight 0.3% in the last 24 hours.</p>
<p>Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/iStock-1322509303-3-460x259.jpg" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dormant Bitcoin Supply Peaks As Institutional Investors Show Increased Involvement</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/dormant-bitcoin-supply-peaks-as-institutional-investors/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samuel Edyme]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 17:30:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=541590</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[According to recent hedge fund Ark Invest data, a historical amount of the Bitcoin supply has remained dormant for at least a year, with roughly 70% of the circulating supply unmoved in June 2023. Despite looming economic uncertainty, this dynamic occurs alongside a surge in institutional interest in the cryptocurrency.  In June, several factors contributed to the increased robustness of the Bitcoin price action. Ark Invest, a renowned asset management firm, highlighted this trend in its recent Bitcoin report. Their data sheds light on the risen support from steadfast holders and a noticeable shift in institutional sentiment towards Bitcoin. Bitcoin Holder Base Strength According to Ark Invest&#8217;s analysis, around 70% of Bitcoin&#8217;s circulating supply has not changed hands for at least one year. This statistic signifies an increase in the confidence of long-term Bitcoin investors, contributing to a sturdier holder base.  As seen in the chart below, there has been a spike in Over-the-Counter Transactions (OTC) that hint at growing institutional demand. A one-year high was seen in the balance of BTC held on over-the-counter (OTC) trading desks, typically used as a gauge for institutional activity. The 60% increase in the OTC Bitcoin balance by quarter-end insinuates that institutions and capital allocators are concentrating more on Bitcoin as an investment avenue. The report stated the following: In our view, increased balances on OTC desks suggest that institutions and other large capital allocators are focused increasingly on bitcoin. Meanwhile, diverging trends were noted between USDC and Tether, two prominent stablecoins. While USDC&#8217;s supply shrunk by 37% year-to-date, Tether&#8217;s supply increased by 25%, hitting a record high in June. Ark Invest attributes this divergence to the uncertain U.S. regulatory climate, which might drive some crypto activity overseas. Rising Institutional Activity Amid Market Dynamics An interesting development in June was the Grayscale Bitcoin Trust (GBTC) discount reduction went from 42% to 30% following BlackRock&#8217;s Bitcoin spot Exchange Traded Fund (ETF) filing. According to Ark Invest&#8217;s report, this lower discount implies market anticipation for a Bitcoin spot ETF approval, subsequently enhancing the possibility of GBTC transitioning into an ETF. Ark Invest&#8217;s report cautioned about potential economic challenges despite these positive indications. According to the Purchasing Managers &#8216; Index, manufacturing sector data suggests a plunge in new orders. Concurrently, the U.S. Gross Domestic Income (GDI) shows signs of contraction, indicating the possibility of an impending recession. BTC is trading above $30,000, following its recovery from last month when its value dipped below that. The asset&#8217;s downturn was largely spurred by a legal challenge launched by the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) against Binance and Coinbase, the two foremost crypto exchanges. Related Reading: Analyst’s Forecast: Bitcoin (BTC) To Hit $310,000 If This Happens Nonetheless, Bitcoin&#8217;s recent rally comes on the heels of endorsement from heavyweight financial institutions such as BlackRock. This embrace of the digital currency market has injected a dose of optimism, driving Bitcoin&#8217;s substantial growth. Related Reading: Bitcoin Could Soar To $140,000 In Next Bull Cycle, Crypto Analysis Channel Yesterday, the asset reclaimed its $31,000 mark. However, over the past 24 hours, BTC has retraced and currently trades for $30,400 at the time of writing. Featured image from iStock, Chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>According to recent hedge fund Ark Invest <a href="https://ark-invest.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/The-Bitcoin-Monthly-June-2023.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">data</a>, a historical amount of the Bitcoin supply has remained dormant for at least a year, with roughly 70% of the circulating supply unmoved in June 2023. Despite looming economic uncertainty, this dynamic occurs alongside a surge in institutional interest in the cryptocurrency. </p>
<p>In June, several factors contributed to the increased robustness of the Bitcoin price action. Ark Invest, a renowned asset management firm, highlighted this trend in its recent Bitcoin report. Their data sheds light on the risen support from steadfast holders and a noticeable shift in institutional sentiment towards Bitcoin.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Holder Base Strength</h2>
<p>According to Ark Invest&#8217;s analysis, around 70% of <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-could-soar-in-next-bull-cycle-predicts-crypto/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Bitcoin&#8217;s circulating supply</a> has not changed hands for at least one year. This statistic signifies an increase in the confidence of long-term Bitcoin investors, contributing to a sturdier holder base. </p>
<p>As seen in the chart below, there has been a spike in Over-the-Counter Transactions (OTC) that hint at growing institutional demand. A one-year high was seen in the balance of BTC held on over-the-counter (OTC) trading desks, typically used as a gauge for institutional activity. </p>
<p>The 60% increase in the OTC <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-miners-send-daily-revenue-to-exchanges/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Bitcoin balance</a> by quarter-end insinuates that institutions and capital allocators are concentrating more on Bitcoin as an investment avenue.</p>
<p>The report stated the following:</p>
<blockquote><p>In our view, increased balances on OTC desks suggest that institutions and other large capital allocators are focused increasingly on bitcoin.</p></blockquote>

<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-541604 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-1-860x679.jpg" alt="Bitcoin BTC BTCUSDT Chart 1" width="860" height="679" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-1-860x679.jpg 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-1-460x363.jpg 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-1-768x607.jpg 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-1-750x593.jpg 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-1.jpg 1010w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/>
<p>Meanwhile, diverging trends were noted between USDC and Tether, two prominent stablecoins. While USDC&#8217;s supply shrunk by 37% year-to-date, Tether&#8217;s supply increased by 25%, hitting a record high in June. Ark Invest attributes this divergence to the uncertain U.S. regulatory climate, which might drive some crypto activity overseas.</p>
<h2>Rising Institutional Activity Amid Market Dynamics</h2>
<p>An interesting development in June was the Grayscale Bitcoin Trust (GBTC) discount reduction went from 42% to 30% following BlackRock&#8217;s <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/btc-uptrend-fidelity-to-submit-bitcoin-spot-etf-filing/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Bitcoin spot Exchange Traded Fund (ETF) filing</a>. According to Ark Invest&#8217;s report, this lower discount implies market anticipation for a Bitcoin spot ETF approval, subsequently enhancing the possibility of GBTC transitioning into an ETF.</p>
<p>Ark Invest&#8217;s report cautioned about potential economic challenges despite these positive indications. According to the Purchasing Managers &#8216; Index, manufacturing sector data suggests a plunge in new orders. Concurrently, the U.S. Gross Domestic Income (GDI) shows signs of contraction, indicating the possibility of an impending recession.</p>
<p>BTC is <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/analysts-forecast-bitcoin-btc-to-hit-310000-if-this-happens/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">trading above $30,000</a>, following its recovery from last month when its value dipped below that. The asset&#8217;s downturn was largely spurred by a legal challenge launched by the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) against Binance and Coinbase, the two foremost crypto exchanges.</p>

<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w" dir="ltr">Nonetheless, Bitcoin&#8217;s recent rally comes on the heels of endorsement from <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/blackrock-inches-closer-to-launching-bitcoin-etf-impact-on-btc-price/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">heavyweight financial institutions such as BlackRock</a>. This embrace of the digital currency market has injected a dose of optimism, driving Bitcoin&#8217;s substantial growth.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/ydueGgBM/" alt="Bitcoin (BTC)’s price chart on TradingView" width="2770" height="1556"/>
<p dir="ltr">Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-could-soar-in-next-bull-cycle-predicts-crypto/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Bitcoin Could Soar To $140,000 In Next Bull Cycle, Crypto Analysis Channel</a></p>
<p dir="ltr">Yesterday, the asset reclaimed its $31,000 mark. However, over the past 24 hours, BTC has retraced and currently trades for $30,400 at the time of writing.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Featured image from iStock, Chart from TradingView</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Bitcoin-460x329.jpeg" width="460" height="329" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>CFTC Investigators Conclude Celsius And Former CEO Violated Rules, Potential Case Looms</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/crypto/cftc-investigators-conclude-celsius-violated-rules/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 16:30:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Alex Mashinsky]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[celsius]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Celsius bankruptcy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto regulation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=541589</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) has concluded its investigation into bankrupt crypto lender Celsius and its former CEO, Alex Mashinsky, and found that they violated United States rules, according to sources familiar with the matter.  The investigation, conducted by attorneys in the CFTC&#8217;s enforcement unit, revealed that Celsius misled investors and failed to register with the regulatory body. If the majority of the CFTC&#8217;s commissioners agree with these findings, the agency could file a case in federal court as early as this month. Celsius Reportedly Misled Investors, Lack Of Registration Surfaces  The findings of the investigation shed light on the actions of Celsius and its former CEO, raising questions about their compliance with regulatory requirements. It is alleged that Celsius engaged in deceptive practices and failed to provide accurate information to investors. Related Reading: Valkyrie Follows In BlackRock’s Footsteps, Refiles For Spot Bitcoin ETF By misleading investors, the lending platform potentially put their funds at risk and undermined market transparency. Furthermore, the failure to register with the CFTC raises concerns about the company&#8217;s adherence to regulatory oversight. The independent examiner appointed during Celsius&#8217; bankruptcy case further shed light on the company&#8217;s operations. The examiner found that Celsius had operated in a manner similar to a Ponzi scheme, which raised concerns about the company&#8217;s business practices and its impact on investors. This finding adds weight to the allegations against Celsius and strengthens the case for regulatory action. CEL token struggles at $0.15 &#124; Source: CELUSD on TradingView.com The potential case against Celsius and its ex-CEO has significant implications for the crypto industry and regulatory enforcement. If the CFTC proceeds with the lawsuit, it would signal a strong stance on holding companies accountable for their actions and ensuring investor protection in the cryptocurrency market. When Celsius filed for voluntary bankruptcy in July 2022, the lending company reportedly owed between $1 billion and $10 billion to creditors. The case is currently ongoing at the United States Bankruptcy Court for the Southern District of New York. Implications For The Crypto Industry And Regulatory Enforcement The allegations against Celsius and its former CEO highlight the need for increased regulatory scrutiny and oversight in the crypto sector. As the market continues to grow and attract more participants, it is crucial to establish clear guidelines and enforce compliance to protect investors and maintain market integrity. Related Reading: Analyst Says XRP Will Reach $100, Here’s Why Nevertheless,  the potential case against Celsius demonstrates the commitment of regulatory authorities to uphold these standards and address violations that occur within the industry. This case could serve as a precedent for future enforcement actions, shaping the regulatory landscape for the industry as a whole. Featured image from IQ.Wiki, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) has concluded its investigation into bankrupt crypto lender Celsius and its former CEO, Alex Mashinsky, and found that they violated United States rules, according to sources familiar with the matter. </p>
<p>The investigation, conducted by attorneys in the CFTC&#8217;s enforcement unit, revealed that Celsius misled investors and failed to register with the regulatory body. </p>
<p>If the majority of the CFTC&#8217;s commissioners agree with these findings, the agency could file a case in federal court as early as this month.</p>
<h2>Celsius Reportedly Misled Investors, Lack Of Registration Surfaces </h2>
<p>The <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-07-05/cftc-probe-concludes-crypto-lender-celsius-ex-ceo-mashinsky-broke-rules#xj4y7vzkg" rel="nofollow">findings</a> of the investigation shed light on the actions of Celsius and its former CEO, raising questions about their compliance with regulatory requirements. It is alleged that Celsius engaged in deceptive practices and failed to provide accurate information to investors.</p>

<p>By misleading investors, the lending platform potentially put their funds at risk and undermined market transparency. Furthermore, the failure to register with the CFTC raises concerns about the company&#8217;s adherence to regulatory oversight.</p>
<p>The independent examiner appointed during Celsius&#8217; bankruptcy case further shed light on the company&#8217;s operations. The examiner found that Celsius had operated in a manner similar to a Ponzi scheme, which raised concerns about the company&#8217;s business practices and its impact on investors. This finding adds weight to the allegations against Celsius and strengthens the case for regulatory action.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/kkbXXkMM/" alt="Celsius Token (CEL) price chart from TradingView.com" width="2884" height="1610"/></p>

<p>The potential case against Celsius and its ex-CEO has significant implications for the crypto industry and regulatory enforcement. If the CFTC proceeds with the lawsuit, it would signal a strong stance on holding companies accountable for their actions and ensuring investor protection in the cryptocurrency market.</p>
<p>When Celsius filed for voluntary bankruptcy in July 2022, the lending company reportedly owed between $1 billion and $10 billion to creditors. The case is currently ongoing at the United States Bankruptcy Court for the Southern District of New York.</p>
<h2>Implications For The Crypto Industry And Regulatory Enforcement</h2>
<p>The allegations against Celsius and its former CEO highlight the need for increased regulatory scrutiny and oversight in the crypto sector. As the market continues to grow and attract more participants, it is crucial to establish clear guidelines and enforce compliance to protect investors and maintain market integrity.</p>

<p>Nevertheless,  the potential case against Celsius demonstrates the commitment of regulatory authorities to uphold these standards and address violations that occur within the industry.</p>
<p>This case could serve as a precedent for future enforcement actions, shaping the regulatory landscape for the industry as a whole.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Celsius-network-460x345.jpeg" width="460" height="345" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Marathon Digital Reports 21% Decline In Bitcoin Production In June</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/marathon-digital-reports-21-decline-in-bitcoin-production-in-june/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Semilore Faleti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 15:30:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin hashrate]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Marathon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Marathon Digital]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=541580</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Prominent Bitcoin mining company Marathon Digital Holdings has published its Bitcoin production and mining operation update for June 2023. In the report released yesterday, Marathon revealed that its Bitcoin production decreased by 21% from May due to weather-related issues in Texas and a decline in transaction fees on the Bitcoin network. &#8220;We produced 979 bitcoin in June, down 21% from last month and up 599% from June 2022,” said the Company’s CEO, Fried Theil. “The decreased production relative to last month was due to weather-related curtailment in Texas and a significant decrease in transaction fees, which fell to approximately 5.1% of the total bitcoin we earned in June compared to 11.8% in May,&#8221; Theil added. The Marathon boss noted that the rise of the Bitcoin ordinals contributed to an increase in network fees back in May, and although network congestion decreased in June, he stated that the mining company is quite optimistic about the future of mining economics.  Marathon’s Operational Hash Rate Boosts By 16% Marathon’s monthly report revealed that the mining company’s operational hash rate gained by 16% in June, rising to 17.2 exahashes/second (EH/s). Its installed hash rate also increased to 21.8 EH/a, representing an 8% gain in the last month.  Related Reading: Bitcoin Exchange Supply Continues To Slip, Holders Not Interested In Selling? According to its CEO, Marathon remains committed to its goal of attaining 23 EH/s by boosting its operations in North Dakota and Texas, as emphasized by its CEO.  Theil said: The final steps to achieving our 23 EH/s goal are in Ellendale, ND and Garden City, TX. The final building in Ellendale is expected to come online this month, and final Garden City tie in is also expected within that same period. Theil also announced that the company’s joint venture with Zero Two in Abu Dhabi began operations last week and is expected to achieve a hash rate of 7 EH/s before the end of the year. However, this JV operation does not contribute to the reported operational hash rate of 17.2 EH/s and the mining target of 23 EH/s.  BTC Trading At $30,147 On The Hourly Chart &#124; Source: BTCUSD Chart On Tradingview.com Marathon’s Growth In The Last Year Looking at its Year-Over-Year production rate, Marathon reports that its level of Bitcoin production has gone up by 599% since June 2022, moving from an average daily intake of 4.7 BTC to 32.6 BTC.  Related Reading: Bitcoin Cash Hashrate, Mining Difficulty Skyrockets As Miners Chase BCH Profits Furthermore, the company&#8217;s current operational hash rate of 17.7 EH/s represents a stunning increase of 2,429% compared to last June’s value of 0.7 EH/s. However, its installed hash rate only experienced a percentage gain of 506% moving from 3.6 EH/s to 21.8 EH/s. That said, Marathon stands as a leading mining company with approximately 149,000 Bitcoin miners as of July 1, 2023. Featured Image from Financial Times, chart from Tradingview]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Prominent Bitcoin mining company Marathon Digital Holdings has published its Bitcoin production and mining operation update for June 2023.</p>
<p>In the <a href="https://ir.mara.com/news-events/press-releases/detail/1320/marathon-digital-holdings-announces-bitcoin-production-and" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">report released yesterday</a>, Marathon revealed that its Bitcoin production decreased by 21% from May due to weather-related issues in Texas and a decline in transaction fees on the Bitcoin network.</p>
<p>&#8220;We produced 979 bitcoin in June, down 21% from last month and up 599% from June 2022,” said the Company’s CEO, Fried Theil. “The decreased production relative to last month was due to weather-related curtailment in Texas and a significant decrease in transaction fees, which fell to approximately 5.1% of the total bitcoin we earned in June compared to 11.8% in May,&#8221; Theil added.</p>
<p>The Marathon boss noted that the rise of the Bitcoin ordinals contributed to an increase in network fees back in May, and although network congestion decreased in June, he stated that the mining company is quite optimistic about the future of mining economics. </p>
<h2>Marathon’s Operational Hash Rate Boosts By 16%</h2>
<p>Marathon’s monthly report revealed that the mining company’s operational hash rate gained by 16% in June, rising to 17.2 exahashes/second (EH/s). Its installed hash rate also increased to 21.8 EH/a, representing an 8% gain in the last month. </p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-exchange-supply-slip-holders-interested-selling/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Bitcoin Exchange Supply Continues To Slip, Holders Not Interested In Selling?</a></p>
<p>According to its CEO, Marathon remains committed to its goal of attaining 23 EH/s by boosting its operations in North Dakota and Texas, as emphasized by its CEO.  </p>
<p>Theil said:</p>
<blockquote><p>The final steps to achieving our 23 EH/s goal are in Ellendale, ND and Garden City, TX. The final building in Ellendale is expected to come online this month, and final Garden City tie in is also expected within that same period.
</p></blockquote>
<p>Theil also announced that the<a href="https://www.globenewswire.com/news-release/2023/05/09/2664929/0/en/Marathon-Digital-Holdings-and-Zero-Two-To-Develop-and-Operate-the-First-Large-Scale-Immersion-Bitcoin-Mining-Facilities-in-Abu-Dhabi.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow"> company’s joint venture with Zero Two</a> in Abu Dhabi began operations last week and is expected to achieve a hash rate of 7 EH/s before the end of the year. However, this JV operation does not contribute to the reported operational hash rate of 17.2 EH/s and the mining target of 23 EH/s. </p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/nJ9FLFSE/" alt="Marathon" width="1479" height="913"/>

<h2>Marathon’s Growth In The Last Year</h2>
<p>Looking at its Year-Over-Year production rate, Marathon reports that its level of Bitcoin production has gone up by 599% since June 2022, moving from an average daily intake of 4.7 BTC to 32.6 BTC. </p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin-cash/bitcoin-cash-hashrate-mining-difficulty-skyrockets-as-miners-chase-bch-profits/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Bitcoin Cash Hashrate, Mining Difficulty Skyrockets As Miners Chase BCH Profits</a></p>
<p>Furthermore, the company&#8217;s current operational hash rate of 17.7 EH/s represents a stunning increase of 2,429% compared to last June’s value of 0.7 EH/s. However, its installed hash rate only experienced a percentage gain of 506% moving from 3.6 EH/s to 21.8 EH/s.</p>
<p>That said, Marathon stands as a leading mining company with approximately 149,000 Bitcoin miners as of July 1, 2023.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/e73494ae-4eb3-47d6-884b-2d9deb402463-460x259.jpg" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
