<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
>

<channel>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.newsbtc.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<description>Bitcoin &#38; Cryptocurrency News Today</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 22:06:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Litecoin Sharks Buy More Than 200,000 LTC Ahead Of Wednesday’s Halving</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/ltc/litecoin-sharks-buy-more-200000-ltc/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Best Owie]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 23:00:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[LTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Litecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[litecoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ltc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LTC dolphins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LTC sharks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LTC whales]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LTCUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=545227</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Over the last few months, Litecoin has emerged as one of the top trending cryptocurrencies due to its halving event happening in August. As this event drew closer, crypto investors began filling up their LTC bags in preparation for what is expected to be a very bullish event. And now, with less than two days left to go before the halving, sharks have made remarkable moves to position themselves for possible upside. Litecoin Sharks Load Up Their Bags A report shared by the on-chain tracking platform Santiment revealed how Litecoin investors are currently looking at the digital asset. The chart showed an impressive accumulation trend from dolphin and shark wallets, which have increased their holdings significantly in the last month. Related Reading: Dogecoin Falls While Others Rally, Is It Decoupling From The Market? Santiment’s report shows that these wallets holding between $9,500 and $950,000 worth of LTC have added over 200,00 coins to their balances since June 14. On this date, the total holdings of these wallets were sitting just slightly below 18 million. However, in the next two weeks, their balances grew above 18.1 million coins. LTC sharks and dolphins buy over 200,000 coins &#124; Source: Santiment There has also been a semi-constant uptrend among these investors. Although there were dips here and there in their holdings, they remained committed to the accumulation over this last two weeks, each time buying more coins than they sold. What Is Driving The LTC Accumulation? The current accumulation from the dolphin and shark wallets are not isolated and just like the whale acquisitions, they are being driven by the same thing. The Litecoin halving is expected to take place on Wednesday and since this event has been historically bullish, it has triggered active participation from investors looking to capitalize on it. If the LTC halving plays out as expected, then it is possible that the price of the altcoin will climb above $100 once more. This would put the majority of the LTC accumulated by the dolphin and shark addresses over the last two weeks back in profit territory. Related Reading: Cardano (ADA) Price Remains Muted Despite Significant Milestones, Why? However, the days leading up to the event haven’t been as bullish as expected. Even though LTC’s price is still trading above $90, it has seen only single-digit daily gains over this time. Naturally, with less than two days to go, there should have already been some rapid increases for the cryptocurrency but there has been none. This current trend suggests that the halving may already be priced into LTC’s price, especially given the fact that the crypto bear market has continued. At the time of writing, LTC is changing hands at a price of $93.80, down 0.98%, according to data from Coinmarketcap. Follow Best Owie on Twitter for market insights, updates, and the occasional funny tweet… Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="p2">Over the last few months, Litecoin has emerged as one of the top trending cryptocurrencies due to its halving event happening in August. As this event drew closer, crypto investors began filling up their LTC bags in preparation for what is expected to be a very bullish event. And now, with less than two days left to go before the halving, sharks have made remarkable moves to position themselves for possible upside.</p>
<h2 class="p2">Litecoin Sharks Load Up Their Bags</h2>
<p class="p2">A report shared by the on-chain tracking platform Santiment revealed how Litecoin <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/the-litecoin-95-question-is-a-bullish-breakout-in-the-pipeline/?swcfpc=1">investors are currently looking at the digital asset</a>. The chart showed an impressive accumulation trend from dolphin and shark wallets, which have increased their holdings significantly in the last month.</p>

<p class="p2">Santiment’s report shows that these wallets holding between $9,500 and $950,000 worth of LTC have added over 200,00 coins to their balances since June 14. On this date, the total holdings of these wallets were sitting just slightly below 18 million. However, in the next two weeks, their balances grew above 18.1 million coins.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-545229 aligncenter" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Litecoin-sharks-and-Dolphins-460x293.jpeg" alt="Litecoin sharks and Dolphins" width="460" height="293" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Litecoin-sharks-and-Dolphins-460x293.jpeg 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Litecoin-sharks-and-Dolphins-860x548.jpeg 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Litecoin-sharks-and-Dolphins-768x490.jpeg 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Litecoin-sharks-and-Dolphins-1536x979.jpeg 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Litecoin-sharks-and-Dolphins-2048x1305.jpeg 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Litecoin-sharks-and-Dolphins-750x478.jpeg 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Litecoin-sharks-and-Dolphins-1140x727.jpeg 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px"/></p>

<p class="p2">There has also been a semi-constant uptrend among these investors. Although there were dips here and there in their holdings, they remained committed to the accumulation over this last two weeks, each time buying more coins than they sold.</p>
What Is Driving The LTC Accumulation?
<p class="p2">The current accumulation from the dolphin and shark wallets are not isolated and just like the whale acquisitions, they are being driven by the same thing. The Litecoin <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/ltc/litecoin-becomes-10th-largest-cryptocurrency/?swcfpc=1">halving</a> is expected to take place on Wednesday and since this event has been historically bullish, it has triggered active participation from investors looking to capitalize on it.</p>
<p class="p2">If the LTC halving plays out as expected, then it is possible that <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/litecoin-shows-solid-bullish-trends/?swcfpc=1">the price of the altcoin will climb above $100</a> once more. This would put the majority of the LTC accumulated by the dolphin and shark addresses over the last two weeks back in profit territory.</p>

<p class="p2">However, the days leading up to the event haven’t been as bullish as expected. Even though LTC’s price is still trading above $90, it has seen only single-digit daily gains over this time. Naturally, with less than two days to go, there should have already been some rapid increases for the cryptocurrency but there has been none.</p>
<p class="p2">This current trend suggests that the halving may already be priced into LTC’s price, especially given the fact that the crypto bear market has continued.</p>
<p class="p2">At the time of writing, LTC is changing hands at a price of $93.80, down 0.98%, according to data from Coinmarketcap.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/iStock-1015828796-460x263.jpg" width="460" height="263" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>29 Other Meme Coins Besides BALD Rugged on Base</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/29-meme-coins-bald-rugged-base-investors-lose-millions/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dalmas Ngetich]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 22:06:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Arbitrum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BALD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Base]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LADYS]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[meme coins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PEPE]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=545256</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Scope data on July 31 shows that 29 meme coins were launched over the weekend on Base to capitalize on the recent frenzy surrounding BaldBaseBald (BALD), a meme coin inspired by Coinbase CEO Brian Armstrong. However, all 29 meme coins have since been rugged, with the deployer exiting with over $1 million after seeding roughly $105,000 of ETH as liquidity. Base is an Ethereum layer-2 platform based on Optimism roll-up technology.  Rug Pulls On Base On July 29 and 30, there was excitement about the meme coin, BALD, as its prices exploded by as much as 4,000X, pushing the token&#8217;s market cap to over $100 million. This was great news for those who invested early as some exited as the wave rise, profiting. Some builders took advantage of the hype and created meme coins to deceive investors eager to join the BALD trend, eventually resulting in losses for some meme coin token holders. Related Reading: BALD Coin Rug Pull: How A $100 Million Memecoin Became Worthless Overnight While BALD has already been rug-pulled, Scope notes that the address behind the 29 meme coins also has a history of rug-pulling in other platforms, including the BNB Chain and Arbitrum, a popular Ethereum layer-2 platform. In platforms where meme coins are traded, liquidity, provided by the community, is essential due to the decentralized nature of trading.  Rug pullers typically supply liquidity to their meme coins, which attracts more users to buy the coin and increases liquidity as prices rise. However, the creator then deliberately withdraws liquidity at this point, converting their meme coins to a more liquid coin like Ethereum, causing their token prices to drop to zero. As of July 31, hours after the rug pull, the address primarily held USDC and a small portion of ETH in their portfolio, with no meme coins. This potentially highlights the rug puller&#8217;s risk-averseness and his concerns about the risks involved in this asset class. Related Reading: Bitcoin Crucial Moment: Will Resistance At $29,500 Trigger A Sell-Off Or Surge? Meme Coins Are Volatile Meme coins are popular in crypto, especially Ethereum, where they are minted as fungible ERC-20 tokens in their trillions. Dogecoin, endorsed by Elon Musk, is the most liquid and widely recognized. Despite rising popularity, there are concerns about their volatility and lack of utility, with some critics labeling them as &#8220;casinos&#8221; that undermine the true vision of crypto as an alternative financial system. For example, the collapse of BALD, which commanded billions in market cap on Base over the weekend, has drawn widespread condemnation. Besides BALD, other like PEPE and LADYS are struggling, dropping by over 70% from their all-time peaks registered in H1 2023. Feature image from Canva, chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Scope <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://twitter.com/0xScopescan/status/1685955109342359552?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">data</a> on July 31 shows that 29 meme coins were launched over the weekend on Base to capitalize on the recent frenzy surrounding BaldBaseBald (BALD), a meme coin inspired by Coinbase CEO Brian Armstrong. </p>
<p>However, all 29 meme coins have since been rugged, with the deployer exiting with over $1 million after seeding roughly $105,000 of ETH as liquidity. Base is an Ethereum layer-2 platform based on Optimism roll-up technology. </p>
<h2>Rug Pulls On Base</h2>
<p>On July 29 and 30, there was excitement about the meme coin, BALD, as its prices exploded by as much as 4,000X, pushing the token&#8217;s market cap to over $100 million. This was great news for those who invested early as some exited as the wave rise, profiting. </p>
<p>Some builders took advantage of the hype and created meme coins to deceive investors eager to join the BALD trend, eventually resulting in losses for some meme coin token holders.</p>

<p>While BALD has <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bald-coin-rug-pull-how-a-100-million-memecoin-became-worthless-overnight/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">already</a> been rug-pulled, Scope notes that the address behind the 29 meme coins also has a history of rug-pulling in other platforms, including the BNB Chain and Arbitrum, a popular Ethereum layer-2 platform. In platforms where meme coins are traded, liquidity, provided by the community, is essential due to the decentralized nature of trading. </p>
<p>Rug pullers typically supply liquidity to their meme coins, which attracts more users to buy the coin and increases liquidity as prices rise. However, the creator then deliberately withdraws liquidity at this point, converting their meme coins to a more liquid coin like Ethereum, causing their token prices to drop to zero.</p>
<p>As of July 31, hours after the rug pull, the address primarily <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://scopescan.ai/address/0xf01e51504a9f5020f6f46cc0bc76c1d2efb40ec0?network=arb" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">held</a> USDC and a small portion of ETH in their portfolio, with no meme coins. This potentially highlights the rug puller&#8217;s risk-averseness and his concerns about the risks involved in this asset class.
</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-crucial-moment-will-resistance-at-29500-trigger-a-sell-off-or-surge/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Bitcoin Crucial Moment: Will Resistance At $29,500 Trigger A Sell-Off Or Surge?</a></p>
<h2>Meme Coins Are Volatile</h2>
<p>Meme coins are popular in crypto, especially Ethereum, where they are minted as fungible ERC-20 tokens in their trillions. Dogecoin, endorsed by Elon Musk, is the most liquid and widely recognized. </p>
<p>Despite rising popularity, there are concerns about their volatility and lack of utility, with some critics labeling them as &#8220;casinos&#8221; that undermine the true vision of crypto as an alternative financial system.</p>
<a href="https://www.tradingview.com/x/Sl9wpPMk/" rel="nofollow"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/Sl9wpPMk/" alt="Dogecoin price on July 31 as 29 meme coins rugged on Base| Source: DOGEUSDT on Binance, TradingView" width="1226" height="595"/></a>
<p>For example, the collapse of BALD, which commanded billions in market cap on Base over the weekend, has drawn widespread condemnation. Besides BALD, other like PEPE and LADYS are struggling, dropping by over 70% from their all-time peaks registered in H1 2023.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Base-Meme-Coins-BALD-PEPE-LADYS-460x260.jpg" width="460" height="260" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>BALD Coin Rug Pull: How A $100 Million Memecoin Became Worthless Overnight</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bald-coin-rug-pull-how-a-100-million-memecoin-became-worthless-overnight/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 20:00:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BALD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Rug Pull]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=545248</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[On July 30, a meme coin called BaldBaseBald (BALD) launched on Base Network, Coinbase&#8217;s new Layer 2 built on Optimism. The coin referenced Brian Armstrong, Coinbase&#8217;s “bald” founder, and quickly became a coordination point for speculators on the frontier chain.  Within two days, the token had reached a market cap of $100 million, with over $25 million in liquidity. However, the token&#8217;s meteoric rise turned out to be a classic case of market manipulation, as the deployer behind the token, BaldBaseBald, rug pulled the token and caused its price to plummet by 85%. Malicious Market Behavior Behind BALD? Market researcher Thiccy indexed all the transactions from the Bald deployer and uncovered a story of malicious market behavior. BaldBaseBald added over 6,700 ETH, or over $12.5 million worth of liquidity, to the pool in the first 24 hours, a surprising amount of capital for a meme coin on a new chain.  Related Reading: Breaking: HEX Token Plummets 25% Following SEC Lawsuit Against Founder Richard Heart The deployer&#8217;s actions were undoubtedly bullish for speculators, and many people speculated that Brian Armstrong had created the coin to drum up hype. However, as soon as the deployer stopped adding liquidity to the pool, the price stagnated and broke down.  24 hours later, the deployer started bidding on BALD again, causing the price to double. Then, the deployer withdrew over 10.500 Ethereum (ETH), or almost $20 million worth of liquidity, leading to an 85% drop in the token&#8217;s value. Thiccy&#8217;s analysis showed that the deployer had made a net profit of 2,789 ETH, or 5.2 million dollars, after adding 6,870 ETH, spending 1,360 ETH buying at an average price of 0.0004, and withdrawing 10,704 ETH.  It was surprising how well-capitalized the actor was and how bold they were in carrying out this apparent manipulative market behavior in the middle of the public light on Coinbase&#8217;s compliance chain. Thiccy Concluded: And with that, the story of BALD has come to a close play stupid games, win stupid prizes. Hopefully we can learn from this as a space this market is rife with market manipulation and unethical shills. Be careful who you trust. Thiccy advises investors to control their Fear of Missing Out (FOMO) and not risk more than they can afford to lose, as survival is too important in this game.  Related Reading: 8-Year Dormant Ethereum Wallet Just Moved $1.2 Million In ETH, Here’s The Destination As for BaldBaseBald has removed the rest of the liquidity, bringing their total Profit and Loss (PnL) to 3,163 ETH, or $5.9 million.  Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com ]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On July 30, a meme coin called BaldBaseBald (BALD) launched on Base Network, Coinbase&#8217;s new Layer 2 built on Optimism. The coin referenced Brian Armstrong, Coinbase&#8217;s “bald” founder, and quickly became a coordination point for speculators on the frontier chain. </p>
<p>Within two days, the token had reached a market cap of $100 million, with over $25 million in liquidity. However, the token&#8217;s meteoric rise turned out to be a classic case of market manipulation, as the deployer behind the token, BaldBaseBald, rug pulled the token and caused its price to plummet by 85%.</p>
<h2>Malicious Market Behavior Behind BALD?</h2>
<p>Market researcher Thiccy indexed all the transactions from the Bald deployer and <a href="https://twitter.com/thiccythot_/status/1686024695865360384?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">uncovered </a>a story of malicious market behavior. BaldBaseBald added over 6,700 ETH, or over $12.5 million worth of liquidity, to the pool in the first 24 hours, a surprising amount of capital for a meme coin on a new chain. </p>

<p>The deployer&#8217;s actions were undoubtedly bullish for speculators, and many people speculated that Brian Armstrong had created the coin to drum up hype. However, as soon as the deployer stopped adding liquidity to the pool, the price stagnated and broke down. </p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-545249 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/F2Xy1yoXMAAE3Do-860x514.jpeg" alt="BALD" width="860" height="514" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/F2Xy1yoXMAAE3Do-860x514.jpeg 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/F2Xy1yoXMAAE3Do-460x275.jpeg 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/F2Xy1yoXMAAE3Do-768x459.jpeg 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/F2Xy1yoXMAAE3Do-1536x919.jpeg 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/F2Xy1yoXMAAE3Do-2048x1225.jpeg 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/F2Xy1yoXMAAE3Do-750x449.jpeg 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/F2Xy1yoXMAAE3Do-1140x682.jpeg 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/>
<p>24 hours later, the deployer started bidding on BALD again, causing the price to double. Then, the deployer withdrew over 10.500 Ethereum (ETH), or almost $20 million worth of liquidity, leading to an 85% drop in the token&#8217;s value.</p>
<p>Thiccy&#8217;s analysis showed that the deployer had made a net profit of 2,789 ETH, or 5.2 million dollars, after adding 6,870 ETH, spending 1,360 ETH buying at an average price of 0.0004, and withdrawing 10,704 ETH. </p>
<p>It was surprising how well-capitalized the actor was and how bold they were in carrying out this apparent manipulative market behavior in the middle of the public light on Coinbase&#8217;s compliance chain. Thiccy Concluded:</p>
<blockquote><p>And with that, the story of BALD has come to a close play stupid games, win stupid prizes. Hopefully we can learn from this as a space this market is rife with market manipulation and unethical shills. Be careful who you trust.</p></blockquote>
<p>Thiccy advises investors to control their Fear of Missing Out (FOMO) and not risk more than they can afford to lose, as survival is too important in this game. </p>

<p>As for BaldBaseBald has removed the rest of the liquidity, bringing their total Profit and Loss (PnL) to 3,163 ETH, or $5.9 million. </p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/SW3rwK5X/" alt="BALD" width="1814" height="858"/>
<p>Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/businessman-saving-piggybank-from-hammering-picture-id921353742-460x259.jpg" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Crucial Moment: Will Resistance At $29,500 Trigger A Sell-Off Or Surge?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-crucial-moment-will-resistance-at-29500-trigger-a-sell-off-or-surge/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 19:00:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=545237</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) has been trading in a tight range for quite some time now, with bulls and bears engaged in a tug-of-war over key support and resistance levels.  The recent move above $29,500 has provided some hope for the bulls, but so far, they have been unable to gather enough momentum to push prices higher. Bitcoin Struggles To Break Above Key Moving Average According to Material Indicators, a leading market analysis firm, the key to a bullish breakout in the BTC market is for the coin to print candles above the 100-week moving average (MA). However, BTC has yet to test this level, and bulls have struggled to maintain the current range. The 50-day MA has been a crucial support level, with BTC testing it for today&#8217;s eighth consecutive day. While the 50-day MA has managed to hold, resistance at $29,500 has been replenishing, posing a challenge for the bulls.  If they cannot clear this level, Material Indicators expects a run at the lows with $28,300 as the last line of defense. The big question for BTC investors is whether the coin will bounce from the $28,000 zone or extend to $25,000 and beyond. All of these moves are possible, but the mystery lies in what order and timeline they will play out. Related Reading: Breaking: HEX Token Plummets 25% Following SEC Lawsuit Against Founder Richard Heart As the market approaches the monthly close, all eyes are on the potential for volatility in the BTC market. Traders and investors closely monitor the price action and indicators to prepare for potential moves. BTC&#8217;s Store Of Value Narrative Solidified The recent changes in the structure of Bitcoin&#8217;s trading volume have sparked a debate among cryptocurrency investors and traders. According to Crypto Quant, since January 2023, the Spot vs. Derivatives volume ratio has dropped from 35% to 6%, resulting in a new era of low volatility in the cryptocurrency market. This decrease in spot volume means that investors are holding onto their Bitcoins instead of selling them, as Bitcoin is now considered a valuable asset, similar to digital gold.  This is seen in the BTC: Binary Coin Days Destroyed (CDD) chart, which shows that since the start of the year, there have been no active sales among the cohort of long-term holders (LTHs). Moreover, the total Simple Moving Average (SMA)-7d weekly trading volume of Bitcoin across all exchanges has dropped from 2.5 million BTC in March to less than 600 thousand BTC in July, representing a more than 75% reduction over the specified period.  While some may see this trend as a crisis, Crypto Quant believes it is a sign of the cryptocurrency market maturing and becoming more stable and predictable. However, this trend could lead to significant changes in the Bitcoin market. A reduction in spot volume may result in a reduction in liquidity, which could increase the demand and price of Bitcoin. The market currently lacks a new wave of optimism, and the question is, where will it come from? Related Reading: US Presidential Candidate Defends Bitcoin, Calls Out Environmental Critics The answer may lie in the growing institutional interest in Bitcoin and other cryptocurrencies. Several major financial institutions, such as Fidelity, Blackrock, and Morgan Stanley, have recently applied for Bitcoin Spot Exchange-Traded Funds (ETFs).  This institutional interest could bring a new wave of optimism to the cryptocurrency market, increasing demand and increasing prices. Bitcoin is facing challenges in its attempt to regain its 50-day moving average (MA) as a support level instead of being another resistance line. As of the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading at $29,200, representing a slight 0.6% decline over the last 24 hours. Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com ]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin (BTC) has been trading in a tight range for quite some time now, with bulls and bears engaged in a tug-of-war over key support and resistance levels. </p>
<p>The recent move above $29,500 has provided some hope for the bulls, but so far, they have been unable to gather enough momentum to push prices higher.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Struggles To Break Above Key Moving Average</h2>
<p><a href="https://twitter.com/MI_Algos/status/1686013278965624832?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">According </a>to Material Indicators, a leading market analysis firm, the key to a bullish breakout in the BTC market is for the coin to print candles above the 100-week moving average (MA). However, BTC has yet to test this level, and bulls have struggled to maintain the current range.</p>
<p>The 50-day MA has been a crucial support level, with BTC testing it for today&#8217;s eighth consecutive day. While the 50-day MA has managed to hold, resistance at $29,500 has been replenishing, posing a challenge for the bulls. </p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large wp-image-545239" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/F2XnxmMWUAA07GL-860x485.jpeg" alt="Bitcoin " width="860" height="485" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/F2XnxmMWUAA07GL-860x485.jpeg 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/F2XnxmMWUAA07GL-460x260.jpeg 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/F2XnxmMWUAA07GL-768x433.jpeg 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/F2XnxmMWUAA07GL-1536x867.jpeg 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/F2XnxmMWUAA07GL-2048x1156.jpeg 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/F2XnxmMWUAA07GL-750x423.jpeg 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/F2XnxmMWUAA07GL-1140x643.jpeg 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/>
<p>If they cannot clear this level, Material Indicators expects a run at the lows with $28,300 as the last line of defense. The big question for BTC investors is whether the coin will bounce from the $28,000 zone or extend to $25,000 and beyond. All of these moves are possible, but the mystery lies in what order and timeline they will play out.</p>

<p>As the market approaches the monthly close, all eyes are on the potential for volatility in the BTC market. Traders and investors closely monitor the price action and indicators to prepare for potential moves.</p>
BTC&#8217;s Store Of Value Narrative Solidified
<p>The recent changes in the structure of Bitcoin&#8217;s trading volume have sparked a debate among cryptocurrency investors and traders. <a href="https://twitter.com/cryptoquant_com/status/1685809330170503169?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">According </a>to Crypto Quant, since January 2023, the Spot vs. Derivatives volume ratio has dropped from 35% to 6%, resulting in a new era of low volatility in the cryptocurrency market.</p>
<p>This decrease in spot volume means that investors are holding onto their Bitcoins instead of selling them, as Bitcoin is now considered a valuable asset, similar to digital gold. </p>
<p>This is seen in the BTC: Binary Coin Days Destroyed (CDD) chart, which shows that since the start of the year, there have been no active sales among the cohort of long-term holders (LTHs).</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large wp-image-545240" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/F2UxgUabsAAO-jU-860x541.jpeg" alt="Bitcoin " width="860" height="541" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/F2UxgUabsAAO-jU-860x541.jpeg 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/F2UxgUabsAAO-jU-460x289.jpeg 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/F2UxgUabsAAO-jU-768x483.jpeg 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/F2UxgUabsAAO-jU-750x472.jpeg 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/F2UxgUabsAAO-jU-1140x717.jpeg 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/F2UxgUabsAAO-jU.jpeg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/>
<p>Moreover, the total Simple Moving Average (SMA)-7d weekly trading volume of Bitcoin across all exchanges has dropped from 2.5 million BTC in March to less than 600 thousand BTC in July, representing a more than 75% reduction over the specified period. </p>
<p>While some may see this trend as a crisis, Crypto Quant believes it is a sign of the cryptocurrency market maturing and becoming more stable and predictable.</p>
<p>However, this trend could lead to significant changes in the Bitcoin market. A reduction in spot volume may result in a reduction in liquidity, which could increase the demand and price of Bitcoin. The market currently lacks a new wave of optimism, and the question is, where will it come from?</p>

<p>The answer may lie in the growing institutional interest in Bitcoin and other cryptocurrencies. Several major financial institutions, such as Fidelity, Blackrock, and Morgan Stanley, have recently applied for Bitcoin Spot Exchange-Traded Funds (ETFs). </p>
<p>This institutional interest could bring a new wave of optimism to the cryptocurrency market, increasing demand and increasing prices.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/XvGNAKZm/" alt="Bitcoin " width="1814" height="858"/>
<p>Bitcoin is facing challenges in its attempt to regain its 50-day moving average (MA) as a support level instead of being another resistance line. As of the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading at $29,200, representing a slight 0.6% decline over the last 24 hours.</p>
<p>Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/iStock-476768648-460x460.jpg" width="460" height="460" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>USDT Issuer Tether Reports A 30% Decline In Profit</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/stablecoin/tether-reports-30-decline-in-profit/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 17:00:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Stablecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[stablecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tether profits]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tether reserves]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=545238</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Stablecoin USDT issuer Tether published its Q2 2023 attestation report on July 31 and according to the report, Tether recorded an “operational profit” of $1 billion in the second quarter, about a 30% decline from its Q1 profit of $1.48 billion. Although its $1 billion “operational profit” represents a decline from the first quarter, there is a 30% increase in comparison with the Q2 of 2022. Tether also disclosed a share buyback amounting to $115 million and its other investments in energy-related initiatives which are financed by some of the profits from Q2.  “The investment in energy-related initiatives is not included in the CRR as these are not considered by Tether as an eligible reserve for the token in circulation, the company clarified. Related Reading: US Presidential Candidate Defends Bitcoin, Calls Out Environmental Critics Tether Sees Increase In Excess Reserves Tether’s excess reserves in the second year of this year increased by $850 million, taking its total excess reserves to around $3.3 billion. These excess reserves are the profits the company doesn’t share as dividends to shareholders. Instead, it holds them to shore up its 100% reserves used in backing all USDT in circulation and maintaining the token’s stability.  The company has explained that keeping an additional 4% of its assets within its reserves is one of its risk management decisions as it aims to protect customers’ funds. It believes this move is necessary and one that other players should emulate, as under-collateralization, brings weakness to the whole system. USDT market cap at $83.8 billion &#124; Source: Market Cap USDT on Tradingview.com Remaining Committed To Transparency In 2021, Tether agreed to release quarterly reports on its reserves for two years as part of its settlement with the authorities. However, the company continues to release these reports as part of its commitment to transparency despite fulfilling its agreement with the authorities earlier this year.  As part of the report, Tether’s CTO stated: Transparency is not just a buzzword for us; it is the cornerstone of our philosophy. We believe that open communication and strong financials foster trust and reliability, and this is what the global community deserves especially in a year devastated by many failures across the banking and crypto industry. Related Reading: Is It A Good Idea To Buy Curve Now? Here’s What This Founder Thinks Tether has faced criticisms in the past, especially concerning its reserves and whether or not the USDT tokens in circulation were 100% backed. However, despite those allegations, USDT has continued to maintain its peg to the US dollar (re-pegging very quickly every time it dropped below a dollar). The USDT token also remains the largest stablecoin with a market cap of $83.8 billion, with its closest rival, Circle’s USDC, boasting a market cap of $26 billion according to data from CoinMarketCap. Featured image from CryptoSlate, chart from Tradingview.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/stablecoin/1-billion-usdt-issuance/?swcfpc=1">Stablecoin USDT issuer</a> Tether published its Q2 2023 attestation <a href="https://tether.to/en/tether-excess-reserves-increase-by-850m-to-reach-3-3b-as-leading-stablecoin-reveals-72-5b-overall-exposure-in-us-t-bills-and-unveils-energy-related-investments/" rel="nofollow">report</a> on July 31 and according to the report, Tether recorded an “operational profit” of $1 billion in the second quarter, about a 30% decline from its Q1 profit of $1.48 billion.</p>
<p>Although its $1 billion “operational profit” represents a decline from the first quarter, there is a 30% increase in comparison with the Q2 of 2022. Tether also disclosed a share buyback amounting to $115 million and its other investments in energy-related initiatives which are financed by some of the profits from Q2. </p>
<p>“The investment in energy-related initiatives is not included in the CRR as these are not considered by Tether as an eligible reserve for the token in circulation, the company clarified.</p>

<h2>Tether Sees Increase In Excess Reserves</h2>
<p>Tether’s excess reserves in the second year of this year increased by $850 million, taking its total excess reserves to around $3.3 billion. These excess reserves are the profits the company doesn’t share as dividends to shareholders. Instead, it holds them to shore up its 100% reserves used in backing all <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/tether-shuffles-the-deck-750-million-usdt-shifted-from-tron-to-ethereum/?swcfpc=1">USDT in circulation</a> and maintaining the token’s stability. </p>
<p>The company has explained that keeping an additional 4% of its assets within its reserves is one of its risk management decisions as it aims to protect customers’ funds. It believes this move is necessary and one that other players should emulate, as under-collateralization, brings weakness to the whole system.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/fhotPPiq/" alt="Tetherr (USDT) market cap chart from Tradingview.com" width="2884" height="1746"/></p>

<h2>Remaining Committed To Transparency</h2>
<p>In 2021, Tether agreed to release quarterly reports on its reserves for two years as part of its settlement with the authorities. However, the company continues to release these reports as part of its commitment to transparency despite fulfilling its agreement with the authorities earlier this year. </p>
<p>As part of the report, Tether’s CTO stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>Transparency is not just a buzzword for us; it is the cornerstone of our philosophy. We believe that open communication and strong financials foster trust and reliability, and this is what the global community deserves especially in a year devastated by many failures across the banking and crypto industry.</p></blockquote>

<p>Tether has faced criticisms in the past, especially concerning its reserves and whether or not the USDT tokens in circulation were 100% backed. However, despite those allegations, USDT has continued to maintain its peg to the US dollar (<a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/tether-usdt-de-pegs-as-crypto-market-stumbles/?swcfpc=1">re-pegging very quickly every time it dropped below a dollar</a>).</p>
<p>The <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/stablecoin/tether-usdt-market-cap-reaches-new-peak-edges-toward-84-billion-mark/?swcfpc=1">USDT token also remains the largest stablecoin</a> with a market cap of $83.8 billion, with its closest rival, Circle’s USDC, boasting a market cap of $26 billion according to data from <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/" rel="nofollow">CoinMarketCap</a>.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Tether-USDT-460x242.png" width="460" height="242" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>US Presidential Candidate Defends Bitcoin, Calls Out Environmental Critics</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/us-presidential-candidate-defends-bitcoin/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 16:00:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin energy usage]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[US presidential candidate]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=545202</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[For an industry that rarely gets mainstream political support, Bitcoin recently received a massive endorsement after Democratic Presidential candidate Robert F. Kennedy spoke out in support of the cryptocurrency. According to RFK, arguments against adopting Bitcoin due to perceived environmental impact are merely a cover to curtail financial freedom.  Responding to the tweet by Feldman, RFK stated that “&#8230; environmental arguments should be used as a smokescreen to curtail freedom to transact.” RFK, who is a holder of BTC, has previously disclosed his intention to return the USD to hard currency backed with assets such as BTC. Bitcoin And The Environment  One of the challenges of Bitcoin adoption is the perceived threat it poses to the environment. According to anti-crypto campaigners and politicians, bitcoin mining is harmful due to its high energy requirement.  Related Reading: Ahead Of The Pack: Binance Moves Forward With New License in Dubai This argument is a prominent position within the political and environmental protection ecosystem, so much so that campaigners like Greenpeace have accused BTC of destroying the planet. However, while Bitcoin mining is energy-intensive, it utilizes more renewable energy presently than ever before.  This position was further reiterated by Daniel Feldman, director of Sangha Systems. According to him, there exists a “symbiotic relationship” between Bitcoin and renewable energy.  Agreeing with the popular Democratic candidate, Feldman noted that bitcoin mining offers a solution to boost the electric grid and limit dependence on fossil fuels. He, however, noted that “most renewable energy sites are not profitable without government subsidies.”  BTC price maintains tight range at $29,450 &#124; Source: BTCUSD on Tradingview.com Subsidies in the form of tax credits generate market distortions and the flow of these credits is managed by banks who are often bailed out by governments during financial crises, the very banks that Bitcoin seeks to free people from. According to Feldman, renewable energy sites experience curtailment and congestion challenges due to the absence of global markets to sell to during demand troughs. BTC solves this challenge by providing a universal market for electricity that will boost investments in renewable energy projects. A Look Into BTC Energy Usage Renewable energy arguments are popular within the green energy industry as they continually seek the flexibility offered by crypto mining operations. However, they are still faced with serious opposition from the media and the political establishment, who believe BTC mining will boil the planet.  Related Reading: Here’s How Long The Majority Of New Ethereum Wallets Are Used Before They’re Dumped According to data obtained from Cambridge University, it is estimated that global BTC mining activities are currently pegged at 137 TW/h (terawatt hours) per year.  This figure surpasses the energy usage of countries such as Ukraine, which utilizes 134 TW/h. In contrast, the electricity distribution and transmission losses in the US are sufficient to power BTC 1.5 times with 206 TW/h per year. Featured image from Sky News, chart from Tradingview.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>For an industry that rarely gets mainstream political support, Bitcoin recently received a massive endorsement after Democratic Presidential candidate Robert F. Kennedy <a href="https://twitter.com/RobertKennedyJr/status/1685776784028028928?s=20" rel="nofollow">spoke</a> out in support of the cryptocurrency. According to RFK, arguments against adopting Bitcoin due to perceived environmental impact are merely a cover to curtail financial freedom. </p>
<p>Responding to the tweet by Feldman, RFK <a href="https://twitter.com/RobertKennedyJr/status/1685776784028028928" rel="nofollow">stated </a>that “&#8230; environmental arguments should be used as a smokescreen to curtail freedom to transact.” RFK, who is a holder of BTC, has previously <a href="https://beincrypto.com/presidential-candidate-rfk-jr-dollars-bitcoin/" rel="nofollow">disclosed</a> his intention to return the USD to hard currency backed with assets such as BTC.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin And The Environment </h2>
<p>One of the challenges of Bitcoin adoption is the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-mining-difficulty-hits-all-time-high-for-the-4th-time-in-2023-heres-why/?swcfpc=1">perceived threat it poses to the environment</a>. According to anti-crypto campaigners and politicians, bitcoin mining is harmful due to its high energy requirement. </p>

<p>This argument is a prominent position within the political and environmental protection ecosystem, so much so that campaigners like Greenpeace have accused BTC of destroying the planet. However, while Bitcoin mining is energy-intensive, it utilizes more <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/how-bitcoin-mining-mitigate-renewable-energy-waste/" rel="nofollow">renewable energy</a> presently than ever before. </p>
<p>This position was further reiterated by Daniel Feldman, director of Sangha Systems. According to him, there exists a “symbiotic relationship” between Bitcoin and renewable energy. </p>
<p>Agreeing with the popular Democratic candidate, Feldman noted that bitcoin mining offers a solution to boost the electric grid and limit dependence on fossil fuels. He, however, noted that “most renewable energy sites are not profitable without government subsidies.” </p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/HhxCu8yn/" alt="Bitcoin (BTC) price chart from Tradingview.com" width="2884" height="1746"/></p>

<p>Subsidies in the form of tax credits generate market distortions and the flow of these credits is managed by banks who are often bailed out by governments during financial crises, the very banks that Bitcoin seeks to free people from.</p>
<p>According to Feldman, renewable energy sites experience curtailment and congestion challenges due to the absence of global markets to sell to during demand troughs. BTC solves this challenge by <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/calls-for-tesla-to-resume-bitcoin-payments-as-mining-reaches-57-renewable-energy/?swcfpc=1">providing a universal market for electricity </a>that will boost investments in renewable energy projects.</p>
<h2>A Look Into BTC Energy Usage</h2>
<p>Renewable energy arguments are popular within the green energy industry as they continually seek the flexibility offered by crypto mining operations. However, they are still faced with serious opposition from the media and the political establishment, who believe BTC mining will boil the planet. </p>

<p>According to data obtained from <a href="https://ccaf.io/cbnsi/cbeci/comparisons" rel="nofollow">Cambridge University</a>, it is estimated that global BTC mining activities are currently pegged at 137 TW/h (terawatt hours) per year. </p>
<p>This figure surpasses the energy usage of countries such as Ukraine, which utilizes 134 TW/h. In contrast, the electricity distribution and transmission losses in the US are sufficient to power BTC 1.5 times with 206 TW/h per year.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Robert-F-Kennedy-Jr-bitcoin-460x259.jpeg" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Breaking: HEX Token Plummets 25% Following SEC Lawsuit Against Founder Richard Heart</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/breaking-news-ticker/breaking-hex-token-plummets-25-following-sec-lawsuit-against-founder-richard-heart/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reynaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 15:20:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Breaking News Ticker]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[HEX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[HEXUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=545232</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) filed a lawsuit against Richard “Heart” Schueler and crypto projects HEX, PULSECHAIN, and PULSEX. According to a document filed with a court for the Eastern District of New York and shared on X by economist Alex Krüeger, the regulator is violating U.S. securities laws. Related Reading: Is Another Bitcoin Rally Coming Soon? This Pattern May Say So As of this writing, HEX is feeling the heat from the lawsuit. The token plummeted over 11% in today’s trade session alone as a direct impact of this development. It continues a downside trend that worsened over the past two weeks when the cryptocurrency saw a 23% loss. SEC Fails With XRP But Goes After HEX Per the document, the regulator claims that Richard Heart raised over $1 billion by allegedly offering unregistered security, the token HEX. The crypto founder supposedly offered the token in December 2019 and for the following three years to “retail investors in the U.S. and abroad.” The SEC claims that Heart operates via PulseChain and PulseX, part of the scheme that allegedly allows him to raise $1 billion from investors. Via these platforms, the regulator argues, Heart made “grandiose” promises of wealth to his investors. Furthermore, the Commission claims that while Heart publicly spoke about supporting free speech, he supposedly purchased “luxury goods” by taking money from his investors. In that sense, the SEC claims that the crypto investor misappropriated his investors’ assets and allegedly defrauded investors. The regulator placed a special focus on HEX’s staking mechanism, its “locked up” periods, and how Heart allegedly manipulated the token’s supply by “recycling transactions.” The document stated: Between December 2019 and November 2020, Heart, via the Hex public wallet address, accepted more than 2.3 million ether (“ETH”), putatively from investors, worth more than $678 million at the time of deposits (…). It appears that 94-97% of these ETH deposits, however, were “recycling” transactions directed by Heart or other insiders, which enabled Heart or other insiders to gain control of a large number of Hex tokens (…). Consensus In The Crypto Community The U.S. SEC is coming out of a major loss after a court ruled out against their claims in the case versus payment company Ripple and its executives. The regulator stated that the company offered unregistered securities. However, unlike the Ripple and XRP case, the crypto community is taking the SEC’s side and believes the regulator is on the right track. Heart has been a controversial figure for years in the nascent industry. Bloomberg Intelligence’s James Seyffart stated the following regarding the case: I may have been cheering for ripple to win their case despite not really liking the project (and honestly thinking it had many security-like traits). But I will be 100% pro SEC in this case. This is the type of project the SEC should have gone after years ago. Related Reading: Dogecoin Price Prospects: Can The Memecoin Climb To The $0.1 Level? It remains to be seen if the regulator will score another negative result, but many in the crypto community are siding with the SEC. Cover image from Unsplash, chart from Tradingview]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) filed a lawsuit against Richard “Heart” Schueler and crypto projects HEX, PULSECHAIN, and PULSEX. According to a document filed with a court for the Eastern District of New York and <a href="https://twitter.com/krugermacro/status/1686023344947101696/photo/1" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">shared</a> on X by economist Alex Krüeger, the regulator is violating U.S. securities laws. </strong></p>

<p>As of this writing, HEX is feeling the heat from the lawsuit. The token plummeted over 11% in today’s trade session alone as a direct impact of this development. It continues a downside trend that worsened over the past two weeks when the cryptocurrency saw a 23% loss.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-545235 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/hex-hexusdt-richard-heart-860x410.png" alt="hex hexusdt richard heart" width="860" height="410" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/hex-hexusdt-richard-heart-860x410.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/hex-hexusdt-richard-heart-460x219.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/hex-hexusdt-richard-heart-768x366.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/hex-hexusdt-richard-heart-1536x732.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/hex-hexusdt-richard-heart-750x358.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/hex-hexusdt-richard-heart-1140x543.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/hex-hexusdt-richard-heart.png 1758w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/>
<h2>SEC Fails With XRP But Goes After HEX</h2>
<p>Per the document, the regulator claims that Richard Heart raised over $1 billion by allegedly offering unregistered security, the token HEX. The crypto founder supposedly offered the token in December 2019 and for the following three years to “retail investors in the U.S. and abroad.”</p>
<p>The SEC claims that Heart operates via PulseChain and PulseX, part of the scheme that allegedly allows him to raise $1 billion from investors. Via these platforms, the regulator argues, Heart made “grandiose” promises of wealth to his investors.</p>
<p>Furthermore, the Commission claims that while Heart publicly spoke about supporting free speech, he supposedly purchased “luxury goods” by taking money from his investors. In that sense, the SEC claims that the crypto investor misappropriated his investors’ assets and allegedly defrauded investors.</p>
<p>The regulator placed a special focus on HEX’s staking mechanism, its “locked up” periods, and how Heart allegedly manipulated the token’s supply by “recycling transactions.” The document stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>Between December 2019 and November 2020, Heart, via the Hex public wallet address, accepted more than 2.3 million ether (“ETH”), putatively from investors, worth more than $678 million at the time of deposits (…). It appears that 94-97% of these ETH deposits, however, were “recycling” transactions directed by Heart or other insiders, which enabled Heart or other insiders to gain control of a large number of Hex tokens (…).</p></blockquote>
Consensus In The Crypto Community
<p>The U.S. SEC is coming out of a major loss after a court ruled out against their claims in the case versus payment company Ripple and its executives. The regulator stated that the company offered unregistered securities.</p>
<p>However, unlike the Ripple and XRP case, the crypto community is taking the SEC’s side and believes the regulator is on the right track. Heart has been a controversial figure for years in the nascent industry.</p>
<p>Bloomberg Intelligence’s James Seyffart <a href="https://twitter.com/JSeyff/status/1686022628643901440" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">stated</a> the following regarding the case:</p>
<blockquote><p>I may have been cheering for ripple to win their case despite not really liking the project (and honestly thinking it had many security-like traits). But I will be 100% pro SEC in this case. This is the type of project the SEC should have gone after years ago.</p></blockquote>

<p>It remains to be seen if the regulator will score another negative result, but many in the crypto community are siding with the SEC.</p>
<p>Cover image from Unsplash, chart from Tradingview</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/HEX-HEXUSDT-Richard-Heart-460x298.jpg" width="460" height="298" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Is It A Good Idea To Buy Curve Now? Here&#8217;s What This Founder Thinks</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/defi/is-it-a-good-idea-to-buy-curve-now/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 15:00:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[DeFi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CRV]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CRV Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CRVUSD CRVUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Curve protocol]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=545203</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[In the wake of a massive exploit, the price of the Curve (CRV) token has declined drastically, recording double-digit losses in the last day. This has led to what some would call an opportunity to buy cheap coins and Matrixport and Bitdeer founder Jihan Wu is one of the believers. A Good Time To Buy Curve (CRV)? Jihan Wu recently tweeted that he bought the CRV dip. According to Wu, he remains a strong believer in the token because of its future applications. Wu’s tweet comes at a time when Decentralized Finance (DeFi) platform Curve DAO’s native token CRV has been down by more than 12% in the last 24 hours. This dip came following an exploit in some of Curve’s stablecoin pools.  Related Reading: Here’s How Long The Majority Of New Ethereum Wallets Are Used Before They’re Dumped The exploit on the protocol reportedly occurred due to a bug in the Vyper programming language, which is used to power part of the DEX’s ecosystem.  Despite this occurrence, Wu believes that this is a good time to invest in the CRV tokens as these tokens will play a significant role in the coming RWA (Real World Assets) wave in reference to the tokenization of physical assets. “In the coming RWA wave, $crv is one of the most important infrastructures. I have BTFD. NFA,” the founder said in the tweet. Without a doubt, the tokenized industry is growing and boasts immense potential. Last year, a World Economic Forum survey projected the tokenized assets industry to account for almost 10% of the global GDP by 2027.  The tokenization of real-world assets will involve bringing physical assets like houses, arts, and precious metals on-chain. This will undoubtedly provide easier access and promote fractional ownership of these assets.  CRV price declines over 14% following exploit &#124; Source: CRVUSD on Tradingview.com As Wu has highlighted, DeFi protocols like Curve and tokens like CRV will play an integral role in facilitating transactions involving the transfer and trade of these tokenized assets.  DeFi Security Remains A Stumbling Block The several exploits on DeFi protocols continue to remain a huge problem in the DeFi ecosystem and something which many consider a stumbling block to the wider adoption of DEXs over CEXs by many crypto users. Recently, Curve Finance’s Omnipool platform, Conic Finance, suffered an exploit that resulted in the hacker stealing over $3 million in Ether. Related Reading: Ahead Of The Pack: Binance Moves Forward With New License in Dubai A report from Web3 portfolio app De.Fi found that over $204 million was lost to hacks and exploits in the DeFi ecosystem in Q2 of 2023 alone. The number of incidents (117) in Q2 this year translated to an “almost 7 times” increase in comparison with Q2 of 2022 (17 incidents).  According to the report, over $665 million have been lost to such exploits this year. And these breaches further highlight the need for DeFi protocols to implement enhanced security mechanisms on their platforms. Featured image from The Coin Republic, chart from Tradingview.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In the wake of a massive exploit, the price of the Curve (CRV) token has declined drastically, recording double-digit losses in the last day. This has led to what some would call an opportunity to buy cheap coins and Matrixport and Bitdeer founder Jihan Wu is one of the believers.</p>
<h2>A Good Time To Buy Curve (CRV)?</h2>
<p>Jihan Wu recently <a href="https://twitter.com/JihanWu/status/1685869881852624896?s=20" rel="nofollow">tweeted</a> that he bought the CRV dip. According to Wu, he remains a strong believer in the token because of its future applications.</p>
<p>Wu’s tweet comes at a time when Decentralized Finance (DeFi) platform Curve DAO’s native token CRV has been down by more than 12% in the last 24 hours. This dip came following an exploit in some of Curve’s stablecoin pools. </p>

<p>The <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/north-korean-hackers-involved-in-euler-finance-exploit-chainalysis/?swcfpc=1">exploit</a> on the protocol reportedly occurred due to a bug in the Vyper programming language, which is used to power part of the DEX’s ecosystem. </p>
<p>Despite this occurrence, Wu believes that this is a good time to invest in the CRV tokens as these tokens will play a significant role in the coming RWA (Real World Assets) wave in reference to the tokenization of physical assets.</p>
<p>“In the coming RWA wave, $crv is one of the most important infrastructures. I have BTFD. NFA,” the founder said in the tweet.</p>
<p>Without a doubt, the tokenized industry is growing and boasts immense potential. Last year, a World Economic Forum survey <a href="https://thetokenizer.io/2022/08/30/mapping-the-asset-tokenization-industry/" rel="nofollow">projected</a> the tokenized assets industry to account for almost 10% of the global GDP by 2027. </p>
<p>The tokenization of real-world assets will involve bringing physical assets like houses, arts, and precious metals on-chain. This will undoubtedly provide easier access and promote fractional ownership of these assets. </p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/KzDTSJUN/" alt="Curve (CRV) price chart from Tradingview.com" width="2884" height="1746"/></p>

<p>As Wu has highlighted, DeFi protocols like Curve and tokens like CRV will play an integral role in facilitating transactions involving the transfer and trade of these tokenized assets. </p>
<h2><b>DeFi Security Remains A Stumbling Block</b></h2>
<p>The several exploits on DeFi protocols continue to remain a huge problem in the DeFi ecosystem and something which many consider a stumbling block to the wider adoption of DEXs over CEXs by many crypto users. Recently, Curve Finance’s Omnipool platform, Conic Finance, suffered an <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/defi-hackers-pilfer-3-26m-from-protocol/" rel="nofollow">exploit</a> that resulted in the hacker stealing over $3 million in Ether.</p>

<p>A <a href="https://de.fi/blog/de-fi-rekt-report-over-204m-lost-in-q2-2023" rel="nofollow">report</a> from Web3 portfolio app De.Fi found that over $204 million was lost to hacks and exploits in the DeFi ecosystem in Q2 of 2023 alone. The number of incidents (117) in Q2 this year translated to an “almost 7 times” increase in comparison with Q2 of 2022 (17 incidents). </p>
<p>According to the report, over $665 million have been lost to such exploits this year. And these breaches further highlight the need for DeFi protocols to implement enhanced security mechanisms on their platforms.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Curve-CRV-token-460x259.jpeg" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Is Another Bitcoin Rally Coming Soon? This Pattern May Say So</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/is-another-bitcoin-rally-coming-soon-this-pattern-may-say-so/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hououin Kyouma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 13:40:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin rally]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[stablecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stablecoin Sharks & Whales]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stablecoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stables]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=545146</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[On-chain data shows a pattern in the stablecoin shark and whale holdings that may suggest the Bitcoin rally could make a return in the near future. Stablecoin Sharks &#38; Whales Have Been Accumulating Recently According to data from the on-chain analytics firm Santiment, the sharks and whales of the major stablecoins have been increasing their reserves while Bitcoin has been struggling recently. The &#8220;sharks&#8221; and &#8220;whales&#8221; are two of the largest cohorts in the sector, with investors belonging to the former holding at least $100,000 and at most $1 million worth of the asset, while the latter has wallet balances in the $1 million to $10 million range. Due to such large holdings, these investors can potentially move around a large number of coins at once, something that can make them influential entities in the market. In the context of the current discussion, the sharks and whales of stablecoins are of interest. In particular, the four largest players in the market are of relevance here: Tether (USDT), USD Coin (USDC), Binance USD (BUSD), and Dai (DAI). Santiment has used its &#8220;Supply Distribution&#8221; metric to track the holdings of these humongous holders and this indicator tells us about the percentage of the supply that each group in the market is holding right now. Here is a chart that shows the trend in this metric specifically for the sharks and whales of the top 4 stablecoins in the sector: The metrics appear to have been going up in recent days &#124; Source: Santiment on Twitter As displayed in the above graph, the holdings of these stablecoin sharks and whales have been on the rise recently. Interestingly, while this trend has formed, the price of Bitcoin has dipped below the $30,000 level. A similar pattern in the supply held by these large investors had also formed last month, as these investors had been buying more stablecoins, while BTC had been on a decline. What followed this period of accumulation back then was a sharp Bitcoin rally that had taken the cryptocurrency&#8217;s price above the $30,000 level. An explanation of this curious trend may lie in what the holdings of these large stablecoin holders signify. Generally, these investors opt for stables whenever they want to exit volatile assets such as BTC. Related Reading: Stanford MBA Explains Why Next Bitcoin Cycle Could Be “Bigger” Such holders, however, usually only seek to temporarily take shelter in these dollar-tied tokens, because if they wanted to stay away from the sector for extended periods, they would have exited through other means like fiat. Thus, these investors would eventually shift their stablecoins into Bitcoin and others again, and with this exchange, provide a bullish boost to their prices. This is why the supply of these sharks and whales may be looked at as the available buying pressure that these humongous investors can put on the asset at any point they want. From the chart, it&#8217;s visible that the BTC rally above $30,000 didn&#8217;t actually kick off from new money being pumped back into the asset by the sharks and whales, but rather the conversions that they made back into the asset, as their holdings decreased while the rally happened. Related Reading: Bitcoin Miner Reserve Rising: Good News For BTC Bulls? As the large investors of the major stables have again been accumulating recently, it&#8217;s possible that Bitcoin could see a bullish effect from this down the road once more, although it&#8217;s uncertain how long it may be before these investors deploy their stablecoins back into the market. Bitcoin Price At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading around $29,300, up 1% in the last week. BTC has stagnated since the decline &#124; Source: BTCUSD on TradingView Featured image from Kanchanara on Unsplash.com, charts from TradingView.com, Santiment.net]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On-chain data shows a pattern in the stablecoin shark and whale holdings that may suggest the Bitcoin rally could make a return in the near future.</p>
<h2>Stablecoin Sharks &amp; Whales Have Been Accumulating Recently</h2>
<p>According to data from the on-chain analytics firm <a href="https://twitter.com/santimentfeed/status/1685895040558899200" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Santiment</a>, the sharks and whales of the major <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/binance/binance-rolls-out-zero-fee-stablecoin-but-hits-pause-soon-after-heres-why/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">stablecoins</a> have been increasing their reserves while Bitcoin has been struggling recently.</p>
<p>The &#8220;sharks&#8221; and &#8220;whales&#8221; are two of the largest cohorts in the sector, with investors belonging to the former holding at least $100,000 and at most $1 million worth of the asset, while the latter has wallet balances in the $1 million to $10 million range.</p>
<p>Due to such large holdings, these investors can potentially move around a large number of coins at once, something that can make them influential entities in the market.</p>
<p>In the context of the current discussion, the sharks and whales of stablecoins are of interest. In particular, the four largest players in the market are of relevance here: Tether (USDT), USD Coin (USDC), Binance USD (BUSD), and Dai (DAI).</p>
<p>Santiment has used its &#8220;<a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-sharks-continue-accumulation-whales-stagnate/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Supply Distribution</a>&#8221; metric to track the holdings of these humongous holders and this indicator tells us about the percentage of the supply that each group in the market is holding right now.</p>
<p>Here is a chart that shows the trend in this metric specifically for the sharks and whales of the top 4 stablecoins in the sector:</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone aligncenter" src="https://pbs.twimg.com/media/F2V_0vHbUAAiuuV?format=jpg&amp;name=4096x4096" alt="Stablecoin Sharks &amp; Whales" width="2796" height="1777"/></p>

<p>As displayed in the above graph, the holdings of these stablecoin sharks and whales have been on the rise recently. Interestingly, while this trend has formed, the price of Bitcoin has dipped below the $30,000 level.</p>
<p>A similar pattern in the supply held by these large investors had also formed last month, as these investors had been buying more stablecoins, while BTC had been on a decline.</p>
<p>What followed this period of <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/how-did-shiba-inu-price-react-to-3-trillion-shib-investor-accumulation/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">accumulation</a> back then was a sharp Bitcoin rally that had taken the cryptocurrency&#8217;s price above the $30,000 level.</p>
<p>An explanation of this curious trend may lie in what the holdings of these large stablecoin holders signify. Generally, these investors opt for stables whenever they want to exit volatile assets such as BTC.</p>

<p>Such holders, however, usually only seek to temporarily take shelter in these dollar-tied tokens, because if they wanted to stay away from the sector for extended periods, they would have exited through other means like fiat.</p>
<p>Thus, these investors would eventually shift their stablecoins into Bitcoin and others again, and with this exchange, provide a bullish boost to their prices. This is why the supply of these sharks and whales may be looked at as the available buying pressure that these humongous investors can put on the asset at any point they want.</p>
<p>From the chart, it&#8217;s visible that the BTC rally above $30,000 didn&#8217;t actually kick off from new money being pumped back into the asset by the sharks and whales, but rather the conversions that they made back into the asset, as their holdings decreased while the rally happened.</p>

<p>As the large investors of the major stables have again been accumulating recently, it&#8217;s possible that Bitcoin could see a bullish effect from this down the road once more, although it&#8217;s uncertain how long it may be before these investors deploy their stablecoins back into the market.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Price</h2>
<p>At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading around $29,300, up 1% in the last week.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium aligncenter" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/qJ4QtnYT/" alt="Bitcoin Price Chart" width="1534" height="877"/></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/kanchanara-tgHk-ipTE2w-unsplash-460x306.jpg" width="460" height="306" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dogecoin Price Prospects: Can The Memecoin Climb To The $0.1 Level?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/can-dogecoin-hit-0-1-level/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 12:30:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Doge price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[meme coins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price action]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=545170</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Dogecoin (DOGE) has been witnessing a notable recovery in recent days, and technical analysis suggests that an ascending trendline is providing significant support to this upward movement.  An ascending trendline represents a price chart that connects a series of higher lows over time. It acts as a visual guide to tracking the price movements of an asset, indicating a bullish sentiment in the market.  Related Reading: XRP Struggles In Its Journey To $1: Market Observers Share Contrasting Views As of the latest data from CoinGecko, Dogecoin price stands at $0.079, experiencing a minor 24-hour slump of 0.9%. However, it has still managed an impressive seven-day rally of 7.2%, hinting at the potential for further gains. Source: Coingecko Understanding DOGE’s Ascending Trendline An ascending trendline is essential for traders and analysts as it helps them visualize an asset&#8217;s market sentiment and potential price levels. When the asset price approaches the ascending trendline, it indicates a likely level of support, and if the price breaks above the trendline, it suggests an uptrend resumption. With sustained buying pressure, DOGE buyers have the potential to re-challenge the last swing high at $0.083. A bullish breakout for DOGE above this resistance level would hint at the resumption of the uptrend, potentially pushing the meme-inspired cryptocurrency&#8217;s market value higher by 21.7% to reach $0.095. As of today, the market cap of Dogecoin reached $11.1 billion. Chart: TradingView.com Positive Indicators On Dogecoin Daily Chart Meanwhile, several indicators signal bullish momentum, as a recent price analysis notes. The Exponential Moving Average (EMA) Ribbon, a cluster of EMAs that smooth out price data, displayed a bullish crossover, further reinforcing the upward momentum. Moreover, the Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD) indicator showed that the bulls have the upperhand, a sign that an upward trend may be in the pipeline. DOGE&#8217;s Money Flow Index (MFI), which measures money flow into or out of an asset, also increased. This development is favorable for buyers as it suggests that more capital is entering the DOGE market, supporting its recent price gains. Dogecoin price action in the last week. Source: CoinMarketCap DOGE Outlook Dogecoin&#8217;s current recovery is supported by an ascending trendline, indicating a positive market sentiment among buyers. With several bullish indicators on the daily chart, including the EMA Ribbon, MACD, and MFI, the potential for an uptrend resumption and a push toward $0.095 is plausible.  Related Reading: Shibarium Hype: Shiba Inu Whales Boost Appetite, Snag 1 Trillion SHIB Tokens However, as with any investment, caution should be exercised, and investors must conduct their research and consider various factors before making any decisions. The crypto market can be volatile, and prices are subject to rapid changes. (This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk). Featured image from Medium]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Dogecoin (DOGE) has been witnessing a notable recovery in recent days, and technical analysis suggests that an ascending trendline is providing significant support to this upward movement. </p>
<p>An ascending trendline represents a price chart that connects a series of higher lows over time. It acts as a visual guide to tracking the price movements of an asset, indicating a bullish sentiment in the market. </p>

<p>As of the latest data from <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/dogecoin" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">CoinGecko</a>, Dogecoin price stands at $0.079, experiencing a minor 24-hour slump of 0.9%. However, it has still managed an impressive seven-day rally of 7.2%, hinting at the potential for further gains.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-545193" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-198.png" alt="" width="1258" height="63" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-198.png 1258w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-198-460x23.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-198-860x43.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-198-768x38.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-198-750x38.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-198-1140x57.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1258px) 100vw, 1258px"/></p>

<h2><strong>Understanding DOGE’s Ascending Trendline</strong></h2>
<p>An ascending trendline is essential for traders and analysts as it helps them visualize an asset&#8217;s market sentiment and potential price levels. When the asset price approaches the ascending trendline, it indicates a likely level of support, and if the price breaks above the trendline, it suggests an uptrend resumption.</p>
<p>With sustained buying pressure, DOGE buyers have the potential to re-challenge the last swing high at $0.083. A <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://coingape.com/markets/is-dogecoin-price-ready-to-reclaim-0-1/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">bullish breakout for DOGE</a> above this resistance level would hint at the resumption of the uptrend, potentially pushing the meme-inspired cryptocurrency&#8217;s market value higher by 21.7% to reach $0.095.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/dcAGxL4n/" width="1835" height="893"/></p>

<h2><strong>Positive Indicators On Dogecoin Daily Chart</strong></h2>
<p>Meanwhile, several indicators signal bullish momentum, as a recent <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://ambcrypto.com/reasons-why-shiba-inu-dogecoin-are-decoupling-from-the-market/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">price analysis</a> notes. The Exponential Moving Average (EMA) Ribbon, a cluster of EMAs that smooth out price data, displayed a bullish crossover, further reinforcing the upward momentum.</p>
<p>Moreover, the Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD) indicator showed that the bulls have the upperhand, a sign that an upward trend may be in the pipeline.</p>
<p>DOGE&#8217;s Money Flow Index (MFI), which measures money flow into or out of an asset, also increased. This development is favorable for buyers as it suggests that more capital is entering the DOGE market, supporting its recent price gains.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-545195 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-199-860x374.png" alt="" width="860" height="374" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-199-860x374.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-199-460x200.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-199-768x334.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-199-750x326.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-199.png 1036w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/></p>

<strong>DOGE Outlook</strong>
<p>Dogecoin&#8217;s current recovery is supported by an ascending trendline, indicating a positive market sentiment among buyers. With several bullish indicators on the daily chart, including the EMA Ribbon, MACD, and MFI, the potential for an uptrend resumption and a push toward $0.095 is plausible. </p>

<p>However, as with any investment, caution should be exercised, and investors must conduct their research and consider various factors before making any decisions. The crypto market can be volatile, and prices are subject to rapid changes.</p>
<p><em>(This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk).</em></p>
<p><em>Featured image from Medium</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a--460x288.jpg" width="460" height="288" />	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
