<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
>

<channel>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.newsbtc.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<description>Bitcoin &#38; Cryptocurrency News Today</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 23:24:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Exodus: Exchange Balances Plummet To Lowest Levels Since 2018</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-exodus-exchange-balances-plummet-to-lowest-levels-since-2018/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 03:00:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin whales]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=544181</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) continues to dominate the cryptocurrency market, as exchange balances have dropped to levels last seen in early 2018. This signals a growing trend of investors moving their Bitcoin holdings to cold storage, which is considered to be more secure.  According to a recent report by Bitfinex, while some of this decline in exchange balances may be attributed to the usage of decentralized exchanges and funds not covered in the data, the overarching trend appears to be a widespread movement of people withdrawing their Bitcoin from exchanges. Bitcoin-Backed Funds Lead Crypto Investment Surge  This trend is also reflected in the recent data from CoinShares, which shows that traditional fund investors are demonstrating a renewed interest in Bitcoin.  Crypto-backed investment funds saw a net inflow of $137 million last week, with a staggering 99 percent of this sum directed toward Bitcoin-backed funds.  Related Reading: Elon Musk Incorporates Dogecoin Symbol In Twitter Bio, Triggering 5% Increase In Price According to Bitfinex, this marks the fourth consecutive week of gross inflows into crypto funds, amassing a total of $742 million over the period, representing the largest run of inflows since the final quarter of 2021. The sustained inflows into Bitcoin-backed funds indicate strong investor confidence in the asset, despite the volatility inherent in the crypto market. Additionally, the outflows from short-Bitcoin funds reinforce the bullish sentiment for the BTC price among investors, which has now been in a tight range for months.  This data can thus be used as a proxy for institutional investor bias that the price will break out of this range toward the upside. Meanwhile, Ethereum funds were the only other category to see outflows last week, losing $1.6 million on a net basis. Altcoin funds, on the other hand, recorded slight inflows, with the largest going to multi-asset funds, followed by funds backed by Solana&#8217;s SOL token and Polygon&#8217;s MATIC.  Overall, this data paints a clear picture of Bitcoin&#8217;s continued dominance in the crypto market. While altcoins are making their presence felt, Bitcoin remains the preferred asset for traditional fund investors.  The sustained inflows into Bitcoin-backed funds suggest that investors have confidence in the asset&#8217;s long-term growth potential, despite the short-term volatility in the crypto market.  BTC Whales Increased Activity Indicates Bullish Market Sentiment According to a report by Glassnode, whales, or entities holding 1,000 or more BTC, have been making significant moves in the cryptocurrency market, with whale inflows to exchanges being historically large and accounting for 41% of the total. The dominance of whale inflow volumes to exchanges is significant, with over 82% of whale inflows destined for Binance, the largest exchange in the industry. This trend highlights the importance of the role played by whales in the cryptocurrency market, as their activity can have a significant impact on the price and overall sentiment of Bitcoin. While the report notes that many of these active whale entities are classified as short-term holders, with notable activity around local market peaks and troughs, it also highlights the long-term behavior of whales.  Related Reading: Russian Introduces A Third Form Of Currency As Putin Signs Digital Ruble Into Law Glassnode&#8217;s Trend Accumulation Score by Cohort shows that the smallest entities with less than 100 BTC have slowed down their spending over the last month.  On the other hand, the whale subdivisions with more than 1,000 BTC demonstrated divergent behavior, with those holding more than 10,000 BTC distributing and those holding between 1,000 and 10,000 BTC accumulating at a significantly higher rate. This behavior suggests that whales are actively reshuffling their holdings, moving funds internally between entities. While this can have short-term implications for the market, it also highlights the long-term potential for Bitcoin to remain a valuable asset for investors. Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com ]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin (BTC) continues to dominate the cryptocurrency market, as exchange balances have dropped to levels last seen in early 2018. This signals a growing trend of investors moving their Bitcoin holdings to cold storage, which is considered to be more secure. </p>
<p>According to a recent <a href="https://blog.bitfinex.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitfinex-Alpha-64.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">report</a> by Bitfinex, while some of this decline in exchange balances may be attributed to the usage of decentralized exchanges and funds not covered in the data, the overarching trend appears to be a widespread movement of people withdrawing their Bitcoin from exchanges.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin-Backed Funds Lead Crypto Investment Surge </h2>
<p>This trend is also reflected in the recent data from CoinShares, which shows that traditional fund investors are demonstrating a renewed interest in Bitcoin. </p>
<img decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-544182" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot_28.jpg" alt="Bitcoin " width="741" height="437" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot_28.jpg 741w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot_28-460x271.jpg 460w" sizes="(max-width: 741px) 100vw, 741px" loading="lazy"/>
<p>Crypto-backed investment funds saw a net inflow of $137 million last week, with a staggering 99 percent of this sum directed toward Bitcoin-backed funds. </p>

<p>According to Bitfinex, this marks the fourth consecutive week of gross inflows into crypto funds, amassing a total of $742 million over the period, representing the largest run of inflows since the final quarter of 2021.</p>
<p>The sustained inflows into Bitcoin-backed funds indicate strong investor confidence in the asset, despite the volatility inherent in the crypto market. Additionally, the outflows from short-Bitcoin funds reinforce the bullish sentiment for the BTC price among investors, which has now been in a tight range for months. </p>
<p>This data can thus be used as a proxy for institutional investor bias that the price will break out of this range toward the upside.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, Ethereum funds were the only other category to see outflows last week, losing $1.6 million on a net basis. Altcoin funds, on the other hand, recorded slight inflows, with the largest going to multi-asset funds, followed by funds backed by Solana&#8217;s SOL token and Polygon&#8217;s MATIC. </p>
<p>Overall, this data paints a clear picture of Bitcoin&#8217;s continued dominance in the crypto market. While altcoins are making their presence felt, Bitcoin remains the preferred asset for traditional fund investors. </p>
<p>The sustained inflows into Bitcoin-backed funds suggest that investors have confidence in the asset&#8217;s long-term growth potential, despite the short-term volatility in the crypto market. </p>
BTC Whales Increased Activity Indicates Bullish Market Sentiment
<p>According to a <a href="https://insights.glassnode.com/the-week-onchain-week-30-2023/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">report</a> by Glassnode, whales, or entities holding 1,000 or more BTC, have been making significant moves in the cryptocurrency market, with whale inflows to exchanges being historically large and accounting for 41% of the total.</p>
<p>The dominance of whale inflow volumes to exchanges is significant, with over 82% of whale inflows destined for Binance, the largest exchange in the industry. This trend highlights the importance of the role played by whales in the cryptocurrency market, as their activity can have a significant impact on the price and overall sentiment of Bitcoin.</p>
<p>While the report notes that many of these active whale entities are classified as short-term holders, with notable activity around local market peaks and troughs, it also highlights the long-term behavior of whales. </p>

<p>Glassnode&#8217;s Trend Accumulation Score by Cohort shows that the smallest entities with less than 100 BTC have slowed down their spending over the last month. </p>
<p>On the other hand, the whale subdivisions with more than 1,000 BTC demonstrated divergent behavior, with those holding more than 10,000 BTC distributing and those holding between 1,000 and 10,000 BTC accumulating at a significantly higher rate.</p>
<p>This behavior suggests that whales are actively reshuffling their holdings, moving funds internally between entities. While this can have short-term implications for the market, it also highlights the long-term potential for Bitcoin to remain a valuable asset for investors.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/flOdP5Mc/" alt="Bitcoin " width="1814" height="858"/>
<p>Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/iStock-1188004097-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fidelity Backs Ethereum: Wall Street&#8217;s Biggest Players Bet On Crypto&#8217;s Number 2</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/fidelity-backs-ethereum-wall-streets-biggest-players-bet-on-cryptos-number-2/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 02:00:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=544185</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Fidelity, a leading financial services provider, has recently released a report on Ethereum (ETH) that sheds light on some key metrics to watch for the cryptocurrency in the coming months.  The report highlights several important indicators, including the 50-day and 200-day moving averages (MA), the realized price, the Net Unrealized Profit/Loss (NUPL) ratio, Market Value to Realized Value (MVRV) Z-Score, percent in profit, and the Pi Cycle indicators, all of which can provide valuable insights into market sentiment and potential price movements. Ethereum Holds Strong Above Key Support Levels Per the report, Ethereum has remained above key support levels, with the realized price serving as a strong support level since January 10th.  Additionally, the NUPL ratio suggests that Ethereum is currently in a neutral zone, while the MVRV Z-Score indicates that the cryptocurrency&#8217;s market value is estimated to be just over the &#8220;fair&#8221; zone, potentially setting the stage for a bull run or at least sideways price action, according to Fidelity.  Another interesting metric highlighted in the report is the percent of unique addresses in profit, which currently sits at nearly 66%. While this metric has not touched the green zone since January 2020, it suggests that Ethereum owners may be using the cryptocurrency for trading, DeFi, staking, or buying other digital assets. Related Reading: Bittrex To US Users: Withdraw Your Crypto Or Risk Running Into Issues Furthermore, the Pi Cycle indicators, which have historically been a good cycle top indicator, are showing that Ethereum is currently in a neutral zone. As the long-term moving average continues to follow the sunken price downward, it may be setting the stage for more volatility shortly. However, whether this volatility will be to the upside or downside remains to be seen and could depend on a variety of macro factors. ETH Adoption On The Rise On the other hand, Fidelity’s report highlights that while monthly active addresses and the monthly transaction count have fallen by 1%, the number of monthly new Ethereum addresses has slowly increased by 9% in Q2 2023. New addresses are defined as unique addresses that appeared for the first time in a transaction. This metric for momentum may not show direct network usage, but it does indicate a clearer picture of Ethereum adoption. The short-term moving average of new addresses is shown to be rising back above that of the longer-term moving average, indicating that the rate of new users joining the network is increasing. New and existing projects are likely incentivizing new users and helping to drive this increase. Another significant metric highlighted in the report is the net issuance of new supply issued by the network minus burned supply from transactions since The Merge.  Related Reading: Bitcoin Plunge To $29,200 Sends 5.9% Of Supply Into Loss This has driven a supply decrease for over five months now, with net issuance surpassing -700,000 Ether. The report notes that this is important because, in theory, as Ethereum&#8217;s supply is destroyed, it raises the relative ownership level of all remaining token holders. As of writing, ETH’s price is at $1,849, which has decreased by 2% within the last 24 hours. Similar to Bitcoin&#8217;s situation, Ethereum has also lost its 50-day MA, which is currently positioned at $1,869. If the market continues to decline, ETH can anticipate several key support levels that may help prevent a further bearish trend. The closest support level is situated at $1,840, followed by another support level of $1,792. However, the most crucial support floor is the 200-day MA, which is located at $1,780. This will be a significant factor in determining who will dominate in the upcoming months. Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Fidelity, a leading financial services provider, has recently released a <a href="https://www.fidelitydigitalassets.com/sites/default/files/documents/1096171.1.0%20Fidelity%20Digital%20Assets%20-%20Q2%20Signals%20Report.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">report </a>on Ethereum (ETH) that sheds light on some key metrics to watch for the cryptocurrency in the coming months. </p>
<p>The report highlights several important indicators, including the 50-day and 200-day moving averages (MA), the realized price, the Net Unrealized Profit/Loss (NUPL) ratio, Market Value to Realized Value (MVRV) Z-Score, percent in profit, and the Pi Cycle indicators, all of which can provide valuable insights into market sentiment and potential price movements.</p>
<h2>Ethereum Holds Strong Above Key Support Levels</h2>
<p>Per the report, Ethereum has remained above key support levels, with the realized price serving as a strong support level since January 10th. </p>
<p>Additionally, the NUPL ratio suggests that Ethereum is currently in a neutral zone, while the MVRV Z-Score indicates that the cryptocurrency&#8217;s market value is estimated to be just over the &#8220;fair&#8221; zone, potentially setting the stage for a bull run or at least sideways price action, according to Fidelity. </p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-544186 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot_29.jpg" alt="Ethereum " width="598" height="301" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot_29.jpg 598w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot_29-460x232.jpg 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot_29-360x180.jpg 360w" sizes="(max-width: 598px) 100vw, 598px"/>
<p>Another interesting metric highlighted in the report is the percent of unique addresses in profit, which currently sits at nearly 66%. While this metric has not touched the green zone since January 2020, it suggests that Ethereum owners may be using the cryptocurrency for trading, DeFi, staking, or buying other digital assets.</p>

<p>Furthermore, the Pi Cycle indicators, which have historically been a good cycle top indicator, are showing that Ethereum is currently in a neutral zone. As the long-term moving average continues to follow the sunken price downward, it may be setting the stage for more volatility shortly. </p>
<p>However, whether this volatility will be to the upside or downside remains to be seen and could depend on a variety of macro factors.</p>
ETH Adoption On The Rise
<p>On the other hand, Fidelity’s report highlights that while monthly active addresses and the monthly transaction count have fallen by 1%, the number of monthly new Ethereum addresses has slowly increased by 9% in Q2 2023.</p>
<p>New addresses are defined as unique addresses that appeared for the first time in a transaction. This metric for momentum may not show direct network usage, but it does indicate a clearer picture of Ethereum adoption.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-544187" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot_30.jpg" alt="Ethereum " width="606" height="307" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot_30.jpg 606w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot_30-460x233.jpg 460w" sizes="(max-width: 606px) 100vw, 606px"/>
<p>The short-term moving average of new addresses is shown to be rising back above that of the longer-term moving average, indicating that the rate of new users joining the network is increasing. New and existing projects are likely incentivizing new users and helping to drive this increase.</p>
<p>Another significant metric highlighted in the report is the net issuance of new supply issued by the network minus burned supply from transactions since The Merge. </p>

<p>This has driven a supply decrease for over five months now, with net issuance surpassing -700,000 Ether. The report notes that this is important because, in theory, as Ethereum&#8217;s supply is destroyed, it raises the relative ownership level of all remaining token holders.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/qu4qoX0B/" alt="Ethereum " width="1815" height="858"/>
<p>As of writing, ETH’s price is at $1,849, which has decreased by 2% within the last 24 hours. Similar to Bitcoin&#8217;s situation, Ethereum has also lost its 50-day MA, which is currently positioned at $1,869.</p>
<p>If the market continues to decline, ETH can anticipate several key support levels that may help prevent a further bearish trend. </p>
<p>The closest support level is situated at $1,840, followed by another support level of $1,792. However, the most crucial support floor is the 200-day MA, which is located at $1,780. This will be a significant factor in determining who will dominate in the upcoming months.</p>
<p>Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/iStock-935533896-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Over $41 Million in Bitcoin Long Positions Liquidated as BTC Crashes Toward $29K</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/over-41-million-bitcoin-liquidated-btc-crashes-29k/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dalmas Ngetich]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 01:00:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin bulls]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[OKX]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=544163</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[On July 24, 2023, Coinglass data revealed that over $41 million worth of Bitcoin long and short leveraged positions were liquidated as the BTC prices unexpectedly crashed below a consolidation level of around $29,500, shrinking by over 4%. The drop below the primary support is heaping pressure on the coin. It may draw more selling pressure in upcoming sessions, pushing prices toward immediate reaction lines, the next being at about $28,300.  Bitcoin Drops, Over $41 Million Of Longs Liquidated In crypto trading, liquidation happens the facilitating exchange, for example, OKX or Binance, forcibly takes over the collateral securing the leverage position whenever prices move against the trader&#8217;s prognosis. In this case, the recent liquidation was triggered by the rapid sell-off in Bitcoin, leading to a more than 4% price decline within a few hours during the New York Session on July 24. Binance, the world&#8217;s largest crypto exchange and a platform facilitating trading crypto derivatives, liquidated most levered positions. Significant liquidation amounts were also observed in ByBit and OKX. Related Reading: Binance Announces Listing Of Sam Altman’s Worldcoin, Opens Deposits A big chunk of liquidated positions were &#8220;longs,&#8221; meaning traders expected prices to rise in the days ahead. Coinglass said over $41 million of cumulative long positions were closed. Meanwhile, only $2.5 million of short positions were closed despite Bitcoin plunging, moving along the traders&#8217; price prediction. Despite Bitcoin remaining in a bullish formation, prices have been moving inside a consolidation, failing to breach the $31,800 level recorded in mid-July 2023. Coinciding with this expansion, a United States judge had ruled to favor Ripple Labs, saying XRP was not a security, in their case against the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). Following this declaration, the broader crypto market edged higher, only to cool off days later. Bitcoin has been no exception, as current price action reveals. Will ETF Applications Support Prices? Still, the collapse comes a few days after the SEC accepted applications from major financial institutions, including BlackRock, a prominent Wall Street giant, to launch Bitcoin exchange-traded funds (ETFs). News of BlackRock applying for a Bitcoin ETF previously triggered a bull run, pumping prices to 2023 highs.  Bitcoin remains bullish as prices remain within the leg-up established from June 15 to July 13. Even though fundamental factors could support prices, BTC may edge lower should bulls fail to prop up prices and push them within the consolidation of the better half of July 2023.  Related Reading: Ethereum Whale Transfers To Exchanges Suggest More Selling Pressure For ETH Technically, a close above $31,800 and July 13 highs may drive the coin towards the $36,000 zone and later $43,000 in a buy trend continuation formation. These are critical levels from the Fibonacci extension levels anchored on the recent leg-up from mid-June to mid-July. Feature image from Canva, chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On July 24, 2023, Coinglass data <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.coinglass.com/currencies/BTC" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">revealed</a> that over $41 million worth of Bitcoin long and short leveraged positions were liquidated as the BTC prices unexpectedly crashed below a consolidation level of around $29,500, shrinking by over 4%. The drop below the primary support is heaping pressure on the coin. </p>
<p>It may draw more selling pressure in upcoming sessions, pushing prices toward immediate reaction lines, the next being at about $28,300. </p>
<h2>Bitcoin Drops, Over $41 Million Of Longs Liquidated</h2>
<p>In crypto trading, liquidation happens the facilitating exchange, for example, OKX or Binance, forcibly takes over the collateral securing the leverage position whenever prices move against the trader&#8217;s prognosis. In this case, the recent liquidation was triggered by the rapid sell-off in Bitcoin, leading to a more than 4% price decline within a few hours during the New York Session on July 24. </p>
<p>Binance, the world&#8217;s largest crypto exchange and a platform facilitating trading crypto derivatives, liquidated most levered positions. Significant liquidation amounts were also observed in ByBit and OKX.</p>

<p>A big chunk of liquidated positions were &#8220;longs,&#8221; meaning traders expected prices to rise in the days ahead. Coinglass said over $41 million of cumulative long positions were closed. Meanwhile, only $2.5 million of short positions were closed despite Bitcoin plunging, moving along the traders&#8217; price prediction.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-544166 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot363.png" alt="Bitcoin liquidation: Coinglass" width="1339" height="348" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot363.png 1339w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot363-460x120.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot363-860x224.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot363-768x200.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot363-750x195.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot363-1140x296.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1339px) 100vw, 1339px"/>
<p>Despite Bitcoin remaining in a bullish formation, prices have been moving inside a consolidation, failing to breach the $31,800 level recorded in mid-July 2023. Coinciding with this expansion, a United States judge had ruled to favor Ripple Labs, saying XRP was not a security, in their case against the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). </p>
<p>Following this declaration, the broader crypto market edged higher, only to cool off days later. Bitcoin has been no exception, as current price action reveals.</p>
<a href="https://www.tradingview.com/x/qe7ir1Ry/" rel="nofollow"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/qe7ir1Ry/" alt="Bitcoin price on July 24| Source: BTCUSDT on Binance, TradingView" width="1226" height="595"/></a>
Will ETF Applications Support Prices?
<p>Still, the collapse comes a few days after the SEC accepted applications from major financial institutions, including BlackRock, a prominent Wall Street giant, to launch Bitcoin exchange-traded funds (ETFs). News of BlackRock applying for a Bitcoin ETF previously triggered a bull run, pumping prices to 2023 highs. </p>
<p>Bitcoin remains bullish as prices remain within the leg-up established from June 15 to July 13. Even though fundamental factors could support prices, BTC may edge lower should bulls fail to prop up prices and push them within the consolidation of the better half of July 2023. </p>

<p>Technically, a close above $31,800 and July 13 highs may drive the coin towards the $36,000 zone and later $43,000 in a buy trend continuation formation. These are critical levels from the Fibonacci extension levels anchored on the recent leg-up from mid-June to mid-July.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/iStock-1305769484-1-460x272.jpg" width="460" height="272" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>This Technical Signal Says Bitcoin Dominance Has Potentially Peaked</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/thbitcoin-dominance-has-potentially-peaked/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tony "The Bull"]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 00:36:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc.d]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=544137</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Altcoin sentiment is at extreme lows, but that’s not the only thing reaching extremes. Bitcoin dominance, a measure of the top cryptocurrency by market cap’s weight compared to the rest of the space, also reached the most extreme reading ever on a technical indicator known for its precise timing and ability to pin-point reversals. If accurate, it’s only a matter of time until altcoins once again outperform BTC. Why The 50% Level In Bitcoin Dominance Is Critical In recent weeks, BTC dominance reached above 50% — an important psychological level in the relationship between Bitcoin and altcoins. While the metric has been much higher — and lower — in the past, the idea that one coin is the size of all others combined is a massive accomplishment. Related Reading: This Bitcoin Continuation Pattern Points To 3-6 Months Of Uptrend Ahead But after reaching only 2% above the 50% zone, Bitcoin dominance has struggled to push any higher and found resistance. The first signs of a possible reversal began as XRP was deemed not a security by a US judge. Since then, the relationship between Bitcoin and alts has since switch course. The change in course coincides with the Fisher Transform flipping downward from the most extreme reading in the history of 2W BTC.D charts. The Fisher is turning down from +4 std. deviation &#124; BTC.D on TradingView.com The Fisher Transform Forecasts A Potential Altcoin Season The Fisher Transform, created by John Elhers, converts price action into a Gaussian normal distribution in order to better highlight precise turning points in markets. The tool’s readings are based on a standard deviation, where readings on the most extreme side of the bell curve are rare, and thus have a higher probability of reversal once the signal turns down. Such moves to extremes require enormous strength behind the underlying trend. But even the most powerful trends must eventually come to an end. Related Reading: Perfect Storm: Why Bitcoin &#38; Crypto Are Poised For A Dramatic Recovery Reversing down from the highest point in 2W BTC.D history could suggest the trend favoring Bitcoin has ended, and the altcoins will perform better for the foreseeable future. Whether or not that leads to a sustainable altcoin season remains to be seen. This chart originally appeared in issue #13 of CoinChartist (VIP). Subscribe for free. Tony is the author of the CoinChartist (VIP) newsletter. Follow @TonyTheBullBTC &#38; @coinchartist_io on Twitter. Or join the TonyTradesBTC Telegram for daily market insights and technical analysis education. Please note: Content is educational and should not be considered investment advice. Featured image from iStockPhoto, Charts from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Altcoin sentiment is at extreme lows, but that’s not the only thing reaching extremes. Bitcoin dominance, a measure of the top cryptocurrency by market cap’s weight compared to the rest of the space, also reached the most extreme reading ever on a technical indicator known for its precise timing and ability to pin-point reversals.</p>
<p>If accurate, it’s only a matter of time until altcoins once again outperform BTC.</p>
<h2>Why The 50% Level In Bitcoin Dominance Is Critical</h2>
<p>In recent weeks, BTC dominance reached above 50% — an important psychological level in the relationship between Bitcoin and altcoins. While the metric has been much higher — and lower — in the past, the idea that one coin is the size of all others combined is a massive accomplishment.</p>

<p>But after reaching only 2% above the 50% zone, Bitcoin dominance has struggled to push any higher and found resistance. The first signs of a possible reversal began as XRP was deemed not a security by a US judge. Since then, the relationship between Bitcoin and alts has since switch course.</p>
<p>The change in course coincides with the Fisher Transform flipping downward from the most extreme reading in the history of 2W BTC.D charts.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-large wp-image-544191 aligncenter" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTC.D_2023-07-21_14-28-31-860x408.png" alt="BTC.D_2023-07-21_14-28-31" width="860" height="408" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTC.D_2023-07-21_14-28-31-860x408.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTC.D_2023-07-21_14-28-31-460x218.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTC.D_2023-07-21_14-28-31-768x364.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTC.D_2023-07-21_14-28-31-1536x728.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTC.D_2023-07-21_14-28-31-2048x971.png 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTC.D_2023-07-21_14-28-31-750x356.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTC.D_2023-07-21_14-28-31-1140x540.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/></p>

<h2>The Fisher Transform Forecasts A Potential Altcoin Season</h2>
<p>The Fisher Transform, created by John Elhers, converts price action into a Gaussian normal distribution in order to better highlight precise turning points in markets.</p>
<p>The tool’s readings are based on a standard deviation, where readings on the most extreme side of the bell curve are rare, and thus have a higher probability of reversal once the signal turns down. Such moves to extremes require enormous strength behind the underlying trend. But even the most powerful trends must eventually come to an end.</p>

<p>Reversing down from the highest point in 2W BTC.D history could suggest the trend favoring Bitcoin has ended, and the altcoins will perform better for the foreseeable future. Whether or not that leads to a sustainable altcoin season remains to be seen.</p>



]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/iStock-1314216441-460x259.jpg" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Critical Support Level: Can It Hold $29,250 Before Monthly Candle Close?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-critical-support-level-can-it-hold-29250-before-monthly-candle-close/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=544170</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC), the world&#8217;s largest cryptocurrency, has experienced a sharp decline recently, mirroring the broader decline in the cryptocurrency market.  This has led to concerns among Bitcoin bulls, who closely monitor the cryptocurrency&#8217;s price movements to determine whether the decline will continue or stabilize the market. Downside Volatility Threatens BTC’s Support According to crypto analyst Rekt Capital, Bitcoin is hovering below a critical support level of $29,250. This is a crucial threshold for Bitcoin bulls, as a sustained breach of this level could trigger a macro trend shift and lead to a retest of lower support lines. Rekt Capital notes that Bitcoin has over a week to continue holding this support level, with the July Monthly Candle Close as an essential milestone. However, the analyst also warns that there is plenty of time for the market to shake out investors with downside volatility below this level potentially. BTC currently trades at $29,000, with the $29,250 50-day Moving Average (MA) being momentarily lost. This aligns with Bitcoin&#8217;s squeeze momentum indicator, which points to a downtrend cycle. Historically, such cycles have resulted in a consolidation period of 15 to 30 days after a sharp decline like the one BTC experienced recently. Related Reading: Binance Announces Listing Of Sam Altman’s Worldcoin, Opens Deposits However, there is positive news for bulls as BTC&#8217;s Average Directional Index (ADX) indicator is spiking, suggesting a loss of momentum in the current downtrend.  Nonetheless, if the current downtrend persists, the only notable support lines would be at $28,200, $28,100, $27,200, and the 200-day MA, which is critical for Bitcoin&#8217;s long-term trend and currently at $26,800. Bulls need to hold the 200-day MA, as losing it could compromise the current bullish trend.  Bitcoin On The Edge On the other hand, the broader cryptocurrency market is under pressure ahead of Wednesday&#8217;s upcoming interest rate decision. However, according to the crypto trader known as The Wolf Of Few Streets, Bitcoin&#8217;s support levels at 28,800 and 28,300 should prevent a significant fall.  The trader believes that the Bitcoin market has already priced in the expected increase. Ideally, the market should bounce off one of these levels and test $32,000 again after the interest rate data is released on Wednesday. Related Reading: Ethereum Whale Transfers To Exchanges Suggest More Selling Pressure For ETH Additionally, The Wolf Of Few Streets is optimistic about the positive news that may emerge regarding Exchange-Traded Funds (ETF) decisions, which could further support the market. The trader sees no immediate negatives for BTC and believes that a minor liquidation of long positions has been long overdue, making the timing for a decline perfect. However, The Wolf Of Few Streets does not expect this decline to last long. Overall, The Wolf Of Few Streets remains bullish on Bitcoin and believes the current market pressure is temporary. The trader&#8217;s analysis suggests that the support levels will hold, and positive news regarding ETF decisions could provide further support.  Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com ]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin (BTC), the world&#8217;s largest cryptocurrency, has experienced a sharp decline recently, mirroring the broader decline in the cryptocurrency market. </p>
<p>This has led to concerns among Bitcoin bulls, who closely monitor the cryptocurrency&#8217;s price movements to determine whether the decline will continue or stabilize the market.</p>
<h2>Downside Volatility Threatens BTC’s Support</h2>
<p><a href="https://twitter.com/rektcapital/status/1683501504844423171?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">According </a>to crypto analyst Rekt Capital, Bitcoin is hovering below a critical support level of $29,250. This is a crucial threshold for Bitcoin bulls, as a sustained breach of this level could trigger a macro trend shift and lead to a retest of lower support lines.</p>
<p>Rekt Capital notes that Bitcoin has over a week to continue holding this support level, with the July Monthly Candle Close as an essential milestone. However, the analyst also warns that there is plenty of time for the market to shake out investors with downside volatility below this level potentially.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/t8OZGzcY/" alt="Bitcoin " width="1814" height="858"/>
<p>BTC currently trades at $29,000, with the $29,250 50-day Moving Average (MA) being momentarily lost. This aligns with Bitcoin&#8217;s squeeze momentum indicator, which points to a downtrend cycle. Historically, such cycles have resulted in a consolidation period of 15 to 30 days after a sharp decline like the one BTC experienced recently.</p>

<p>However, there is positive news for bulls as BTC&#8217;s Average Directional Index (ADX) indicator is spiking, suggesting a loss of momentum in the current downtrend. </p>
<p>Nonetheless, if the current downtrend persists, the only notable support lines would be at $28,200, $28,100, $27,200, and the 200-day MA, which is critical for Bitcoin&#8217;s long-term trend and currently at $26,800.</p>
<p>Bulls need to hold the 200-day MA, as losing it could compromise the current bullish trend. </p>
Bitcoin On The Edge
<p>On the other hand, the broader cryptocurrency market is under pressure ahead of Wednesday&#8217;s upcoming interest rate decision. However, <a href="https://twitter.com/wolf_of_streets/status/1683434219748327424" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">according </a>to the crypto trader known as The Wolf Of Few Streets, Bitcoin&#8217;s support levels at 28,800 and 28,300 should prevent a significant fall. </p>
<p>The trader believes that the Bitcoin market has already priced in the expected increase. Ideally, the market should bounce off one of these levels and test $32,000 again after the interest rate data is released on Wednesday.</p>

<p>Additionally, The Wolf Of Few Streets is optimistic about the positive news that may emerge regarding Exchange-Traded Funds (ETF) decisions, which could further support the market.</p>
<p>The trader sees no immediate negatives for BTC and believes that a minor liquidation of long positions has been long overdue, making the timing for a decline perfect. However, The Wolf Of Few Streets does not expect this decline to last long.</p>
<p>Overall, The Wolf Of Few Streets remains bullish on Bitcoin and believes the current market pressure is temporary. The trader&#8217;s analysis suggests that the support levels will hold, and positive news regarding ETF decisions could provide further support. </p>
<p>Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/iStock-186295282-460x260.jpg" width="460" height="260" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Aave May Rally 20% Supported by Historical Levels, But Crucial Resistance Remains</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/aave/aave-may-rally-20-supported-by-historical-levels-but-crucial-resistance-remains/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[anushsamal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 23:00:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Aave]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[aave]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AAVEUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[aaveusdt]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=544128</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Aave&#8217;s price surged to $88 just two weeks ago, but currently, the altcoin is experiencing a correction. Over the past 24 hours, Aave has dropped over 4%, and on the weekly chart, it has depreciated more than 7%. The technical outlook for Aave appears bearish, with both demand and accumulation declining on the one-day chart. Related Reading: Ethereum Whale Transfers To Exchanges Suggest More Selling Pressure For ETH Presently, Aave is hovering near a critical support level, and upcoming trading sessions will be decisive in determining the coin&#8217;s direction. Although the price is currently above the crucial support zone, it faces two important resistance levels that it must overcome. Failure to surpass the immediate resistance could lead to a resurgence of bearish sentiment, potentially pushing the price below the local support level. Additionally, Aave&#8217;s market capitalization has declined, indicating a gradual loss of buyer momentum on the daily chart. Aave Price Analysis: One-Day Chart As of press time, the altcoin&#8217;s value stands at $70, following a correction from its previous $88 peak. The coin encounters resistance levels at $72 and $75. It is important to note that if the price drops from its current level, sellers could become active. This is due to the presence of a bearish order block, signifying high sell volume. Failing to maintain a price above $68 may result in Aave trading near $66 and $64. However, historically, the $68 price mark has proven to be a crucial rallying point, as evidenced by the previous rally to $88, which was initiated from the same level. However, if the coin can maintain its price above the $68 level in the upcoming trading sessions, it may have the potential for a 27% rally opportunity. Technical Outlook Following the rejection at the $75 level, Aave&#8217;s buyers have been encountering difficulties in the market. The Relative Strength Index (RSI) also signalled this weakening buying strength as it dipped below the half-line. Additionally, the price fell below the 20-Simple Moving Average line, indicating a shift away from buyer-driven momentum. To revive buyer interest, Aave would need to break above the $72 mark, potentially drawing them back into the market. The altcoin showed sell signals in line with declining demand. The Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD) was negative, displaying red histograms, which are associated with sell signals on the chart. Related Reading: Bitcoin Cash Price Could Restart Rally To $300 If It Breaks This Resistance Additionally, the Chaikin Money Flow (CMF), an indicator of capital inflows and outflows, was below the half-line, indicating that at the time of writing, capital outflows exceeded inflows. These technical indicators suggest a bearish sentiment in the market and potentially lower demand for the altcoin. Featured image from UnSplash, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Aave&#8217;s price surged to $88 just two weeks ago, but currently, the altcoin is experiencing a correction. Over the past 24 hours, Aave has dropped over 4%, and on the weekly chart, it has depreciated more than 7%. The technical outlook for Aave appears bearish, with both demand and accumulation declining on the one-day chart.</p>

<p>Presently, Aave is hovering near a critical support level, and upcoming trading sessions will be decisive in determining the coin&#8217;s direction. Although the price is currently above the crucial support zone, it faces two important resistance levels that it must overcome.</p>
<p>Failure to surpass the immediate resistance could lead to a resurgence of bearish sentiment, potentially pushing the price below the local support level. Additionally, Aave&#8217;s market capitalization has declined, indicating a gradual loss of buyer momentum on the daily chart.</p>
<h2>Aave Price Analysis: One-Day Chart</h2>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-544147 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/AAVEUSDT_2023-07-24_22-42-24.png" alt="Aave" width="1817" height="743" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/AAVEUSDT_2023-07-24_22-42-24.png 1817w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/AAVEUSDT_2023-07-24_22-42-24-460x188.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/AAVEUSDT_2023-07-24_22-42-24-860x352.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/AAVEUSDT_2023-07-24_22-42-24-768x314.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/AAVEUSDT_2023-07-24_22-42-24-1536x628.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/AAVEUSDT_2023-07-24_22-42-24-750x307.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/AAVEUSDT_2023-07-24_22-42-24-1140x466.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1817px) 100vw, 1817px"/>
<p>As of press time, the altcoin&#8217;s value stands at $70, following a correction from its previous $88 peak. The coin encounters resistance levels at $72 and $75.</p>
<p>It is important to note that if the price drops from its current level, sellers could become active. This is due to the presence of a bearish order block, signifying high sell volume.</p>
<p>Failing to maintain a price above $68 may result in Aave trading near $66 and $64. However, historically, the $68 price mark has proven to be a crucial rallying point, as evidenced by the previous rally to $88, which was initiated from the same level.</p>
<p>However, if the coin can maintain its price above the $68 level in the upcoming trading sessions, it may have the potential for a 27% rally opportunity.</p>
<h2>Technical Outlook</h2>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-544154 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/AAVEUSDT_2023-07-24_22-29-34.png" alt="Aave" width="1817" height="829" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/AAVEUSDT_2023-07-24_22-29-34.png 1817w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/AAVEUSDT_2023-07-24_22-29-34-460x210.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/AAVEUSDT_2023-07-24_22-29-34-860x392.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/AAVEUSDT_2023-07-24_22-29-34-768x350.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/AAVEUSDT_2023-07-24_22-29-34-1536x701.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/AAVEUSDT_2023-07-24_22-29-34-750x342.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/AAVEUSDT_2023-07-24_22-29-34-1140x520.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1817px) 100vw, 1817px"/>
<p>Following the rejection at the $75 level, Aave&#8217;s buyers have been encountering difficulties in the market. The Relative Strength Index (RSI) also signalled this weakening buying strength as it dipped below the half-line.</p>
<p>Additionally, the price fell below the 20-Simple Moving Average line, indicating a shift away from buyer-driven momentum. To revive buyer interest, Aave would need to break above the $72 mark, potentially drawing them back into the market.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-544157 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/AAVEUSDT_2023-07-24_22-30-00.png" alt="Aave" width="1817" height="743" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/AAVEUSDT_2023-07-24_22-30-00.png 1817w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/AAVEUSDT_2023-07-24_22-30-00-460x188.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/AAVEUSDT_2023-07-24_22-30-00-860x352.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/AAVEUSDT_2023-07-24_22-30-00-768x314.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/AAVEUSDT_2023-07-24_22-30-00-1536x628.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/AAVEUSDT_2023-07-24_22-30-00-750x307.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/AAVEUSDT_2023-07-24_22-30-00-1140x466.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1817px) 100vw, 1817px"/>
<p>The altcoin showed sell signals in line with declining demand. The Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD) was negative, displaying red histograms, which are associated with sell signals on the chart.</p>

<p>Additionally, the Chaikin Money Flow (CMF), an indicator of capital inflows and outflows, was below the half-line, indicating that at the time of writing, capital outflows exceeded inflows. These technical indicators suggest a bearish sentiment in the market and potentially lower demand for the altcoin.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/wance-paleri-s7gyjnH7Ulk-unsplash-460x258.jpg" width="460" height="258" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Plunge To $29,200 Sends 5.9% Of Supply Into Loss</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-plunge-to-29200-sends-5-9-of-supply-into-loss/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hououin Kyouma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 21:30:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Plunge]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Supply In Loss]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Supply In Profit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=544046</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[On-chain data shows an additional 5.9% of the total Bitcoin supply has entered into losses as the cryptocurrency&#8217;s price has plummeted to $29,200 today. Bitcoin Supply In Profit Has Declined To 70.4% After Today&#8217;s Price Plunge According to data from the on-chain analytics firm Glassnode, 1.11 million BTC has gone underwater with the latest asset value drop. The relevant indicator here is the &#8220;percent supply in profit,&#8221; which tells us about the percentage of the total Bitcoin supply currently carrying some profit. Related Reading: Bitcoin Cash Price Could Restart Rally To $300 If It Breaks This Resistance This metric works by going through the on-chain history of each coin in circulation to see what price it was previously moved at on the network. If this last transfer price for any coin were less than the current spot price of the asset, then that particular coin would be holding an unrealized gain currently. The percent supply in profit adds up all such coins and calculates what part of the total supply they make up for. A counterpart indicator called the &#8220;percent supply in loss&#8221; keeps track of the opposite type of tokens, and its value can be simply found by subtracting the supply in profit from 100. Now, here is a chart that shows the trend in the Bitcoin percent supply in profit over the past day or so: The value of the indicator seems to have taken a hit in recent hours &#124; Source: Glassnode on Twitter As displayed in the above graph, the Bitcoin percent supply in profit had been floating around 76.3% when the cryptocurrency price was above $30,200 yesterday. With the plunge to $29,200 over the past day, though, the metric has also taken a sharp hit, as only 70.4% of the total circulating supply is holding some unrealized profit now. Historically, whenever the profit in supply has crossed the 75% mark, declines in the price have become more probable. This is because investors become more likely to sell the more profits they hold. The latest tumble in the asset may have come because of this, as the investors who had been sitting on profits may have buckled and sold their coins to harvest their gains. As the metric has cooled down well below the 75% mark now, it&#8217;s possible that this may be it for the correction. Before the plunge to $29,200, Bitcoin had been consolidating above $30,000 since many weeks ago. As buying and selling took place in this sideways trend, many investors slowly gained their cost basis at or above this level. Related Reading: Bitcoin (BTC) Address Dormant For More Than 11 Years Moves $31 Million In BTC Due to this reason, the drop below this level has resulted in a significant part of the supply going into loss. More specifically, around 1.11 million BTC (equivalent to 5.9% of the total supply) has entered into the red. BTC Price At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading around $29,100, down 4% in the last week. BTC has seen a sharp drop during the last 24 hours &#124; Source: BTCUSD on TradingView Featured image from Kanchanara on Unsplash.com, charts from TradingView.com, Glassnode.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On-chain data shows an additional 5.9% of the total Bitcoin supply has entered into losses as the cryptocurrency&#8217;s price has plummeted to $29,200 today.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Supply In Profit Has Declined To 70.4% After Today&#8217;s Price Plunge</h2>
<p>According to data from the on-chain analytics firm <a href="https://twitter.com/glassnode/status/1683438241234427905" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Glassnode</a>, 1.11 million BTC has gone underwater with the latest asset value drop. The relevant indicator here is the &#8220;<a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/75-of-bitcoin-supply-now-in-profit-will-drop-happen/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">percent supply in profit</a>,&#8221; which tells us about the percentage of the total Bitcoin supply currently carrying some profit.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/bch/bitcoin-cash-price-rally-to-300/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Bitcoin Cash Price Could Restart Rally To $300 If It Breaks This Resistance</a></p>
<p>This metric works by going through the on-chain history of each coin in circulation to see what price it was previously moved at on the network. If this last transfer price for any coin were less than the current spot price of the asset, then that particular coin would be holding an unrealized gain currently.</p>
<p>The percent supply in profit adds up all such coins and calculates what part of the total supply they make up for. A counterpart indicator called the &#8220;<a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-crash-to-25700-sends-6-5-supply-loss/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">percent supply in loss</a>&#8221; keeps track of the opposite type of tokens, and its value can be simply found by subtracting the supply in profit from 100.</p>
<p>Now, here is a chart that shows the trend in the Bitcoin percent supply in profit over the past day or so:</p>
<p><img decoding="async" class="aligncenter" src="https://pbs.twimg.com/media/F1y9U15WIAAWe1h?format=jpg&amp;name=4096x4096" alt="Image" loading="lazy"/></p>

<p>As displayed in the above graph, the Bitcoin percent supply in profit had been floating around 76.3% when the cryptocurrency price was above $30,200 yesterday.</p>
<p>With the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-plunges-30k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">plunge</a> to $29,200 over the past day, though, the metric has also taken a sharp hit, as only 70.4% of the total circulating supply is holding some unrealized profit now.</p>
<p>Historically, whenever the profit in supply has crossed the 75% mark, declines in the price have become more probable. This is because investors become more likely to sell the more profits they hold.</p>
<p>The latest tumble in the asset may have come because of this, as the investors who had been sitting on profits may have buckled and sold their coins to harvest their gains. As the metric has cooled down well below the 75% mark now, it&#8217;s possible that this may be it for the correction.</p>
<p>Before the plunge to $29,200, Bitcoin had been consolidating above $30,000 since many weeks ago. As buying and selling took place in this sideways trend, many investors slowly gained their cost basis at or above this level.</p>

<p>Due to this reason, the drop below this level has resulted in a significant part of the supply going into loss. More specifically, around 1.11 million BTC (equivalent to 5.9% of the total supply) has entered into the red.</p>
<h2>BTC Price</h2>
<p>At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading around $29,100, down 4% in the last week.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium aligncenter" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/73TBETu7/" alt="Bitcoin Price Chart" width="1534" height="877"/></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/kanchanara-7E3QGntO66M-unsplash-2-460x306.jpg" width="460" height="306" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Russian Introduces A Third Form Of Currency As Putin Signs Digital Ruble Into Law</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/russian-introduces-a-third-form-of-currency-as-putin-signs-digital-ruble-into-law/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[anushsamal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 20:30:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CBDC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Digital Ruble]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=544097</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Russia is progressing with its central bank digital currency (CBDC). President Vladimir Putin has endorsed the digital ruble bill, signing it into law on July 24. As a result of this approval, the digital ruble law is officially set to take effect starting from August 1, 2023. Related Reading: XRP Position In The Crypto Top 4 Ranking: Can It Endure? The digital ruble will serve as an additional form of the Russian national currency. It will run alongside the existing cash and non-cash forms. This development means that the Russian ruble will exist in three different forms. This includes physical cash, non-cash transactions (such as electronic transfers and online payments), and the newly introduced digital version. The digital ruble will primarily function as a medium for payments and transfers. However, opening a bank account using digital rubles or obtaining a loan denominated in digital rubles will not be possible. The recently passed legislation now grants the Russian central bank the authority to conduct the first CBDC pilot involving real consumers. Earlier, the government had planned to initiate trials in April. It was to collaborate with multiple local banks, including major institutions like Sberbank. Russia&#8217;s Central Bank To Be The Principal Operator Of Digital Ruble According to the newly enacted law, Russia&#8217;s central bank will assume the role of the principal operator for the digital ruble infrastructure. It will be responsible for safeguarding the stored assets. Additionally, individuals or entities not operators or participants in the digital ruble platform, are prohibited from using the phrase &#8220;digital ruble platform&#8221; for their benefit. This also includes banning any related words and expressions in their advertising. Elvira Nabiullina, the Bank of Russia governor, has stated that Russian citizens will not be obligated to use the CBDC. The usage of the digital ruble will be entirely voluntary. The decision to adopt the CBDC will rest with the individuals. Nabiullina stated: No one is going to force anyone into the digital ruble [&#8230;] But we really hope that it will be more convenient and cheaper for both people and businesses, and they will start using it. This is a new opportunity. Provisions For The Inheritance Of Digital Rubles The document outlines provisions for the inheritance of digital rubles. It allows individuals to pass on their rights to these digital assets through testamentary dispositions or wills. The Russian government will establish the process and rules for issuing such orders in collaboration with the Bank of Russia. This ensures that digital rubles can be transferred or inherited according to the legal framework set by the authorities. It allows for adequately managing and distributing these digital assets during a person&#8217;s passing. Related Reading: X Coin Explodes 1,600% Despite No Connection To Musk’s Twitter Rebrand – Details However, the government does not anticipate widespread adoption of the digital ruble anytime soon. Mass adoption is not expected to happen before 2025 or possibly even 2027, as stated by Bank of Russia deputy governor Olga Skorobogatova. Featured image from BBC, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Russia is progressing with its central bank digital currency (CBDC). President Vladimir Putin has endorsed the digital ruble bill, signing it into law on July 24. As a result of this <a href="https://tass.com/politics/1651135" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">approval</a>, the digital ruble law is officially set to take effect starting from August 1, 2023.</p>

<p>The digital ruble will serve as an additional form of the Russian national currency. It will run alongside the existing cash and non-cash forms.</p>
<p>This development means that the Russian ruble will exist in three different forms. This includes physical cash, non-cash transactions (such as electronic transfers and online payments), and the newly introduced digital version.</p>
<p>The digital ruble will primarily function as a medium for payments and transfers. However, opening a bank account using digital rubles or obtaining a loan denominated in digital rubles will not be possible.</p>
<p>The recently passed <a href="https://publication.pravo.gov.ru/document/0001202307240009?index=4" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">legislation</a> now grants the Russian central bank the authority to conduct the first CBDC pilot involving real consumers. Earlier, the government had <a href="https://www.russia-briefing.com/news/russia-to-pilot-the-digital-ruble-from-april-2023.html/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">planned</a> to initiate trials in April. It was to collaborate with multiple local banks, including major institutions like Sberbank.</p>
<h2>Russia&#8217;s Central Bank To Be The Principal Operator Of Digital Ruble</h2>
<p>According to the newly enacted law, Russia&#8217;s central bank will assume the role of the principal operator for the digital ruble infrastructure. It will be responsible for safeguarding the stored assets.</p>
<p>Additionally, individuals or entities not operators or participants in the digital ruble platform, are prohibited from using the phrase &#8220;digital ruble platform&#8221; for their benefit. This also includes banning any related words and expressions in their advertising.</p>
<p>Elvira Nabiullina, the Bank of Russia governor, has stated that Russian citizens will not be obligated to use the CBDC. The usage of the digital ruble will be entirely voluntary. The decision to adopt the CBDC will rest with the individuals.</p>
<p>Nabiullina stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>No one is going to force anyone into the digital ruble [&#8230;] But we really hope that it will be more convenient and cheaper for both people and businesses, and they will start using it. This is a new opportunity.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Provisions For The Inheritance Of Digital Rubles</h2>
<p>The document outlines provisions for the inheritance of digital rubles. It allows individuals to pass on their rights to these digital assets through testamentary dispositions or wills. The Russian government will establish the process and rules for issuing such orders in collaboration with the Bank of Russia.</p>
<p>This ensures that digital rubles can be transferred or inherited according to the legal framework set by the authorities. It allows for adequately managing and distributing these digital assets during a person&#8217;s passing.</p>

<p>However, the government does not anticipate widespread adoption of the digital ruble anytime soon. Mass adoption is not expected to happen before 2025 or possibly even 2027, as stated by Bank of Russia deputy governor Olga Skorobogatova.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-544114 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/TOTAL_2023-07-24_16-37-55-2.png" alt="Digital Ruble" width="1818" height="830" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/TOTAL_2023-07-24_16-37-55-2.png 1818w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/TOTAL_2023-07-24_16-37-55-2-460x210.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/TOTAL_2023-07-24_16-37-55-2-860x393.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/TOTAL_2023-07-24_16-37-55-2-768x351.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/TOTAL_2023-07-24_16-37-55-2-1536x701.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/TOTAL_2023-07-24_16-37-55-2-750x342.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/TOTAL_2023-07-24_16-37-55-2-1140x520.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1818px) 100vw, 1818px"/>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/230703004542-01-putin-file-070323-1-460x259.jpg" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Elon Musk Incorporates Dogecoin Symbol In Twitter Bio, Triggering 5% Increase In Price</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/dogecoin/elon-musk-incorporates-dogecoin-symbol/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 19:30:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[doge]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Doge price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dogeusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dogeusdt]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[elon musk]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[twitter]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=544100</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Elon Musk is, once again, showing his support for Dogecoin in a subtle but meaningful way. Twitter, one of the biggest social media companies now under the leadership of Musk, recently changed its logo from the infamous ‘blue bird’ to a seemingly discrete X symbol. However, this was not the end of the changes as Musk also changed his Twitter bio to display the Dogecoin symbol.  Elon Musk Highlights Dogecoin In Recent Changes On Monday, Elon Musk changed his Twitter location to “XÐ&#8221;, X for the new Twitter logo, and Ð for Dogecoin&#8217;s logo, sparking speculations about a possible integration of Dogecoin into the Twitter platform. Related Reading: Bitcoin (BTC) Address Dormant For More Than 11 Years Moves $31 Million In BTC This isn’t the first time Musk has promoted DOGE and caused a stir in the crypto community, as he has tweeted about the meme coin several times in the past. With almost 150 million followers on the social media platform, Musk&#8217;s tweets garner a huge amount of attention. So when he mentions specific companies or cryptocurrencies, it often leads to big price swings.  Musk changes profile to include DOGE symbol &#124; Source: Twitter His tweets in the past have triggered double-digit percentage increases in the price of Dogecoin in particular. This time, Musk’s support seems to have had more of a subtle price reaction.  Following the implementation of the new bio, the price of Dogecoin shot up more than 5%. Trading volume on exchanges also increased drastically as investors rushed to buy the altcoin. According to Coinmarketcap, Dogecoin has seen a total increase of 309.19% in trading volume in the past 24 hours.  Dogecoin was created as a &#8220;meme currency,&#8221; but has since developed its own very passionate community and following, including Elon Musk, who is one of the world&#8217;s richest men. Will The New Twitter X Support DOGE? There’s a good chance that Twitter (now X) may incorporate Dogecoin payments into its platform, especially given Musk’s continuous support. As Twitter’s largest shareholder, Musk could push for the social media company to incorporate the meme coin into its ecosystem. This will enable users to seamlessly make payments on the site using Dogecoin, which may attract more crypto investors to the platform and boost user engagement. Related Reading: Dogecoin Becomes 8th-Largest Cryptocurrency After Adding $1 Billion To Market Cap However, there are a few roadblocks in the way. More stable cryptos like Bitcoin and Ethereum are starting to be accepted as payment methods in various aspects of the world. However, altcoins like Dogecoin are still very volatile with little utility and there are questions about its stability before Twitter (X) seriously considers it as an official payment method. At the time of writing, DOGE is trading at $0.07535, a quick increase from its price of $0.07081 earlier in the day. DOGE price jumps 5% following Musk's Twitter profile update &#124; Source: DOGEUSD on TradingView.com Featured image from Coinmarketcap, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Elon Musk is, once again, showing his support for Dogecoin in a subtle but meaningful way. Twitter, one of the biggest social media companies now under the leadership of Musk, recently changed its logo from the infamous ‘blue bird’ to a seemingly discrete X symbol. However, this was not the end of the changes as Musk also changed his Twitter bio to display the Dogecoin symbol. </p>
<h2>Elon Musk Highlights Dogecoin In Recent Changes</h2>
<p>On Monday, Elon Musk changed his Twitter location to “XÐ&#8221;, X for the new Twitter logo, and Ð for Dogecoin&#8217;s logo, sparking speculations about a possible integration of Dogecoin into the Twitter platform.</p>

<p>This isn’t the first time Musk has promoted DOGE and caused a stir in the crypto community, as he has tweeted about the meme coin several times in the past. With almost 150 million followers on the social media platform, Musk&#8217;s tweets garner a huge amount of attention. So when he mentions specific companies or cryptocurrencies, it often leads to big price swings. </p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-544103 aligncenter" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/WhatsApp-Image-2023-07-24-at-14.13.46-373x460.jpeg" alt="Elon Musk Dogecoin" width="373" height="460" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/WhatsApp-Image-2023-07-24-at-14.13.46-373x460.jpeg 373w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/WhatsApp-Image-2023-07-24-at-14.13.46-698x860.jpeg 698w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/WhatsApp-Image-2023-07-24-at-14.13.46-768x946.jpeg 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/WhatsApp-Image-2023-07-24-at-14.13.46-750x924.jpeg 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/WhatsApp-Image-2023-07-24-at-14.13.46-1140x1405.jpeg 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/WhatsApp-Image-2023-07-24-at-14.13.46.jpeg 1214w" sizes="(max-width: 373px) 100vw, 373px"/></p>

<p>His tweets in the past have triggered double-digit percentage increases in the price of Dogecoin in particular. This time, Musk’s support seems to have had more of a subtle price reaction. </p>
<p>Following the implementation of the new bio, the price of Dogecoin shot up more than 5%. Trading volume on exchanges also increased drastically as investors rushed to buy the altcoin. According to Coinmarketcap, Dogecoin has seen a total increase of 309.19% in trading volume in the past 24 hours. </p>
<p>Dogecoin was created as a &#8220;meme currency,&#8221; but has since developed its own very passionate community and following, including Elon Musk, who is one of the world&#8217;s richest men.</p>
<h2>Will The New Twitter X Support DOGE?</h2>
<p>There’s a good chance that Twitter (now X) may incorporate Dogecoin payments into its platform, especially given Musk’s continuous support. As Twitter’s largest shareholder, Musk could push for the social media company to incorporate the meme coin into its ecosystem. This will enable users to seamlessly make payments on the site using Dogecoin, which may attract more crypto investors to the platform and boost user engagement.</p>

<p>However, there are a few roadblocks in the way. More stable cryptos like Bitcoin and Ethereum are starting to be accepted as payment methods in various aspects of the world. However, altcoins like Dogecoin are still very volatile with little utility and there are questions about its stability before Twitter (X) seriously considers it as an official payment method.</p>
<p>At the time of writing, DOGE is trading at $0.07535, a quick increase from its price of $0.07081 earlier in the day.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/8lIEWvjy/" alt="Dogecoin price chart from TradingView.com" width="2884" height="1758"/></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Elon-Musk-Dogecoin-Twitter-460x259.jpeg" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance Announces Listing Of Sam Altman&#8217;s Worldcoin, Opens Deposits</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/altcoin/binance-announces-listing-worldcoin/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 18:30:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[exchange listing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[WLD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[WLD listing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[WLD token]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[WorldCoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=544099</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Binance, the world&#8217;s largest cryptocurrency exchange, has now listed Worldcoin (WLD), the much-anticipated digital asset founded by Sam Altman, the CEO of OpenAI. This listing has garnered immense attention from the global crypto community, with investors eager to participate in this new venture. The listing, announced today at 12:00 will include trading pairs such as WLD/BTC, WLD/USDT, and WLD/USDC. Worldcoin (WLD) aims to empower humanity in the Age of AI Worldcoin and revolutionize the digital identity landscape in the era of artificial intelligence. As the project&#8217;s service token, the WLD token carries essential governance features. This ambitious endeavor introduces the World ID system, Orb with iris scanner, and World App wallets.  Related Reading: Dogecoin Becomes 8th-Largest Cryptocurrency After Adding $1 Billion To Market Cap Despite privacy and security concerns expressed by experts, Altman is confident that Worldcoin&#8217;s open-source AI technology with iris scanning capabilities will alleviate these concerns over time.  Crypto Exchanges Line Up To List Worldcoin’s Newly Launched WLD Token Binance is not the only cryptocurrency exchange to participate in the listing of Worldcoin&#8217;s newly launched WLD token. Several other major exchanges, including OKX, Huobi, Bybit, and Gate.io, have also jumped on board to offer trading services for WLD. These listings have given a bullish birth to the newbie token (WLD). The token&#8217;s early trading on ByBit saw a remarkable surge, reaching highs of $2.79 within minutes of its debut. With a total token supply of 10 billion tokens, the WLD token&#8217;s fully diluted value currently stands at an alarming $25.6 billion. WLD falls from $2.99 to $2.199 &#124; Source: WLDUSDT on TradingView.com Worldcoin&#8217;s Ambitious Vision And Support Sam Altman&#8217;s mission to provide universal access to cryptocurrency has struck a chord with investors and communities worldwide. The World ID system, authenticated through iris scanning technology called &#8220;The Orb,&#8221; aims to establish a trustable and reliable global identification system for all individuals. With financial backing of $115 million from its Series C funding round, the project is expected to make significant strides toward achieving its goals. The World ID&#8217;s potential to distinguish between real humans and AI-generated entities has caught the attention of Twitter co-founder Jack Dorsey, who is confident in its bright future. Related Reading: Bitcoin (BTC) Address Dormant For More Than 11 Years Moves $31 Million In BTC “At no time should a corporation or state own any part of the global financial system,” Dorsey said in response to a tweet from the Worldcoin Twitter account. As the project gains momentum, its role in reshaping the economy through generative AI, and potentially contributing to the concept of universal basic income, is becoming increasingly apparent. However, whether this will be good or bad remains to be seen. Featured image from CryptoSlate, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Binance, the world&#8217;s largest cryptocurrency exchange, has now <a href="https://www.binance.com/en/support/announcement/binance-will-list-worldcoin-wld-9bc08522433c44b1b0b9978d65c4f5e5" rel="nofollow">listed</a> Worldcoin (WLD), the much-anticipated digital asset founded by Sam Altman, the CEO of OpenAI. This listing has garnered immense attention from the global crypto community, with investors eager to participate in this new venture. The listing, announced today at 12:00 will include trading pairs such as WLD/BTC, WLD/USDT, and WLD/USDC.</p>
<p>Worldcoin (WLD) aims to empower humanity in the Age of AI Worldcoin and revolutionize the digital identity landscape in the era of artificial intelligence.</p>
<p>As the project&#8217;s service token, the WLD token carries essential governance features. This ambitious endeavor introduces the World ID system, Orb with iris scanner, and World App wallets. </p>

<p>Despite privacy and security concerns expressed by experts, Altman is confident that Worldcoin&#8217;s open-source AI technology with iris scanning capabilities will alleviate these concerns over time. </p>
<h2>Crypto Exchanges Line Up To List Worldcoin’s Newly Launched WLD Token</h2>
<p>Binance is not the only cryptocurrency exchange to participate in the listing of Worldcoin&#8217;s newly launched WLD token. Several other major exchanges, including OKX, Huobi, Bybit, and Gate.io, have also jumped on board to offer trading services for WLD.</p>
<p>These listings have given a bullish birth to the newbie token (WLD). The token&#8217;s early trading on ByBit saw a remarkable surge, reaching highs of $2.79 within minutes of its debut. With a total token supply of 10 billion tokens, the WLD token&#8217;s fully diluted value currently stands at an alarming $25.6 billion.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/4C43bvJN/" alt="Worldcoin (WLD) price chart from TradingView.com" width="2884" height="1758"/></p>

<h2>Worldcoin&#8217;s Ambitious Vision And Support</h2>
<p>Sam Altman&#8217;s mission to provide universal access to cryptocurrency has struck a chord with investors and communities worldwide. The World ID system, authenticated through iris scanning technology called &#8220;The Orb,&#8221; aims to establish a trustable and reliable global identification system for all individuals.</p>
<p>With financial backing of $115 million from its Series C funding round, the project is expected to make significant strides toward achieving its goals.</p>
<p>The World ID&#8217;s potential to distinguish between real humans and AI-generated entities has caught the attention of Twitter co-founder <a href="https://twitter.com/jack/status/1683334640831205378" rel="nofollow">Jack Dorsey</a>, who is confident in its bright future.</p>

<p>“At no time should a corporation or state own any part of the global financial system,” Dorsey said in response to a tweet from the Worldcoin Twitter account.</p>
<p>As the project gains momentum, its role in reshaping the economy through generative AI, and potentially contributing to the concept of universal basic income, is becoming increasingly apparent. However, whether this will be good or bad remains to be seen.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Worldcoin-WLD-460x242.jpeg" width="460" height="242" />	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
