<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	 xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" >

<channel>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://newsbtc.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://newsbtc.com</link>
	<description>Bitcoin &#38; cryptocurrency news today, price &#38; technical analysis</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 14:04:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<link>https://newsbtc.com</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Dogecoin (DOGE) Is Now 4th Most Popular Cryptocurrency On BitPay</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/dogecoin-4th-most-popular-on-bitpay/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 14:04:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitpay]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[doge]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[meme crypto]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=515286</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Dogecoin, a dog-themed meme crypto that appears to enjoy strong ties with tech billionaire and Twitter owner Elon Musk, appears to be struggling to gain enough ground for a major upward swing. After peaking at $0.0749 on January 5, DOGE fell victim to a price retracement that pulled it all the way down to $0.0705 the following day. Since then, the altcoin launched a mini rally to recoup some of its losses, enabling it to notch a 2.4% increase in value over the last seven days. According to tracking from Coingecko, at the time of writing, Dogecoin is changing hands at $0.0719 and despite its early struggles this year, it is able to strongly keep its place as the 8th largest cryptocurrency courtesy of its market cap which currently stands at $9.90 billion. Dogecoin Still Among The More Popular Crypto Assets Although still far from rewarding its faithful holders with significant profit through a massive price hike, DOGE continues to establish itself as among the well-known digital currencies. Just recently, BitPay, one of the world&#8217;s leading crypto payments processors, revealed that the meme token is the fourth most popular transactional currency in its platform. Related Reading: Ethereum Classic (ETC) Price Balloons To Nearly 30% In Last 7 Days Source: Bitpay According to data shared by the company, in December 2022, Dogecoin accounted for 10% of all transactions it processed, almost doubling the 6% tally it had in June. The memecoin placed behind Bitcoin (1st, 41.81%), Litecoin (2nd, 25.51%) and Ethereum (3rd, 11.53%). This development could be interpreted as an indication that more and more people are using the digital asset as a means of exchange. Along this line, leading Indian cryptocurrency trading app CoinSwitch with more or less 20 million users mentioned in its report that DOGE was included in the list of the most popular virtual currencies owned by its customers. Related Reading: Lido DAO Surges By More Than 57% in Just A Week – More Gains Up Ahead? DOGE total market cap at $9.4 billion on the weekend chart &#124; Chart: TradingView.com The Undeniable Musk Effect As time goes by, it is slowly becoming apparent that Dogecoin might live and fade with the self-proclaimed &#8220;Dogefather&#8221; Elon Musk as his social media comments of the memecoin triggers instant price movements. For example, when the Tesla CEO completed his controversial purchase of social media giant Twitter back in October 2022, DOGE&#8217;s price registered a significant uptick, from $0.0720 in October 27 to $0.1572 on November 1. Months before his acquisition of the company, Musk floated the idea of having Dogecoin accepted as a payment for Twitter&#8217;s Blue services.  -Featured image: Cryptoglobe]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Dogecoin, a dog-themed meme crypto that appears to enjoy strong ties with tech billionaire and Twitter owner Elon Musk, appears to be struggling to gain enough ground for a major upward swing.</p>
<p>After peaking at $0.0749 on January 5, DOGE fell victim to a price retracement that pulled it all the way down to $0.0705 the following day.</p>
<p>Since then, the altcoin launched a mini rally to recoup some of its losses, enabling it to notch a 2.4% increase in value over the last seven days.</p>
<p>According to tracking from <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/dogecoin" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Coingecko</a>, at the time of writing, Dogecoin is changing hands at $0.0719 and despite its early struggles this year, it is able to strongly keep its place as the 8th largest cryptocurrency courtesy of its market cap which currently stands at $9.90 billion.</p>
<h2><b>Dogecoin Still Among The More Popular Crypto Assets</b></h2>
<p>Although still far from rewarding its faithful holders with significant profit through a massive price hike, DOGE continues to establish itself as among the well-known digital currencies.</p>
<p>Just recently, BitPay, one of the world&#8217;s leading crypto payments processors, revealed that the meme token is the <a href="https://www.tronweekly.com/bitpay-reveals-doge-is-fourth-popular-crypto/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">fourth most popular transactional currency</a> in its platform.</p>

<p><img loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-515290 size-full" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/a-26.png" alt="" width="771" height="571" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/a-26.png 771w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/a-26-460x341.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/a-26-768x569.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/a-26-750x555.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 771px) 100vw, 771px" /></p>

<p>According to data shared by the company, in December 2022, Dogecoin accounted for 10% of all transactions it processed, almost doubling the 6% tally it had in June.</p>
<p>The memecoin placed behind Bitcoin (1st, 41.81%), Litecoin (2nd, 25.51%) and Ethereum (3rd, 11.53%).</p>
<p>This development could be interpreted as an indication that more and more people are using the digital asset as a means of exchange.</p>
<p>Along this line, leading Indian cryptocurrency trading app <a href="https://watcher.guru/news/dogecoin-is-now-one-of-the-most-held-crypto-on-indias-coinswitch" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">CoinSwitch</a> with more or less 20 million users mentioned in its report that DOGE was included in the list of the most popular virtual currencies owned by its customers.</p>

<p><img loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/8Mt8wxXV/" width="2047" height="979" /></p>

<h2><b>The Undeniable Musk Effect</b></h2>
<p>As time goes by, it is slowly becoming apparent that Dogecoin might live and fade with the self-proclaimed &#8220;Dogefather&#8221; Elon Musk as his social media comments of the memecoin triggers instant price movements.</p>
<p>For example, when the Tesla CEO completed his controversial <a href="https://www.investors.com/news/dogecoin-rallies-on-elon-musk-twitter-news/#:~:text=Elon%20Musk%20finally%20purchased%20Twitter,with%20its%20community%20of%20users." target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">purchase of social media giant Twitter</a> back in October 2022, DOGE&#8217;s price registered a significant uptick, from $0.0720 in October 27 to $0.1572 on November 1.</p>
<p>Months before his acquisition of the company, Musk floated the idea of having Dogecoin accepted as a payment for Twitter&#8217;s Blue services. </p>
<p><em>-Featured image: Cryptoglobe</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Dogecoin-460x274.png" width="460" height="274" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum Classic (ETC) Price Balloons To Nearly 30% In Last 7 Days</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/ethereum-classic-climbs-30/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 10:17:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum Classic]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=515271</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Ethereum Classic (ETC), a decentralized, open-source and blockchain-based cryptocurrency, might soon lose its current momentum that allowed it to become one of the top performing crypto assets for the past week. A quick review at some data points for the digital asset reveals that it is currently trading at an overbought position which might cause buyers to be “exhausted” and unable to sustain a further rally, yielding technical advantage to the bears once again. Moreover, the altcoin’s Bollinger Bands indicate that it is extremely volatile at the moment, making it susceptible to significant price swings that could happen in just a wink of an eye. This makes Ethereum Classic a more risky asset to trade or hold. Related Reading: Lido DAO Surges By More Than 57% in Just A Week – More Gains Up Ahead? Image: Coinpedia Ethereum Classic: A Quick Glance At Impressive Run According to latest tracking from Coingecko, at the time of writing, ETC was changing hands at $19.82. Although the crypto has declined by 2% over the last 24 hours, it is still enjoying a nearly 30% jump from its value seven days ago. Moreover, on a bi-weekly basis, the digital token tallied an upswing of 20.3%. During the last few days, Ethereum Classic was among the few cryptocurrencies that managed to post double-digit gains within the previous week led by Solana which surged by an astonishing 35%. As for the reason, some experts believe that the pivotal turnaround in the hash rate of the ETC towards the end of 2022 paved the way for miner profitability which, in turn, increased the number of transactions processed by the asset’s network. In fact, during the last two days, Ethereum Classic transaction count surged and hit a new monthly high. Following this, ETC recorded a 12% increase in its trading price, indicating that the spike in volume triggered an upward movement for the altcoin’s value. Related Reading: MATIC Advances 6.5% In Last 7 Days – Can It Sustain Gains For Another Week? ETC total market cap at $2.7 billion on the weekend chart &#124; Chart: TradingView.com Preparing For Possible Price Drawback Despite being “in the green” for more than a week now, Ethereum Classic is still haunted by the negative weighted sentiment that denotes bad convictions that investors harbor for the digital token. Holders and prospective buyers are therefore advised to be cautious as non-positive sentiment is usually followed by a price retracement. Coincodex, however, seems to disagree with this thesis as its forecasts for ETC remains bullish despite technical indicators saying otherwise. In fact, the online crypto data provider predicts the digital coin will change hands at $19.76 five days from now and will make another massive surge within the next 30 days to trade at $47.48. -Featured image: Invezz]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ethereum Classic (ETC), a decentralized, open-source and blockchain-based cryptocurrency, might soon lose its current momentum that allowed it to become one of the top performing crypto assets for the past week.</p>
<p>A quick <a href="https://ambcrypto.com/ethereum-classic-etc-sends-cautionary-signals-as-price-grows-by-over-25/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">review at some data points</a> for the digital asset reveals that it is currently trading at an overbought position which might cause buyers to be “exhausted” and unable to sustain a further rally, yielding technical advantage to the bears once again.</p>
<p>Moreover, the altcoin’s Bollinger Bands indicate that it is extremely volatile at the moment, making it susceptible to significant price swings that could happen in just a wink of an eye. This makes Ethereum Classic a more risky asset to trade or hold.</p>

<p><img loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-515274 size-full" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/etcc.png" alt="" width="768" height="401" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/etcc.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/etcc-460x240.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/etcc-750x392.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" /></p>

<h2><strong>Ethereum Classic: A Quick Glance At Impressive Run</strong></h2>
<p>According to latest tracking from <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/ethereum-classic" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Coingecko</a>, at the time of writing, ETC was changing hands at $19.82.</p>
<p>Although the crypto has declined by 2% over the last 24 hours, it is still enjoying a nearly 30% jump from its value seven days ago. Moreover, on a bi-weekly basis, the digital token tallied an upswing of 20.3%.</p>
<p>During the last few days, Ethereum Classic was among the few cryptocurrencies that managed to post double-digit gains within the previous week led by Solana which surged by an astonishing 35%.</p>
<p>As for the reason, some experts believe that the pivotal turnaround in the hash rate of the ETC towards the end of 2022 paved the way for miner profitability which, in turn, <a href="https://www.fxstreet.com/cryptocurrencies/news/heres-why-ethereum-classic-witnessed-a-massive-rebound-in-its-price-with-hashrate-simulation-202301071253" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">increased the number of transactions</a> processed by the asset’s network.</p>
<p>In fact, during the last two days, Ethereum Classic transaction count surged and hit a new monthly high. Following this, ETC recorded a 12% increase in its trading price, indicating that the spike in volume triggered an upward movement for the altcoin’s value.</p>

<p><img loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/efPf5nLj/" width="2047" height="979" /></p>

<h2><b>Preparing For Possible Price Drawback</b></h2>
<p>Despite being “in the green” for more than a week now, Ethereum Classic is still haunted by the negative weighted sentiment that denotes bad convictions that investors harbor for the digital token.</p>
<p>Holders and prospective buyers are therefore advised to be cautious as non-positive sentiment is usually followed by a price retracement.</p>
<p>Coincodex, however, seems to disagree with this thesis as its forecasts for <a href="https://coincodex.com/crypto/ethereum-classic/price-prediction/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">ETC remains bullish</a> despite technical indicators saying otherwise.</p>
<p>In fact, the online crypto data provider predicts the digital coin will change hands at $19.76 five days from now and will make another massive surge within the next 30 days to trade at $47.48.</p>
<p><em>-Featured image: Invezz</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Etc-460x226.png" width="460" height="226" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Shibarium Developers Say Each On-Chain Transaction Will Burn SHIB Tokens</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/shibarium-burn-of-shib-tokens/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samuel Edyme]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 08:56:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIB]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shiba Inu (SHIB)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shibarium]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=515211</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Shibarium is one of the most anticipated projects, mainly in the Shiba Inu community; most SHIB community members are eager for the launch as it could be enough of a catalyst to pump their SHIB bags.  Latest on the news about the layer two blockchain scaling solution, the developers announced via a short thread on Twitter earlier today that every transaction on the Shibarium network would result in a burn of Shiba Inu (SHIB) token. Shibarium Burn Mechanism To Boost SHIB Price Over Time? Currently, SHIB has a circulating supply of 589 trillion units and a total supply that exceeds 900 trillion. Its initial total supply was reduced with a recent burn and with the soon-to-be-introduced burning mechanism by Shibarium, SHIB&#8217;s price is likely to appreciate as the supply will be reduced. Though the amount of SHIB token that will be burned after each transaction has not been revealed, the burning mechanism is likely to be a good enough catalyst for not only the SHIB token but the Shibarium blockchain.  Related Reading: Dogecoin’s (DOGE) space mission, Shiba Inu’s (SHIB) Shibarium, and Snowfall Protocol’s (SNW) grand launch – Here’s why January 2023 looks promising for these tokens Recent Update Reflects On BONE Token In its previous update, the Shibarium team cleared some false circulating speculations about the blockchain and what native token it will utilize. Shibarium developers noted that BONE will be the only token that would be used for gas fees and “No other tokens will be necessary to operate within the protocol.” For context, BONE is a governance token of the Shibaswap ecosystem, allowing the SHIB community to vote on upcoming proposals in the ecosystem. The more BONE coins a user holds, the more weight their vote carries in future proposal. Though it may seem as though BONE is the main character of the Shibarium blockchain, it is not, but more of a partner that will work hand in hand with SHIB. “Shibarium has been developed for SHIB token and not for the sake of other projects who claim ownership or speculation surrounding its operability dependency on any other tokens,” the Shibarium team announced. Related Reading: Shiba Inu Lead Dev Ignites Buzz About New Partnership, SHIB Price Stagnates So far, BONE has been moving in a positive direction. With consolidation almost as if it’s waiting for the Shibarium launch to make a significant move, the BONE token currently ranks at a position of 113 on CoinGecko with a market cap of more than $250 million. Its current market price at the time of writing is $1.1, with a 24-hour trading volume of $4.1 million. SHIB token, on the other hand, currently ranks higher on CoinGecko, owning the 16th position with a market cap almost heading to $5 billion. It currently has a trading price of $0.00000845 at the time of writing, with a 24-hour trading volume of $175 million. -Featured image: Shib Army News]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Shibarium is one of the most anticipated projects, mainly in the <a href="https://newsbtc.com/press-releases/dogecoin-doge-and-shiba-inu-shib-investors-are-moving-to-snowfall-protocol-snw/">Shiba Inu</a> community; most SHIB community members are eager for the launch as it could be enough of a catalyst to pump their SHIB bags. </p>
<p>Latest on the news about the layer two blockchain scaling solution, the developers <a href="https://twitter.com/shibariumnet/status/1611542769561964544?s=46&amp;t=DVo232iASskHFU5NJXyCqw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">announced</a> via a short thread on Twitter earlier today that every transaction on the Shibarium network would result in a burn of Shiba Inu (SHIB) token.</p>
<h2><strong>Shibarium Burn Mechanism To Boost SHIB Price Over Time?</strong></h2>
<p>Currently, <a href="https://newsbtc.com/press-releases/shiba-inu-shib-snowfall-protocol-snw-or-terra-classic-lunc-which-crypto-will-touch-the-1-mark-first/">SHIB</a> has a circulating supply of 589 trillion units and a total supply that exceeds 900 trillion. Its initial total supply was reduced with a recent burn and with the soon-to-be-introduced burning mechanism by Shibarium, SHIB&#8217;s price is likely to appreciate as the supply will be reduced.</p>
<p>Though the amount of SHIB token that will be burned after each transaction has not been revealed, the burning mechanism is likely to be a good enough catalyst for not only the SHIB token but the Shibarium blockchain. </p>

<h2><strong>Recent Update Reflects On BONE Token</strong></h2>
<p>In its previous update, the Shibarium team cleared some false circulating speculations about the <a href="https://newsbtc.com/press-releases/vision-of-blockchain-vob-is-now-available-for-trading-on-lbank-exchange/">blockchain</a> and what native token it will utilize. Shibarium developers noted that BONE will be the only token that would be used for gas fees and “No other tokens will be necessary to operate within the protocol.”</p>
<p>For context, BONE is a governance token of the Shibaswap ecosystem, allowing the SHIB community to vote on upcoming proposals in the ecosystem. The more BONE coins a user holds, the more weight their vote carries in future proposal.</p>
<p>Though it may seem as though <a href="https://newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/why-is-shiba-inus-bone-on-the-rise-and-is-it-time-to-get-in/">BONE</a> is the main character of the Shibarium blockchain, it is not, but more of a partner that will work hand in hand with SHIB. “Shibarium has been developed for <a href="https://newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/shiba-inu-lead-ignites-buzz-partnership/">SHIB token </a>and not for the sake of other projects who claim ownership or speculation surrounding its operability dependency on any other tokens,” the Shibarium team announced.</p>

<p>So far, BONE has been moving in a positive direction. With consolidation almost as if it’s waiting for the Shibarium launch to make a significant move, the BONE token currently ranks at a position of 113 on CoinGecko with a market cap of more than $250 million. Its current market price at the time of writing is $1.1, with a 24-hour trading volume of $4.1 million.</p>
<img loading="lazy" class="size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/XUBHZGw0/" alt="SHIB Price Chart On TradingView" width="1381" height="753" />
<p>SHIB token, on the other hand, currently ranks higher on CoinGecko, owning the 16th position with a market cap almost heading to $5 billion. It currently has a trading price of $0.00000845 at the time of writing, with a 24-hour trading volume of $175 million.</p>
<p><em>-Featured image: Shib Army News</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/shiba-460x258.png" width="460" height="258" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Lido DAO Surges By More Than 57% in Just A Week &#8211; More Gains Up Ahead?</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/lido-up-by-more-than-55/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 08:40:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LDO]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Lido DAO]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Lido Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[platform]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Staking]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=515258</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Lido DAO (LDO), the native cryptocurrency of Lido Finance, significantly increased its total market capitalization which now stands at $1.25 billion. This no longer comes as a surprise as the crypto asset is in the midst of an incredible run that enabled it to post double-digit gains on its intraday, weekly, bi-weekly and monthly charts. At press time, according to data from Coingecko, LDO is changing hands at $1.51, increasing its value by 13% during the last 24 hours. Over the previous seven days, the digital token went up by 56.5% while also posting a bi-weekly gain of 60% and monthly increase of 50%. Already in the middle of an impressive showing, some analysts believe that Lido DAO still has room for improvement, thanks to a new upcoming ETH upgrade. Related Reading: MATIC Advances 6.5% In Last 7 Days – Can It Sustain Gains For Another Week? Image: The Crypto Times Lido Expected To Benefit From ETH Shanghai Upgrade According to a recently released analysis, Lido Finance, at the time of this writing, is responsible for nearly 30% of all staked ETH tokens, making it the largest liquid staking platform for Ethereum right now. It has been noted that the demand for the platform increased dramatically after Ethereum switched from proof-of-work to proof-of-stake mechanism back in 2022. Moreover, the analysis stated that the blockchain’s upcoming Shanghai fork will enable users to withdraw their staked ETH tokens which, in turn, is expected to encourage more people to stake through Lido Finance. This will then increase the demand for the project’s native token. Some experts believe that these are just some of the triggers that helped the crypto asset go up by more than 55% in just seven days and will also play a vital role in the altcoin’s attempt to sustain its bullish run. LDO total market cap at $1.28 billion on the weekend chart &#124; Chart: TradingView.com &#8230; But LDO Could Lose Its Momentum Although things are looking good right now, there’s still a chance that LDO could enter a price correction phase that will not only halt its upward movement but will also make it lose most, if not all of its current gains. LDO is currently in an overbought territory and has reached a point for psychological take-profit zone which are indications of an impending intense selling pressure. Related Reading: Polkadot (DOT) Inks 10% Rally In Last 7 Days, Makes Case As ‘Non-Security’ Asset There is also a noticeable drop in the number of LDO tokens being held by its top addresses, indicative of whales selling their holdings. This is expected, given the massive surge that Lido DAO has made over the last few days which presents an opportunity for investors to take profit. If these conditions don’t change, there’s a high possibility that the crypto asset’s incredible run will come to an abrupt end and it will return into its previous bearish track. -Featured image: Coinpedia]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Lido DAO (LDO), the native cryptocurrency of <a href="https://lido.fi/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Lido Finance</a>, significantly increased its total market capitalization which now stands at $1.25 billion.</p>
<p>This no longer comes as a surprise as the crypto asset is in the midst of an incredible run that enabled it to post double-digit gains on its intraday, weekly, bi-weekly and monthly charts.</p>
<p>At press time, according to data from <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/lido-dao" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Coingecko</a>, LDO is changing hands at $1.51, increasing its value by 13% during the last 24 hours.</p>
<p>Over the previous seven days, the digital token went up by 56.5% while also posting a bi-weekly gain of 60% and monthly increase of 50%.</p>
<p>Already in the middle of an impressive showing, some analysts believe that Lido DAO still has room for improvement, thanks to a new upcoming ETH upgrade.</p>

<h2><img loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-515261 size-full" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Shang.png" alt="" width="722" height="449" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Shang.png 722w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Shang-460x286.png 460w" sizes="(max-width: 722px) 100vw, 722px" /></h2>

<h2><b>Lido Expected To Benefit From ETH Shanghai Upgrade</b></h2>
<p>According to a recently released analysis, Lido Finance, at the time of this writing, is responsible for nearly 30% of all staked ETH tokens, making it the <a href="https://thedefiant.io/lido-tops-defi-liquid-staking-surge" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">largest liquid staking platform for Ethereum</a> right now.</p>
<p>It has been noted that the demand for the platform increased dramatically after Ethereum switched from proof-of-work to proof-of-stake mechanism back in 2022.</p>
<p>Moreover, the analysis stated that the blockchain’s upcoming <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-01-05/ethereum-developers-push-ahead-with-update-enabling-withdrawals" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Shanghai fork</a> will enable users to withdraw their staked ETH tokens which, in turn, is expected to encourage more people to stake through Lido Finance. This will then increase the demand for the project’s native token.</p>
<p>Some experts believe that these are just some of the triggers that helped the crypto asset go up by more than 55% in just seven days and will also play a vital role in the altcoin’s attempt to sustain its bullish run.</p>

<h2><b>&#8230; But LDO Could Lose Its Momentum</b></h2>
<p>Although things are looking good right now, there’s still a chance that LDO could enter a price correction phase that will not only halt its upward movement but will also make it lose most, if not all of its current gains.</p>
<p>LDO is currently in an <a href="https://ambcrypto.com/ldo-analysis-by-intotheblock-reveals-this-about-its-performance-and-what-to-expect/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">overbought territory</a> and has reached a point for psychological take-profit zone which are indications of an impending intense selling pressure.</p>

<p>There is also a noticeable drop in the number of LDO tokens being held by its top addresses, indicative of whales selling their holdings. This is expected, given the massive surge that Lido DAO has made over the last few days which presents an opportunity for investors to take profit.</p>
<p>If these conditions don’t change, there’s a high possibility that the crypto asset’s incredible run will come to an abrupt end and it will return into its previous bearish track.</p>
<p><em>-Featured image: Coinpedia</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Lido-1-460x239.png" width="460" height="239" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Balancer’s Native Coin BAL Resilient Amidst Security Emergency</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/bal-token-strong-amidst-balancer-security-isssues/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[semilorefaleti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 05:46:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[balancer]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[balusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto exploit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[decentralized exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DeFi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DeFi protocol]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DEX]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=515223</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Balancer’s native token, BAL, appears to be holding up despite the platform’s ongoing security issues. On Friday, Jan. 6, the DeFi project tweeted a statement asking liquidity providers on its platform to withdraw their tokens from certain pools valued at $6.3 million.  Via their official Twitter handle, the decentralized exchange stated there was a security risk that could not be resolved by the platform&#8217;s emergency DAO. Thus, they advised LPs to immediately remove their assets from all affected pools.  Related Reading: Polkadot (DOT) Inks 10% Rally In Last 7 Days, Makes Case As ‘Non-Security’ Asset IMPORTANT: Because of a related issue, LPs of the following pools should remove their liquidity ASAP as the issue cannot be mitigated by the emergency DAO. https://t.co/WcBeBvjdY2 — Balancer (@Balancer) January 6, 2023 BAL Token Holds Its Ground For Now Earlier today, Balancer confirmed that 85% of the assets in those pools had been moved while still urging LPs to withdraw the remainder as they attempt to resolve the issue at hand. Interestingly, amid the ongoing problem of the decentralized exchange, several investors appeared to have retained their faith in the platform’s native cryptocurrency BAL.  In the last 24 hours following Balancer’s warning, BAL has appeared unaffected, decreasing in value only by 0.13% based on data from CoinMarketCap. At the time of writing, the ERC-20 token is exchanging hands at $5.35, with its market cap value set at $248,354,921, representing only a 0.11% negative change over the last day.  BAL trading at $5.34 &#124; Source: BALUSD chart on Tradingview.com While it is still too early to determine the effect of the Balancer security problem on BAL’s market performance &#8211; especially with the details still unknown &#8211; these early signs show that BAL may pull through this period, and investors need not panic.  Related Reading: MATIC Advances 6.5% In Last 7 Days – Can It Sustain Gains For Another Week? Is Balancer Experiencing Another Crypto Exploit? Like every coin in the cryptoverse, there is no given certainty on market patterns. While Balancer has not revealed the nature of the security risk and has assured the public of full disclosure after a successful mitigation, much speculation is still flying around the crypto community.  Many suspect a smart-contract exploit as it won’t be the first the Ethereum-based DEX would fall victim to such. In August 2020, Balancer was hacked, leading to the loss of $500,000 worth of ETH.  However, compared to 2020, when Balancer was still a budding crypto project, the DeFi protocol currently ranks as the fourth biggest decentralized exchange with a TVL value of $1.49 based on data from the DeFi analytics platform Defillama. If the current fears of exploitation are confirmed, the consequences may be quite drastic for a crypto market that is currently trying to recover after the crash of the FTX exchange late last year.  In November 2022, FTX, formerly one of the biggest cryptocurrency exchanges, collapsed, causing the crypto market to lose billions of dollars. The crash was due to heightened leverage and solvency concerns about FTX&#8217;s trading arm Alameda Research, leading to many investors trying to withdraw their assets from the exchange simultaneously, which resulted in a liquidity crisis and, ultimately, bankruptcy.  Featured Image: ICOnow.net, Chart from Tradingview.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Balancer’s native token, BAL, appears to be holding up despite the platform’s ongoing security issues. On Friday, Jan. 6, the DeFi project <a href="https://twitter.com/Balancer/status/1611363559685898247?s=20&amp;t=SKwGEht-Qiw_03nV5aZ4BQ" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">tweeted</a> a statement asking liquidity providers on its platform to withdraw their tokens from certain pools valued at $6.3 million. </p>
<p>Via their official Twitter handle, the decentralized exchange stated there was a security risk that could not be resolved by the platform&#8217;s emergency DAO. Thus, they advised LPs to immediately remove their assets from all affected pools. </p>

<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">IMPORTANT: Because of a related issue, LPs of the following pools should remove their liquidity ASAP as the issue cannot be mitigated by the emergency DAO. <a href="https://t.co/WcBeBvjdY2" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">https://t.co/WcBeBvjdY2</a></p>
<p>— Balancer (@Balancer) <a href="https://twitter.com/Balancer/status/1611363559685898247?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">January 6, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<h2><strong>BAL Token Holds Its Ground For Now</strong></h2>
<p>Earlier today, Balancer <a href="https://twitter.com/Balancer/status/1611750957657821185?s=20&amp;t=SKwGEht-Qiw_03nV5aZ4BQ" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">confirmed</a> that 85% of the assets in those pools had been moved while still urging LPs to withdraw the remainder as they attempt to resolve the issue at hand. Interestingly, amid the ongoing problem of the decentralized exchange, several investors appeared to have retained their faith in the platform’s native cryptocurrency BAL. </p>
<p>In the last 24 hours following Balancer’s warning, BAL has appeared unaffected, decreasing in value only by 0.13% based on data from CoinMarketCap. At the time of writing, the ERC-20 token is exchanging hands at $5.35, with its market cap value set at $248,354,921, representing only a 0.11% negative change over the last day. </p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-515225 aligncenter" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Screenshot-212-460x272.png" alt="" width="460" height="272" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Screenshot-212-460x272.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Screenshot-212-860x508.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Screenshot-212-768x454.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Screenshot-212-750x443.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Screenshot-212-1140x673.png 1140w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Screenshot-212.png 1517w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px" /></p>
<p style="text-align: center">BAL trading at $5.34 | Source: <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BALUSD/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">BALUSD chart on Tradingview.com</a></p>
<p>While it is still too early to determine the effect of the Balancer security problem on BAL’s market performance &#8211; especially with the details still unknown &#8211; these early signs show that BAL may pull through this period, and investors need not panic. </p>

<h2><strong>Is Balancer Experiencing Another Crypto Exploit?</strong></h2>
<p>Like every coin in the cryptoverse, there is no given certainty on market patterns. While Balancer has not revealed the nature of the security risk and has assured the public of full disclosure after a successful mitigation, much speculation is still flying around the crypto community. </p>
<p>Many suspect a smart-contract exploit as it won’t be the first the Ethereum-based DEX would fall victim to such. In August 2020, Balancer was hacked, leading to the loss of $500,000 worth of ETH. </p>
<p>However, compared to 2020, when Balancer was still a budding crypto project, the DeFi protocol currently ranks as the fourth biggest decentralized exchange with a TVL value of $1.49 based on data from the DeFi analytics platform Defillama.</p>
<p>If the current fears of exploitation are confirmed, the consequences may be quite drastic for a crypto market that is currently trying to recover after the crash of the FTX exchange late last year. </p>
<p>In November 2022, FTX, formerly one of the biggest cryptocurrency exchanges, collapsed, causing the crypto market to lose billions of dollars. The crash was <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/company/behind-the-collapse-of-ftx-and-sbf-traditional-finance-vs-crypto/amp/">due</a> to heightened leverage and solvency concerns about FTX&#8217;s trading arm Alameda Research, leading to many investors trying to withdraw their assets from the exchange simultaneously, which resulted in a liquidity crisis and, ultimately, bankruptcy. </p>
<p>Featured Image: ICOnow.net, Chart from Tradingview.com</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/download-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>MATIC Advances 6.5% In Last 7 Days &#8211; Can It Sustain Gains For Another Week?</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/matic-up-6-5-in-last-7-days/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2023 03:24:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Layer 2]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MATIC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Polygon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[price analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=515184</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The year 2022 saw the value of Polygon’s native token MATIC drop by 64%. But the network started this year on a positive note, with the price shooting up 8% according to the charts. However, can MATIC maintain this momentum?  Related Reading: Ethereum Gains 4.5% in Weekly Timescale As Shanghai Upgrade Nears On-Chain Developments To Play A Big Role For MATIC The Layer 2 ecosystem has been seeing on-chain developments grow. Just before the turn of the new year, Polygon’s first prediction market Bhavish Finance made several records that brought Polygon in the spotlight. Uniswap, a decentralized exchange in the ecosystem, ended 2022 with a $28 billion annual volume.  The DEX surprisingly accomplished that with a sub-$100 million TVL, but as of writing Uniswap’s TVL on Polygon is at $111.21 million, according to the DEX’s public dashboard.  &#160; Chart: Uniswap.org These bullish developments, however, are preceded by big news on Polygon’s NFT arm. DeGods and y00ts, two of the biggest names on Solana, will bridge their collections on Polygon and Ethereum on Q1 of 2023.  This would inevitably bring interest on Polygon’s NFT market, pushing the price of MATIC upwards. However, with the nearing timeline of the ‘Shanghai’ network upgrade of Ethereum, Polygon’s main offering, which are low gas fees due to a better roll-up protocol, will be challenged. With this in mind, it remains to be seen what developments on-chain would differentiate Polygon with Ethereum’s upgrade and other L2 protocols.  Crypto FUD Will Strengthen Bears Long-Term The crypto market has definitely suffered from last year’s big collapses. But the FUD (fear, uncertainty and doubt) that came about these events might be strengthened as Huobi, a centralized exchange, seems to be melting down in real time.  Recent news shows that the CEX will be laying off 20% of its employees. Tweets about Huobi’s situation show that Justin Sun, the touted shadow owner of Huobi, has been converting billions of his crypto to fiat on Binance.  Related Reading: Binance Acquisition Moves See BNB Riding A Wave of Enthusiasm MATIC total market cap at $7 billion on the daily chart &#124; Chart: TradingView.com The exchange itself is also observed to have increased withdrawals in the past couple of days. This led to some speculation that the exchange could be the next FTX. Any negative development here would affect Polygon as insolvency news hit the crypto markets particularly hard.  🟡 What could happen to Huobi? &#8211; Huobi has $80m(4%) outflow in the past 24H, and $133m(7%) in 7D VS their $2B clean assets &#8211; Could halt withdrawals and activities if situation gets out of proportion &#8211; Risk-averse thing to do right now is to withdraw and self-custody 5/ pic.twitter.com/osCCyCzpGa — Rock 🪨 (@DataaRocks) January 6, 2023 Short- to mid-term however, MATIC has some room to grow as the current support at $0.7538 proves to be a barrier for the bears. Previous bullish on-chain developments also help investor sentiment to remain positive. But with the token’s strong correlation with ETH, negative macros could pull the king of altcoins down along with MATIC.  Investors and traders should target $0.8106 price resistance to continue the bullishness of MATIC.  -Featured Image: The Daily Hodl]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The year 2022 saw the value of Polygon’s native token MATIC drop by <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/polygon" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">64%</a>. But the network started this year on a positive note, with the price shooting up 8% according to the charts. However, can MATIC maintain this momentum? </p>

<h2><strong>On-Chain Developments To Play A Big Role For MATIC</strong></h2>
<p>The Layer 2 ecosystem has been seeing on-chain developments grow. Just before the turn of the new year, Polygon’s first prediction market Bhavish Finance made <a href="https://twitter.com/BhavishFinance/status/1608763628337131520?s=20" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">several records</a> that brought Polygon in the spotlight. Uniswap, a decentralized exchange in the ecosystem, <a href="https://twitter.com/0xPolygon/status/1610683710008852481" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">ended</a> 2022 with a $28 billion annual volume. </p>
<p>The DEX surprisingly accomplished that with a sub-$100 million TVL, but as of writing Uniswap’s TVL on Polygon is at <a href="https://info.uniswap.org/#/polygon/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">$111.21 million</a>, according to the DEX’s public dashboard. </p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-515186 size-large" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/a-22-860x333.png" alt="" width="860" height="333" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/a-22-860x333.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/a-22-460x178.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/a-22-768x297.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/a-22-750x290.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/a-22-1140x441.png 1140w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/a-22.png 1228w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" /></p>

<p>These bullish developments, however, are preceded by big news on Polygon’s NFT arm. <a href="https://www.degods.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">DeGods</a> and <a href="https://www.y00ts.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">y00ts</a>, two of the biggest names on Solana, will bridge their collections on Polygon and Ethereum on Q1 of 2023. </p>
<p>This would inevitably bring interest on Polygon’s NFT market, pushing the price of MATIC upwards. However, with the nearing timeline of the <a href="https://guarda.com/academy/blockchain/ethereum-shanghai-upgrade/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">‘Shanghai’ network upgrade</a> of Ethereum, Polygon’s main offering, which are low gas fees due to a better roll-up protocol, will be challenged.</p>
<p>With this in mind, it remains to be seen what developments on-chain would <a href="https://u.today/polygon-matic-fights-for-relevance-amid-growing-l2-competition" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">differentiate</a> Polygon with Ethereum’s upgrade and other L2 protocols. </p>
<h2><strong>Crypto FUD Will Strengthen Bears Long-Term</strong></h2>
<p>The crypto market has definitely suffered from last year’s <a href="https://talkmarkets.com/content/financial/crypto-collapse-5-major-crypto-firms-that-bit-the-dust-in-2022?post=361980" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">big collapses</a>. But the FUD (fear, uncertainty and doubt) that came about these events might be strengthened as Huobi, a centralized exchange, seems to be melting down in real time. </p>
<p>Recent news shows that the CEX will be <a href="https://www.reuters.com/technology/crypto-exchange-huobi-lay-off-20-staff-justin-sun-2023-01-06/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">laying off</a> 20% of its employees. Tweets about Huobi’s situation show that Justin Sun, the touted shadow owner of Huobi, has been <a href="https://twitter.com/mikealfred/status/1611154832471228416?s=20" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">converting</a> billions of his crypto to fiat on Binance. </p>

<p><img loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/tP9VMwl2/" width="2047" height="979" /></p>

<p>The exchange itself is also observed to have <a href="https://twitter.com/DataaRocks/status/1611261229733117953?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">increased withdrawals</a> in the past couple of days. This led to some speculation that the exchange could be the next FTX. Any negative development here would affect Polygon as insolvency news hit the crypto markets particularly hard. </p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en"><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f7e1.png" alt="🟡" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> What could happen to Huobi?</p>
<p>&#8211; Huobi has $80m(4%) outflow in the past 24H, and $133m(7%) in 7D VS their $2B clean assets
&#8211; Could halt withdrawals and activities if situation gets out of proportion
&#8211; Risk-averse thing to do right now is to withdraw and self-custody</p>
<p>5/ <a href="https://t.co/osCCyCzpGa" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/osCCyCzpGa</a></p>
<p>— Rock <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1faa8.png" alt="🪨" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> (@DataaRocks) <a href="https://twitter.com/DataaRocks/status/1611261229733117953?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">January 6, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p>Short- to mid-term however, MATIC has some room to grow as the current support at $0.7538 proves to be a barrier for the bears. </p>
<p>Previous bullish on-chain developments also help investor sentiment to remain positive. But with the token’s strong correlation with ETH, <a href="https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/biden-says-us-economy-headed-new-plateau-amid-recession-fears-2023-01-05/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">negative macros</a> could pull the king of altcoins down along with MATIC. </p>
<p>Investors and traders should target $0.8106 price resistance to continue the bullishness of MATIC. </p>
<p><em>-Featured Image: The Daily Hodl</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/matic-460x229.png" width="460" height="229" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Polkadot (DOT) Inks 10% Rally In Last 7 Days, Makes Case As &#8216;Non-Security&#8217; Asset</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/polkadot-dot-inks-10-rally/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2023 01:20:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DOT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[polkadot]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[security]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=515198</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Polkadot (DOT) is riding a solid bullish momentum that enabled it to stay in the green for the past 24 hours and maintain significant gains in the last seven days. According to tracking from Coingecko, at the time of writing, DOT is changing hands at $4.69, tallying a weekly hike of 10%. Moreover, the 13th largest cryptocurrency in terms of market cap has managed to trim its 30-day losses down to just 11.4% although it is still several miles away from its all-time high value of $54.98%. Related Reading: Ethereum Gains 4.5% in Weekly Timescale As Shanghai Upgrade Nears Holders, though, need to be cautious as some of its technical indicators show that Polkadot’s surge might be short-lived. DOT might soon experience strong selling pressure as indicated by its Relative Strength Index (RSI) which is currently hovering at the 50% region. DOT No Longer A Security Although there’s a lot of uncertainty in DOT’s future as far as trading price is concerned, it would seem that the crypto asset has put itself in a very good position to avoid being choked by strict regulations that threatens the broader crypto space. Following the collapse of the FTX exchange platform that made investors lost a lot of money and the continued proliferation of crypto scams, analysts expect that international governments will soon bring the hammer down to better regulate ownership, selling, buying, trading and use of cryptocurrencies. Polkadot, however, could be safe from this looming threat as according to Web3 Foundation, the altcoin is no longer considered as a security but more like a software. In addition, the team behind the project have been proactively working with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) for a more sensible regulation.  In doing so, DOT might have just saved itself from this market landscape-changing development. DOT total market cap at $5.3 billion on the daily chart &#124; Chart: TradingView.com Polkadot Price Forecast As there is no clear timetable yet for the enforcement of additional regulations for the crypto space, DOT investors need to turn their focus first on what awaits the digital asset in the days to come. Chart: Coincodex Related Reading: MATIC Advances 6.5% In Last 7 Days – Can It Sustain Gains For Another Week? According to Coincodex, Polkadot’s price is poised slightly increase within the next five days as the digital currency is forecasted to change hands at $4.73. The 30-day forecast for the altcoin is also bullish as it is predicted to make a significant jump from its current trading value all the way up to $6.26. -Featured image: Coin Guru]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Polkadot (DOT) is riding a solid bullish momentum that enabled it to stay in the green for the past 24 hours and maintain significant gains in the last seven days.</p>
<p>According to tracking from <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/polkadot" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Coingecko</a>, at the time of writing, DOT is changing hands at $4.69, tallying a weekly hike of 10%.</p>
<p>Moreover, the 13th largest cryptocurrency in terms of market cap has managed to trim its 30-day losses down to just 11.4% although it is still several miles away from its all-time high value of $54.98%.</p>

<p>Holders, though, need to be cautious as some of its technical indicators show that Polkadot’s surge might be short-lived.</p>
<p>DOT might soon experience strong selling pressure as indicated by its Relative Strength Index (RSI) which is currently hovering at the 50% region.</p>
<h2><b>DOT No Longer A Security</b></h2>
<p>Although there’s a lot of uncertainty in DOT’s future as far as trading price is concerned, it would seem that the crypto asset has put itself in a very good position to avoid being choked by strict regulations that threatens the broader crypto space.</p>
<p>Following the collapse of the FTX exchange platform that made investors lost a lot of money and the continued proliferation of crypto scams, analysts expect that international governments will soon bring the hammer down to <a href="https://ambcrypto.com/what-dot-holders-need-to-know-in-case-crypto-regulation-hammer-drops/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">better regulate</a> ownership, selling, buying, trading and use of cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="size-medium wp-image-515199 aligncenter" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/a-24-419x460.png" alt="" width="419" height="460" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/a-24-419x460.png 419w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/a-24.png 568w" sizes="(max-width: 419px) 100vw, 419px" /></p>
<p>Polkadot, however, could be safe from this looming threat as <a href="https://twitter.com/Web3foundation/status/1610947645299736576?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw%7Ctwcamp%5Etweetembed%7Ctwterm%5E1610947645299736576%7Ctwgr%5E768f961b4c8319390557d464c4af91f61802ecce%7Ctwcon%5Es1_&amp;ref_url=https%3A%2F%2Fambcrypto.com%2Fwhat-dot-holders-ne" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">according to Web3 Foundation</a>, the altcoin is no longer considered as a security but more like a software.</p>
<p>In addition, the team behind the project have been proactively working with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) for a more sensible regulation.  In doing so, DOT might have just saved itself from this market landscape-changing development.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/PWS7RROc/" width="2047" height="979" /></p>

<h2><b>Polkadot Price Forecast</b></h2>
<p>As there is no clear timetable yet for the enforcement of additional regulations for the crypto space, DOT investors need to turn their focus first on what awaits the digital asset in the days to come.</p>


<p>According to <a href="https://coincodex.com/crypto/polkadot/price-prediction/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Coincodex</a>, Polkadot’s price is poised slightly increase within the next five days as the digital currency is forecasted to change hands at $4.73.</p>
<p>The 30-day forecast for the altcoin is also bullish as it is predicted to make a significant jump from its current trading value all the way up to $6.26.</p>
<p><em>-Featured image: Coin Guru</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/dott-460x258.png" width="460" height="258" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>XRP Spikes 2% In Past 24 Hours Despite Recent Bearish Developments</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/xrp-up-2-in-24-hours/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 23:20:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoin news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[policy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ripple labs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrp]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=515192</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Ripple has been locked in a bitter court battle with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission regarding whether XRP should be classified as a security or not. Ripple’s CEO, Brad Garlinghouse, recently tweeted about him being optimistic but cautious of what 2023 brings in terms of regulations. Because of this, XRP has been trading sideways, a movement not altered since FTX’s collapse. Adding to the downward pressure is the significant whale activity on the market. According to Whale Alert, whales have been moving hundreds of millions worth of XRP to the open market with the biggest transfer worth $92 million.  Related Reading: Ethereum Gains 4.5% in Weekly Timescale As Shanghai Upgrade Nears However, the market seems bullish despite recent bearish developments as XRP, as of writing, went up by 2% in the past 24 hours. XRP is currently trading at $0.3435, down 0.5% in the last seven days, data by Coingecko shows. Today is the first day of the 118th Congress. While prior efforts at regulatory clarity for crypto in the US have stalled, I am cautiously optimistic that 2023 is the year we will (finally!) see a breakthrough. A thread on why… — Brad Garlinghouse (@bgarlinghouse) January 3, 2023 What XRP’s Case Mean For Crypto And Its Price The day the SEC filed the complaint, December 21, 2020, XRP fell by 67.13% on the charts. However, December 5 proved to be a day XRP holders should rejoice. According to a report, the SEC failed to satisfy the three elements of the Howey Test which determines whether the asset is a security or not.  This is a big win not just for Ripple but for the entire crypto industry as this would legitimize crypto’s place in the financial space. With the company and community hopeful for a win, Ripple released to escrow over 55% of XRP’s total supply out of which is a billion XRP.  Although the market is very hopeful for a win, Garlinghouse’s statement shows a very mixed sentiment about what 2023 will bring for the company and for the world of crypto. But he is very clear on what could – or better yet, should – happen this year; break the status quo in the current U.S. legislation about what crypto should and shouldn’t be or America will lose its innovation leader status.  Related Reading: MATIC Advances 6.5% In Last 7 Days – Can It Sustain Gains For Another Week? XRP total market cap at $17.3 billion on the daily chart &#124; Chart: TradingView.com Investors Should Watch Out For This&#8230; Currently, the sideways market movement could be broken in the next few weeks. As of writing, investors and traders of the token are pushing the price up to test the $0.3680 price resistance range.  With low correlation with Bitcoin and Ethereum, it might only be slightly dampened by bad macroeconomics as recession fears grow.  Crypto market FUD (fear, uncertainty and doubt), however, might become a problem. As of now, two events are sending negative signals to investors of crypto. First is Huobi’s decision to lay-off 20% of its workers, and the second is the Genesis-DCG fiasco.  Any negative developments here might affect XRP’s ability to test its current resistance range. As the situation develops, investors and traders should capitalize on the token’s current bullish momentum.   -Featured Image: The Daily Hodl]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ripple has been <a href="https://beincrypto.com/learn/ripple-vs-sec/#h-ripple-vs-sec-lawsuit-a-detailed-timeline-of-events" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">locked</a> in a bitter court battle with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission regarding whether XRP should be classified as a security or not.</p>
<p>Ripple’s CEO, <a href="https://twitter.com/bgarlinghouse?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Brad Garlinghouse</a>, recently tweeted about him being optimistic but cautious of what 2023 brings in terms of regulations.</p>
<p>Because of this, XRP has been trading sideways, a movement not altered since <a href="https://www.wired.com/story/ftx-collapse-binance-crypto-deal/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">FTX’s collapse</a>. Adding to the downward pressure is the significant whale activity on the market. According to <a href="https://twitter.com/whale_alert" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">Whale Alert</a>, whales have been moving hundreds of millions worth of XRP to the open market with the biggest transfer worth <a href="https://twitter.com/whale_alert/status/1611048312936726528" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">$92 million</a>. </p>

<p>However, the market seems bullish despite recent bearish developments as XRP, as of writing, went up by <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/xrp" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">2%</a> in the past 24 hours. <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">XRP</a> is currently trading at $0.3435, down 0.5% in the last seven days, data by Coingecko shows.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Today is the first day of the 118th Congress. While prior efforts at regulatory clarity for crypto in the US have stalled, I am cautiously optimistic that 2023 is the year we will (finally!) see a breakthrough. A thread on why…</p>
<p>— Brad Garlinghouse (@bgarlinghouse) <a href="https://twitter.com/bgarlinghouse/status/1610352765129338880?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">January 3, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<h2><strong>What XRP’s Case Mean For Crypto And Its Price</strong></h2>
<p>The day the SEC filed the complaint, December 21, 2020, XRP fell by 67.13% on the charts. However, December 5 proved to be a day XRP holders should rejoice. According to a <a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/ripple-vs-sec-case-closure-soon/#Whats_the_importance_of_the_Ripple_vs_SEC_court_ruling" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">report</a>, the SEC failed to satisfy the three elements of the <a href="https://www.investopedia.com/terms/h/howey-test.asp" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Howey Test</a> which determines whether the asset is a security or not. </p>
<p>This is a big win not just for Ripple but for the entire crypto industry as this would legitimize crypto’s place in the financial space. With the company and community hopeful for a win, Ripple released to escrow over 55% of XRP’s total supply out of which is a billion XRP. </p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="size-medium wp-image-515194 aligncenter" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/a-23-460x271.png" alt="" width="460" height="271" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/a-23-460x271.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/a-23.png 548w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px" /></p>
<p>Although the market is very hopeful for a win, Garlinghouse’s <a href="https://twitter.com/bgarlinghouse/status/1610352765129338880?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">statement</a> shows a very mixed sentiment about what 2023 will bring for the company and for the world of crypto. </p>
<p>But he is very clear on what could – or better yet, should – happen this year; break the status quo in the current U.S. legislation about what crypto should and shouldn’t be or America will lose its innovation leader status. </p>


<h2><strong>Investors Should Watch Out For This&#8230;</strong></h2>
<p>Currently, the sideways market movement could be broken in the next few weeks. As of writing, investors and traders of the token are pushing the price up to test the $0.3680 price resistance range. </p>
<p>With low correlation with Bitcoin and Ethereum, it might only be slightly dampened by bad macroeconomics as <a href="https://www.ctpublic.org/2023-01-06/the-u-s-job-market-is-still-healthy-but-its-slowing-down-as-recession-fears-mount" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">recession fears</a> grow. </p>
<p>Crypto market FUD (fear, uncertainty and doubt), however, might become a problem. As of now, two events are sending negative signals to investors of crypto. First is Huobi’s <a href="https://ph.news.yahoo.com/crypto-exchange-huobi-lay-off-070546959.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">decision</a> to lay-off 20% of its workers, and the second is the <a href="https://www.crowdfundinsider.com/2023/01/200748-genesis-pondering-bankruptcy-filing-report/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Genesis-DCG fiasco</a>. </p>
<p>Any negative developments here might affect XRP’s ability to test its current resistance range. As the situation develops, investors and traders should capitalize on the token’s current bullish momentum.  </p>
<p><em>-Featured Image: The Daily Hodl</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XRP-460x231.png" width="460" height="231" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cardano Whales Start 2023 With Accumulation Trend That Could Be Bullish For ADA</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/analysis/ada/cardano-whales-start-2023-with-accumulation/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Best Owie]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 23:00:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[ADA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[adausd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADAUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano performance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=515120</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Cardano (ADA) has seen some pretty tragic price action in the last couple of months, which has dragged its price down toward two-year lows. It still continues to maintain this downtrend and is barely moving, just like the rest of the crypto market, but some developments among large ADA investors could see some bullish momentum for the digital asset. Cardano Whales Begin Accumulating In New Year Toward the end of 2022 when momentum in the crypt market was dropping, there had been some selling from large ADA investors. This was not out of the ordinary as the holidays have historically triggered selling and profit-taking.  Related Reading: MATIC Holders Suffer Massive Losses, Here’s How Many Wallets Are In The Red Cardano whales had sold over 569 million ADA during this time. The result was more selling pressure on the digital asset that dragged its price down below $0.25, making its lowest price point since early 2021. As Santiment notes, this saw the total holdings of investors holding between 1 million and 100 million ADA on their balances drop drastically just as 2022 drew to a close. ADA whales increase holdings &#124; Source: Santiment However, this investor class seems to have entered the new year with renewed vigor as they have already begun buying back the tokens they had dumped. The report shows that in the first five days of 2023, these large investors have already added more than 217 million ADA to their stash. This brought the percentage of supply that they now hold back up to the 57.22% level, not the highest it’s ever been, but certainly an encouraging figure. ADA Enjoys The Spoils Of Accumulation The price of ADA is already reacting to the number of coins that these Cardano whales are buying. Over the last 24 hours, the cryptocurrency has jumped back into the green, and its price has already moved above $0.27 once more. Related Reading: Ethereum Could Jump 27% To Trade At $1,600, How Is This Possible? A continuation of the accumulation trend could possibly lead to a much larger break out for the digital asset, especially now that investor sentiment is doing much better. If this happens, a 10% upside that pushes ADA’s price above $0.3 will be easily achieved. ADA price trading at $0.26 &#124; Source: ADAUSD on TradingView.com Perhaps more important is the fact that the bulls are already mounting support at the $0.26 level. The successful switch from a resistance point to a support point also shows the determination of the bulls to continue the uptrend. However, there is still the threat of bears dragging down the price of the digital asset, especially with trading volume not growing as expected. Another fall below $0.25 will likely end up putting ADA’s price at pre-2021 levels. Follow Best Owie on Twitter for market insights, updates, and the occasional funny tweet… Featured image from Forbes, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="p2">Cardano (ADA) has seen some pretty tragic price action in the last couple of months, which has dragged its price down toward two-year lows. It still continues to maintain this downtrend and is barely moving, just like the rest of the crypto market, but some developments among large ADA investors could see some bullish momentum for the digital asset.</p>
<h2 class="p2">Cardano Whales Begin Accumulating In New Year</h2>
<p class="p2">Toward the end of 2022 when momentum in the crypt market was dropping, there had been some selling from large ADA investors. This was not out of the ordinary as the holidays have historically triggered selling and profit-taking. </p>

<p class="p2">Cardano whales had sold over 569 million ADA during this time. The result was more selling pressure on the digital asset that dragged its price down below $0.25, making its lowest price point since early 2021. As <a href="https://twitter.com/santimentfeed/status/1611168969301581824?s=20&amp;t=tgbZ4ZsPFqrAcTq5ksYzIA" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">Santiment</a> notes, this saw the total holdings of investors holding between 1 million and 100 million ADA on their balances drop drastically just as 2022 drew to a close.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-515122 aligncenter" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Cardano-ADA-460x297.jpeg" alt="Cardano (ADA)" width="460" height="297" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Cardano-ADA-460x297.jpeg 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Cardano-ADA-860x556.jpeg 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Cardano-ADA-768x497.jpeg 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Cardano-ADA-1536x993.jpeg 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Cardano-ADA-2048x1324.jpeg 2048w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Cardano-ADA-750x485.jpeg 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Cardano-ADA-1140x737.jpeg 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px" /></p>

<p class="p2">However, this investor class seems to have entered the new year with renewed vigor as they have already begun buying back the tokens they had dumped. The report shows that in the first five days of 2023, these large investors have already added more than 217 million ADA to their stash. This brought the percentage of supply that they now hold back up to the 57.22% level, not the highest it’s ever been, but certainly an encouraging figure.</p>
<h2 class="p2">ADA Enjoys The Spoils Of Accumulation</h2>
<p class="p2">The price of ADA is already reacting to the number of coins that these Cardano whales are buying. Over the last 24 hours, the cryptocurrency has jumped back into the green, and its price has already moved above $0.27 once more.</p>

<p class="p2">A continuation of the accumulation trend could possibly lead to a much larger break out for the digital asset, especially now that investor sentiment is doing much better. If this happens, a 10% upside that pushes ADA’s price above $0.3 will be easily achieved.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/U19SfWVn/" alt="Cardano (ADA) price chart from TradingView.com" width="3284" height="1646" /></p>

<p class="p2">Perhaps more important is the fact that the bulls are already mounting support at the $0.26 level. The successful switch from a resistance point to a support point also shows the determination of the bulls to continue the uptrend.</p>
<p class="p2">However, there is still the threat of bears dragging down the price of the digital asset, especially with trading volume not growing as expected. Another fall below $0.25 will likely end up putting ADA’s price at pre-2021 levels.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Cardano-460x259.jpg" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>AVAX Value Drops By 2% Following Grayscale Removal of Avalanche From Large Cap Fund</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/altcoin/avax-drops-2-as-grayscale-rebalances-portfolio/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samuel Edyme]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 23:00:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Avalanche (Avax)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AVAX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AVAXUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[grayscale]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=515178</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[In its latest quarterly update, Grayscale announced the rebalancing of funds for the fourth quarter of 2022. As part of the rebalancing, Grayscale sold off a certain amount of its Digital Large Cap Fund and dumped its held tokens, including Avalanche Network token AVAX.   AVAX has slipped by 2% following the sell-off in the past 24 hours. According to Grayscale, the sold-off AVAX tokens were replaced with the purchase of the existing fund components in proportion to their respective weightings. Grayscale Purchased And Existing Tokens The AVAX sell-off was only part of the CoinDesk Large Cap Select Index and Grayscale Digital Large Cap Fund. In its CoinDesk Smart Contract Platform Select Ex ETH Index and Grayscale Smart Contract Platform Ex-Ethereum Fund portfolio rebalancing, the company sold off Algorand native token ALGO. In its CoinDesk DeFi Select Index methodology, Grayscale adjusted its DeFi Fund’s portfolio and purchased Synthetix (SNX) after selling some existing assets.  Related Reading: Grayscale Says It May Return 20% Of Investor Capital, Bitcoin Refuses To Budge As of now, the Grayscale portfolio fund now includes 65% Bitcoin (BTC), 30% Ethereum (ETH), 1.86% Cardano (ADA), 1.39% Polygon (MATIC), and 1% Solana (SOL). Meanwhile, its DeFi Fund’s Fund Components include  65.05% Uniswap (UNI), 12.39% Aave (AAVE), 8.15% MakerDAO (MKR), 6.02% Synthetix (SNX), 4.58% Curve DAO Token (CRV), and 3.81% Compound (COMP).  Since July, Grayscale has been carefully monitoring the CoinDesk Large Cap Select Index. The index launched in April tracks the market capitalization-loaded performance of “the largest and most liquid digital assets.” During Grayscale usage of the Index, the quarterly scheduled rebalancing resulted in the dumping of Bitcoin Cash (BCH), Litecoin (LTC), Chainlink (LINK), Polkadot (DOT), and more Uniswap (UNI) purchases. AVAX Slips After Grayscale Dumped Before the sell-off, AVAX was still sitting at a $12 zone; however, after Grayscale dumped its holdings, the AVAX token dropped by 2% and traded at $11.39 Friday morning.  AVAX has appreciated over the past months. It has surged from around $9 to $13. Notably, Grayscale fund’s portfolio, which currently has $163 million in assets under management (AUM), only held a small portion of AVAX tokens. As of September 30, AVAX made up less than 1% of the company’s fund’s assets, according to its previous quarterly report. Related Reading: Avalanche: Will 2023 Bring A Fruitful Recovery For The AVAX Ecosystem? There was no significant move from ALGO, which was also removed from the Grayscale portfolio fund. It fell from a range of $0.17 to $0.15. As of the time of writing, ALGO currently trades at $11.73 with a 24-hour trading volume of $45 million.  On the other hand, AVAX seems to be gaining momentum to the upside at the time of writing as it has already formed a retracement; a reversal is likely to happen. AVAX currently trades at $11.73, down by 0.8% in the last 24 hours, with a trading volume of $125 million over the same period.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In its latest quarterly update, Grayscale announced the rebalancing of funds for the fourth quarter of 2022. As part of the rebalancing, Grayscale sold off a certain amount of its Digital Large Cap Fund and dumped its held tokens, including <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/avalanche-exits-2022-with-10-decline/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Avalanche</a> Network token AVAX.  </p>
<p>AVAX has slipped by 2% following the sell-off in the past 24 hours. According to Grayscale, the sold-off AVAX tokens were replaced with the purchase of the existing fund components in proportion to their respective weightings.</p>
<h2>Grayscale Purchased And Existing Tokens</h2>
<p>The AVAX <a href="https://twitter.com/grayscale/status/1611392521552252928?s=46&amp;t=zcoKrOKGfdFdEzvz_iTrWg" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">sell-off</a> was only part of the CoinDesk Large Cap Select Index and Grayscale Digital Large Cap Fund. In its CoinDesk Smart Contract Platform Select Ex ETH Index and Grayscale Smart Contract Platform Ex-Ethereum Fund portfolio rebalancing, the company sold off Algorand native token ALGO.</p>
<p>In its CoinDesk DeFi Select Index methodology, Grayscale adjusted its DeFi Fund’s portfolio and purchased Synthetix (SNX) after selling some existing assets. </p>

<p>As of now, the Grayscale portfolio fund now includes 65% <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-exchange-transaction-4-low-bottom/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a> (BTC), 30% Ethereum (ETH), 1.86% Cardano (ADA), 1.39% Polygon (MATIC), and 1% Solana (SOL). Meanwhile, its DeFi Fund’s Fund Components include  65.05% Uniswap (UNI), 12.39% Aave (AAVE), 8.15% MakerDAO (MKR), 6.02% Synthetix (SNX), 4.58% Curve DAO Token (CRV), and 3.81% Compound (COMP). </p>
<p>Since July, Grayscale has been carefully monitoring the CoinDesk Large Cap Select Index. The index launched in April tracks the market capitalization-loaded performance of “the largest and most liquid digital assets.”</p>
<p>During Grayscale usage of the Index, the quarterly scheduled rebalancing resulted in the dumping of Bitcoin Cash (BCH), Litecoin (LTC), Chainlink (LINK), Polkadot (DOT), and more <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/uniswap/uniswap-saved-vulnerability-security-firm/">Uniswap</a> (UNI) purchases.</p>
<h2>AVAX Slips After Grayscale Dumped</h2>
<p>Before the sell-off, <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/avalanche-recovery-for-the-ecosystem/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">AVAX</a> was still sitting at a $12 zone; however, after Grayscale dumped its holdings, the AVAX token dropped by 2% and traded at $11.39 Friday morning. </p>
<p>AVAX has appreciated over the past months. It has surged from around $9 to $13. Notably, Grayscale fund’s portfolio, which currently has $163 million in assets under management (AUM), only held a small portion of AVAX tokens. As of September 30, AVAX made up less than 1% of the company’s fund’s assets, according to its previous quarterly report.</p>

<p>There was no significant move from ALGO, which was also removed from the Grayscale portfolio fund. It fell from a range of $0.17 to $0.15. As of the time of writing, ALGO currently trades at $11.73 with a 24-hour trading volume of $45 million. </p>
<img loading="lazy" class="size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/YVOFy1sS/" alt="AVAX price chart on TradingView" width="1280" height="538" />
<p>On the other hand, AVAX seems to be gaining momentum to the upside at the time of writing as it has already formed a retracement; a reversal is likely to happen. AVAX currently trades at $11.73, down by 0.8% in the last 24 hours, with a trading volume of $125 million over the same period.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/AVALANCHE-AVAX-460x230.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
