<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
>

<channel>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.newsbtc.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<description>Bitcoin &#38; cryptocurrency news today, price &#38; technical analysis</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 05:44:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>XRP Price Set To Skyrocket, Expert Predicts $3.82 Target Amidst Bullish Sentiment</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/xrp-price-set-to-skyrocket-expert-predict-3-82-target-amidst-bullish-sentiment/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 01:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrp]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrpusdt]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=533363</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The XRP community has been relatively quiet lately, and according to crypto analyst Dark Defender, this could be a positive sign that XRP is ready for a breakout. Dark Defender, a cryptocurrency analyst and researcher, has analyzed patterns in XRP&#8217;s price movements and predicts that a break above the resistance line could happen anytime between now and August 2023. Related Reading: DeFi’s Rising Star: Why Rook DAO Is The Best-Performing Token Of 2023 Poised For Explosive Growth? Once XRP breaks through the resistance line, Dark Defender predicts the price will hit $1.33 and then $3.82. These projections are based on technical analysis and historical patterns.  Moreover, XRP is facing two significant resistances in the short term before it can hope to reach the $0.500 mark and rally further to its annual high of $0.5838, reached in March 2023. These resistances are represented by the yellow line, which denotes the 200-day Moving Average (MA), and the brown line, which represents the 50-day MA, as shown in the chart below. Furthermore, despite XRP&#8217;s current downtrend, crypto analyst Dark Defender has noted that the token has shown resilience by bouncing back from its primary support level of $0.42. This rebound can be attributed, in part, to the Relative Strength Index (RSI) reaching an oversold zone in the daily indicator, suggesting that XRP may have been oversold and due for a rebound. In the short term, Dark Defender has identified a crucial resistance level for XRP at $0.4696. This level will need to be overcome by XRP&#8217;s bulls if the token is to continue its potential bullish momentum and push above the $0.500 line. XRP Ledger Sees Explosive Growth In NFTs And Tokenization It has been approximately six months since the introduction of XLS-20 to the XRP Ledger. XLS-20 includes extensions to the XRP Ledger that support a native NFT type and operations to enumerate, transfer and hold such tokens, providing native NFT functionality to the platform. Since the amendment was proposed, voted on, and approved by the validator community, the XRP Ledger&#8217;s developer and creator ecosystem has flourished. This has resulted in new projects, use cases, and collections on the XRPL, showcasing the platform&#8217;s potential for NFTs. Since the mainnet launch of XLS-20, over 1.3 million NFTs have been minted, with over 740,000 offers to buy NFTs accepted. This has made the XRP Ledger among the top 10 blockchains for NFT sales volume and transactions. The top three natively built marketplaces by XRP volume are OnXRP, Sologenic, and xrp.cafe, which account for over 80% of total NFT transactions on the Ledger. In addition, over 5,000 total issuers and hundreds of NFT collections spanning various use cases, from events and ticketing to music and IP access rights, to the metaverse and loyalty rewards, to real estate and beyond. The top three NFT collections by lifetime sales volume, including IOUs, are XPUNKS, Bored Apes XRP, and The Bearable Bulls. Alongside NFT projects, infrastructure apps and tools are being developed on the XRPL to provide additional resources and support to the developer community. This includes tokenization infrastructure and tooling, which can help facilitate the creation and management of tokens on the XRP Ledger. Related Reading: Algorand (ALGO) Price Turns Positive, Bulls Eyeing Further Gains? David Schwartz, CTO of Ripple, has stated that the growth of NFTs on the XRP Ledger is a testament to the platform&#8217;s versatility and potential for innovation. He believes that the XRPL is uniquely positioned to support the development of new use cases and applications for blockchain technology and that the growth of the NFT ecosystem on the platform is just the beginning. Featured image from iStock, a chart from TradingView.com ]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The XRP community has been relatively quiet lately, and according to crypto analyst Dark Defender, this could be a positive sign that XRP is ready for a breakout. Dark Defender, a cryptocurrency analyst and researcher, has <a href="https://twitter.com/DefendDark/status/1656929451681239040?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">analyzed </a>patterns in XRP&#8217;s price movements and predicts that a break above the resistance line could happen anytime between now and August 2023.</p>

<h2><b>Poised For Explosive Growth?</b></h2>
<p>Once XRP breaks through the resistance line, Dark Defender predicts the price will hit $1.33 and then $3.82. These projections are based on technical analysis and historical patterns. </p>
<p>Moreover, XRP is facing two significant resistances in the short term before it can hope to reach the $0.500 mark and rally further to its annual high of $0.5838, reached in March 2023. These resistances are represented by the yellow line, which denotes the 200-day Moving Average (MA), and the brown line, which represents the 50-day MA, as shown in the chart below.</p>
<img decoding="async" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/VCOM7vXk/" alt="XRP" width="1814" height="858" loading="lazy"/>
<p>Furthermore, despite XRP&#8217;s current downtrend, crypto analyst Dark Defender has noted that the token has shown resilience by bouncing back from its primary support level of $0.42. This rebound can be attributed, in part, to the Relative Strength Index (RSI) reaching an oversold zone in the daily indicator, suggesting that XRP may have been oversold and due for a rebound.</p>
<p>In the short term, Dark Defender has identified a crucial resistance level for XRP at $0.4696. This level will need to be overcome by XRP&#8217;s bulls if the token is to continue its potential bullish momentum and push above the $0.500 line.</p>
<b>XRP Ledger Sees Explosive Growth In NFTs And Tokenization</b>
<p>It has been approximately six months since the <a href="https://dev.to/ripplexdev/six-months-on-mainnet-the-growth-of-nfts-and-tokenization-on-the-xrp-ledger-2jb5" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">introduction of XLS-20</a> to the XRP Ledger. XLS-20 includes extensions to the XRP Ledger that support a native NFT type and operations to enumerate, transfer and hold such tokens, providing native NFT functionality to the platform.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">1/ XLS-20 went live on mainnet six months ago, bringing native NFT functionality to the <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/XRPLedger?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#XRPLedger</a>. The developer and creator communities have been thriving with exciting projects, new use cases and collections coming to life on the <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/XRPL?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#XRPL</a>. <a href="https://t.co/tmmb2vo31t" rel="nofollow">https://t.co/tmmb2vo31t</a></p>
<p>&mdash; RippleX (@RippleXDev) <a href="https://twitter.com/RippleXDev/status/1658251389859147776?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">May 15, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p></p>
<p>Since the amendment was proposed, voted on, and approved by the validator community, the XRP Ledger&#8217;s developer and creator ecosystem has flourished. This has resulted in new projects, use cases, and collections on the XRPL, showcasing the platform&#8217;s potential for NFTs.</p>
<p>Since the mainnet launch of XLS-20, over 1.3 million NFTs have been minted, with over 740,000 offers to buy NFTs accepted. This has made the XRP Ledger among the top 10 blockchains for NFT sales volume and transactions. The top three natively built marketplaces by XRP volume are OnXRP, Sologenic, and xrp.cafe, which account for over 80% of total NFT transactions on the Ledger.</p>
<p>In addition, over 5,000 total issuers and hundreds of NFT collections spanning various use cases, from events and ticketing to music and IP access rights, to the metaverse and loyalty rewards, to real estate and beyond. The top three NFT collections by lifetime sales volume, including IOUs, are XPUNKS, Bored Apes XRP, and The Bearable Bulls.</p>
<p>Alongside NFT projects, infrastructure apps and tools are being developed on the XRPL to provide additional resources and support to the developer community. This includes tokenization infrastructure and tooling, which can help facilitate the creation and management of tokens on the XRP Ledger.</p>

<p>David Schwartz, CTO of Ripple, has stated that the growth of NFTs on the XRP Ledger is a testament to the platform&#8217;s versatility and potential for innovation. He believes that the XRPL is uniquely positioned to support the development of new use cases and applications for blockchain technology and that the growth of the NFT ecosystem on the platform is just the beginning.</p>
<p>Featured image from iStock, a chart from TradingView.com </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/iStock-1369021012-460x300.jpg" width="460" height="300" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cardano Price Rejected at $0.36, How Long Will The Correction Last?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/cardano/cardano-price-rejected-at-0-36-how-long-will-the-correction-last/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[anushsamal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 00:00:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cardano]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[adausd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADAUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=533360</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The price of Cardano has been following a bearish trajectory for the past couple of weeks. However, in recent trading sessions, there were bullish attempts as buyers tried to push the price higher. Unfortunately, selling pressure emerged again, causing Cardano to trade near its crucial support level. The technical outlook for ADA is bearish. The chart&#8217;s demand and accumulation indicators have been depreciating, suggesting a lack of buying interest in the market. Moreover, the broader market strength remains uncertain, with Bitcoin recently dipping below the $27,000 price zone in the recent past. This has resulted in many major altcoins, including Cardano, facing rejection at their immediate resistance levels. Related Reading: Why Litecoin Is The Most Undervalued Asset in Crypto Currently, Cardano finds itself at a critical price point. If it manages to move above the overhead resistance, it could initiate a recovery for the coin. However, if the price falls from its current level, it would struggle to sustain itself above the crucial support, potentially leading to bearish dominance. If Bitcoin trades above the $27,000 mark, it might positively impact Cardano&#8217;s price and potentially lead to a recovery. However, for a significant price turnaround, it is essential for buying confidence to resurface in the market. The decline in Cardano&#8217;s market capitalization indicates that sellers have dominated the market. Cardano Price Analysis: One-Day Chart At the time of writing, Cardano (ADA) was priced at $0.367. Over the past 24 hours, ADA experienced a 1.3% decline in price, while there hasn&#8217;t been any significant movement on the weekly chart. The key resistance level for ADA is at $0.37, which has proven to be a strong barrier that the bulls have failed to break through in recent weeks. If ADA surpasses the $0.37 resistance, it can reach $0.39, resulting in a significant price increase. However, if the price falls from its current level, it could drop below the crucial support line of $0.35, which the bulls have been defending thus far. The trading volume of ADA in the last session was in red, indicating a decrease in the number of buyers participating in the market. Technical Analysis Throughout the month, ADA has displayed weak buying strength. This is evident from the Relative Strength Index (RSI) staying below the 40-mark, indicating a prevalence of selling strength rather than buying strength. However, if ADA surpasses its immediate price ceiling, it could lead to a recovery in buying strength. Moreover, ADA has also fallen below its 20-Simple Moving Average (SMA) line, further confirming that sellers have been driving the price momentum in the market. Contrary to previous observations, ADA showed buy signals on the one-day chart. The Awesome Oscillator, which indicates momentum and trend reversal, displayed green histograms associated with buy signals. This suggests a potential price appreciation in the upcoming trading sessions. Related Reading: Historical Crossover Suggests Ethereum (ETH) Top Is In The Bollinger Bands, which represent price fluctuation and volatility, were also parallel and wide. This indicates a higher likelihood of price fluctuations. Featured Image From UnSplash, Charts From TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The price of Cardano has been following a bearish trajectory for the past couple of weeks. However, in recent trading sessions, there were bullish attempts as buyers tried to push the price higher. Unfortunately, selling pressure emerged again, causing Cardano to trade near its crucial support level.</p>
<p>The technical outlook for ADA is bearish. The chart&#8217;s demand and accumulation indicators have been depreciating, suggesting a lack of buying interest in the market.</p>
<p>Moreover, the broader market strength remains uncertain, with Bitcoin recently dipping below the $27,000 price zone in the recent past. This has resulted in many major altcoins, including Cardano, facing rejection at their immediate resistance levels.</p>

<p>Currently, Cardano finds itself at a critical price point. If it manages to move above the overhead resistance, it could initiate a recovery for the coin. However, if the price falls from its current level, it would struggle to sustain itself above the crucial support, potentially leading to bearish dominance.</p>
<p>If Bitcoin trades above the $27,000 mark, it might positively impact Cardano&#8217;s price and potentially lead to a recovery.</p>
<p>However, for a significant price turnaround, it is essential for buying confidence to resurface in the market. The decline in Cardano&#8217;s market capitalization indicates that sellers have dominated the market.</p>
<h2>Cardano Price Analysis: One-Day Chart</h2>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-533366 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ADAUSD_2023-05-17_01-38-37.png" alt="Cardano" width="1816" height="830" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ADAUSD_2023-05-17_01-38-37.png 1816w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ADAUSD_2023-05-17_01-38-37-460x210.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ADAUSD_2023-05-17_01-38-37-860x393.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ADAUSD_2023-05-17_01-38-37-768x351.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ADAUSD_2023-05-17_01-38-37-1536x702.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ADAUSD_2023-05-17_01-38-37-750x343.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ADAUSD_2023-05-17_01-38-37-1140x521.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1816px) 100vw, 1816px"/>
<p>At the time of writing, Cardano (ADA) was priced at $0.367. Over the past 24 hours, ADA experienced a 1.3% decline in price, while there hasn&#8217;t been any significant movement on the weekly chart. The key resistance level for ADA is at $0.37, which has proven to be a strong barrier that the bulls have failed to break through in recent weeks.</p>
<p>If ADA surpasses the $0.37 resistance, it can reach $0.39, resulting in a significant price increase. However, if the price falls from its current level, it could drop below the crucial support line of $0.35, which the bulls have been defending thus far.</p>
<p>The trading volume of ADA in the last session was in red, indicating a decrease in the number of buyers participating in the market.</p>
<h2>Technical Analysis</h2>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-533367 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ADAUSD_2023-05-17_01-39-06.png" alt="Cardano" width="1816" height="743" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ADAUSD_2023-05-17_01-39-06.png 1816w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ADAUSD_2023-05-17_01-39-06-460x188.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ADAUSD_2023-05-17_01-39-06-860x352.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ADAUSD_2023-05-17_01-39-06-768x314.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ADAUSD_2023-05-17_01-39-06-1536x628.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ADAUSD_2023-05-17_01-39-06-750x307.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ADAUSD_2023-05-17_01-39-06-1140x466.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1816px) 100vw, 1816px"/>
<p>Throughout the month, ADA has displayed weak buying strength. This is evident from the Relative Strength Index (RSI) staying below the 40-mark, indicating a prevalence of selling strength rather than buying strength. However, if ADA surpasses its immediate price ceiling, it could lead to a recovery in buying strength.</p>
<p>Moreover, ADA has also fallen below its 20-Simple Moving Average (SMA) line, further confirming that sellers have been driving the price momentum in the market.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-533368 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ADAUSD_2023-05-17_01-39-30.png" alt="Cardano" width="1816" height="743" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ADAUSD_2023-05-17_01-39-30.png 1816w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ADAUSD_2023-05-17_01-39-30-460x188.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ADAUSD_2023-05-17_01-39-30-860x352.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ADAUSD_2023-05-17_01-39-30-768x314.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ADAUSD_2023-05-17_01-39-30-1536x628.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ADAUSD_2023-05-17_01-39-30-750x307.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ADAUSD_2023-05-17_01-39-30-1140x466.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1816px) 100vw, 1816px"/>
<p>Contrary to previous observations, ADA showed buy signals on the one-day chart. The Awesome Oscillator, which indicates momentum and trend reversal, displayed green histograms associated with buy signals. This suggests a potential price appreciation in the upcoming trading sessions.</p>

<p>The Bollinger Bands, which represent price fluctuation and volatility, were also parallel and wide. This indicates a higher likelihood of price fluctuations.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/traxer-bJTGZrHCIVg-unsplash-460x306.jpg" width="460" height="306" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Jump Trading&#8217;s Covert Operations: How They Made $1.28 Billion From Terra Labs&#8217; Downfall</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/jump-tradings-covert-operations-how-they-made-1-28-billion-from-terra-labs-downfall/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 23:30:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Terra]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Terraform Labs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=533350</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[According to recent court filings by the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), the Chicago-based firm Jump Trading LLC secretly propped up Terra (UST), the algorithmic stablecoin created by Do Kwon, a year before its eventual collapse. The Wall Street Journal reported on the findings, revealing that Jump Trading made a staggering $1.28 billion from the scheme. Jump Trading is a Chicago-based global trading firm specializing in various financial products, including equities, futures, options, currencies, and cryptocurrencies. The company was founded in 1999 by a group of former pit traders and has since grown to become one of the largest trading firms in the world, with offices in Chicago, New York, London, Singapore, and Shanghai. Related Reading: Why Litecoin Is The Most Undervalued Asset in Crypto The Dark Side Of Terra&#8217;s Collapse The court filings shed light on the covert operations of Jump Trading, which allegedly used its trading power to prop up the UST project without any public disclosure. The stablecoin&#8217;s peg was artificially maintained, leading to a prolonged &#8220;Ponzi scheme&#8221; that eventually led to its downfall. &#160; The filings also reveal the role of Do Kwon, the founder of Terra and UST, in the scheme. Kwon is accused of falsely claiming the project&#8217;s stability and performance, leading investors to pour money into the project. According to the Wall Street Journal, Kwon allegedly used the funds to prop up the UST peg, prolonging the Ponzi scheme and allowing Jump Trading to profit massively.  Furthermore, the Chicago-based firm allegedly purchased over 62 million stablecoin tokens, pushing its price back to $1 and propping up the Ponzi scheme. The revelations raise questions about the transparency and integrity of the UST project. Terra Labs And Jump Trading Under Scrutiny Per the report, after the stablecoin&#8217;s recovery, Do Kwon touted the algorithm&#8217;s “self-healing” abilities and its ability to maintain a dollar peg through a code-enabled balancing act with sister cryptocurrency Luna. However, the court filings suggest that the recovery was due to Jump Trading&#8217;s covert operations rather than the algorithm&#8217;s inherent stability. The report reveals that Jump Trading had a three-year loan agreement with Terraform Labs for 30 million Luna tokens with a 2% annualized interest payable in Luna tokens. The loan agreement was part of a larger deal that saw Terraform Labs receive a multimillion-dollar cash injection from Jump Trading in exchange for allowing the firm to buy Luna tokens for 30, 40, and 50 cents over three years.  The court filings also include an email from Kwon to investors, in which he states that Terraform Labs had made an &#8220;important arrangement&#8221; with Jump Trading and asked investors to keep quiet about it. The revelations raise serious questions about the transparency and integrity of the UST project and the crypto industry. Furthermore, Jump Trading has not been accused of wrongdoing about the UST project, although the firm is facing a class action lawsuit from an investor over its alleged role in propping up the stablecoin. The company has not commented on the allegations. Related Reading: Shiba Inu Event Raises The Bar With A 26,000% Surge In 24-Hour Burn Rate Featured image from Unsplash, a chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>According to recent court filings by the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), the Chicago-based firm Jump Trading LLC secretly propped up Terra (UST), the algorithmic stablecoin created by Do Kwon, a year before its eventual collapse. The Wall Street Journal <a href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/jump-trading-did-secret-deal-to-prop-up-terrausd-stablecoin-sec-says-11335951" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">reported </a>on the findings, revealing that Jump Trading made a staggering $1.28 billion from the scheme.</p>
<p>Jump Trading is a Chicago-based global trading firm specializing in various financial products, including equities, futures, options, currencies, and cryptocurrencies. The company was founded in 1999 by a group of former pit traders and has since grown to become one of the largest trading firms in the world, with offices in Chicago, New York, London, Singapore, and Shanghai.</p>

<h2><b>The Dark Side Of Terra&#8217;s Collapse</b></h2>
<p>The court filings shed light on the covert operations of Jump Trading, which allegedly used its trading power to prop up the UST project without any public disclosure. The stablecoin&#8217;s peg was artificially maintained, leading to a prolonged &#8220;Ponzi scheme&#8221; that eventually led to its downfall.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">The SEC has now directly confirmed that Jump secretly bailed out the UST project, propping up the peg and prolonging the Ponzi without any public disclosure whatsoever. Jump made over $1b in profits through their dealings with TFL and Do Kwon. <a href="https://t.co/SGQwFBppoe" rel="nofollow">https://t.co/SGQwFBppoe</a></p>
<p>&mdash; FatMan (@FatManTerra) <a href="https://twitter.com/FatManTerra/status/1658398203979476993?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">May 16, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The filings also reveal the role of Do Kwon, the founder of Terra and UST, in the scheme. Kwon is accused of falsely claiming the project&#8217;s stability and performance, leading investors to pour money into the project. According to the Wall Street Journal, Kwon allegedly used the funds to prop up the UST peg, prolonging the Ponzi scheme and allowing Jump Trading to profit massively. </p>
<p>Furthermore, the Chicago-based firm allegedly purchased over 62 million stablecoin tokens, pushing its price back to $1 and propping up the Ponzi scheme. The revelations raise questions about the transparency and integrity of the UST project.</p>
<b>Terra Labs And Jump Trading Under Scrutiny</b>
<p>Per the report, after the stablecoin&#8217;s recovery, Do Kwon touted the algorithm&#8217;s “self-healing” abilities and its ability to maintain a dollar peg through a code-enabled balancing act with sister cryptocurrency Luna. However, the court filings suggest that the recovery was due to Jump Trading&#8217;s covert operations rather than the algorithm&#8217;s inherent stability.</p>
<p>The report reveals that Jump Trading had a three-year loan agreement with Terraform Labs for 30 million Luna tokens with a 2% annualized interest payable in Luna tokens. The loan agreement was part of a larger deal that saw Terraform Labs receive a multimillion-dollar cash injection from Jump Trading in exchange for allowing the firm to buy Luna tokens for 30, 40, and 50 cents over three years. </p>
<p>The court filings also include an email from Kwon to investors, in which he states that Terraform Labs had made an &#8220;important arrangement&#8221; with Jump Trading and asked investors to keep quiet about it. The revelations raise serious questions about the transparency and integrity of the UST project and the crypto industry.</p>
<p>Furthermore, Jump Trading has not been accused of wrongdoing about the UST project, although the firm is facing a class action lawsuit from an investor over its alleged role in propping up the stablecoin. The company has not commented on the allegations.</p>

<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/xjrsgJwe/" alt="Terra" width="1813" height="858"/>
<p>Featured image from Unsplash, a chart from TradingView.com </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/iStock-877508718-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Whales Break A Pattern Held Throughout Halving Cycles: Glassnode</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-whales-break-pattern-halving-cycles-glassnode/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hououin Kyouma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 23:00:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Halving]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Halving Cycles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin whales]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[glassnode]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=533309</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[On-chain data from Glassnode shows the Bitcoin whales have recently broken a pattern that was previously held through the halving cycles. Bitcoin Whale Growth Had Previously Been Diminishing With Each Cycle According to data from the on-chain analytics firm Glassnode, the current cycle is displaying an interesting deviation from the rule followed during the last few cycles. Here, the cycles or the &#8220;epochs&#8221; for the cryptocurrency have been defined using the halving events. &#8220;Halvings&#8221; are periodic blockchain events that permanently cut in half the block rewards that the miners receive for solving blocks. These events occur every time 210,000 blocks have been mined on the network, or approximately every four years. The reason they are generally selected as the start and end points for BTC cycles is that they carry profound impact on the economics of the market as the production rate of the asset is cut in half following them. This increase in the scarcity of the asset is a narrative so strong that bull runs have always followed the halving events. The next halving is supposed to take place sometime in the first half of next year. Currently, miners receive 6.25 BTC for every block that they mine, so following this next event, they will only receive 3.125 BTC in their rewards. Now, there have been many patterns that have held throughout the Bitcoin cycles, but one such trend looks to be breaking down with the latest epoch, as the below chart highlights. The total number of whales seems to have gone up by 98% in the current cycle &#124; Source: Glassnode on Twitter The metric of interest here is the percentage growth that the number of whales have registered during each of the epochs. The analytics firm has defined &#8220;whales&#8221; as entities that are holding at least 1,000 BTC in their wallets. Note that entities here don&#8217;t just refer to individual wallets, but also &#8220;a cluster of addresses that are controlled by the same network entity,&#8221; which are &#8220;estimated through advanced heuristics and Glassnode&#8217;s proprietary clustering algorithms.&#8221; Related Reading: Bitcoin Active Addresses Sharply Decline Despite Transaction Demand, Why? From the chart, it&#8217;s apparent that the number of whales went up by 436% in the first cycle, while they only went up by 139% in the second one. The third one saw even less growth at about 91%. This would indicate that with each of these Bitcoin cycles, while the BTC whales had continued to increase in number, their percentage growth had been diminishing. The current cycle, however, seems to have turned out different from these past cycles so far, as the growth in the number of whales has actually been stronger than the previous epoch this time. Related Reading: PEPE Unlikely To Be As Big As DOGE &#38; SHIB, Says Santiment Whales have grown by 98% since the start of the cycle, but it&#8217;s worth noting that there are still around 344 days to go before the next halving event. It now remains to be seen whether the indicator resumes the trend from the last epochs before the end of the current one, or if the cycle will truly end with the pattern being broken. BTC Price At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading around $27,000, down 2% in the last week. BTC has mostly moved sideways in the last few days &#124; Source: BTCUSD on TradingView Featured image from Mike Doherty on Unsplash.com, charts from TradingView.com, Glassnode.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On-chain data from Glassnode shows the Bitcoin whales have recently broken a pattern that was previously held through the halving cycles.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Whale Growth Had Previously Been Diminishing With Each Cycle</h2>
<p>According to data from the on-chain analytics firm <a href="https://twitter.com/glassnode/status/1658198926489427975" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Glassnode</a>, the current cycle is displaying an interesting deviation from the rule followed during the last few cycles.</p>
<p>Here, the cycles or the &#8220;epochs&#8221; for the cryptocurrency have been defined using the halving events. &#8220;<a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/altcoin/analyst-predicts-altcoins-boom-ahead-of-bitcoin-halving-is-it-time-to-invest/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Halvings</a>&#8221; are periodic blockchain events that permanently cut in half the block rewards that the miners receive for solving blocks.</p>
<p>These events occur every time 210,000 blocks have been mined on the network, or approximately every four years. The reason they are generally selected as the start and end points for BTC cycles is that they carry profound impact on the economics of the market as the production rate of the asset is cut in half following them. This increase in the scarcity of the asset is a narrative so strong that <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-bull-run-higher-time-frames-still-bullish-despite-correction/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">bull runs</a> have always followed the halving events.</p>
<p>The next halving is supposed to take place sometime in the first half of next year. Currently, miners receive 6.25 BTC for every block that they mine, so following this next event, they will only receive 3.125 BTC in their rewards.</p>
<p>Now, there have been many patterns that have held throughout the Bitcoin cycles, but one such trend looks to be breaking down with the latest epoch, as the below chart highlights.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone aligncenter" src="https://pbs.twimg.com/media/FwMaaGiXsAALQos?format=jpg&amp;name=4096x4096" alt="Bitcoin Whales Growth Since Halving" width="4081" height="2352"/></p>

<p>The metric of interest here is the percentage growth that the number of whales have registered during each of the epochs. The analytics firm has defined &#8220;<a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/whales-keep-buying-bitcoin-what-they-might-know/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">whales</a>&#8221; as entities that are holding at least 1,000 BTC in their wallets.</p>
<p>Note that entities here don&#8217;t just refer to individual wallets, but also &#8220;a cluster of addresses that are controlled by the same network entity,&#8221; which are &#8220;estimated through advanced heuristics and Glassnode&#8217;s proprietary clustering algorithms.&#8221;</p>

<p>From the chart, it&#8217;s apparent that the number of whales went up by 436% in the first cycle, while they only went up by 139% in the second one. The third one saw even less growth at about 91%.</p>
<p>This would indicate that with each of these Bitcoin cycles, while the BTC whales had continued to increase in number, their percentage growth had been diminishing.</p>
<p>The current cycle, however, seems to have turned out different from these past cycles so far, as the growth in the number of whales has actually been stronger than the previous epoch this time.</p>

<p>Whales have grown by 98% since the start of the cycle, but it&#8217;s worth noting that there are still around 344 days to go before the next halving event. It now remains to be seen whether the indicator resumes the trend from the last epochs before the end of the current one, or if the cycle will truly end with the pattern being broken.</p>
<h2>BTC Price</h2>
<p>At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading around $27,000, down 2% in the last week.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium aligncenter" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/kVROQ5DW/" alt="Bitcoin Price Chart" width="1533" height="911"/></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/mike-doherty-larQY4lhbT4-unsplash-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Shiba Inu Could Rally Another 10% Upon Surpassing This Price Level</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/shiba-inu-could-rally-another-10-upon-surpassing-this-price-level/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[anushsamal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 22:30:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[SHIB]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shiba Inu]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIBUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIBUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=533303</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The price of Shiba Inu has been consolidating, leading to a downward trend. In the last 24 hours, SHIB has lost 2% of its value, and there has been limited movement on the weekly chart. This indicates a decrease in buying interest and an increase in selling pressure. The market for SHIB appears oversold, but there is still a possibility of a price recovery if buyers step in. A small increase in buying activity could result in a significant appreciation of SHIB over the next trading sessions. Related Reading: PEPE Unlikely To Be As Big As DOGE &#38; SHIB, Says Santiment Moreover, there are bullish signals suggesting a potential breakout. The price movements of altcoins, including SHIB, have been similar to Bitcoin, which is currently experiencing uncertainty. For SHIB to see positive momentum, a shift towards a more optimistic buying sentiment is necessary. However, it is worth noting that the market capitalization of SHIB has decreased, indicating that sellers currently have control over the asset&#8217;s price. Shiba Inu Price Analysis: One-Day Chart At the time of writing, SHIB was priced at $0.000008, trading near its resistance level of $0.000009. Prior to reaching $0.000009, the coin may face a minor resistance at $0.0000088. A symmetrical triangle pattern has formed for SHIB, indicating a bullish signal. If SHIB successfully surpasses the $0.0000088 level, it could experience an upward breakout from the triangle, potentially reaching $0.0000096. This would result in a significant rally of over 10% for the coin. Conversely, a decline from the current price would push SHIB down to $0.0000084, leading to a considerable loss. The recent session showed a decrease in trading volume for SHIB, indicating low buying strength. Technical Analysis Throughout most of this month, SHIB has experienced increased selling pressure. The Relative Strength Index (RSI) dropped below the 20-mark, indicating an oversold condition due to a significant decrease in demand. If SHIB manages to surpass immediate resistance levels, buyers may reenter the market. Similarly, the coin&#8217;s price fell below the 20-Simple Moving Average (SMA) line, suggesting that sellers were driving the market&#8217;s momentum. Furthermore, a bearish signal was observed as the 200-SMA (green) crossed over the 50-SMA (yellow), forming a death cross pattern. A death cross typically signifies a downward price movement. Confirming the bearish indications, the meme-coin showed sell signals. The Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD) which indicates price momentum and trend reversals exhibited red histograms which are associated with the sell signals. Related Reading: The Aura Around PEPE Isn’t Good For The Market, Especially Bitcoin – Here’s Why Conversely, the Chaikin Money Flow (CMF) remained positive, with the indicator above the half-line. This indicated that there were more capital inflows than outflows at the time of writing. Featured Image From iStock, Charts From TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The price of Shiba Inu has been consolidating, leading to a downward trend. In the last 24 hours, SHIB has lost 2% of its value, and there has been limited movement on the weekly chart. This indicates a decrease in buying interest and an increase in selling pressure.</p>
<p>The market for SHIB appears oversold, but there is still a possibility of a price recovery if buyers step in. A small increase in buying activity could result in a significant appreciation of SHIB over the next trading sessions.</p>

<p>Moreover, there are bullish signals suggesting a potential breakout. The price movements of altcoins, including SHIB, have been similar to Bitcoin, which is currently experiencing uncertainty.</p>
<p>For SHIB to see positive momentum, a shift towards a more optimistic buying sentiment is necessary. However, it is worth noting that the market capitalization of SHIB has decreased, indicating that sellers currently have control over the asset&#8217;s price.</p>
<h2>Shiba Inu Price Analysis: One-Day Chart</h2>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-533310 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/SHIBUSD_2023-05-16_20-52-16.png" alt="Shiba Inu" width="1817" height="743" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/SHIBUSD_2023-05-16_20-52-16.png 1817w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/SHIBUSD_2023-05-16_20-52-16-460x188.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/SHIBUSD_2023-05-16_20-52-16-860x352.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/SHIBUSD_2023-05-16_20-52-16-768x314.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/SHIBUSD_2023-05-16_20-52-16-1536x628.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/SHIBUSD_2023-05-16_20-52-16-750x307.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/SHIBUSD_2023-05-16_20-52-16-1140x466.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1817px) 100vw, 1817px"/>
<p>At the time of writing, SHIB was priced at $0.000008, trading near its resistance level of $0.000009. Prior to reaching $0.000009, the coin may face a minor resistance at $0.0000088. A symmetrical triangle pattern has formed for SHIB, indicating a bullish signal.</p>
<p>If SHIB successfully surpasses the $0.0000088 level, it could experience an upward breakout from the triangle, potentially reaching $0.0000096. This would result in a significant rally of over 10% for the coin.</p>
<p>Conversely, a decline from the current price would push SHIB down to $0.0000084, leading to a considerable loss. The recent session showed a decrease in trading volume for SHIB, indicating low buying strength.</p>
<h2>Technical Analysis</h2>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-533311 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/SHIBUSD_2023-05-16_20-49-13.png" alt="Shiba Inu" width="1817" height="743" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/SHIBUSD_2023-05-16_20-49-13.png 1817w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/SHIBUSD_2023-05-16_20-49-13-460x188.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/SHIBUSD_2023-05-16_20-49-13-860x352.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/SHIBUSD_2023-05-16_20-49-13-768x314.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/SHIBUSD_2023-05-16_20-49-13-1536x628.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/SHIBUSD_2023-05-16_20-49-13-750x307.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/SHIBUSD_2023-05-16_20-49-13-1140x466.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1817px) 100vw, 1817px"/>
<p>Throughout most of this month, SHIB has experienced increased selling pressure. The Relative Strength Index (RSI) dropped below the 20-mark, indicating an oversold condition due to a significant decrease in demand.</p>
<p>If SHIB manages to surpass immediate resistance levels, buyers may reenter the market. Similarly, the coin&#8217;s price fell below the 20-Simple Moving Average (SMA) line, suggesting that sellers were driving the market&#8217;s momentum.</p>
<p>Furthermore, a bearish signal was observed as the 200-SMA (green) crossed over the 50-SMA (yellow), forming a death cross pattern. A death cross typically signifies a downward price movement.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-533312 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/SHIBUSD_2023-05-16_20-49-35.png" alt="Shiba Inu" width="1817" height="743" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/SHIBUSD_2023-05-16_20-49-35.png 1817w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/SHIBUSD_2023-05-16_20-49-35-460x188.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/SHIBUSD_2023-05-16_20-49-35-860x352.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/SHIBUSD_2023-05-16_20-49-35-768x314.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/SHIBUSD_2023-05-16_20-49-35-1536x628.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/SHIBUSD_2023-05-16_20-49-35-750x307.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/SHIBUSD_2023-05-16_20-49-35-1140x466.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1817px) 100vw, 1817px"/>
<p>Confirming the bearish indications, the meme-coin showed sell signals. The Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD) which indicates price momentum and trend reversals exhibited red histograms which are associated with the sell signals.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/aura-around-pepe-not-good-for-market/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">The Aura Around PEPE Isn’t Good For The Market, Especially Bitcoin – Here’s Why</a></p>
<p>Conversely, the Chaikin Money Flow (CMF) remained positive, with the indicator above the half-line. This indicated that there were more capital inflows than outflows at the time of writing.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/istockphoto-1327123774-612x612-1-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>This Bitcoin Metric Is At A Crucial Junction, Will Bulls Find Victory?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-metric-nearing-crucial-retest-will-bulls-find-victory/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hououin Kyouma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 22:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin bulls]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Retest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin short-term holders]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin SOPR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=533260</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[On-chain data shows a Bitcoin indicator is currently retesting a crucial level that could decide the direction the market takes from here. Bitcoin Short-Term Holder SOPR Has Plunged To A Value Of 1 As pointed out by an analyst in a CryptoQuant post, the short-term holders are currently selling at their break-even mark. The relevant indicator here is the &#8220;Spent Output Profit Ratio&#8221; (SOPR), which tells us whether Bitcoin investors are moving their coins at a profit or at a loss right now. When the value of this metric is greater than 1, it means the average holder in the market is currently selling their coins at a profit. On the other hand, the indicator having values below this threshold suggests the market as a whole is realizing a net amount of loss. The level at which SOPR becomes exactly equal to one implies that the loss realization is exactly equal to the profit realization right now, and hence, the average investor is just breaking even on their investment. In the context of the current topic, the entire market isn&#8217;t of interest; only a segment of it: the &#8220;short-term holders&#8221; (STHs). The STHs include all BTC investors that bought their coins within the last 155 days. Now, here is a chart that shows the trend in the 14-day moving average (MA) Bitcoin SOPR specifically for these STHs over the last few years: The value of the metric seems to have been going down in recent days &#124; Source: CryptoQuant Historically, the Bitcoin STH SOPR has followed a curious pattern. During bullish periods, the indicator has generally stayed above the line where the metric&#8217;s value becomes 1. This makes sense, as rallies allow the STHs many profit-taking opportunities, so the majority should be selling at some gains. Related Reading: PEPE Unlikely To Be As Big As DOGE &#38; SHIB, Says Santiment What&#8217;s actually interesting, though, is that whenever the metric has dropped to the 1 line, it has provided support to the price (and has also made the indicator rebound back above it). Examples of this have been marked with the green arrows in the graph. As already mentioned before, the 1 line signifies the level where the average STH is just breaking even, meaning that they are selling at the price at which they acquired their coins, that is, their cost basis. The reason why this level acts as support during bullish trends is that the investors see their cost basis as a profitable buying opportunity (since they believe the price would go up in the near future). So, a large amount of buying takes place here. Related Reading: Aura Around PEPE Isn’t Good For The Market, Especially Bitcoin – Here’s Why In bear markets, the opposite behavior is seen; the level acts as resistance to the price since selling tends to happen at it. Because of this pattern, the indicator&#8217;s behavior about the 1 level can provide hints about whether a bullish or a bearish regime is active currently. Recently, the indicator has once again dipped to this crucial level. If the Bitcoin rally is still on right now, then the Bitcoin STH SOPR should observe a rebound here. This has already happened once during this rally, as the price felt support at this level back in March. If, however, the retest ends up failing, then it may mean that a transition back to a bearish period may have occurred for the cryptocurrency. BTC Price At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading around $27,000, down 2% in the last week. Looks like BTC has been moving sideways recently &#124; Source: BTCUSD on TradingView Featured image from iStock.com, charts from TradingView.com, CryptoQuant.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On-chain data shows a Bitcoin indicator is currently retesting a crucial level that could decide the direction the market takes from here.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Short-Term Holder SOPR Has Plunged To A Value Of 1</h2>
<p>As pointed out by an analyst in a CryptoQuant <a href="https://cryptoquant.com/insights/quicktake/64636497b1620f2a5804eaaf-Short-term-holders-are-having-their-cost-base-tested-now-will-they-hold" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">post</a>, the short-term holders are currently selling at their break-even mark. The relevant indicator here is the &#8220;<a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-decision-point-asopr-retests-crucial-level/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Spent Output Profit Ratio</a>&#8221; (SOPR), which tells us whether Bitcoin investors are moving their coins at a profit or at a loss right now.</p>
<p>When the value of this metric is greater than 1, it means the average holder in the market is currently selling their coins at a profit. On the other hand, the indicator having values below this threshold suggests the market as a whole is realizing a net amount of loss.</p>
<p>The level at which SOPR becomes exactly equal to one implies that the loss realization is exactly equal to the profit realization right now, and hence, the average investor is just breaking even on their investment.</p>
<p>In the context of the current topic, the entire market isn&#8217;t of interest; only a segment of it: the &#8220;<a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-short-term-holder-profit-nov-2021/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">short-term holders</a>&#8221; (STHs). The STHs include all BTC investors that bought their coins within the last 155 days.</p>
<p>Now, here is a chart that shows the trend in the 14-day moving average (MA) Bitcoin SOPR specifically for these STHs over the last few years:</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone aligncenter" src="https://img.cryptoquant.com/342335/quicktake/TLOGzuc_f8bbf90ee636b62d2abf05cfc06fcc68b093a7e5ea73b649e2e69dadd9570a08.png" alt="Bitcoin STH SOPR" width="1280" height="701"/></p>

<p>Historically, the Bitcoin STH SOPR has followed a curious pattern. During bullish periods, the indicator has generally stayed above the line where the metric&#8217;s value becomes 1. This makes sense, as rallies allow the STHs many profit-taking opportunities, so the majority should be selling at some gains.</p>

<p>What&#8217;s actually interesting, though, is that whenever the metric has dropped to the 1 line, it has provided support to the price (and has also made the indicator rebound back above it). Examples of this have been marked with the green arrows in the graph.</p>
<p>As already mentioned before, the 1 line signifies the level where the average STH is just breaking even, meaning that they are selling at the price at which they acquired their coins, that is, their cost basis.</p>
<p>The reason why this level acts as support during bullish trends is that the investors see their cost basis as a profitable buying opportunity (since they believe the price would go up in the near future). So, a large amount of buying takes place here.</p>

<p>In bear markets, the opposite behavior is seen; the level acts as resistance to the price since selling tends to happen at it. Because of this pattern, the indicator&#8217;s behavior about the 1 level can provide hints about whether a bullish or a bearish regime is active currently.</p>
<p>Recently, the indicator has once again dipped to this crucial level. If the Bitcoin <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-rally-already-hit-top-puell-multiple-says/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">rally</a> is still on right now, then the Bitcoin STH SOPR should observe a rebound here. This has already happened once during this rally, as the price felt support at this level back in March.</p>
<p>If, however, the retest ends up failing, then it may mean that a transition back to a bearish period may have occurred for the cryptocurrency.</p>
<h2>BTC Price</h2>
<p>At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading around $27,000, down 2% in the last week.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium aligncenter" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/0JI6pUUw/" alt="Bitcoin Price Chart" width="1533" height="911"/></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/iStock-1436397713-460x242.jpg" width="460" height="242" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Bullish Structure Holds Firm: $31,000 Breakthrough Imminent?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-bullish-structure-holds-firm-31000-breakthrough-imminent/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 21:00:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=533321</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[In the world of cryptocurrency, the market can be a confusing and volatile place. This is especially true for Bitcoin (BTC), which has seen its fair share of ups and downs in recent days. Jackis, a well-known analyst in the crypto community, has recently commented on the current state of the market, and his words may be of interest to investors. Related Reading: Japan Loses 30% Of Total Crypto Hacks In North Korea, Elliptic Reports Bitcoin&#8217;s Potential For A $31,000 Breakthrough According to Jackis, Bitcoin’s weekly structure remains bullish, which means that despite any potential dips, the overall trend is upward. He suggests that even if there is a deeper pullback, it can be seen as a potential higher low in a bullish trend, which should eventually lead to a break of the $31,000 level. However, Jackis also warns that this bullish trend must be proven, and until then, investors should be cautious. &#160; On the daily chart, Jackis notes that the market has just swept the range low of $26,500, which could be seen as a potential deviation. However, despite this, the overall structure on the daily chart remains bearish, and investors should treat it as such until further highs are reclaimed. He suggests that while there may be a decent buyback from the higher time frame (HTF) range lows, the market is still in a bearish structure. Until there is evidence to the contrary or a convincing low time frame (LTF) structure too long, Jackis expects a new lower low to be seen. Furthermore, according to Jackis, the current structure of the Bitcoin market is bullish, but this could change quickly. He notes that the market is currently trading at a premium, which is known as the Golden Zone, compared to the H4 Swing. To continue pushing higher, the market needs to show real strength at this level. However, the current market conditions are challenging to read, and there are arguments for both bullish and bearish positions. Bitcoin And Ethereum Part Ways, Correlation Hits Lowest Point In Two Years A recent report by Kaiko, a leading provider of market data and insights, has shed light on an interesting trend in the Bitcoin and Ethereum (ETH) markets. According to the report, the correlation between Bitcoin and Ethereum has hit its lowest level since November 2021. The rolling correlation between the two cryptocurrencies has weakened from 96% to 77% since mid-March, indicating that they are increasingly being driven by divergent idiosyncratic factors. The report highlights that Ethereum has lost momentum since the Shapella upgrade, dropping by nearly 14%, while Bitcoin is down by around 11% over the same period. This divergence suggests that the two cryptocurrencies are being influenced by different factors, rather than moving in tandem as they have in the past. As of this writing, the largest cryptocurrency on the market, Bitcoin, is trading at $27,000, which is slightly below its 50-day Moving Average (MA). While BTC has managed to reclaim the $27,000 level, it has seen a minor decline of 1.4% over the last 24 hours. Related Reading: Breaking Above This Level Might Trigger A Bullish Momentum For Ethereum Price Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com ]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In the world of cryptocurrency, the market can be a confusing and volatile place. This is especially true for Bitcoin (BTC), which has seen its fair share of ups and downs in recent days. Jackis, a well-known analyst in the crypto community, has recently commented on the current state of the market, and his words may be of interest to investors.</p>

<h2><b>Bitcoin&#8217;s Potential For A $31,000 Breakthrough</b></h2>
<p><a href="https://twitter.com/i_am_jackis/status/1658392039396978690?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">According </a>to Jackis, Bitcoin’s weekly structure remains bullish, which means that despite any potential dips, the overall trend is upward. He suggests that even if there is a deeper pullback, it can be seen as a potential higher low in a bullish trend, which should eventually lead to a break of the $31,000 level. However, Jackis also warns that this bullish trend must be proven, and until then, investors should be cautious.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">H4:</p>
<p>Surely a decent buyback from the HTF range lows but as of now remains in a bearish structure</p>
<p>Until proven otherwise or until we see a LTF convincing structure to long, we expect a new LL <a href="https://t.co/9VUY79bnPT" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/9VUY79bnPT</a></p>
<p>&mdash; JACKIS (@i_am_jackis) <a href="https://twitter.com/i_am_jackis/status/1658392042718765056?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">May 16, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>On the daily chart, Jackis notes that the market has just swept the range low of $26,500, which could be seen as a potential deviation. However, despite this, the overall structure on the daily chart remains bearish, and investors should treat it as such until further highs are reclaimed. He suggests that while there may be a decent buyback from the higher time frame (HTF) range lows, the market is still in a bearish structure. Until there is evidence to the contrary or a convincing low time frame (LTF) structure too long, Jackis expects a new lower low to be seen.</p>
<p>Furthermore, according to Jackis, the current structure of the Bitcoin market is bullish, but this could change quickly. He notes that the market is currently trading at a premium, which is known as the Golden Zone, compared to the H4 Swing. To continue pushing higher, the market needs to show real strength at this level. However, the current market conditions are challenging to read, and there are arguments for both bullish and bearish positions.</p>
<b>Bitcoin And Ethereum Part Ways, Correlation Hits Lowest Point In Two Years</b>
<p>A recent <a href="https://research.kaiko.com/insights/market-makers-continue-to-reduce-liquidity" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">report </a>by Kaiko, a leading provider of market data and insights, has shed light on an interesting trend in the Bitcoin and Ethereum (ETH) markets. According to the report, the correlation between Bitcoin and Ethereum has hit its lowest level since November 2021. The rolling correlation between the two cryptocurrencies has weakened from 96% to 77% since mid-March, indicating that they are increasingly being driven by divergent idiosyncratic factors.</p>
<p>The report highlights that Ethereum has lost momentum since the Shapella upgrade, dropping by nearly 14%, while Bitcoin is down by around 11% over the same period. This divergence suggests that the two cryptocurrencies are being influenced by different factors, rather than moving in tandem as they have in the past.</p>
<p>As of this writing, the largest cryptocurrency on the market, Bitcoin, is trading at $27,000, which is slightly below its 50-day Moving Average (MA). While BTC has managed to reclaim the $27,000 level, it has seen a minor decline of 1.4% over the last 24 hours.</p>

<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/OHrpChGs/" alt="Bitcoin " width="1813" height="858"/>
<p>Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/iStock-1370952479-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Lido DAO (LDO) Surges Nearly 20% In The Past 7 Days, Here’s Why</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/altcoin/lido-dao-ldo-surges-nearly-20-in-the-past-7-days-heres-why/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Edyme]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 20:30:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LDO]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Lido]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Staking]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=533252</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[In the fast-paced world of cryptocurrencies, Lido DAO (LDO) has made significant waves in the past week, experiencing an impressive surge of nearly 20%. Though the surge comes at a time the global crypto market is not deep in a downtrend, Lido&#8217;s current rally can be attributed to two notable factors. Over the past seven days, LDO has recorded a significant spike, up by 16%. The asset has picked up from trading at a low of below $2 as of May 9 to trading at a high of $2.25, at the time of writing. Meanwhile, over the past 24 hours, the rally continues as the asset is currently up 6.3% with an increasing trading volume. Whale Accumulation Fuels Lido&#8217;s Surge One possible catalyst for Lido&#8217;s remarkable performance over the past 7 days is the increased buying activity by cryptocurrency whales. According to a recent report by Onchain analyst Lookonchain, three whale accounts have been observed accumulating LDO tokens. Related Reading: Lido (LDO) Surges 16% In Single Day, Maintains Dominance In Liquid Staking Market Notably, these whales have been seen transferring their LDO assets from centralized cryptocurrency exchange Binance to personal wallets, indicating a deliberate accumulation strategy. The magnitude of these whale transactions is noteworthy. For instance, one address withdrew a substantial amount of 724,822 LDO tokens, valued at approximately $1.52 million, from Binance for $2.01 per token. Another whale withdrew 655,641 LDO tokens, equivalent to $1.38 million, from Binance at $1.83 per token.  Additionally, a third whale purchased 570,883 LDO tokens using 974,000 USDC for $1.71 on May 12. This influx of capital from these significant players in the market has undoubtedly contributed to the surge in Lido&#8217;s value. Lido V2 Launch Amplifies Momentum Another driving force behind Lido&#8217;s recent upward trend is the launch of Lido V2. This highly anticipated upgrade brings several notable features to the Lido DAO ecosystem, enhancing its appeal to investors and participants. A key highlight of the V2 release is the ability for users to withdraw their staked Ethereum (ETH). With the new Withdrawals page, Lido users can easily deposit their staked Ethereum tokens, such as stETH or wstETH, and receive ETH in return. Lido has streamlined the withdrawal process, reducing the withdrawal period to as short as 1-5 days. This improvement not only enhances the liquidity and accessibility of staked Ethereum but also provides users with greater flexibility and control over their assets. Additionally, the V2 upgrade introduces a modular staking router, which promotes staking diversity among several cohorts. Related Reading: Lido DAO (LDO) Holds 10% Gains On Weekly Chart While Majority Of Coins Shrink Solo stakers, decentralized autonomous organizations (DAOs), and Distributed Validator Technology (DVT) clusters can now participate in staking activities through Lido, further expanding the network&#8217;s staking capabilities. LDO&#8217;s price has already risen nearly 20% since the upgrade, with a market currently above $2 at the time of writing. Alongside the price surge, Lido DAO&#8217;s market capitalization has also experienced a notable rise. The market cap moved from $1.4 billion last Friday to $1.9 billion today. Moreover, the trading volume of LDO has also witnessed a significant uptick over the same period indicating the increasing accumulation of the asset. Lido&#8217;s trading volume has surged from $47.4 million last Friday to more than $104 million in the past 24 hours. Featured image from iStock, Chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In the fast-paced world of cryptocurrencies, Lido DAO (LDO) has made significant waves in the past week, experiencing an impressive surge of nearly 20%. Though the surge comes at a time the global crypto market is not deep in a downtrend, Lido&#8217;s current rally can be attributed to two notable factors.</p>
<p>Over the past seven days, LDO has recorded a <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/lido-surges-in-single-day-maintains-dominance-in-liquid-staking/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">significant spike, up by 16%</a>. The asset has picked up from trading at a low of below $2 as of May 9 to trading at a high of $2.25, at the time of writing. Meanwhile, over the past 24 hours, the rally continues as the asset is currently up 6.3% with an increasing trading volume.</p>
<h2>Whale Accumulation Fuels Lido&#8217;s Surge</h2>
<p>One possible catalyst for Lido&#8217;s remarkable performance over the past 7 days is the increased buying activity by cryptocurrency whales. According to a recent <a href="https://twitter.com/lookonchain/status/1658329812090617857?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">report</a> by Onchain analyst Lookonchain, three whale accounts have been observed accumulating LDO tokens.</p>

<p>Notably, these whales have been seen transferring their <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/defi/lido-ldo-plummets-over-20-in-past-week-heres-why/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">LDO assets</a> from centralized cryptocurrency exchange Binance to personal wallets, indicating a deliberate accumulation strategy. The magnitude of these whale transactions is noteworthy. </p>
<p>For instance, one address withdrew a substantial amount of 724,822 LDO tokens, valued at approximately $1.52 million, from Binance for $2.01 per token. Another whale withdrew 655,641 LDO tokens, equivalent to $1.38 million, from Binance at $1.83 per token.  Additionally, a third whale purchased 570,883 LDO tokens using 974,000 USDC for $1.71 on May 12. </p>
<p>This influx of capital from these significant players in the market has undoubtedly contributed to the surge in Lido&#8217;s value.</p>
<h2>Lido V2 Launch Amplifies Momentum</h2>
<p>Another driving force behind Lido&#8217;s recent upward trend is the<a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/altcoin/lido-ldo-bulls-lock-horns-for-rally-this-week-ahead-of-v2-update/" target="_blank" rel="noopener "> launch of Lido V2</a>. This highly anticipated upgrade brings several notable features to the Lido DAO ecosystem, enhancing its appeal to investors and participants. A key highlight of the V2 release is the ability for users to withdraw their staked Ethereum (ETH).</p>
<p>With the new Withdrawals page, Lido users can easily deposit their staked Ethereum tokens, such as stETH or wstETH, and receive ETH in return. Lido has streamlined the withdrawal process, reducing the withdrawal period to as short as 1-5 days. </p>
<p>This improvement not only enhances the liquidity and accessibility of staked Ethereum but also provides users with greater flexibility and control over their assets. Additionally, the V2 upgrade introduces a modular staking router, which promotes staking diversity among several cohorts.</p>

<p>Solo stakers, decentralized autonomous organizations (DAOs), and Distributed Validator Technology (DVT) clusters can now participate in staking activities through Lido, further expanding the network&#8217;s staking capabilities.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/2mPUpk92/" alt="Lido DAO (LDO)&#039;s price chart on TradingView" width="2768" height="1556"/>
<p>LDO&#8217;s price has already risen nearly 20% since the upgrade, with a market currently above $2 at the time of writing. Alongside the price surge, Lido DAO&#8217;s market capitalization has also experienced a notable rise. The market cap moved from $1.4 billion last Friday to $1.9 billion today.</p>
<p>Moreover, the trading volume of LDO has also witnessed a significant uptick over the same period indicating the increasing <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/crypto/lido-finance-ldo-is-down-18-in-7-days-buy-the-dip/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">accumulation of the asset</a>. Lido&#8217;s trading volume has surged from $47.4 million last Friday to more than $104 million in the past 24 hours.</p>
<p>Featured image from iStock, Chart from TradingView</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Mining-460x272.jpg" width="460" height="272" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Algorand (ALGO) Price Turns Positive, Bulls Eyeing Further Gains?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/algorand/algorand-algo-price-turns-positive-bulls-eyeing-further-gains/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Eli Dambel]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 19:30:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Algorand]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[algorand]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ALGOUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dapps]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=533264</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Algorand (ALGO) has recovered from the bearish trend seen at the end of February 2023. From February 21 till May 8, ALGO recorded a loss of 45.13%, dropping to a low of $1.592. Despite the crash, buyers still pushed up the price of ALGO by more than 6% in the past few days. Traders are optimistic and are eyeing the next move in the current trend, while the bears are slowing building momentum by holding their strong short position. Will The Bulls Maintain This Current Bullish Momentum? The sustainability of ALGO&#8217;s current price trend relies on several factors. Market conditions, such as supply and demand dynamics, overall economic factors, and external events, can generally influence the price. However, the current market sentiment is bullish, while the Fear &#38; Greed Index is 45, indicating neutral. This means the market&#8217;s state is stable, and the volatility is not high. Within the last 24 hours, Algo&#8217;s general market cap gained 1.57%, rising to over $1 billion. The 24-hour trading volume surged by 15% overnight, rising to about $33 million. Related Reading: US Banking Crisis Worsens With Half Of America’s Banks On the Verge Of Failure Notably, at the time of writing, the ALGO token is trading at $0.1683 as bulls continue to have a good day with gains of 2.50%.  However, the recent increase in ALGO&#8217;s general market suggests increased demand for the asset. As more investors and traders buy the asset, the increased buying pressure can lead to a rise in its price. The increase in trading volume suggests improved liquidity for the asset, which tend to attract more investor to the market.  ALGO Technical Analysis The price is below the 200-Day and 50-Day Simple Moving Averages (SMA). This suggests that ALGO market sentiment is still bearish; the selling momentum is stronger than the bull&#8217;s buying momentum. However, the asset might rebound if the bulls increase their momentum, as green candles are showing today in the chart. The Relative Strength Index oscillator is showing 40.18. This means the asset is currently at neutral levels; the pressure from bulls and bears is normal. Related Reading: Crypto Firms Should Ditch Banks To De-risk From Volatile Systems, Says Cardano Founder Also, MACD is currently above the signal indicating a potential uptrend. The histogram confirms the bullish sentiment as its showing green candles and also above zero. ALGO trades between its primary support and resistance levels of $0.1587 and $0.1853, respectively. The next key zones are the support level &#8211; $0.0992 and the resistance level &#8211; $0.2427. Recent Development In The Algorand Ecosystem Alogrand recently introduced a new plugin-based tool for enhancing Blockchain Data Access named Conduit. Conduit aims at providing improved access to blockchain data. It is an upgrade to the conventional one-size-fits-all Indexer, designed as a modular plugin-based tool.  This plugin empowers decentralized applications (DApps) by offering precise and tailored data retrieval capabilities, all while maintaining cost-effective deployment options. Such developments on the network could increase adoption and utility and, in time, boost ALGO&#8217;s price. Featured image from Pixabay and chart from Tradingview.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Algorand (ALGO) has recovered from the bearish trend seen at the end of February 2023. From February 21 till May 8, ALGO recorded a loss of 45.13%, dropping to a low of $1.592. Despite the crash, buyers still pushed up the price of ALGO by more than 6% in the past few days.</p>
<p>Traders are optimistic and are eyeing the next move in the current trend, while the bears are slowing building momentum by holding their strong short position.</p>
<h2>Will The Bulls Maintain This Current Bullish Momentum?</h2>
<p>The sustainability of ALGO&#8217;s current price trend relies on several factors. Market conditions, such as supply and demand dynamics, overall economic factors, and external events, can generally influence the price.</p>
<p>However, the current market sentiment is bullish, while the <a href="https://cfgi.io/algorand-fear-greed-index/" rel="nofollow">Fear &amp; Greed Index</a> is 45, indicating neutral. This means the market&#8217;s state is stable, and the volatility is not high.</p>
<p>Within the last 24 hours, Algo&#8217;s general market cap gained 1.57%, rising to over $1 billion. The 24-hour trading volume surged by 15% overnight, rising to about $33 million.</p>

<p>Notably, at the time of writing, the ALGO token is trading at $0.1683 as bulls continue to have a good day with gains of 2.50%. </p>
<p>However, the recent increase in ALGO&#8217;s general market suggests increased demand for the asset. As more investors and traders buy the asset, the increased buying pressure can lead to a rise in its price. The increase in trading volume suggests improved liquidity for the asset, which tend to attract more investor to the market. </p>
<h2>ALGO Technical Analysis</h2>
<p>The price is below the 200-Day and 50-Day Simple Moving Averages (SMA). This suggests that ALGO market sentiment is still bearish; the selling momentum is stronger than the bull&#8217;s buying momentum.</p>
<p>However, the asset might rebound if the bulls increase their momentum, as green candles are showing today in the chart. The Relative Strength Index oscillator is showing 40.18. This means the asset is currently at neutral levels; the pressure from bulls and bears is normal.</p>

<p>Also, MACD is currently above the signal indicating a potential uptrend. The histogram confirms the bullish sentiment as its showing green candles and also above zero.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-533279 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ALGOUSDT_2023-05-16_18-54-19-860x471.png" alt="Algorand (ALGO) Price Turns Positive, Bulls Eyeing Further Gains?" width="860" height="471" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ALGOUSDT_2023-05-16_18-54-19-860x471.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ALGOUSDT_2023-05-16_18-54-19-460x252.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ALGOUSDT_2023-05-16_18-54-19-768x420.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ALGOUSDT_2023-05-16_18-54-19-750x411.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ALGOUSDT_2023-05-16_18-54-19-1140x624.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ALGOUSDT_2023-05-16_18-54-19.png 1529w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/>
<p>ALGO trades between its primary support and resistance levels of $0.1587 and $0.1853, respectively. The next key zones are the support level &#8211; $0.0992 and the resistance level &#8211; $0.2427.</p>
Recent Development In The Algorand Ecosystem
<p>Alogrand recently <a href="https://algorand.com/" rel="nofollow">introduced</a> a new plugin-based tool for enhancing Blockchain Data Access named Conduit. Conduit aims at providing improved access to blockchain data. It is an upgrade to the conventional one-size-fits-all Indexer, designed as a modular plugin-based tool. </p>
<p>This plugin empowers decentralized applications (DApps) by offering precise and tailored data retrieval capabilities, all while maintaining cost-effective deployment options. Such developments on the network could increase adoption and utility and, in time, boost ALGO&#8217;s price.</p>
<p>Featured image from Pixabay and chart from Tradingview.com</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/elk-g706905866_1280-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Top-Rated Bitcoin Slot Sites in 2023: A Comprehensive Guide</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/gambling/best-bitcoin-slots-guide/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Thompson Mimi]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 18:35:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Gambling]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=533232</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[With the rise of crypto at online casinos, Bitcoin slots are becoming a go-to choice for players worldwide. In this comprehensive guide, we&#8217;ll explore the top-rated Bitcoin slot sites you need to sign-up for in 2023, as well as the best slot machines accepting Bitcoin. BC.GAME – Outstanding Casino Metaspins – Best Crypto Casino Betplay – Top Rated New Casino Jackbit – Great Casino Promotions Cloudbet – Award Winning Casino Luckyblock – Best Crypto Games Wild.io – Superb Web3 Casino Vave.com – Cutting-Edge Casino Flush.com – Excellent Mobile Casino CryptoLoko – Highest Welcome Rewards Katsubet – Unique Casino Theme Blizz.io – Swift Payment Casino Bets.io – Well Established Casino Coinzino – Cool Casino Experience Justbit – Premier Crypto Option MiraxCasino – Best Anonymous Casino We&#8217;ll also touch on the key features, bonuses, and gameplay strategies to maximize your winnings and optimize your experience. Best Online Casinos for Crypto Slots Here are the top online casinos that offer the best Bitcoin slots in 2023: BC.Game – Outstanding Gambling Site No KYC needed with save and anonymous play Supported Currencies: Bitcoin, Ethereum, Litecoin, Dogecoin Available for players from the US and around the world. Games provided by Endorphina, Pragmatic Play and many more Welcome bonus up to $20,000 and 200 free spins Live chat is available 24/7 for customer support Outstanding Pros Secure payments with solid encryption technology Variety of games to choose from Generous welcome bonuses Why We Recommend This Site We absolutely love playing at BC.Game. The selection of Bitcoin slots is huge and the graphics are stunning. The gameplay strategies are exciting and there&#8217;s plenty of options to choose from. With generous welcome bonuses for new players and plenty of promotions to keep existing players engaged. Metaspins – Best Rated Crypto Casino Established 2022 Play anonymous with no KYC Supported currencies: Bitcoin, Litecoin, Ethereum,  Zcash, and more Games provided by Betsoft Gaming, Habanero Systems Welcome bonus up to 100% up to 1BTC Live Chat Support is Available 24/7 Pros Easy navigational layout Provably fair gaming systems Variety of games offered Why We Recommend This Site Metaspins is another great choice if you want to play Bitcoin slots. There&#8217;s a variety of games that allow us to enjoy the thrill of gambling with our cryptocurrency, plus a wide range of bonuses like daily leaderboard rewards and weekly cashback bonuses that make it even more exciting! Betplay – Best Rated New Casino Established in 2022 No KYC needed and fully anonymous Supported currencies: Bitcoin, Ethereum, Litecoin, and more Available worldwide including US and UK Games provided by RTG, Habanero Systems, and others 100% welcome bonus up to 1,000 USDT / 50,000mBTC Live chat available 24/7 for customer support Pros: Huge selection of slots with high RTP Easy navigational layout Crypto deposits accepted Why We Recommend This Site Betplay is another great option for those looking to maximize their bankrolls, as they have some of the highest payouts available online. They also host a great library of crypto and bitcoin slots with lightning-fast withdrawals so you can get your winnings right away. Jackbit – Benefit from Great Casino Promotions Diverse Portfolio: Jackbit Casino offers a wide selection of games, including video slots, table games, live dealer rooms, and sports betting, ensuring an extensive gaming experience. Renowned software providers such as Pragmatic Play, Play&#8217;n GO, Push Gaming, Big Time Gaming, and NetEnt. User-Friendly Navigation allows players to locate their preferred games effortlessly. Over 6500+ Games from various providers. Thrilling live dealer section featuring games such as Live Baccarat, Live Blackjack, and Live Poker, hosted by real-life dealers. Fully optimized for mobile gaming, supporting iOS and Android devices. Prioritizes player safety by utilizing SSL encryption methods to protect sensitive information. Why We Recommend This Site At Jackbit we discovered an impressive online gambling platform that offers an extensive selection of games, including the latest video slots, table games, live dealer options, and sports betting. The user-friendly interface, availability in multiple languages, and compatibility with web and mobile platforms enhance accessibility. With over 6500+ casino games, including a variety of table games, and an extensive live dealer section, there are options to suit every preference. Cloudbet – Award Winning Casino and Sports Anonymous and No KYC required Supported Currencies: Bitcoin, Ethereum, and Litecoin Available in the US and worldwide Games provided by Betsoft Gaming, Habanero Systems, and more 100% up to 5BTC welcome bonus Live chat available 24/7 for customer support Pros: Secure payments with encryption Generous welcome bonuses Variety of crypto games to choose from Why We Recommend This Site At Cloudbet.io, we love the way they strive to provide a secure and fair gaming environment for all their players. Not only do they use top-of-the-line encryption to protect our deposits and withdrawals, but they also offer provably fair gaming when you play slots. Plus, their welcome bonus is generous &#8211; offering up to a 100% match bonus on your first deposit. Luckyblock – Best Crypto Slots and Games Established in 2022 No KYC required Supported currencies: Bitcoin, Ethereum, Dogecoin, and Litecoin Available worldwide Games provided by Pragmatic Play and Netent Welcome bonus of 200% up to $20,000 + 50 free spins Live Chat Support 24/7 Why We Recommend This Site Luckyblock.io is another great choice for quality Bitcoin slot games. Their selection of slots is huge and their rewards program is incredibly rewarding. We especially appreciate their innovative wagering strategies which give us more control over our bets while still offering plenty of exciting features and bonuses along the way. Wild Casino – The Ultimate Web3 Casino Established in 2020 Supported currencies: Bitcoin, Ethereum, and Tron Play from the US and worldwide Games provided by Betsoft Gaming, Habanero Systems, and more 150% welcome bonus up to $30,000 + 500 free spins Live chat is available 24/7 for customer support Pros Secure payments with solid encryption technology Generous welcome bonuses Variety of games to choose from Why We Recommend This Site Wild.io has been a go-to destination since its launch in 2023 due to its impressive selection of over 2000+ different casino games including the best bitcoin slots from leading developers around the world. We especially appreciate their innovative gameplay strategies which give us much more control over our wagering amounts than other casinos do. Vave Casino – Cutting Edge Casino Technology Established in 2018 Supported currencies: Bitcoin, Ethereum, and Dogecoin Available for players worldwide Games provided by Endorphina, Pragmatic Play, and more 100% cashback bonus up to 1BTC Live Chat Support is Available 24/7 Pros: Secure payments Variety of games and jackpot slots to choose from Generous welcome bonuses Why We Recommend This Site Vave gives us yet another alternative when it comes to free spins, tournaments, VIP programs, and exclusive prizes &#8211; plus, they let us play our favorite bitcoin slot games through mobile devices with ease and convenience. Flush Casino – Best For Mobile Gambling On the Go Established in 2020 Supported currencies: Bitcoin, Ethereum, and Ripple Available worldwide Games provided by RTG, Habanero Systems, and other providers Welcome bonus of 150% up to $1,000 Live chat is available 24/7 for customer support Variety of payment options including bank transfers, credit cards, debit cards, and crypto deposits Pros: Secure payments with encryption Generous welcome bonuses Large variety of games offered Why We Recommend This Site Flush has earned a spot in our top list due to its commitment to providing players with provably fair games on all spins &#8211; something that not all crypto casinos have &#8211; as well as secure deposits and withdrawals and exciting bitcoin slot games. CryptoLoko – Casino With Great Bonus Rewards Established in 2023 No KYC required Supported currencies: Bitcoin, Ethereum, and Ripple Open for the US and worldwide Games provided by Play&#8217;n GO and Evolution Gaming Welcome bonus up to 505% + 55 free spins Live chat is available 24/7 for customer support Pros Fast payouts within 15 minutes High-quality games with immersive graphics Generous welcome bonuses Why We Recommend This Site CryptoLoko is one of our favorites because they offer an incredibly generous welcome bonus for new players as well as ongoing promotions for existing members. Plus, the deposits and withdrawals are secure and the withdrawal process is lightning-fast so you can get your winnings instantly! Katsubet – Exciting Asian Casino Theme Established in 2019 No KYC required Supported currencies: Bitcoin, Ethereum, and Ripple Available for the US and worldwide Games provided by RTG, Habanero Systems, and other providers Welcome bonus of 100% up to 1,5BTC Live chat available 24/7 for customer support Variety of payment options including bank transfers, credit cards, debit cards, and cryptocurrency deposits Why We Recommend This Site KatsuBet offers an amazing range of slot games that are easy to play and backed by reliable customer service should you ever need it. Their fast withdrawal system makes it super convenient to get our winnings when we want them &#8211; plus, there&#8217;s always something new going on with cool tournaments and exclusive prizes for members. Blizz.io – Casino With Swift Payments Established in 2020 Licensed &#38; regulated by the government of Curacao Games provided by RTG, Habanero Systems, and other providers Welcome offer: 100% up to 1BTC Live chat 24/7 for customer support Variety of payment options including bank transfers, credit cards, debit cards, and cryptocurrency deposits Great selection of high RTP games and jackpot slots Why We Recommend This Site Blizz.io is yet another great option for Bitcoin slots in 2023 &#8211; offering hundreds of slot games from leading developers around the world as well as providing players with secure deposits and lightning-fast withdrawals. The selection of bonuses here is also impressive, from welcome packages to daily leaderboard rewards. Bets.io – Well Established Crypto Casino Established in 2018 Bitcoin, Ethereum, and many more Available worldwide including US/UK Games provided by Endorphina, Pragmatic Play, and others Welcome bonus up to 1BTC plus 100 Free Spins Live Chat 24/7 for customer support Variety of payment options including bank transfers, credit cards, debit cards, and crypto deposits Why We Recommend This Online Casino Bets.io stands out in the crowd due to its unique approach &#8211; allowing players to set limits on how much they can bet each time so that they can stay on top of their budgeting practices while still fully enjoying the thrill of gambling with crypto. Plus, their loyalty points system gives us plenty of ways to earn additional rewards along the way. Coinzino – Big Selection of Casino Games Established in 2018 Supported currencies: Bitcoin, Ethereum, Dogecoin, and Litecoin Licensed &#38; regulated by the government of Curacao Games provided by Betsoft Gaming, Habanero Systems, etc. Welcome bonus up to $500 Live chat available 24/7 for customer support Variety of payment options including bank transfers, credit cards, debit cards, and cryptocurrency deposits Why We Recommend This Site Coinzino.io has got us hooked thanks to its incredible selection of bitcoin slots, jackpot slots, and other casino games designed by some of the best developers in the business. All backed by a secure payment system and fully licensed by the Curaçao eGaming Commission. Plus, they offer daily free spins exclusively for members. Justbit.io – Top Notch Casino Experience Established in 2020 Supported currencies: Bitcoin, Ethereum, and Dogecoin Licensed &#38; regulated by the government of Curacao Games provided by Pragmatic Play, Endorphina, and other providers Welcome bonuses on every deposit + 45% cash back Live chat available 24/7 for customer support Variety of payment options including bank transfers, credit cards, debit cards, and cryptocurrency Why We Recommend This Crypto Casino Justbit.io impresses us with its wide variety of cryptos accepted here &#8211; including Bitcoin Cash (BCH), Ethereum (ETH), Litecoin (LTC), Ripple (XRP), and many more. They also have a generous welcome package tailored specifically for new players as well as ongoing promotions such as weekly cashback bonuses that make it even more exciting. At Justbit you can try the free bitcoin slots before betting any money. MiraxCasino – Best Casino for Anonymous Players Established in 2019 No KYC needed Supported currencies: Bitcoin, Ethereum, Litecoin, and more Licensed &#38; regulated by the government of Curacao Games provided by Red Tiger Gaming, Habanero Systems, and others Welcome bonus up to 1.5BTC Live chat available 24/7 for customer support Variety of payment options including crypto deposits Why We Recommend This Bitcoin Casino Mirax Casino rounds off our list with its impressive selection of over 1000 different bitcoin slot games (including jackpot slots) from leading developers across the globe plus an array of generous bonuses such as daily leaderboard rewards and exclusive VIP programs for loyal members. Important Factors We Have Considered Reliability and Security Before you sign up at an online casino, it&#8217;s important to do some research into their reputation and trust. One way to do this is by looking up customer reviews on independent review sites. Our reviews look into how other customers have experienced the services offered by the casino in question, from game selection and payout speed to customer support. Diverse Game Selection When selecting a Bitcoin Slots site, make sure that they offer a wide variety of crypto games that fit your preferences. Most online Bitcoin casinos will offer a variety of crypto slots, table games, video poker, jackpot slots, and live dealer games for you to choose from. We help you find the cream of the crop with all the best Bitcoin slot machines available. Efficient Payouts and Withdrawals The speed at which payouts are processed can vary greatly between different online casinos. Before you start to play Bitcoin games online, it’s important to check what their withdrawal times are like in order to ensure that you receive your winnings quickly and without any delays. Lucrative Bonuses and VIP Programs The bitcoin casinos offer various bonuses or VIP programs as incentives for new players or for loyal members. However, It’s important to know all of the details in order to understand which bonuses suit the Bitcoin slots players best so that you can maximize your winnings during gameplay. Excluded Countries While many gambling sites do not restrict users by country, some do. It&#8217;s important to read through each online casino&#8217;s terms and conditions before signing up so that you can make sure your country is not restricted. Our recommended casinos are accessible worldwide including the US. Transparency and Provably Fair Games Provably fair games ensure that the casino games are fair and random by enabling players to verify the fairness of their results through proofing techniques. Make sure that the online gambling site has provably fair games so that you know that all outcomes are generated randomly without any manipulation or interference from third parties. With that in mind, all of the Bitcoin slots casino sites we recommend are certified for provable fair games and tested for fairness. Step-By-Step Guide To Playing Bitcoin Slots Even though playing crypto and bitcoin slots is very easy and straightforward, we have created an in-depth guide with all you need to know about the process. Simply follow these steps and you will be playing exciting bitcoin slot machines in no time. Prerequisites Before you can start playing Bitcoin slot games, there are some prerequisites that must be met. First, check which types of cryptocurrencies are accepted by the casino; most crypto casinos accept popular currencies such as Bitcoin (BTC) and Ethereum (ETH), and many more. Finally, it is important to choose an online casino that is safe and secure; look at our top list for recommended, trusted, and reviewed sites. Signing Up Once you have chosen a Bitcoin gambling site, signing up is easy. All you need to do is fill out a short form with your personal information such as name, address, email address, etc., then submit it for review. Make sure to read through the terms of service before submitting your information; this will ensure that your data remains secure and protected from any third-party access. Once your account has been approved, you can move on to depositing funds using Bitcoin. Depositing Funds Using Bitcoin Depositing funds using Bitcoin is easy; all you need is a wallet where you can store your cryptocurrency. Once you have chosen a wallet, simply transfer the desired amount of BTC into it from another wallet or exchange platform Then go back to the online casino&#8217;s website and select &#8220;deposit&#8221; from the menu bar; enter the amount of cryptocurrency you want to deposit along with your wallet address, then click &#8220;submit&#8221;. Your funds should appear in your account within minutes. Gameplay Now that you have deposited funds into your account using Bitcoin, it&#8217;s time to start playing. Before placing any bets on Bitcoin slot machines or other games available at the casino, make sure to read through their paytable first; this will give you an idea of how much each bet pays out when certain combinations are hit. It&#8217;s also good to understand any strategies associated with slot machines; these can help increase your chances of winning big jackpots. Finally, remember that all winnings are paid out in crypto; this means they must be converted into fiat currency before they can be spent outside of the casino&#8217;s platform. Withdrawing Winnings in Bitcoin When it comes time to withdraw winnings earned while playing Bitcoin slots at an online casino, simply select &#8220;withdraw&#8221; from the menu bar on their website and enter the amount of crypto you wish to withdraw along with your wallet address. The withdrawal process usually takes between 24-48 hours depending on how busy their system is; once completed though, all winnings should appear in your wallet. To convert them into fiat currency for spending outside of the casino&#8217;s platform, simply transfer them into an exchange platform such as Coinbase or Kraken where they can be exchanged for USD instantly. Play Free Bitcoin Slots (demo mode) One of the best ways to get started playing crypto slot games is by playing in demo mode. This allows you to test out different titles without risking any of your own money. Most gambling sites offer a demo mode for their online slot games, so be sure to take advantage of this before committing any real money. Play Slots With High RTP When playing online slots, it&#8217;s important to look for games with high Return To Player (RTP) percentages. The higher the RTP, the more likely you are to win when playing that particular game. Be sure to do some research and find out which games have the highest RTP before you play online slots. Claim Casino Bonuses And Free Spins Another great way to get started bitcoin casino slots is by taking advantage of casino bonuses and free spins offers. Many sites offer these types of promotions, so make sure you&#8217;re taking advantage of them when signing up for an account. This can help give you an edge over other players and increase your chances of winning big. Online Slots &#8211; Budget And Responsible Gambling Finally, it&#8217;s important to set a gambling budget before getting started with bitcoin casino slots. Make sure you only gamble what you can afford to lose and never chase losses or try to win back what you&#8217;ve already lost. Setting a budget will help ensure that your gambling experience remains enjoyable and safe. Top Bitcoin Slot Games to Watch in 2023 These Bitcoin slots are definitely worth checking out due to their exceptional themes, graphics, special features, and payout ratios: BTC Quest Embrace the adventure with this innovative Bitcoin slot game, offering a variety of features, including expanding wilds and free spins. The game has an industry-leading payout ratio, helping you maximize your winnings. Crypto Fruit This visually captivating slot game combines modern twists with a classic fruit machine design. As usual at video slots, you will enjoy high-quality graphics and enticing bonuses, all while experiencing the simplicity and familiarity of traditional slots. Blockchain Rush A Bitcoin slot game with a futuristic twist, featuring innovative gameplay elements, such as cascading reels and expanding wilds. The engaging theme centers around the use of blockchain technology in the world of cryptocurrencies. Magical Crypto Land Immerse yourself in a mythical world of magic at crypto slots. This enchanting game offers bonus rounds, free spins, and a captivating storyline, all while providing industry-leading payout ratios. Bitcoin Billionaire A high-stakes, VIP Bitcoin slot game tailored for those who love the thrill of big bets and even bigger returns. With easy-to-navigate gameplay and exceptional graphics, this high-roller slot game offers unique features like progressive jackpots and bonuses. Tips and Tricks for Bitcoin Slots Choose the best Bitcoin casinos: Always select a trustworthy platform that has a proven track record of provably fair games, swift payouts, and top-notch security measures. Check our top list of recommendations for the best crypto casinos in 2023. Understand the game: Before playing bitcoin slot games, take the time to understand how it works and what bonuses are available. This is essential for maximizing your winnings. Play with smaller bets: Avoid using large amounts of money for each bet and opt for smaller ones instead. This strategy helps you minimize losses and increase profits in the long run. Take advantage of bonuses: Many online Bitcoin casinos offer generous bonuses that can help you boost your bankroll if you play slots. Make sure to read all terms and conditions before claiming them, as some offers may have wagering requirements attached to them. Set a budget and stick to it: Gambling should be done responsibly, and that means setting a budget and sticking to it. Make sure to keep your winnings separate from the amount you have set aside for gambling. This way, you avoid getting carried away and spending more than you can afford. Bonus Tip Be sure to check out our reviews and ratings of Bitcoin slots and casinos before playing, as this can help you choose the best Bitcoin slot sites for your needs. This will also give you insight into the experience of other players, allowing you to make an informed decision about where to play. With the help of our guide and reviews, you can be confident that your gaming experience at the slot machines will be enjoyable and hopefully profitable. Questions &#38; Answers About Bitcoin Slots Are Bitcoin slots different from traditional slots? Bitcoin slots function similarly to traditional slots and video slots, but they accept Bitcoin or other cryptocurrencies as the betting currency. The gameplay and mechanics remain largely the same, offering the excitement of spinning the reels and winning potential. How do I play Bitcoin slots? Playing Bitcoin slots is straightforward. Choose a reputable online casino that accepts Bitcoin, create an account, deposit your desired amount of Bitcoin, select your preferred slot game, set your bet amount, and spin the reels. Winnings are paid out in Bitcoin as well. Are Crypto Slot Machines fair? Online casinos that offer the best Bitcoin slots typically utilize provably fair technology. This ensures that the outcomes of each spin are genuinely random and not manipulated. You can verify the fairness of the game by checking the provably fair feature provided by the casino. Can I win real Bitcoin by playing slots? Absolutely! When you play Bitcoin slots, you have the chance to win real Bitcoin. If you hit a winning combination, your winnings will be credited to your account in Bitcoin, which you can then withdraw or use for further gameplay. What are the advantages of Bitcoin slots? Bitcoin slots offers several advantages, including faster transactions, increased privacy, and often lower fees compared to traditional payment methods. Additionally, Bitcoin&#8217;s value can fluctuate, providing an opportunity for potential appreciation if you hold onto your winnings. Can I play Bitcoin slots on my mobile device? Yes, many online casinos that offer Bitcoin slots have mobile-compatible platforms. You can access and play the best Bitcoin slots on your smartphone or tablet by visiting the casino&#8217;s website through your mobile browser or using their dedicated mobile app. Do Bitcoin slots offer bonuses and promotions? Yes, Bitcoin casinos often provide bonuses and promotions specifically tailored for Bitcoin slots players. These bonuses can include welcome bonuses, free spins, reload bonuses, and more. Make sure to check the promotions page or contact customer support to learn about the available offers. Are there any specific strategies to use? Bitcoin slots, like traditional slots, rely on luck and random number generation. There is no guaranteed winning strategy. However, managing your bankroll, setting limits, and choosing slots with higher return-to-player (RTP) percentages can help enhance your overall gameplay experience. Are there progressive jackpot Bitcoin slots? Yes, some of the best Bitcoin slots feature progressive jackpots, where the jackpot amount increases with each bet placed by players until it is won. These jackpots can often reach substantial amounts, providing an exciting opportunity to win big with Bitcoin. Is it safe to play Crypto Slots? As long as you choose trusted bitcoin casinos that are properly licensed and regulated, Bitcoin slots are safe. Ensure that the casino has a secure website with encryption technology to protect your personal and financial information. Additionally, read reviews and do some research to select a trustworthy Bitcoin casino for your slot gaming enjoyment. Article Summary Bitcoin slots are an exciting and fun form of online crypto gambling. With the right strategy, you can maximize your winnings and enjoy a great gaming experience. To get started, select the best crypto casino site with provably fair games from our top list above, understand the rules and bonus features of each game, use smaller bets when possible, take advantage of casino bonuses, and set a budget for yourself. When done responsibly, Crypto slots can be an enjoyable way to make some extra money.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>With the rise of crypto at online casinos, Bitcoin slots are becoming a go-to choice for players worldwide. In this comprehensive guide, we&#8217;ll explore the top-rated Bitcoin slot sites you need to sign-up for in 2023, as well as the best slot machines accepting Bitcoin.</p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><a href="https://partnerbcgame.com/ddb5f3620" target="_blank" rel="noopener sponsored nofollow">BC.GAME</a> – Outstanding Casino</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><a href="https://metamedialinks.com/ef42416f0" target="_blank" rel="noopener sponsored nofollow">Metaspins</a> – Best Crypto Casino</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><a href="https://betplay.io?ref=ee090640e3ae" target="_blank" rel="noopener sponsored nofollow">Betplay</a> – Top Rated New Casino</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><a href="https://go.affision.com/visit/?bta=36967&amp;brand=jackbit&amp;utm_campaign=bitcoinist" target="_blank" rel="noopener sponsored nofollow">Jackbit</a> – Great Casino Promotions</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><a href="https://www.cloudbet.com/en/landing/bitcoin-bonus/?af_token=584829e9daca534ccf1b1811da89c313&amp;aftm_source=bitcoinist" target="_blank" rel="noopener sponsored nofollow">Cloudbet</a> – Award Winning Casino</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><a href="https://pretoastbutter.care/box_46369e636e358077413f6e68271cd350?aff=6703&amp;sub_id_1=btc_bbcb_top" target="_blank" rel="noopener sponsored nofollow">Luckyblock</a> – Best Crypto Games</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><a href="https://wildpartners.app/a17ee3d8d" target="_blank" rel="noopener sponsored nofollow">Wild.io</a> – Superb Web3 Casino</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><a href="https://go.vavepartners.com/redirect.aspx?pid=17192&amp;bid=1481&amp;lpid=198" target="_blank" rel="noopener sponsored nofollow">Vave.com</a> – Cutting-Edge Casino</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><a href="https://flushlinks.com/d8fead05c" target="_blank" rel="noopener sponsored nofollow">Flush.com</a> – Excellent Mobile Casino</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><a href="https://cryptolokolink.com/click/77/446/3545/1/btc_bbcb_top" target="_blank" rel="noopener sponsored nofollow">CryptoLoko</a> – Highest Welcome Rewards</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><a href="https://katsubet.partners/aa78e79bc" target="_blank" rel="noopener sponsored nofollow">Katsubet</a> – Unique Casino Theme</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><a href="https://record.blizzaffiliates.io/_UUfKM9dYkemVAv0U_Fv2nWNd7ZgqdRLk/1/" target="_blank" rel="noopener sponsored nofollow">Blizz.io</a> – Swift Payment Casino</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><a href="https://betsio.link/h8b7b6ad6" target="_blank" rel="noopener sponsored nofollow">Bets.io</a> – Well Established Casino</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><a href="https://coinzino.io?ref=6b5486b85d33" target="_blank" rel="noopener sponsored nofollow">Coinzino</a> – Cool Casino Experience</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><a href="https://trackingjustbit.io/da8209b32" target="_blank" rel="noopener sponsored nofollow">Justbit</a> – Premier Crypto Option</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><a href="https://mirax.partners/abcf969f9" target="_blank" rel="noopener sponsored nofollow">MiraxCasino</a> – Best Anonymous Casino</li>
</ul>
<p>We&#8217;ll also touch on the key features, bonuses, and gameplay strategies to maximize your winnings and optimize your experience.</p>
<h2>Best Online Casinos for Crypto Slots</h2>
<p>Here are the top online casinos that offer the best Bitcoin slots in 2023:</p>
<a href="https://partnerbcgame.com/d53cfd3dd" target="_blank" rel="noopener sponsored nofollow">BC.Game</a> – Outstanding Gambling Site
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-528781 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BCGame-casino-Compressified.jpg" alt="BC Game Bitcoin slot casino" width="1280" height="787"/></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400">No KYC needed with save and anonymous play</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400">Supported Currencies: Bitcoin, Ethereum, Litecoin, Dogecoin</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400">Available for players from the US and around the world.</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400">Games provided by Endorphina, Pragmatic Play and many more</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400">Welcome bonus up to $20,000 and 200 free spins</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400">Live chat is available 24/7 for customer support</li>
</ul>
Outstanding Pros
<ul>
<li>Secure payments with solid encryption technology</li>
<li>Variety of games to choose from</li>
<li>Generous welcome bonuses</li>
</ul>
Why We Recommend This Site
<p>We absolutely love playing at BC.Game. The selection of Bitcoin slots is huge and the graphics are stunning. The gameplay strategies are exciting and there&#8217;s plenty of options to choose from. With generous welcome bonuses for new players and plenty of promotions to keep existing players engaged.
<a href="https://partnerbcgame.com/d53cfd3dd" target="_blank" rel="noopener sponsored nofollow"> <strong><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-528865 size-full" style="margin-bottom: 80px;margin-top: 40px" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BCGame-casino-button.jpg" alt="Visit bc game slot site" width="460" height="74"/></strong></a></p>
<a href="https://metamedialinks.com/e2663e89b" target="_blank" rel="noopener sponsored nofollow">Metaspins</a> – Best Rated Crypto Casino
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-528781 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Metaspins-casino-Compressifyed.jpg" alt="Metaspins Bitcoin slot site" width="1280" height="787"/></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400">Established 2022</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400">Play anonymous with no KYC</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400">Supported currencies: Bitcoin, Litecoin, Ethereum,  Zcash, and more</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400">Games provided by Betsoft Gaming, Habanero Systems</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400">Welcome bonus up to 100% up to 1BTC</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400">Live Chat Support is Available 24/7</li>
</ul>
Pros
<ul>
<li>Easy navigational layout</li>
<li>Provably fair gaming systems</li>
<li>Variety of games offered</li>
</ul>
Why We Recommend This Site
<p>Metaspins is another great choice if you want to play Bitcoin slots. There&#8217;s a variety of games that allow us to enjoy the thrill of gambling with our cryptocurrency, plus a wide range of bonuses like daily leaderboard rewards and weekly cashback bonuses that make it even more exciting!
<a href="https://metamedialinks.com/e2663e89b" target="_blank" rel="noopener sponsored nofollow"> <strong><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-528865 size-full" style="margin-bottom: 80px;margin-top: 40px" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Metaspins-casino-button.jpg" alt="Visit Metaspins slot site" width="460" height="74"/></strong></a></p>
<a href="https://betplay.io?ref=ee090640e3ae" target="_blank" rel="noopener sponsored nofollow">Betplay</a> – Best Rated New Casino
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-528781 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Betplay-casino-Compressifyied.jpg" alt="Betplay bitcoin slot site" width="1280" height="787"/></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400">Established in 2022</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400">No KYC needed and fully anonymous</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400">Supported currencies: Bitcoin, Ethereum, Litecoin, and more</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400">Available worldwide including US and UK</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400">Games provided by RTG, Habanero Systems, and others</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400">100% welcome bonus up to 1,000 USDT / 50,000mBTC</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400">Live chat available 24/7 for customer support</li>
</ul>
Pros:
<ul>
<li>Huge selection of slots with high RTP</li>
<li>Easy navigational layout</li>
<li>Crypto deposits accepted</li>
</ul>
Why We Recommend This Site
<p>Betplay is another great option for those looking to maximize their bankrolls, as they have some of the highest payouts available online. They also host a great library of crypto and bitcoin slots with lightning-fast withdrawals so you can get your winnings right away.
<a href="https://betplay.io?ref=ee090640e3ae" target="_blank" rel="noopener sponsored nofollow"> <strong><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-528865 size-full" style="margin-bottom: 80px;margin-top: 40px" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Betplay-casino-button.jpg" alt="Visit betplay bitcoin slot site" width="460" height="74"/></strong></a></p>
<a href="https://go.affision.com/visit/?bta=36967&amp;brand=jackbit&amp;utm_campaign=bitcoinist" target="_blank" rel="noopener sponsored nofollow">Jackbit</a> – Benefit from Great Casino Promotions
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-528781 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Jackbit-casino-Compressifyed.jpg" alt="Jackbit Bitcoin Slot Casino" width="1280" height="787"/></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400">Diverse Portfolio: Jackbit Casino offers a wide selection of games, including video slots, table games, live dealer rooms, and sports betting, ensuring an extensive gaming experience.</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400">Renowned software providers such as Pragmatic Play, Play&#8217;n GO, Push Gaming, Big Time Gaming, and NetEnt.</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400">User-Friendly Navigation allows players to locate their preferred games effortlessly.</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400">Over 6500+ Games from various providers.</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400">Thrilling live dealer section featuring games such as Live Baccarat, Live Blackjack, and Live Poker, hosted by real-life dealers.</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400">Fully optimized for mobile gaming, supporting iOS and Android devices.</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400">Prioritizes player safety by utilizing SSL encryption methods to protect sensitive information.</li>
</ul>
Why We Recommend This Site
<p>At Jackbit we discovered an impressive online gambling platform that offers an extensive selection of games, including the latest video slots, table games, live dealer options, and sports betting.</p>
<p>The user-friendly interface, availability in multiple languages, and compatibility with web and mobile platforms enhance accessibility. With over 6500+ casino games, including a variety of table games, and an extensive live dealer section, there are options to suit every preference.
<a href="https://go.affision.com/visit/?bta=36967&amp;brand=jackbit&amp;utm_campaign=bitcoinist" target="_blank" rel="noopener sponsored nofollow"><strong> <img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-528865 size-full" style="margin-bottom: 80px;margin-top: 40px" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Jackbit-casino-button.jpg" alt="Visit Jackbit Bitcoin slot site" width="460" height="74"/></strong></a></p>
<a href="https://www.cloudbet.com/en/landing/bitcoin-bonus/?af_token=584829e9daca534ccf1b1811da89c313&amp;aftm_source=bitcoinist" target="_blank" rel="noopener sponsored nofollow">Cloudbet </a>– Award Winning Casino and Sports
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-528781 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Cloudbet-casino-Compressifyifeid.jpg" alt="Cloudbet Bitcoin slot Casino" width="1280" height="787"/></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400">Anonymous and No KYC required</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400">Supported Currencies: Bitcoin, Ethereum, and Litecoin</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400">Available in the US and worldwide</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400">Games provided by Betsoft Gaming, Habanero Systems, and more</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400">100% up to 5BTC welcome bonus</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400">Live chat available 24/7 for customer support</li>
</ul>
Pros<strong>:</strong>
<ul>
<li>Secure payments with encryption</li>
<li>Generous welcome bonuses</li>
<li>Variety of crypto games to choose from</li>
</ul>
Why We Recommend This Site
<p>At Cloudbet.io, we love the way they strive to provide a secure and fair gaming environment for all their players. Not only do they use top-of-the-line encryption to protect our deposits and withdrawals, but they also offer provably fair gaming when you play slots. Plus, their welcome bonus is generous &#8211; offering up to a 100% match bonus on your first deposit.
<a href="https://www.cloudbet.com/en/landing/bitcoin-bonus/?af_token=584829e9daca534ccf1b1811da89c313&amp;aftm_source=bitcoinist" target="_blank" rel="noopener sponsored nofollow"> <strong><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-528865 size-full" style="margin-bottom: 80px;margin-top: 40px" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Cloudbet-casino-button.jpg" alt="Visit cloudbet bitcoin slot site" width="460" height="74"/></strong></a></p>
<a href="https://pretoastbutter.care/box_46369e636e358077413f6e68271cd350?aff=6703&amp;sub_id_1=head" target="_blank" rel="noopener sponsored nofollow">Luckyblock</a> – Best Crypto Slots and Games
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-528781 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Luckyblock-casino-Compressifyed.jpg" alt="Luckyblock Bitcoin slot casino" width="1280" height="787"/></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400">Established in 2022</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400">No KYC required</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400">Supported currencies: Bitcoin, Ethereum, Dogecoin, and Litecoin</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400">Available worldwide</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400">Games provided by Pragmatic Play and Netent</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400">Welcome bonus of 200% up to $20,000 + 50 free spins</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400">Live Chat Support 24/7</li>
</ul>
Why We Recommend This Site
<p>Luckyblock.io is another great choice for quality Bitcoin slot games. Their selection of slots is huge and their rewards program is incredibly rewarding. We especially appreciate their innovative wagering strategies which give us more control over our bets while still offering plenty of exciting features and bonuses along the way.
<a href="https://pretoastbutter.care/box_46369e636e358077413f6e68271cd350?aff=6703&amp;sub_id_1=head" target="_blank" rel="noopener sponsored nofollow"> <strong><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-528865 size-full" style="margin-bottom: 80px;margin-top: 40px" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Luckyblock-casino-button.jpg" alt="Visit Luckyblock bitcoin slot site" width="460" height="74"/></strong></a></p>
<a href="https://wildpartners.app/aa86edb09" target="_blank" rel="noopener sponsored nofollow">Wild Casino</a> – The Ultimate Web3 Casino
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-528781 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Wild-casino.jpg" alt="Wild Bitcoin slot casino" width="1280" height="787"/></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400">Established in 2020</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400">Supported currencies: Bitcoin, Ethereum, and Tron</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400">Play from the US and worldwide</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400">Games provided by Betsoft Gaming, Habanero Systems, and more</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400">150% welcome bonus up to $30,000 + 500 free spins</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400">Live chat is available 24/7 for customer support</li>
</ul>
Pros
<ul>
<li>Secure payments with solid encryption technology</li>
<li>Generous welcome bonuses</li>
<li>Variety of games to choose from</li>
</ul>
Why We Recommend This Site
<p>Wild.io has been a go-to destination since its launch in 2023 due to its impressive selection of over 2000+ different casino games including the best bitcoin slots from leading developers around the world. We especially appreciate their innovative gameplay strategies which give us much more control over our wagering amounts than other casinos do.
<a href="https://wildpartners.app/aa86edb09" target="_blank" rel="noopener sponsored nofollow"><strong> <img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-528865 size-full" style="margin-bottom: 80px;margin-top: 40px" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Wild-casino-button.jpg" alt="Visit Wild bitcoin slot site" width="460" height="74"/></strong></a></p>
<a href="https://go.vavepartners.com/redirect.aspx?pid=17193&amp;bid=1481&amp;lpid=198" target="_blank" rel="noopener sponsored nofollow"><b>Vave Casino</b></a><b> – Cutting Edge Casino Technology</b>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-528781 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Vave-casino-Compressifyed.jpg" alt="Vave Bitcoin slot Casino" width="1280" height="787"/></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400">Established in 2018</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400">Supported currencies: Bitcoin, Ethereum, and Dogecoin</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400">Available for players worldwide</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400">Games provided by Endorphina, Pragmatic Play, and more</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400">100% cashback bonus up to 1BTC</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400">Live Chat Support is Available 24/7</li>
</ul>
Pros:
<ul>
<li>Secure payments</li>
<li>Variety of games and jackpot slots to choose from</li>
<li>Generous welcome bonuses</li>
</ul>
Why We Recommend This Site
<p>Vave gives us yet another alternative when it comes to free spins, tournaments, VIP programs, and exclusive prizes &#8211; plus, they let us play our favorite bitcoin slot games through mobile devices with ease and convenience.
<a href="https://go.vavepartners.com/redirect.aspx?pid=17193&amp;bid=1481&amp;lpid=198" target="_blank" rel="noopener sponsored nofollow"><strong> <img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-528865 size-full" style="margin-bottom: 80px;margin-top: 40px" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Vave-casino-button.jpg" alt="Visit Vave Bitcoin slot site" width="460" height="74"/></strong></a></p>
<a href="https://flushlinks.com/d3cdd1533" target="_blank" rel="noopener sponsored nofollow">Flush Casino</a> – Best For Mobile Gambling On the Go
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-528781 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Flush-casino-Compressifyfied.jpg" alt="Flush Bitcoin slot Casino" width="1280" height="787"/></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400">Established in 2020</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400">Supported currencies: Bitcoin, Ethereum, and Ripple</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400">Available worldwide</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400">Games provided by RTG, Habanero Systems, and other providers</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400">Welcome bonus of 150% up to $1,000</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400">Live chat is available 24/7 for customer support</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400">Variety of payment options including bank transfers, credit cards, debit cards, and crypto deposits</li>
</ul>
Pros:
<ul>
<li>Secure payments with encryption</li>
<li>Generous welcome bonuses</li>
<li>Large variety of games offered</li>
</ul>
Why We Recommend This Site
<p>Flush has earned a spot in our top list due to its commitment to providing players with provably fair games on all spins &#8211; something that not all crypto casinos have &#8211; as well as secure deposits and withdrawals and exciting bitcoin slot games.
<a href="https://flushlinks.com/d3cdd1533" target="_blank" rel="noopener sponsored nofollow"> <strong><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-528865 size-full" style="margin-bottom: 80px;margin-top: 40px" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Flush-casino-button.jpg" alt="Visit Flush Bitcoin Slot site" width="460" height="74"/></strong></a></p>
<a href="https://cryptolokolink.com/click/77/446/3545/1/btc_bbcb_head" target="_blank" rel="noopener sponsored nofollow">CryptoLoko</a> – Casino With Great Bonus Rewards
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-528781 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Cryptoloko-casino-Compressifyfied.jpg" alt="Cryptoloko Bitcoin Slot Casino" width="1280" height="787"/></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400">Established in 2023</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400">No KYC required</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400">Supported currencies: Bitcoin, Ethereum, and Ripple</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400">Open for the US and worldwide</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400">Games provided by Play&#8217;n GO and Evolution Gaming</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400">Welcome bonus up to 505% + 55 free spins</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400">Live chat is available 24/7 for customer support</li>
</ul>
Pros
<ul>
<li>Fast payouts within 15 minutes</li>
<li>High-quality games with immersive graphics</li>
<li>Generous welcome bonuses</li>
</ul>
Why We Recommend This Site
<p>CryptoLoko is one of our favorites because they offer an incredibly generous welcome bonus for new players as well as ongoing promotions for existing members. Plus, the deposits and withdrawals are secure and the withdrawal process is lightning-fast so you can get your winnings instantly!
<a href="https://cryptolokolink.com/click/77/446/3545/1/btc_bbcb_head" target="_blank" rel="noopener sponsored nofollow"> <strong><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-528865 size-full" style="margin-bottom: 80px;margin-top: 40px" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Cryptoloko-casino-button.jpg" alt="Visit Cryptoloko bitcoin slot casino" width="460" height="74"/></strong></a></p>
<a href="https://katsubet.partners/aa78e79bc" target="_blank" rel="noopener sponsored nofollow">Katsubet</a> – Exciting Asian Casino Theme
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-528781 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Katsubet-casino.jpg" alt="Katsubet Bitcoin slot Casino" width="1280" height="787"/></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400">Established in 2019</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400">No KYC required</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400">Supported currencies: Bitcoin, Ethereum, and Ripple</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400">Available for the US and worldwide</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400">Games provided by RTG, Habanero Systems, and other providers</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400">Welcome bonus of 100% up to 1,5BTC</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400">Live chat available 24/7 for customer support</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400">Variety of payment options including bank transfers, credit cards, debit cards, and cryptocurrency deposits</li>
</ul>
Why We Recommend This Site
<p>KatsuBet offers an amazing range of slot games that are easy to play and backed by reliable customer service should you ever need it. Their fast withdrawal system makes it super convenient to get our winnings when we want them &#8211; plus, there&#8217;s always something new going on with cool tournaments and exclusive prizes for members.
<a href="https://katsubet.partners/aa78e79bc" target="_blank" rel="noopener sponsored nofollow"><strong> <img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-528865 size-full" style="margin-bottom: 80px;margin-top: 40px" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Katsubet-casino-button.jpg" alt="Visit Katsubet bitcoin slot casino" width="460" height="74"/></strong></a></p>
<a href="https://record.blizzaffiliates.io/_UUfKM9dYkelHH6eEtUVc2GNd7ZgqdRLk/2/" target="_blank" rel="noopener sponsored nofollow">Blizz.io</a> – Casino With Swift Payments
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-528781 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Blizz-casino-Compressifyied.jpg" alt="Blizz Bitcoin slot Casino" width="1280" height="787"/></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400">Established in 2020</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400">Licensed &amp; regulated by the government of Curacao</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400">Games provided by RTG, Habanero Systems, and other providers</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400">Welcome offer: 100% up to 1BTC</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400">Live chat 24/7 for customer support</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400">Variety of payment options including bank transfers, credit cards, debit cards, and cryptocurrency deposits</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400">Great selection of high RTP games and jackpot slots</li>
</ul>
Why We Recommend This Site
<p>Blizz.io is yet another great option for Bitcoin slots in 2023 &#8211; offering hundreds of slot games from leading developers around the world as well as providing players with secure deposits and lightning-fast withdrawals. The selection of bonuses here is also impressive, from welcome packages to daily leaderboard rewards.
<a href="https://record.blizzaffiliates.io/_UUfKM9dYkelHH6eEtUVc2GNd7ZgqdRLk/2/" rel="noopener sponsored nofollow"> <strong><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-528865 size-full" style="margin-bottom: 80px;margin-top: 40px" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Blizz-casino-button.jpg" alt="Visit Blizz Bitcoin slot site" width="460" height="74"/></strong></a></p>
<a href="https://betsio.link/h78e09d0e" target="_blank" rel="noopener sponsored nofollow">Bets.io</a> – Well Established Crypto Casino
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-528781 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bets-casino.jpg" alt="Bets.io Bitcoin slot Casino" width="1280" height="787"/></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400">Established in 2018</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400">Bitcoin, Ethereum, and many more</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400">Available worldwide including US/UK</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400">Games provided by Endorphina, Pragmatic Play, and others</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400">Welcome bonus up to 1BTC plus 100 Free Spins</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400">Live Chat 24/7 for customer support</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400">Variety of payment options including bank transfers, credit cards, debit cards, and crypto deposits</li>
</ul>
Why We Recommend This Online Casino
<p>Bets.io stands out in the crowd due to its unique approach &#8211; allowing players to set limits on how much they can bet each time so that they can stay on top of their budgeting practices while still fully enjoying the thrill of gambling with crypto. Plus, their loyalty points system gives us plenty of ways to earn additional rewards along the way.
<a href="https://betsio.link/h78e09d0e" rel="noopener sponsored nofollow"> <strong><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-528865 size-full" style="margin-bottom: 80px;margin-top: 40px" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bets-casino-button.jpg" alt="Visit Bets.io Bitcoin slot site" width="460" height="74"/></strong></a></p>
<a href="https://coinzino.io?ref=6b5486b85d33" target="_blank" rel="noopener sponsored nofollow">Coinzino </a>– Big Selection of Casino Games
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-528781 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Coinzino-casino.jpg" alt="Coinzino Bitcoin slot Casino" width="1280" height="787"/></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400">Established in 2018</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400">Supported currencies: Bitcoin, Ethereum, Dogecoin, and Litecoin</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400">Licensed &amp; regulated by the government of Curacao</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400">Games provided by Betsoft Gaming, Habanero Systems, etc.</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400">Welcome bonus up to $500</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400">Live chat available 24/7 for customer support</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400">Variety of payment options including bank transfers, credit cards, debit cards, and cryptocurrency deposits</li>
</ul>
Why We Recommend This Site
<p>Coinzino.io has got us hooked thanks to its incredible selection of bitcoin slots, jackpot slots, and other casino games designed by some of the best developers in the business. All backed by a secure payment system and fully licensed by the Curaçao eGaming Commission. Plus, they offer daily free spins exclusively for members.
<a href="https://coinzino.io?ref=6b5486b85d33" rel="noopener sponsored nofollow"> <strong><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-528865 size-full" style="margin-bottom: 80px;margin-top: 40px" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Coinzino-casino-button.jpg" alt="Visit Coinzino Bitcoin slot site" width="460" height="74"/></strong></a></p>
<a href="https://trackingjustbit.io/da8209b32" target="_blank" rel="noopener sponsored nofollow">Justbit.io</a> – Top Notch Casino Experience
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-528781 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Justbit-casino.jpg" alt="Justbit Bitcoin slot Casino" width="1280" height="787"/></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400">Established in 2020</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400">Supported currencies: Bitcoin, Ethereum, and Dogecoin</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400">Licensed &amp; regulated by the government of Curacao</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400">Games provided by Pragmatic Play, Endorphina, and other providers</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400">Welcome bonuses on every deposit + 45% cash back</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400">Live chat available 24/7 for customer support</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400">Variety of payment options including bank transfers, credit cards, debit cards, and cryptocurrency</li>
</ul>
Why We Recommend This Crypto Casino
<p>Justbit.io impresses us with its wide variety of cryptos accepted here &#8211; including Bitcoin Cash (BCH), Ethereum (ETH), Litecoin (LTC), Ripple (XRP), and many more. They also have a generous welcome package tailored specifically for new players as well as ongoing promotions such as weekly cashback bonuses that make it even more exciting. At Justbit you can try the free bitcoin slots before betting any money.
<a href="https://trackingjustbit.io/da8209b32" rel="noopener sponsored nofollow"> <strong><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-528865 size-full" style="margin-bottom: 80px;margin-top: 40px" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Justbit-casino-button.jpg" alt="Visit justbit Bitcoin slot casino" width="460" height="74"/></strong></a></p>
<a href="https://mirax.partners/abcf969f9" target="_blank" rel="noopener sponsored nofollow">MiraxCasino</a> – Best Casino for Anonymous Players
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-528781 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Mirax-casino.jpg" alt="Mirax Bitcoin slot Casino" width="1280" height="787"/></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400">Established in 2019</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400">No KYC needed</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400">Supported currencies: Bitcoin, Ethereum, Litecoin, and more</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400">Licensed &amp; regulated by the government of Curacao</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400">Games provided by Red Tiger Gaming, Habanero Systems, and others</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400">Welcome bonus up to 1.5BTC</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400">Live chat available 24/7 for customer support</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400">Variety of payment options including crypto deposits</li>
</ul>
Why We Recommend This Bitcoin Casino
<p>Mirax Casino rounds off our list with its impressive selection of over 1000 different bitcoin slot games (including jackpot slots) from leading developers across the globe plus an array of generous bonuses such as daily leaderboard rewards and exclusive VIP programs for loyal members.
<a href="https://mirax.partners/abcf969f9" rel="noopener sponsored nofollow"> <strong><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-528865 size-full" style="margin-bottom: 80px;margin-top: 40px" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Mirax-casino-button.jpg" alt="Visit Miraxcasino Bitcoin slot casino" width="460" height="74"/></strong></a></p>
<h2>Important Factors We Have Considered</h2>
Reliability and Security
<p>Before you sign up at an online casino, it&#8217;s important to do some research into their reputation and trust. One way to do this is by looking up customer reviews on independent review sites. Our reviews look into how other customers have experienced the services offered by the casino in question, from game selection and payout speed to customer support.</p>
Diverse Game Selection
<p>When selecting a Bitcoin Slots site, make sure that they offer a wide variety of crypto games that fit your preferences. Most online Bitcoin casinos will offer a variety of crypto slots, table games, video poker, jackpot slots, and live dealer games for you to choose from. We help you find the cream of the crop with all the best Bitcoin slot machines available.</p>
Efficient Payouts and Withdrawals
<p>The speed at which payouts are processed can vary greatly between different online casinos. Before you start to play Bitcoin games online, it’s important to check what their withdrawal times are like in order to ensure that you receive your winnings quickly and without any delays.</p>
Lucrative Bonuses and VIP Programs
<p>The bitcoin casinos offer various bonuses or VIP programs as incentives for new players or for loyal members. However, It’s important to know all of the details in order to understand which bonuses suit the Bitcoin slots players best so that you can maximize your winnings during gameplay.</p>
Excluded Countries
<p>While many gambling sites do not restrict users by country, some do. It&#8217;s important to read through each online casino&#8217;s terms and conditions before signing up so that you can make sure your country is not restricted. Our recommended casinos are accessible worldwide including the US.</p>
Transparency and Provably Fair Games
<p>Provably fair games ensure that the casino games are fair and random by enabling players to verify the fairness of their results through proofing techniques.</p>
<p>Make sure that the online gambling site has provably fair games so that you know that all outcomes are generated randomly without any manipulation or interference from third parties. With that in mind, all of the Bitcoin slots casino sites we recommend are certified for provable fair games and tested for fairness.
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-528781 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Paragraph1-bitcoin-slot.jpg" alt="Guide to play bitcoin slots" width="1920" height="645"/></p>
<h2>Step-By-Step Guide To Playing Bitcoin Slots</h2>
<p>Even though playing crypto and bitcoin slots is very easy and straightforward, we have created an in-depth guide with all you need to know about the process. Simply follow these steps and you will be playing exciting bitcoin slot machines in no time.</p>
<ol>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><b>Prerequisites</b><b>
</b>Before you can start playing Bitcoin slot games, there are some prerequisites that must be met. First, check which types of cryptocurrencies are accepted by the casino; most crypto casinos accept popular currencies such as Bitcoin (BTC) and Ethereum (ETH), and many more. Finally, it is important to choose an online casino that is safe and secure; look at our top list for recommended, trusted, and reviewed sites.</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><b>Signing Up</b><b>
</b>Once you have chosen a Bitcoin gambling site, signing up is easy. All you need to do is fill out a short form with your personal information such as name, address, email address, etc., then submit it for review.
Make sure to read through the terms of service before submitting your information; this will ensure that your data remains secure and protected from any third-party access. Once your account has been approved, you can move on to depositing funds using Bitcoin.</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><b>Depositing Funds Using Bitcoin</b><b>
</b>Depositing funds using Bitcoin is easy; all you need is a wallet where you can store your cryptocurrency.
Once you have chosen a wallet, simply transfer the desired amount of BTC into it from another wallet or exchange platform
Then go back to the online casino&#8217;s website and select &#8220;deposit&#8221; from the menu bar; enter the amount of cryptocurrency you want to deposit along with your wallet address, then click &#8220;submit&#8221;. Your funds should appear in your account within minutes.</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><b>Gameplay</b><b>
</b>Now that you have deposited funds into your account using Bitcoin, it&#8217;s time to start playing. Before placing any bets on Bitcoin slot machines or other games available at the casino, make sure to read through their paytable first; this will give you an idea of how much each bet pays out when certain combinations are hit.
It&#8217;s also good to understand any strategies associated with slot machines; these can help increase your chances of winning big jackpots.
Finally, remember that all winnings are paid out in crypto; this means they must be converted into fiat currency before they can be spent outside of the casino&#8217;s platform.</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><b>Withdrawing Winnings in Bitcoin</b><b>
</b>When it comes time to withdraw winnings earned while playing Bitcoin slots at an online casino, simply select &#8220;withdraw&#8221; from the menu bar on their website and enter the amount of crypto you wish to withdraw along with your wallet address.
The withdrawal process usually takes between 24-48 hours depending on how busy their system is; once completed though, all winnings should appear in your wallet.
To convert them into fiat currency for spending outside of the casino&#8217;s platform, simply transfer them into an exchange platform such as Coinbase or Kraken where they can be exchanged for USD instantly.</li>
</ol>
Play Free Bitcoin Slots (demo mode)
<p>One of the best ways to get started playing crypto slot games is by playing in demo mode. This allows you to test out different titles without risking any of your own money.</p>
<p>Most gambling sites offer a demo mode for their online slot games, so be sure to take advantage of this before committing any real money.</p>
Play Slots With High RTP
<p>When playing online slots, it&#8217;s important to look for games with high Return To Player (RTP) percentages. The higher the RTP, the more likely you are to win when playing that particular game. Be sure to do some research and find out which games have the highest RTP before you play online slots.</p>
Claim Casino Bonuses And Free Spins
<p>Another great way to get started bitcoin casino slots is by taking advantage of casino bonuses and free spins offers. Many sites offer these types of promotions, so make sure you&#8217;re taking advantage of them when signing up for an account. This can help give you an edge over other players and increase your chances of winning big.</p>
Online Slots &#8211; Budget And Responsible Gambling
<p>Finally, it&#8217;s important to set a gambling budget before getting started with bitcoin casino slots. Make sure you only gamble what you can afford to lose and never chase losses or try to win back what you&#8217;ve already lost. Setting a budget will help ensure that your gambling experience remains enjoyable and safe.
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-528781 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Paragraph2-bitcoin-slot.jpg" alt="Top bitcoin slots to watch to win big" width="1920" height="645"/></p>
<h2>Top Bitcoin Slot Games to Watch in 2023</h2>
<p>These Bitcoin slots are definitely worth checking out due to their exceptional themes, graphics, special features, and payout ratios:</p>
<p><b>BTC Quest</b></p>
<p>Embrace the adventure with this innovative Bitcoin slot game, offering a variety of features, including expanding wilds and free spins. The game has an industry-leading payout ratio, helping you maximize your winnings.</p>
<p><b>Crypto Fruit</b></p>
<p>This visually captivating slot game combines modern twists with a classic fruit machine design. As usual at video slots, you will enjoy high-quality graphics and enticing bonuses, all while experiencing the simplicity and familiarity of traditional slots.</p>
<p><b>Blockchain Rush</b></p>
<p>A Bitcoin slot game with a futuristic twist, featuring innovative gameplay elements, such as cascading reels and expanding wilds. The engaging theme centers around the use of blockchain technology in the world of cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p><b>Magical Crypto Land</b></p>
<p>Immerse yourself in a mythical world of magic at crypto slots. This enchanting game offers bonus rounds, free spins, and a captivating storyline, all while providing industry-leading payout ratios.</p>
<p><b>Bitcoin Billionaire</b></p>
<p>A high-stakes, VIP Bitcoin slot game tailored for those who love the thrill of big bets and even bigger returns. With easy-to-navigate gameplay and exceptional graphics, this high-roller slot game offers unique features like progressive jackpots and bonuses.</p>
<h2>Tips and Tricks for Bitcoin Slots</h2>
<ol>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><b>Choose the best Bitcoin casinos:</b> Always select a trustworthy platform that has a proven track record of provably fair games, swift payouts, and top-notch security measures. Check our top list of recommendations for the best crypto casinos in 2023.</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><b>Understand the game:</b> Before playing bitcoin slot games, take the time to understand how it works and what bonuses are available. This is essential for maximizing your winnings.</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><b>Play with smaller bets:</b> Avoid using large amounts of money for each bet and opt for smaller ones instead. This strategy helps you minimize losses and increase profits in the long run.</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><b>Take advantage of bonuses:</b> Many online Bitcoin casinos offer generous bonuses that can help you boost your bankroll if you play slots. Make sure to read all terms and conditions before claiming them, as some offers may have wagering requirements attached to them.</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><b>Set a budget and stick to it:</b> Gambling should be done responsibly, and that means setting a budget and sticking to it. Make sure to keep your winnings separate from the amount you have set aside for gambling. This way, you avoid getting carried away and spending more than you can afford.</li>
</ol>
<p><b>Bonus Tip</b></p>
<p>Be sure to check out our reviews and ratings of Bitcoin slots and casinos before playing, as this can help you choose the best Bitcoin slot sites for your needs. This will also give you insight into the experience of other players, allowing you to make an informed decision about where to play.</p>
<p>With the help of our guide and reviews, you can be confident that your gaming experience at the slot machines will be enjoyable and hopefully profitable.
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-528781 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Paragraph3-bitcoin-slot.jpg" alt="Questions anad answers surrounding bitcoin slots" width="1920" height="645"/></p>
<h2>Questions &amp; Answers About Bitcoin Slots</h2>
Are Bitcoin slots different from traditional slots?
<p>Bitcoin slots function similarly to traditional slots and video slots, but they accept Bitcoin or other cryptocurrencies as the betting currency. The gameplay and mechanics remain largely the same, offering the excitement of spinning the reels and winning potential.</p>
How do I play Bitcoin slots?
<p>Playing Bitcoin slots is straightforward. Choose a reputable online casino that accepts Bitcoin, create an account, deposit your desired amount of Bitcoin, select your preferred slot game, set your bet amount, and spin the reels. Winnings are paid out in Bitcoin as well.</p>
Are Crypto Slot Machines fair?
<p>Online casinos that offer the best Bitcoin slots typically utilize provably fair technology. This ensures that the outcomes of each spin are genuinely random and not manipulated. You can verify the fairness of the game by checking the provably fair feature provided by the casino.</p>
Can I win real Bitcoin by playing slots?
<p>Absolutely! When you play Bitcoin slots, you have the chance to win real Bitcoin. If you hit a winning combination, your winnings will be credited to your account in Bitcoin, which you can then withdraw or use for further gameplay.</p>
What are the advantages of Bitcoin slots?
<p>Bitcoin slots offers several advantages, including faster transactions, increased privacy, and often lower fees compared to traditional payment methods. Additionally, Bitcoin&#8217;s value can fluctuate, providing an opportunity for potential appreciation if you hold onto your winnings.</p>
Can I play Bitcoin slots on my mobile device?
<p>Yes, many online casinos that offer Bitcoin slots have mobile-compatible platforms. You can access and play the best Bitcoin slots on your smartphone or tablet by visiting the casino&#8217;s website through your mobile browser or using their dedicated mobile app.</p>
Do Bitcoin slots offer bonuses and promotions?
<p>Yes, Bitcoin casinos often provide bonuses and promotions specifically tailored for Bitcoin slots players. These bonuses can include welcome bonuses, free spins, reload bonuses, and more. Make sure to check the promotions page or contact customer support to learn about the available offers.</p>
Are there any specific strategies to use?
<p>Bitcoin slots, like traditional slots, rely on luck and random number generation. There is no guaranteed winning strategy. However, managing your bankroll, setting limits, and choosing slots with higher return-to-player (RTP) percentages can help enhance your overall gameplay experience.</p>
Are there progressive jackpot Bitcoin slots?
<p>Yes, some of the best Bitcoin slots feature progressive jackpots, where the jackpot amount increases with each bet placed by players until it is won. These jackpots can often reach substantial amounts, providing an exciting opportunity to win big with Bitcoin.</p>
Is it safe to play Crypto Slots?
<p>As long as you choose trusted <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/gambling/best-crypto-casinos/">bitcoin casinos</a> that are properly licensed and regulated, Bitcoin slots are safe. Ensure that the casino has a secure website with encryption technology to protect your personal and financial information. Additionally, read reviews and do some research to select a trustworthy Bitcoin casino for your slot gaming enjoyment.</p>
<h2>Article Summary</h2>
<p>Bitcoin slots are an exciting and fun form of online <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/gambling/best-crypto-gambling-sites/">crypto gambling</a>. With the right strategy, you can maximize your winnings and enjoy a great gaming experience.</p>
<p>To get started, select the best crypto casino site with provably fair games from our top list above, understand the rules and bonus features of each game, use smaller bets when possible, take advantage of casino bonuses, and set a budget for yourself. When done responsibly, Crypto slots can be an enjoyable way to make some extra money.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Featured-bitcoin-slots-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
