<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
>

<channel>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://newsbtc.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://newsbtc.com/</link>
	<description>Bitcoin &#38; cryptocurrency news today, price &#38; technical analysis</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2022 23:06:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<link>https://newsbtc.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Survey Reveals Turkey is Highly Obsessed With Crypto, Especially Dogecoin</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/survey-reveals-turkey-is-highly-obsessed-with-crypto-especially-dogecoin/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ana N.]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2022 23:00:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Turkey]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=511933</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The entire crypto industry has been experiencing a winter since the last quarter of 2021. Some cryptocurrency prices experienced a massive price slump, with many declining over 65%. However bad things may look, crypto may not go extinct as its popularity has not reduced. A recent study by CryptoManiaks, a crypto education platform, shows that Turkey and the Netherlands ranked top in cryptocurrency awareness. As per the survey, 5.5% and 8.2% of the population in Turkey and the Netherlands searched for crypto-related terms. Turkey accounted for 4.7 million searches, topping the chart with large numbers. Related Reading: Ethereum Price Bulls Hold Strong, Indicators Suggest Fresh Rally To $1,400 Turkey has made tremendous improvements in crypto adoption since the beginning of 2022. A 2022 research by the Turkish crypto exchange Paribu estimated that at least 8 million people in Turkey engaged in crypto. Turkish President Recep Tayyip Erdogan spoke about the benefits of blockchain innovations. In his statement, Erdogan added that Turkey wants to be a producer of digital assets, not a consumer. DOGE Outranks Ether In Terms Of User-Curiosity In Turkey The latest CryptoManiaks study analyzed the number of searches for some selected cryptocurrencies. They represented the number of cryptocurrencies as a percentage of the population for each country to calculate the monthly local searches. Turkey ranked second in the overall study and first with 812,000 monthly searches related to Dogecoin. According to the survey, the number of searches for Dogecoin doubled that of Ethereum, the third most searched crypto in the country. CryptoManiaks&#8217; spokesperson commented on the rising Dogecoin curiosity over the last 12 months. He said Dogecoin&#8217;s popularity has significantly exceeded Ethereum&#8217;s, with almost 2 million monthly searches worldwide. DOGE became popular after Elon musk revealed plans to make it the official token for Twitter monetization. As a result, the memecoin&#8217;s price soared to an all-time high within the week of the complete official acquisition of the social media platform by Elon Musk. The survey didn&#8217;t feature only DOGE and Ethereum. It also featured Solana, BNB, Bitcoin, and others. After Turkey and the Netherlands, Canada, Germany, and the Czech Republic followed in ranking. Bear Market Didn&#8217;t Cripple People&#8217;s Interest In Crypto Although the United Kingdom and the United States are top global players in the cryptocurrency industry, none ranked in the top. That is because the number of searches is insignificant compared to their population sizes. For example, the United States ranked 15th, with 1.9% of its population searching for crypto-related terms, whereas the United Kingdom took the 12th spot with 2.6%. Related Reading: Ethereum: On-Chain And Social Metrics Reveal Bulls Vs. Bears Battle – Who’s Winning? Recent research by Cointelegraph also showed that the bear market did not affect the interests of several institutions in the Crypto industry. According to the report, top institutions are still interested in the cryptocurrency industry and continue to invest millions in crypto-related projects. Featured image from Pixabay, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The entire crypto industry has been experiencing a winter since the last quarter of 2021. Some cryptocurrency prices experienced a massive price slump, with many declining over 65%. However bad things may look, crypto may not go extinct as its popularity has not reduced.</p>
<p>A recent <a href="https://cryptomaniaks.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">study by CryptoManiaks</a>, a crypto education platform, shows that Turkey and the Netherlands ranked top in cryptocurrency awareness. As per the survey, 5.5% and 8.2% of the population in Turkey and the Netherlands searched for crypto-related terms. Turkey accounted for 4.7 million searches, topping the chart with large numbers.</p>

<p>Turkey has made tremendous improvements in crypto adoption since the beginning of 2022. A 2022 research by the Turkish crypto exchange Paribu <a href="https://coindcx.com/blog/crypto-news-global/top-crypto-news-crypto-in-turkey-whats-driving-mass-scale-crypto-adoption-in-this-country-26-october-2022/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">estimated</a> that at least 8 million people in Turkey engaged in crypto. Turkish President Recep Tayyip Erdogan spoke about the benefits of blockchain innovations. In his statement, Erdogan added that Turkey wants to be a producer of digital assets, not a consumer.</p>
<h2>DOGE Outranks Ether In Terms Of User-Curiosity In Turkey</h2>
<p>The latest CryptoManiaks study analyzed the number of searches for some selected cryptocurrencies. They represented the number of cryptocurrencies as a percentage of the population for each country to calculate the monthly local searches.</p>
<p>Turkey ranked second in the overall study and first with 812,000 monthly searches related to Dogecoin. According to the survey, the number of searches for Dogecoin doubled that of Ethereum, the third most searched crypto in the country.</p>
<p>CryptoManiaks&#8217; spokesperson commented on the rising Dogecoin curiosity over the last 12 months. He said Dogecoin&#8217;s popularity has significantly exceeded Ethereum&#8217;s, with almost 2 million monthly searches worldwide.</p>
<p>DOGE became popular after Elon musk <a href="https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1596718851097755648?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">revealed plans</a> to make it the official token for Twitter monetization. As a result, the memecoin&#8217;s price soared to an all-time high within the week of the complete official acquisition of the social media platform by Elon Musk.</p>
<p>The survey didn&#8217;t feature only DOGE and Ethereum. It also featured Solana, BNB, Bitcoin, and others. After Turkey and the Netherlands, Canada, Germany, and the Czech Republic followed in ranking.</p>
<img class="wp-image-511934 size-large" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/DOGEUSDT_2022-12-10_19-16-04-860x499.png" alt="Survey Reveals Turkey is Highly Obsessed with Crypto, Especially Dogecoin" width="860" height="499" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/DOGEUSDT_2022-12-10_19-16-04-860x499.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/DOGEUSDT_2022-12-10_19-16-04-460x267.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/DOGEUSDT_2022-12-10_19-16-04-768x446.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/DOGEUSDT_2022-12-10_19-16-04-750x435.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/DOGEUSDT_2022-12-10_19-16-04.png 1116w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" />
<h2>Bear Market Didn&#8217;t Cripple People&#8217;s Interest In Crypto</h2>
<p>Although the United Kingdom and the United States are top global players in the cryptocurrency industry, none ranked in the top. That is because the number of searches is insignificant compared to their population sizes. For example, the United States ranked 15th, with 1.9% of its population searching for crypto-related terms, whereas the United Kingdom took the 12th spot with 2.6%.</p>

<p>Recent research by Cointelegraph also showed that the bear market did not affect the interests of several institutions in the Crypto industry. According to the report, top <a href="https://newsroom.porsche.com/en/2022/innovation/porsche-unveils-entry-into-virtual-worlds-at-art-basel-in-miami-30519.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">institutions</a> are still interested in the cryptocurrency industry and continue to invest millions in crypto-related projects.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/hot-air-balloons-gca3245b2d_1280-460x259.jpg" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Whales Move Over 275 Million XRP Amid Price Surge</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/ripple/whales-move-over-275-million-xrp-amid-price-surge/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ana N.]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2022 14:27:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stuart Alderoty]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrpusdt]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=511929</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Amid the crypto winter and the Ripple lawsuit saga, XRP is breaking records with over a 4% price surge in 30 days. Unfortunately, the past 30 days have been terrible in the market after the FTX collapse, which broke down cryptocurrency values. However, the low price period proved very beneficial to some fat wallet holders who seized the opportunity to accumulate more assets. Ripple&#8217;s native token, XRP, recorded more recovery than Bitcoin amid whale accumulations in the past 24 hours. Related Reading: Ethereum: On-Chain And Social Metrics Reveal Bulls Vs. Bears Battle – Who’s Winning? WhaleAlert reported that crypto whales moved over 275 million XRP tokens, worth more than $107 million, throughout the past 24 hours. The data also revealed that whales purchased over 113 million XRP, about $44 million, in the past 24 hours. Is XRP Showing Signs Of Dominance Over Bitcoin? Most of the transactions came from the Bitso crypto exchange, with the highest record being XRP tokens worth over $15.3 million. These movements saw a price surge in the XRP token, bringing over a 4% increase. However, Bitcoin trades at the $17,153 level, with a 3% dump in the last 30 days. Around the same time, Ripple&#8217;s general counsel, Stuart Alderoty, announced the filing of their final briefing in the XRP lawsuit. The two-year-long legal tussle between the SEC and Ripple is approaching the summary judgment stage. The crypto industry anticipates the outcome of the court&#8217;s ruling as it would affect the future of XRP and the broader digital assets. If the SEC wins the case, XRP will be seen as a security, and other similar tokens may follow suit. Ripples believe the long-standing battle with the Securities and Exchanges Commission is a fight for the crypto industry. However, Stuart Alderoty affirms that the Securities and Exchanges Commission holds no proof to satisfy its claims that XRP is a security. The attorney believes the defendants have an advantage over the commission in the case. Whales&#8217; Continuous Transfer Of XRP: Hold Or Sell signal? Meanwhile, as the firm faces the watchdog in their lawsuit, whales continue accumulating more tokens. To book more profit as the token price surged, whales transferred over 162 million XRP, worth about $63.1 million, in the past 24 hours. On-chain data revealed that most tokens went to the Bitstamp crypto exchange. The report shows that whales moved another 160 million of the token on Thursday as the Ripple/SEC lawsuit approaches the final round. In addition, more than 4 billion XRP tokens also went from Bittrex to an unknown wallet. Data revealed that the tokens are worth about $1.5 billion in total. Related Reading: Ethereum Price Bulls Hold Strong, Indicators Suggest Fresh Rally To $1,400 As large numbers of these tokens moved among exchanges and whale accounts, the token has continued to bag profits. As a result, the token now trades at $0.3872 with a live market capitalization of $19,477,214,657. Featured image from Pixabay, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Amid the crypto winter and the Ripple lawsuit saga, XRP is breaking records with over a 4% price surge in 30 days. Unfortunately, the past 30 days have been terrible in the market after the FTX collapse, which broke down cryptocurrency values.</p>
<p>However, the low price period proved very beneficial to some fat wallet holders who seized the opportunity to accumulate more assets. Ripple&#8217;s native token, XRP, recorded more recovery than Bitcoin amid whale accumulations in the past 24 hours.</p>

<p>WhaleAlert <a href="https://twitter.com/whale_alert/status/1600643510356660224" target="_blank" rel="noopener">reported</a> that crypto whales moved over 275 million XRP tokens, worth more than $107 million, throughout the past 24 hours. The data also revealed that whales purchased over 113 million XRP, about $44 million, in the past 24 hours.</p>
<h2>Is XRP Showing Signs Of Dominance Over Bitcoin?</h2>
<p>Most of the transactions came from the Bitso crypto exchange, with the highest record being XRP tokens worth over $15.3 million. These movements saw a price surge in the XRP token, bringing over a 4% increase. However, Bitcoin trades at the $17,153 level, with a 3% dump in the last 30 days.</p>
<p>Around the same time, Ripple&#8217;s general counsel, Stuart Alderoty, announced the filing of their final briefing in the XRP lawsuit. The two-year-long legal tussle between the SEC and Ripple is approaching the summary judgment stage.</p>
<p>The crypto industry anticipates the outcome of the court&#8217;s ruling as it would affect the future of XRP and the broader digital assets.</p>
<p>If the SEC wins the case, XRP will be seen as a security, and other similar tokens may follow suit. Ripples believe the long-standing battle with the Securities and Exchanges Commission is a fight for the crypto industry.</p>
<p>However, Stuart Alderoty <a href="https://twitter.com/s_alderoty/status/1600535886361411588" target="_blank" rel="noopener">affirms</a> that the Securities and Exchanges Commission holds no proof to satisfy its claims that XRP is a security. The attorney believes the defendants have an advantage over the commission in the case.</p>
<h2>Whales&#8217; Continuous Transfer Of XRP: Hold Or Sell signal?</h2>
<p>Meanwhile, as the firm faces the watchdog in their lawsuit, whales continue accumulating more tokens. To book more profit as the token price surged, whales transferred over 162 million XRP, worth about $63.1 million, in the past 24 hours. On-chain data revealed that most tokens went to the Bitstamp crypto exchange.</p>
<p>The report shows that whales moved another 160 million of the token on Thursday as the Ripple/SEC lawsuit approaches the final round. In addition, more than 4 billion XRP tokens also went from Bittrex to an unknown wallet. Data revealed that the tokens are worth about $1.5 billion in total.</p>

<p>As large numbers of these tokens moved among exchanges and whale accounts, the token has continued to bag profits. As a result, the token now trades at $0.3872 with a live market capitalization of $19,477,214,657.</p>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-511930 size-large" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/XRPUSDT_2022-12-10_18-40-28-860x499.png" alt="Whales Move Over 275 Million Ripple Tokens Amid Price Surge" width="860" height="499" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/XRPUSDT_2022-12-10_18-40-28-860x499.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/XRPUSDT_2022-12-10_18-40-28-460x267.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/XRPUSDT_2022-12-10_18-40-28-768x446.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/XRPUSDT_2022-12-10_18-40-28-750x435.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/XRPUSDT_2022-12-10_18-40-28.png 1116w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" />

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/whale-g919e6d832_1280-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum Price To Remain Sluggish Before It Attempts A Rally</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/ethereum-price-to-remain-sluggish-before-it-attempts-a-rally/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[anushsamal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2022 03:00:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=511877</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Ethereum price has moved in the same direction as the broader market. In the last 24 hours, Ethereum has moved up by 2.5%. On the weekly timeframe, the altcoin has rarely registered any movement. This reflects lateral trading for ETH. In the short term, the altcoin might be registering gains, but as the technicals indicate, the coin can depreciate again before it rallies. Accumulation has been considerably low on the chart. Buying activity must significantly increase if ETH is to break above the $1,300 price mark. Even though ETH remained comfortably above the $1,220 price, buying strength has been weak on the daily chart. Ethereum has to keep trading above the $1,240 and $1,250 price levels for the coin to take a shot at $1,300. The bulls will lose all strength if the Ethereum price moves below the $1,240 mark and closes near $1,230. This price pullback can then further fuel a rally to $1,300. Related Reading: Ethereum: On-Chain And Social Metrics Reveal Bulls Vs. Bears Battle – Who’s Winning? Ethereum Price Analysis: One-Day Chart ETH was trading at $1,275 at the time of writing. The coin is presently consolidating after flipping the $1,240 level as support. Immediate resistance for Ethereum stood at $1,290; the coin is expected to encounter a setback at that level. However, ETH must stay above $1,250 to avoid a significant loss of value. The bulls must keep defending the $1,250 level regarding the closest support line. The amount of Ethereum traded in the last session declined slightly, indicating a fall in the number of buyers in the market. Technical Analysis Corresponding to the earlier statement about low buyers, the technical outlook also painted the same picture. Although above the half-line, the Relative Strength Index remained weak as it displayed a downtick on the daily chart. This reading is associated with a fall in demand and accumulation. On the contrary, the Ethereum price was above the 20-Simple Moving Average. The indicator depicted that ETH was in the hands of the buyers, as the buyers were driving the price momentum in the market. With buyers still under some control of the price, the Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD) reflected the same sentiment. MACD indicates price movements and trend reversals; the indicator displays small green signal bars tied to the buy signal for ETH. However, it is to be remembered that the signals were declining in height, indicating a fall in demand. Bollinger Bands demonstrate the chance of price fluctuation and volatility in the market. Because the bands remained parallel, Ethereum is expected to trade within a range in the coming trading sessions. Related Reading: Ethereum Price Bulls Hold Strong, Indicators Suggest Fresh Rally To $1,400 Featured image from Unsplash, Chart: TradingView.com ]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Ethereum price has moved in the same direction as the broader market. In the last 24 hours, Ethereum has moved up by 2.5%. On the weekly timeframe, the altcoin has rarely registered any movement. This reflects lateral trading for ETH.</p>
<p>In the short term, the altcoin might be registering gains, but as the technicals indicate, the coin can depreciate again before it rallies. Accumulation has been considerably low on the chart. Buying activity must significantly increase if ETH is to break above the $1,300 price mark.</p>
<p>Even though ETH remained comfortably above the $1,220 price, buying strength has been weak on the daily chart. Ethereum has to keep trading above the $1,240 and $1,250 price levels for the coin to take a shot at $1,300. The bulls will lose all strength if the Ethereum price moves below the $1,240 mark and closes near $1,230. This price pullback can then further fuel a rally to $1,300.</p>

<h2>Ethereum Price Analysis: One-Day Chart</h2>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-511878 size-full" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETHUSD_2022-12-09_22-28-27.png" alt="Ethereum Price" width="1816" height="782" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETHUSD_2022-12-09_22-28-27.png 1816w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETHUSD_2022-12-09_22-28-27-460x198.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETHUSD_2022-12-09_22-28-27-860x370.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETHUSD_2022-12-09_22-28-27-768x331.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETHUSD_2022-12-09_22-28-27-1536x661.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETHUSD_2022-12-09_22-28-27-750x323.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETHUSD_2022-12-09_22-28-27-1140x491.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1816px) 100vw, 1816px" />
<p>ETH was trading at $1,275 at the time of writing. The coin is presently consolidating after flipping the $1,240 level as support. Immediate resistance for Ethereum stood at $1,290; the coin is expected to encounter a setback at that level.</p>
<p>However, ETH must stay above $1,250 to avoid a significant loss of value. The bulls must keep defending the $1,250 level regarding the closest support line. The amount of Ethereum traded in the last session declined slightly, indicating a fall in the number of buyers in the market.</p>
<h2>Technical Analysis</h2>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-511879 size-full" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETHUSD_2022-12-09_22-28-58.png" alt="Ethereum Price" width="1816" height="695" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETHUSD_2022-12-09_22-28-58.png 1816w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETHUSD_2022-12-09_22-28-58-460x176.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETHUSD_2022-12-09_22-28-58-860x329.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETHUSD_2022-12-09_22-28-58-768x294.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETHUSD_2022-12-09_22-28-58-1536x588.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETHUSD_2022-12-09_22-28-58-750x287.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETHUSD_2022-12-09_22-28-58-1140x436.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1816px) 100vw, 1816px" />
<p>Corresponding to the earlier statement about low buyers, the technical outlook also painted the same picture. Although above the half-line, the Relative Strength Index remained weak as it displayed a downtick on the daily chart.</p>
<p>This reading is associated with a fall in demand and accumulation. On the contrary, the Ethereum price was above the 20-Simple Moving Average. The indicator depicted that ETH was in the hands of the buyers, as the buyers were driving the price momentum in the market.</p>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-511880 size-full" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETHUSD_2022-12-09_22-29-22.png" alt="Ethereum Price" width="1816" height="695" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETHUSD_2022-12-09_22-29-22.png 1816w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETHUSD_2022-12-09_22-29-22-460x176.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETHUSD_2022-12-09_22-29-22-860x329.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETHUSD_2022-12-09_22-29-22-768x294.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETHUSD_2022-12-09_22-29-22-1536x588.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETHUSD_2022-12-09_22-29-22-750x287.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETHUSD_2022-12-09_22-29-22-1140x436.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1816px) 100vw, 1816px" />
<p>With buyers still under some control of the price, the Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD) reflected the same sentiment. MACD indicates price movements and trend reversals; the indicator displays small green signal bars tied to the buy signal for ETH.</p>
<p>However, it is to be remembered that the signals were declining in height, indicating a fall in demand. Bollinger Bands demonstrate the chance of price fluctuation and volatility in the market. Because the bands remained parallel, Ethereum is expected to trade within a range in the coming trading sessions.</p>




]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/guerrillabuzz-blockchain-pr-agency-lBXpVIhN_Us-unsplash-460x259.jpg" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Quant Explains How This Nasdaq Support Retest Could Also Help Reverse Bitcoin</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/quant-explains-nasdaq-support-retest-reverse-bitcoin/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hououin Kyouma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2022 00:00:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin NASDAQ correlation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Stock market correlation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NASDAQ]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stock Market]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=511824</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A quant has explained why the recent retest of a critical support level by Nasdaq may help Bitcoin reverse its own trend. Nasdaq-100 Has Recently Retested A Critical Support Trendline As pointed out by an analyst in a CryptoQuant post, Nasdaq-100 is currently above a support line that has historically been important. Nasdaq-100 (NDX) is a stock market index that includes 102 equity securities issued by 101 of the largest non-financial companies (based on their market caps) listed on the Nasdaq stock exchange. Here is a chart that shows how this trendline has acted as a bounce in the index&#8217;s price over the past decade: The value of the asset seems to have touched this line recently &#124; Source: CryptoQuant As you can see in the above graph, the price of NDX has been supported five times by this trendline since the year 2010. In each of these instances, the line has put a check on the decline in the index, and has consequently reversed it back up. Related Reading: Upcoming FOMC Meeting Is The Most Important Ever For Bitcoin – Watch Out For The Dot Plot Recently, the Nasdaq-100 index has once again made a touch of this trendline, and has so far managed to stay above it. The quant notes that this retest could have been the end of the latest downwards trend, and might have also been the point of return of a bullish trend. However, if the trendline is lost instead, it would show the extreme strength of the downtrend, and would suggest that there is more drawdown ahead for the market. Related Reading: Is Bitcoin Bottom In? This On-Chain Condition Hasn’t Been Met Yet At the same time, Bitcoin has also been testing a support line, as the analyst has highlighted in the chart: Looks like BTC is also just above a support trendline right now &#124; Source: CryptoQuant In the past year or so, Bitcoin has shown to be highly correlated with the stock market. The reason behind this correlation has been the rise of institutional investors in the crypto who treat it like a risk asset. The quant believes that if the current support retest in the stock market proves to be successful, then BTC could also be expected to see a reversal of its own due to its correlation with the stocks. Bitcoin Price At the time of writing, Bitcoin&#8217;s price floats around $17.2k, up 1% in the last week. Over the past month, the crypto has lost 7% in value. Below is a chart that shows the trend in the price of the coin over the last five days. The value of the crypto seems to have observed a sharp surge to $17.2k over the past day &#124; Source: BTCUSD on TradingView Featured image from Maxim Hopman on Unsplash.com, charts from TradingView.com, CryptoQuant.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A quant has explained why the recent retest of a critical support level by Nasdaq may help Bitcoin reverse its own trend.</p>
<h2>Nasdaq-100 Has Recently Retested A Critical Support Trendline</h2>
<p>As pointed out by an analyst in a CryptoQuant <a href="https://cryptoquant.com/quicktake/6393014da60e9b7fa21dbbf7-Bitcoin-Correlation-with-Stock-market-Nasdaq-is-at-a-sensitive-point-above-trend">post</a>, Nasdaq-100 is currently above a support line that has historically been important.</p>
<p>Nasdaq-100 (NDX) is a stock market index that includes 102 equity securities issued by 101 of the largest non-financial companies (based on their market caps) listed on the <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/nasdaq-valkyrie-mining-etf/">Nasdaq</a> stock exchange.</p>
<p>Here is a chart that shows how this trendline has acted as a bounce in the index&#8217;s price over the past decade:</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone aligncenter" src="https://img.cryptoquant.com/331846/quicktake/Fsoepud_7bf39d62b2d205fffc4db72bf3065f67dc571fbde9436d413656e65b26cbb02d.png" alt="NASDAQ Support Line Bitcoin" width="1280" height="632" /></p>

<p>As you can see in the above graph, the price of NDX has been supported five times by this trendline since the year 2010. In each of these instances, the line has put a check on the decline in the index, and has consequently reversed it back up.</p>

<p>Recently, the Nasdaq-100 index has once again made a touch of this trendline, and has so far managed to stay above it.</p>
<p>The quant notes that this retest could have been the end of the latest downwards trend, and might have also been the point of return of a bullish trend.</p>
<p>However, if the trendline is lost instead, it would show the extreme strength of the downtrend, and would suggest that there is more drawdown ahead for the market.</p>

<p>At the same time, Bitcoin has also been testing a support line, as the analyst has highlighted in the chart:</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone aligncenter" src="https://img.cryptoquant.com/331846/quicktake/TAri03MI2_31e847d7fd790a27dcf2f60242baa4ae459b04a295110df58ba7aec857e29551.png" alt="Bitcoin Support" width="1280" height="718" /></p>

<p>In the past year or so, Bitcoin has shown to be <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-moves-us-stock-market-correlation-weakening/">highly correlated</a> with the stock market. The reason behind this correlation has been the rise of institutional investors in the crypto who treat it like a risk asset.</p>
<p>The quant believes that if the current support retest in the stock market proves to be successful, then BTC could also be expected to see a reversal of its own due to its correlation with the stocks.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Price</h2>
<p>At the time of writing, <a href="https://newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-regains-strength-17k/">Bitcoin&#8217;s price</a> floats around $17.2k, up 1% in the last week. Over the past month, the crypto has lost 7% in value.</p>
<p>Below is a chart that shows the trend in the price of the coin over the last five days.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-511839 aligncenter" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/chart-11-460x255.png" alt="Bitcoin Price Chart" width="460" height="255" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/chart-11-460x255.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/chart-11-860x476.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/chart-11-768x425.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/chart-11-750x415.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/chart-11.png 973w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px" /></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/maxim-hopman-fiXLQXAhCfk-unsplash-1-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Luna Classic (LUNC) Price Under Bearish Pull Despite New Developments</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/luna-classic-lunc-price-under-bearish-pull-despite-new-developments/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[anushsamal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 22:00:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Luna Classic]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LUNC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LUNCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LUNCUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=511860</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The LUNA Classic (LUNC) price has noted a fresh decline in the last 24 hours. In that time frame, the altcoin depreciated by 1%. In the past week, LUNC logged gains worth 2.5%. Much of the weekly gains have been lost due to losses on the daily chart. At the moment, LUNC depicts consolidation beneath its immediate resistance mark. With the FTX collapse, LUNC has been teetering under a bearish influence for quite some time. Over the last month, the coin has lost more than 10% of its market value. On the development front, there is a new update. This is the introduction of the new Alpha package for TerraDart. TerraDart is a Dart SDK that is used for writing applications that would be interacting with the Terra blockchain, which has launched a new package called Alpha. The Alpha package has been available to communicate with the LUNC blockchain within Flutter and Dart environments. Related Reading: Yearn Finance: What The Final Quarter Of 2022 Has In Store For YFI Price Luna Classic (LUNC) Price Analysis: One-Day Chart LUNC was exchanging hands at $0.000162 at press time. The altcoin just fell from $0.000170 due to intra-day losses. Even with developments in the ecosystem, the LUNC price remains largely unaltered. The rigid price ceiling was at $0.000175, but demand for the coin was too low for bulls to take charge. Once the altcoin topples above the $0.000175 mark, it will be an easy path to the psychological level of $0.00019. On the flip side, with lesser accumulation, LUNC would eye its closest support line of $0.000148. Falling through the $0.000148 mark will bring LUNC to $0.00012. The amount of LUNC traded in the last session was low, indicating bearish strength. Technical Analysis In the past month, the coin displayed a bullish divergence, after which LUNC noted a slight increase in price. Despite that, the bulls could not build on their strength. The Relative Strength Index was near the 40-mark, which meant that the coin was moving toward the oversold zone. Similarly, the LUNC price was below the 20-Simple Moving Average line, which denoted a lack of demand. The reading also indicates that sellers were driving the price momentum in the market. In regards to buying strength, capital inflows have also declined due to a lack of investor interest. The Chaikin Money Flow depicts capital inflows and outflows at a given point. The indicator was below the half-line which meant low capital inflows. Related Reading: Ethereum: On-Chain And Social Metrics Reveal Bulls Vs. Bears Battle – Who’s Winning? The Directional Movement Index indicates the general price direction and trend of the asset. DMI was negative as the -DI (orange) line was above the +DI (blue) line. The Average Directional Index (red) was below the 25 mark, indicating a loss of strength in the current price action. Presently, LUNC is trading at 100% lower than its all-time high secured approximately eight months ago. Featured image from Wccftech, Chart: TradingView.com ]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The LUNA Classic (LUNC) price has noted a fresh decline in the last 24 hours. In that time frame, the altcoin depreciated by 1%. In the past week, LUNC logged gains worth 2.5%. Much of the weekly gains have been lost due to losses on the daily chart.</p>
<p>At the moment, LUNC depicts consolidation beneath its immediate resistance mark. With the FTX collapse, LUNC has been teetering under a bearish influence for quite some time. Over the last month, the coin has lost more than 10% of its market value.</p>
<p>On the development front, there is a new update. This is the introduction of the new Alpha package for TerraDart. TerraDart is a Dart SDK that is used for writing applications that would be interacting with the Terra blockchain, which has launched a new package called Alpha. The Alpha package has been available to communicate with the LUNC blockchain within Flutter and Dart environments.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/yearn-finance-what-the-final-quarter-of-2022-has-in-store-for-yfi-price/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Yearn Finance: What The Final Quarter Of 2022 Has In Store For YFI Price</a></p>
<h2>Luna Classic (LUNC) Price Analysis: One-Day Chart</h2>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-511861 size-full" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/LUNCUSD_2022-12-09_21-04-28.png" alt="Luna Classic" width="1816" height="695" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/LUNCUSD_2022-12-09_21-04-28.png 1816w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/LUNCUSD_2022-12-09_21-04-28-460x176.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/LUNCUSD_2022-12-09_21-04-28-860x329.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/LUNCUSD_2022-12-09_21-04-28-768x294.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/LUNCUSD_2022-12-09_21-04-28-1536x588.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/LUNCUSD_2022-12-09_21-04-28-750x287.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/LUNCUSD_2022-12-09_21-04-28-1140x436.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1816px) 100vw, 1816px" />
<p>LUNC was exchanging hands at $0.000162 at press time. The altcoin just fell from $0.000170 due to intra-day losses. Even with developments in the ecosystem, the LUNC price remains largely unaltered. The rigid price ceiling was at $0.000175, but demand for the coin was too low for bulls to take charge. Once the altcoin topples above the $0.000175 mark, it will be an easy path to the psychological level of $0.00019.</p>
<p>On the flip side, with lesser accumulation, LUNC would eye its closest support line of $0.000148. Falling through the $0.000148 mark will bring LUNC to $0.00012. The amount of LUNC traded in the last session was low, indicating bearish strength.</p>
<h2>Technical Analysis</h2>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-511867 size-full" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/LUNCUSD_2022-12-09_21-06-11.png" alt="Luna Classic " width="1816" height="695" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/LUNCUSD_2022-12-09_21-06-11.png 1816w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/LUNCUSD_2022-12-09_21-06-11-460x176.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/LUNCUSD_2022-12-09_21-06-11-860x329.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/LUNCUSD_2022-12-09_21-06-11-768x294.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/LUNCUSD_2022-12-09_21-06-11-1536x588.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/LUNCUSD_2022-12-09_21-06-11-750x287.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/LUNCUSD_2022-12-09_21-06-11-1140x436.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1816px) 100vw, 1816px" />
<p>In the past month, the coin displayed a bullish divergence, after which LUNC noted a slight increase in price. Despite that, the bulls could not build on their strength. The Relative Strength Index was near the 40-mark, which meant that the coin was moving toward the oversold zone.</p>
<p>Similarly, the LUNC price was below the 20-Simple Moving Average line, which denoted a lack of demand. The reading also indicates that sellers were driving the price momentum in the market.</p>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-511868 size-full" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/LUNCUSD_2022-12-09_21-06-37.png" alt="Luna Classic" width="1816" height="695" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/LUNCUSD_2022-12-09_21-06-37.png 1816w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/LUNCUSD_2022-12-09_21-06-37-460x176.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/LUNCUSD_2022-12-09_21-06-37-860x329.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/LUNCUSD_2022-12-09_21-06-37-768x294.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/LUNCUSD_2022-12-09_21-06-37-1536x588.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/LUNCUSD_2022-12-09_21-06-37-750x287.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/LUNCUSD_2022-12-09_21-06-37-1140x436.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1816px) 100vw, 1816px" />
<p>In regards to buying strength, capital inflows have also declined due to a lack of investor interest. The Chaikin Money Flow depicts capital inflows and outflows at a given point. The indicator was below the half-line which meant low capital inflows.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/ethereum/ethereum-metrics-reveal-bulls-vs-bears-battle-whos-winning/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ethereum: On-Chain And Social Metrics Reveal Bulls Vs. Bears Battle – Who’s Winning?</a></p>
<p>The Directional Movement Index indicates the general price direction and trend of the asset. DMI was negative as the -DI (orange) line was above the +DI (blue) line. The Average Directional Index (red) was below the 25 mark, indicating a loss of strength in the current price action.</p>
<p>Presently, LUNC is trading at 100% lower than its all-time high secured approximately eight months ago.</p>



]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Terra-460x259.jpg" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Whales Continue To Shed Holdings, Prices Not Attractive Enough?</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-whales-shed-holdings-prices-attractive-enough/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hououin Kyouma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 21:00:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin bearish]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Whale Holdings]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin whales]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=511799</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[On-chain data shows Bitcoin whales have continued to shave off their holdings in recent weeks, suggesting that the current lows may not be attractive enough to them. Bitcoin Whales Continue To Sell Despite The Recent Deep Lows As pointed out by an analyst in a CryptoQuant post, the number of investors with balances in the 1k to 10k BTC range have continued to decline recently. The relevant indicator here is the &#8220;UTXO Count &#8211; Value Bands,&#8221; which tells us about the number of UTXOs (or wallets) that are currently in each Bitcoin value band. These value bands are groups that define ranges between which the balances of UTXOs falling into said bands lie. For example, the 100-1k BTC value band includes all UTXOs (or wallets) that currently have between 100 and 1,000 coins. Related Reading: Ethereum Bullish Signal: Whales And Sharks Continue To Add To Their Holdings The value band of interest in the current context is the &#8220;1k-10k BTC&#8221; group. Here is a chart that shows how the UTXO Count of this value band has changed over the last several months: Looks like the value of the metric has taken a hit in recent days &#124; Source: CryptoQuant As you can see in the above graph, the Bitcoin UTXO Count for the 1k-10k BTC value band has observed some steep decline over the past month. Wallets with such large balances usually belong to the whales. This means that the holdings of these humongous holders have gone down in this period. This entire latest decline has come following the crash caused by crypto exchange&#8217;s FTX collapse, which means whales have sold their coins while the prices have been hitting lows. Related Reading: Is Bitcoin Bottom In? This On-Chain Condition Hasn’t Been Met Yet Historically, whales have shown accumulation behavior as bear markets have bottomed out. But recently instead of seeing an increase or even sideways movement, the UTXO Count of this whale value band has been strangely decreasing. This trend could be a sign that whales are still not finding the current lows attractive enough to buy more, and that they may rather be selling off their reserves as they expect the bearish winds to continue further. BTC Price At the time of writing, Bitcoin&#8217;s price floats around $17.2k, up 1% in the last week. Over the past month, the crypto has lost 7% in value. Below is a chart that shows the trend in the price of the coin over the last five days. The value of the crypto seems to have seen some rise during the past day &#124; Source: BTCUSD on TradingView Bitcoin has been stuck moving sideways around the $17k level recently, but at the moment it&#8217;s unclear when some real volatility may return to the crypto. Featured image from Thomas Lipke on Unsplash.com, charts from TradingView.com, CryptoQuant.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On-chain data shows Bitcoin whales have continued to shave off their holdings in recent weeks, suggesting that the current lows may not be attractive enough to them.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Whales Continue To Sell Despite The Recent Deep Lows</h2>
<p>As pointed out by an analyst in a CryptoQuant <a href="https://cryptoquant.com/quicktake/63925145edf9756d0ec3ad2c-STILL-SELLING">post</a>, the number of investors with balances in the 1k to 10k BTC range have continued to decline recently.</p>
<p>The relevant indicator here is the &#8220;UTXO Count &#8211; Value Bands,&#8221; which tells us about the number of UTXOs (or wallets) that are currently in each Bitcoin value band.</p>
<p>These value bands are groups that define ranges between which the balances of UTXOs falling into said bands lie. For example, the 100-1k BTC value band includes all UTXOs (or wallets) that currently have between 100 and 1,000 coins.</p>

<p>The value band of interest in the current context is the &#8220;<a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-bearish-signal-whales-1k-10k-btc-exchanges/">1k-10k BTC</a>&#8221; group. Here is a chart that shows how the UTXO Count of this value band has changed over the last several months:</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone aligncenter" src="https://img.cryptoquant.com/353981/quicktake/3yiBvYx2_a7efd7a2cd0854e474b0a1f93a33e6916e9deb77137fd6ab0f56e711ffd11ed6.png" alt="Bitcoin Whale Holdings" width="1280" height="806" /></p>

<p>As you can see in the above graph, the Bitcoin UTXO Count for the 1k-10k BTC value band has observed some steep decline over the past month.</p>
<p>Wallets with such large balances usually belong to the <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-whales-dump-20000-btc-on-the-market-sell-side-strengthens/">whales</a>. This means that the holdings of these humongous holders have gone down in this period.</p>
<p>This entire latest decline has come following the crash caused by crypto exchange&#8217;s FTX collapse, which means whales have sold their coins while the prices have been hitting lows.</p>

<p>Historically, whales have shown accumulation behavior as bear markets have bottomed out. But recently instead of seeing an increase or even sideways movement, the UTXO Count of this whale value band has been strangely decreasing.</p>
<p>This trend could be a sign that whales are still not finding the current lows attractive enough to buy more, and that they may rather be selling off their reserves as they expect the bearish winds to continue further.</p>
<h2>BTC Price</h2>
<p>At the time of writing, <a href="https://newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-regains-strength-17k/">Bitcoin&#8217;s price</a> floats around $17.2k, up 1% in the last week. Over the past month, the crypto has lost 7% in value.</p>
<p>Below is a chart that shows the trend in the price of the coin over the last five days.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-511802 aligncenter" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/chart-10-460x255.png" alt="Bitcoin Price Chart" width="460" height="255" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/chart-10-460x255.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/chart-10-860x478.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/chart-10-768x426.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/chart-10-750x416.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/chart-10.png 976w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px" /></p>

<p>Bitcoin has been stuck moving sideways around the $17k level recently, but at the moment it&#8217;s unclear when some real volatility may return to the crypto.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/thomas-lipke-kkXDhAUnxYI-unsplash-1-460x283.jpg" width="460" height="283" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum: On-Chain And Social Metrics Reveal Bulls Vs. Bears Battle &#8211; Who&#8217;s Winning?</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/ethereum/ethereum-metrics-reveal-bulls-vs-bears-battle-whos-winning/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jake Simmons]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 13:44:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=511827</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Ethereum (ETH) has failed to rise above key resistance at $1,300 despite rising around 4% over the past 24 hours. At press time, the second largest cryptocurrency by market cap was trading at $1,289. As the trading volume shows, the bulls and bears have woken up again. In the last 24 hours, the trading volume was $6.4 billion, which is about 31% higher than the previous day. Ethereum On-Chain And Social Metrics Show Uncertainty Analysis company Santiment has conducted an analysis of bullish and bearish signs in on-chain and social data for Ethereum and the result is mixed. A bullish argument is made by Ethereum&#8217;s shark and whale addresses. As Santiment writes, just as with Bitcoin, the ETH millionaire addresses gave up much of their supply while conditions looked poor. Related Reading: How Litecoin (LTC) Outperforms Other Top Cryptocurrencies In This Department However, this circumstance has fundamentally changed recently. A month ago, large ETH addresses started accumulating Ethereum again. Since November 7, Ethereum addresses holding 100 million to 1 million coins have accumulated 1.36% of the total supply and 2.09% more ETH overall (than before). Social volume, on the other hand, looks bearish. As with the majority of all cryptocurrencies, the number of discussions on Ethereum is decreasing, but this seems normal for a bear market. As Santiment notes, this is not necessarily a bad thing when the weak hands leave the market. What is negative, however, is that &#8220;there is so little talk about Ethereum compared to other top assets.&#8221; Related Reading: Upcoming FOMC Meeting Is The Most Important Ever For Bitcoin – Watch Out For The Dot Plot At the same time, this could also turn into a bullish argument if bullish whales can drive the price higher with little resistance, thus significantly affecting the general market sentiment. Currently bearish is also the MVRV (average trading return of addresses). The average return among long-term (365-day) addresses still indicates a &#8220;lot of pain.&#8221; However, based on an emerging long-term uptrend in the MVRV, the metric could also be moving into bullish territory. Extremely bullish is the remaining supply of Ethereum on exchanges. This is at a 4-year low of 12.1% of total supply. Thus, the metric clearly points to a nascent bottom that is forming. Sides Are Still Polarized In contrast, funding rates (perpetual contracts) are neutral. Neither the bulls nor bears can prevail on this metric at the moment. ETH funding rates have been too flat to swing in either direction since the FTX implosion. In terms of realized gains/losses, the bears are clearly winning at the moment, according to Santiment&#8217;s analysis. Given the recent surge in the Ethereum price, there is currently a lot of short-term profit-taking. Ultimately, Santiment summarizes: Overall, Ethereum&#8217;s on-chain and social metrics are about as mixed as the crowd&#8217;s perspective is. [&#8230;]Long-term? [&#8230;] Ethereum is very likely closer to its upcoming 3-year low vs. its 3-year high. But are we at maximal pain? Probably not yet.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ethereum (ETH) has failed to rise above key resistance at $1,300 despite rising around 4% over the past 24 hours. At press time, the second largest cryptocurrency by market cap was trading at $1,289.</p>
<p>As the trading volume shows, the bulls and bears have woken up again. In the last 24 hours, the trading volume was $6.4 billion, which is about 31% higher than the previous day.</p>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-511837 size-full" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETHUSD_2022-12-09_13-04-52.png" alt="Ethereum ETH USD 2022-12-09" width="2954" height="1607" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETHUSD_2022-12-09_13-04-52.png 2954w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETHUSD_2022-12-09_13-04-52-460x250.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETHUSD_2022-12-09_13-04-52-860x468.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETHUSD_2022-12-09_13-04-52-768x418.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETHUSD_2022-12-09_13-04-52-1536x836.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETHUSD_2022-12-09_13-04-52-2048x1114.png 2048w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETHUSD_2022-12-09_13-04-52-750x408.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETHUSD_2022-12-09_13-04-52-1140x620.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 2954px) 100vw, 2954px" />
<h2>Ethereum On-Chain And Social Metrics Show Uncertainty</h2>
<p>Analysis company Santiment has conducted an <a href="https://twitter.com/santimentfeed/status/1601028485941600257" target="_blank" rel="noopener">analysis</a> of bullish and bearish signs in on-chain and social data for Ethereum and the result is mixed.</p>
<p>A bullish argument is made by Ethereum&#8217;s shark and whale addresses. As Santiment writes, just as with Bitcoin, the ETH millionaire addresses gave up much of their supply while conditions looked poor.</p>

<p>However, this circumstance has fundamentally changed recently. A month ago, large ETH addresses started <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/ethereum-addresses-holding-32-eth-or-more-on-the-rise-this-on-chain-data-shows/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">accumulating</a> Ethereum again. Since November 7, Ethereum addresses holding 100 million to 1 million coins have accumulated 1.36% of the total supply and 2.09% more ETH overall (than before).</p>
<p>Social <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/chainlink-rally-in-social-activity-hits-ath-of-44173-will-link-price-climb-as-well/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">volume</a>, on the other hand, looks bearish. As with the majority of all cryptocurrencies, the number of discussions on Ethereum is decreasing, but this seems normal for a bear market.</p>
<p>As Santiment notes, this is not necessarily a bad thing when the weak hands leave the market. What is negative, however, is that &#8220;there is so little talk about Ethereum compared to other top assets.&#8221;</p>

<p>At the same time, this could also turn into a bullish argument if bullish whales can drive the price higher with little resistance, thus significantly affecting the general market sentiment.</p>
<p>Currently bearish is also the MVRV (average trading return of addresses). The average return among long-term (365-day) addresses still indicates a &#8220;lot of pain.&#8221;</p>
<p>However, based on an emerging long-term uptrend in the MVRV, the metric could also be moving into bullish territory.</p>
<p>Extremely bullish is the remaining supply of Ethereum on exchanges. This is at a 4-year low of 12.1% of total supply. Thus, the metric clearly points to a nascent bottom that is forming.</p>
<h2>Sides Are Still Polarized</h2>
<p>In contrast, funding rates (perpetual contracts) are neutral. Neither the bulls nor bears can prevail on this metric at the moment. ETH funding rates have been too flat to swing in either direction since the FTX implosion.</p>
<p>In terms of realized gains/losses, the bears are clearly winning at the moment, according to Santiment&#8217;s analysis. Given the recent surge in the Ethereum price, there is currently a lot of short-term profit-taking.</p>
<p>Ultimately, Santiment summarizes:</p>
<blockquote><p><strong>Overall, Ethereum&#8217;s on-chain and social metrics are about as mixed as the crowd&#8217;s perspective is. [&#8230;]Long-term? [&#8230;] Ethereum is very likely closer to its upcoming 3-year low vs. its 3-year high. But are we at maximal pain? Probably not yet.</strong></p></blockquote>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/iStock-1329407939-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Yearn Finance: What The Final Quarter Of 2022 Has In Store For YFI Price</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/yearn-finance-what-the-final-quarter-of-2022-has-in-store-for-yfi-price/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 13:40:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Token]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[yearn finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[yfi]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=511803</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Yearn Finance (YFI) has performed relatively well over the last 30 days, painting its charts in green despite the lingering uncertainty in the crypto market. According to information from Coingecko, at press time, the ERC20 governance token built on the Ethereum blockchain is changing hands at $7,087, going up by 5.7% during the past week and tallying an impressive 15.7% jump on its bi-weekly gauge. Here&#8217;s a quick glance of YFI performance: YFI is experiencing a significant decline in its daily trading volume Yearn Finance could fall all the way down to $6K within the next few days The altcoin could start 2023 with a bullish run to reclaim the $8K territory However, the altcoin’s technical indicators, specifically its Relative Strength Index (RSI) and Chaikin Money Flow (CMF), on its 4-hour chart doesn’t give much for traders to desire as they indicate a potential bearish run for the asset. The RSI settled below the 50-neutral zone at 48.97, suggesting that selling pressure increased and a lot of buyers veered away from the asset. Meanwhile, Yearn Finance’s CMF fell into a negative value of -0.07 – an indication of a weakened buying activity. Related Reading: How Litecoin (LTC) Outperforms Other Top Cryptocurrencies In This Department Source: TradingView Daily Active Addresses Count And Trading Volume Decline Along with the above-mentioned technical indicators, some developments concerning the cryptocurrency and its network pointed towards a bearish momentum. During the previous week, the number of unique addresses that traded Yearn Finance decreased sharply, going down by 41%. In fact, at the time of this writing, there were only 248 wallets monitored to have participated in YFI transactions. While the cryptocurrency’s spot trading price went up by 3% over the last 24 hours, its trading volume took a hit as it became lower by 25% during the same period. With these, there is a need for a significant uptick in demand for the crypto asset for another increase in value to be triggered as buyers in YFI market appear to be exhausted. However, it would seem that the digital currency could not catch a break as even in that particular department, it is showing signs of struggle. According to latest data, at the moment, only 59 new addresses were present at the network – 48% lower than what was observed within the last eight days. Chart: Santiment Coincodex Forecasts YFI At Over $8K By 2023 Although Yearn Finance’s short-term trajectory looks bleak, it is expected to have a strong start for the year 2023. According to the predictions of online crypto data information aggregator Coincodex, the digital asset is expected to decline significantly within the next five days and will eventually change hands at $$6,094 by December 15. Related Reading: Solana Price Falls Below $14 – Does This Signal A Gloomy Week For SOL? Chart: Coincodex However, the altcoin is expected to bounce back and reclaim its losses just few days after the expected price dump. By January 9, 2023, YFI is seen to trade at $8,891. YFI total market cap at $258 million on the daily chart &#124; Featured image - Altcoin Buzz, Chart: TradingView.com ]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Yearn Finance (YFI) has performed relatively well over the last 30 days, painting its charts in green despite the lingering uncertainty in the crypto market.</p>
<p>According to information from <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/yearn-finance" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Coingecko</a>, at press time, the ERC20 governance token built on the Ethereum blockchain is changing hands at $7,087, going up by 5.7% during the past week and tallying an impressive 15.7% jump on its bi-weekly gauge.</p>
<p>Here&#8217;s a quick glance of YFI performance:</p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400">YFI is experiencing a significant decline in its daily trading volume</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400">Yearn Finance could fall all the way down to $6K within the next few days</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400">The altcoin could start 2023 with a bullish run to reclaim the $8K territory</li>
</ul>
<p>However, the altcoin’s technical indicators, specifically its Relative Strength Index (RSI) and Chaikin Money Flow (CMF), on its 4-hour chart doesn’t give much for traders to desire as they indicate a potential bearish run for the asset.</p>
<p>The RSI settled below the 50-neutral zone at 48.97, suggesting that selling pressure increased and a lot of buyers veered away from the asset. Meanwhile, Yearn Finance’s CMF fell into a negative value of -0.07 – an indication of a weakened buying activity.</p>


<h2><b>Daily Active Addresses Count And Trading Volume Decline</b></h2>
<p>Along with the above-mentioned technical indicators, some developments concerning the cryptocurrency and its network pointed towards a bearish momentum.</p>
<p>During the previous week, the number of unique <a href="https://ambcrypto.com/assessing-whats-next-for-yearn-finance-yfi-as-we-gear-up-to-close-q4/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">addresses that traded Yearn Finance decreased</a> sharply, going down by 41%. In fact, at the time of this writing, there were only 248 wallets monitored to have participated in YFI transactions.</p>
<p>While the cryptocurrency’s spot trading price went up by 3% over the last 24 hours, its trading volume took a hit as it became lower by 25% during the same period.</p>
<p>With these, there is a need for a significant uptick in demand for the crypto asset for another increase in value to be triggered as buyers in YFI market appear to be exhausted.</p>
<p>However, it would seem that the digital currency could not catch a break as even in that particular department, it is showing signs of struggle.</p>
<p>According to latest <a href="https://app.santiment.net/charts/ds1-ZWU8__sCl">data,</a> at the moment, only 59 new addresses were present at the network – 48% lower than what was observed within the last eight days.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-511851 size-jnews-750x375" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/C1-15-750x375.png" alt="" width="750" height="375" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/C1-15-750x375.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/C1-15-360x180.png 360w" sizes="(max-width: 750px) 100vw, 750px" /></p>

<h2><b>Coincodex Forecasts YFI At Over $8K By 2023</b></h2>
<p>Although Yearn Finance’s short-term trajectory looks bleak, it is expected to have a strong start for the year 2023.</p>
<p>According to the predictions of online crypto data information aggregator <a href="https://coincodex.com/crypto/yearn-finance/price-prediction/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Coincodex</a>, the digital asset is expected to decline significantly within the next five days and will eventually change hands at $$6,094 by December 15.</p>

<p><img loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-511852 size-jnews-750x375" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/c2-1-750x375.png" alt="" width="750" height="375" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/c2-1-750x375.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/c2-1-360x180.png 360w" sizes="(max-width: 750px) 100vw, 750px" /></p>

<p>However, the altcoin is expected to bounce back and reclaim its losses just few days after the expected price dump. By January 9, 2023, YFI is seen to trade at $8,891.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/ZC18Xcab/" width="2047" height="979" /></p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Yearn-Finance-460x241.png" width="460" height="241" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Latest Ethereum Short Price Rally &#8211; Courtesy Of Whale Activities?</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/ethereum/latest-ethereum-short-price-rally-courtesy-of-whale-activities/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sarah]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 12:41:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrp]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=511747</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Ethereum has been showing bullish momentum in the last seven days. ETH has gained momentum in the past 24 hours, while other coins are still declining. This rally supports some theories that the asset will rise above the resistance level in the coming days. Weeks after a massive fallout, the second largest cryptocurrency is heading towards a comeback. The FTX crisis, with other macro factors, affected the entire crypto market, with many assets crashing flat. Although there are many uncertainties in the crypto market, hope seems to be returning to the Ethereum community. Related Reading: MATIC Price Battles Under $1 Despite Bullish Signals Vitalik Buterin, the Ethereum co-founder, made a statement urging people to focus on the technology instead of the current prices. The co-founder was confident that Ethereum-based applications for monetary transactions would scale up the blockchain in the long run. Ethereum Whales Are Buying The Dip In Buterin&#8217;s notes, he expressed a bullish stance that the decentralized stablecoins and the other applications built on Ethereum could have long-term benefits. Meanwhile, bullish Ethereum holders are taking advantage of the dip to accumulate more Ether positions. According to data from Santiment, Ethereum whales are taking advantage of the low prices to buy more ETH. The blockchain analytical firm tweeted that the shark and whale address, with 100 to 1 million ETH, added 2.1% more coins to their wallets. It could be a sign of bullish sentiment for a price rally in the weeks to come. Ethereum is currently trading at $1,280. Two months ago, before Ethereum transitioned to proof of stake, many investors were bullish about the price increase the upgrade could bring. However, two months after the merger, their hopes got dashed as the asset price continuously dropped. Although the upgrade sought to improve the blockchain&#8217;s infrastructure, the co-founder said it could take months to reflect on the ETH price. Bitcoin Stays Down While XRP Surges Amid Whale Accumulations While Ethereum seems to exhibit some bullish trend, Bitcoin is declining with a 24-hour price drop of $0.02%. Other coins are not doing any better, including FTX, except XRP. The report shows that the XRP price increased in the last 24 hours after whale accounts moved over 160 million tokens. According to a report, whales accumulated more than $19 million of XRP tokens from the Bitso crypto exchange. In addition, the report revealed that the tracker recorded another whale addition of 40 million XRP,  approximately $15.3 million. Related Reading: Bitcoin Price Prediction: What Elliott Wave Theory Suggests Is Next For BTC The tracker also reported that an account with the name, Ripple, moved more than 50 million XRP of about $19.2 million to an anonymous wallet. These accumulations saw XRP&#8217;s price gain a 2% increase in the last 24 hours and are currently trading at $0.3918. The news comes as the XRP lawsuit tends towards a summary judgment. Featured image from Pixabay, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ethereum has been showing bullish momentum in the last seven days. ETH has gained momentum in the past 24 hours, while other coins are still declining. This rally supports some theories that the asset will rise above the resistance level in the coming days.</p>
<p>Weeks after a massive fallout, the second largest cryptocurrency is heading towards a comeback. The FTX crisis, with other macro factors, affected the entire crypto market, with many assets crashing flat. Although there are many uncertainties in the crypto market, hope seems to be returning to the Ethereum community.</p>

<p>Vitalik Buterin, the Ethereum co-founder, made a statement urging people to focus on the technology instead of the current prices. The co-founder was confident that Ethereum-based applications for monetary transactions would scale up the blockchain in the long run.</p>
<h2>Ethereum Whales Are Buying The Dip</h2>
<p>In Buterin&#8217;s notes, he expressed a bullish stance that the decentralized stablecoins and the other applications built on Ethereum could have long-term benefits.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, bullish Ethereum holders are taking advantage of the dip to accumulate more Ether positions. According to data from <a href="https://twitter.com/santimentfeed/status/1600525985329270784" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Santiment</a>, Ethereum whales are taking advantage of the low prices to buy more ETH.</p>
<p>The blockchain analytical firm tweeted that the shark and whale address, with 100 to 1 million ETH, added 2.1% more coins to their wallets. It could be a sign of bullish sentiment for a price rally in the weeks to come.</p>
<p>Ethereum is currently trading at $1,280. Two months ago, before Ethereum transitioned to proof of stake, many investors were bullish about the price increase the upgrade could bring. However, two months after the merger, their hopes got dashed as the asset price continuously dropped.</p>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-511767 size-large" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETHUSDT_2022-12-09_11-21-47-860x499.png" alt="Latest Ethereum Short Price Rally, Courtesy Of Whale Activities?" width="860" height="499" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETHUSDT_2022-12-09_11-21-47-860x499.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETHUSDT_2022-12-09_11-21-47-460x267.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETHUSDT_2022-12-09_11-21-47-768x446.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETHUSDT_2022-12-09_11-21-47-750x435.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETHUSDT_2022-12-09_11-21-47.png 1116w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" />
<p>Although the upgrade sought to improve the blockchain&#8217;s infrastructure, the co-founder said it could take months to reflect on the ETH price.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Stays Down While XRP Surges Amid Whale Accumulations</h2>
<p>While Ethereum seems to exhibit some bullish trend, Bitcoin is declining with a 24-hour price drop of $0.02%. Other coins are not doing any better, including FTX, except XRP. The report shows that the XRP price increased in the last 24 hours after whale accounts moved over 160 million tokens.</p>
<p>According to a report, <a href="https://twitter.com/whale_alert/status/1600601607716093952">whales accumulated</a> more than $19 million of XRP tokens from the Bitso crypto exchange. In addition, the report revealed that the tracker recorded another whale addition of 40 million XRP,  approximately $15.3 million.</p>

<p>The tracker also reported that an account with the name, Ripple, moved more than 50 million XRP of about $19.2 million to an anonymous wallet.</p>
<p>These accumulations saw XRP&#8217;s price gain a 2% increase in the last 24 hours and are currently trading at $0.3918. The news comes as the XRP lawsuit tends towards a summary judgment.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/money-gf44a0010a_1280-460x305.jpg" width="460" height="305" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Upcoming FOMC Meeting Is The Most Important Ever For Bitcoin &#8211; Watch Out For The Dot Plot</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/upcoming-fomc-meeting-is-the-most-important-ever-for-bitcoin/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jake Simmons]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 11:52:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fed]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FOMC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Powell]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=511797</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[With the Bitcoin price posting a small gain of over 1.5% over the last seven days, the market is in for a blockbuster next week. The release of the Consumer Price Index (CPI) on December 13, Tuesday at 08:30 AM ET, will once again be &#8220;the most important CPI ever&#8221;. Just one day later, on December 14, Wednesday at 2:00 PM ET, the final Federal Open Market Committee (FOMC) meeting of the year will take place. Remarkably, FED members will release their updated forecasts for inflation and interest rates (dot plot) at the meeting. A Blockbuster Week The dot plot is released only four times a year &#8211; in March, June, September, and December &#8211; and presents the FOMC&#8217;s economic projections, which look at GDP, unemployment rates, and inflation for the coming months as well as over the longer term. Within the dot plot, each member of the Committee publishes its view of potential interest rates over the longer term. For investors, this is extremely useful information as it allows market participants to see if the consensus path for longer-term interest rates is changing. Related Reading: Bitcoin Price Regains Strength, Why BTC Could Surpass $18K This Time The markets, as well as Bitcoin investors, will therefore be eagerly watching the inflation forecasts for next year, as well as the interest rate expectations for 2023 and 2024. As economic journalist Colby Smith wrote in November, the September dot plot showed most officials favored a slowdown to 50 basis points in December. The question for next week will be whether the Fed, led by Powell, will put into play a slower rate hike pace of 25 basis points (bps) or even a pivot. The Fed introduced the notion of slowing down the pace of hikes in July and the September dot plot showed support from most officials for a downshift to 50bps in December. The question today is how far Powell goes to ratify that move https://t.co/Pn8n0lh4kZ @FinancialTimes pic.twitter.com/62XOqMlm3T &#8212; Colby Smith (@colbyLsmith) November 2, 2022 A Year-End Rally for Bitcoin? These two events could be the &#8220;last remaining hurdles&#8221; for a year-end rally for Bitcoin, QCP Capital wrote in an analysis. However, a higher-than-expected consumer price index and a tighter stance by the Federal Reserve could derail that rally, as was seen in the April and August reversals. Related Reading: Ethereum Addresses Holding 32 ETH Or More On The Rise, This On-Chain Data Shows On the other hand, further disinflation could lead many to seek a continuation of the rally through the end of the year, according to QCP Capital&#8217;s analysis. It goes on to say that the question markets now face is where inflation will bottom. Even if 2% inflation is out of reach next year, will it fall low enough such that the Fed will have room to cut rates while keeping real rates positive? Therefore, one key market theme for next year will be the shift from &#8216;peak inflation&#8217; to &#8216;trough inflation&#8217;. This is another reason why the dot plot is of paramount importance. As the last two releases show, Powell has stuck relatively strictly to projections regarding interest rates. Thus, the dot plot could reveal some insights into Powell&#8217;s thoughts about a pivot. If the new data matches CPI expectations, it would be the fifth consecutive monthly decline. After peaking at 9.1% YoY in June. Next week&#8217;s reading could be even the lowest since January. Will Powell Follow His Words Given Powell&#8217;s recent comments to the Brookings Institute on November 30, it is also likely that the FED will stick to the script and raise the policy rate by only 50 basis points to 4.5%, reinforcing bullish sentiment in the market. If the CPI even comes in below expectations, markets could frontrun the Fed&#8217;s decision and trigger an end-of-year rally. In any case, next week will provide blockbuster volatility in the Bitcoin and crypto markets. Investors should pay close attention to the release of the FED&#8217;s dot plot. At press time, Bitcoin was trading at $17,228, showing signs of strength ahead of the FOMC meeting.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>With the Bitcoin price posting a small gain of over 1.5% over the last seven days, the market is in for a blockbuster next week.</p>
<p>The release of the Consumer Price Index (CPI) on December 13, Tuesday at 08:30 AM ET, will once again be &#8220;the most important CPI ever&#8221;.</p>
<p>Just one day later, on December 14, Wednesday at 2:00 PM ET, the final Federal Open Market Committee (FOMC) meeting of the year will take place. Remarkably, FED members will release their updated forecasts for inflation and interest rates (dot plot) at the meeting.</p>
<h2>A Blockbuster Week</h2>
<p>The dot plot is released only four times a year &#8211; in March, June, September, and December &#8211; and presents the FOMC&#8217;s economic projections, which look at GDP, unemployment rates, and inflation for the coming months as well as over the longer term.</p>
<p>Within the dot plot, each member of the Committee publishes its view of potential interest rates over the longer term.</p>
<p>For investors, this is extremely useful information as it allows market participants to see if the consensus path for longer-term interest rates is changing.</p>

<p>The markets, as well as Bitcoin investors, will therefore be eagerly watching the inflation forecasts for next year, as well as the interest rate expectations for 2023 and 2024.</p>
<p>As economic journalist Colby Smith wrote in November, the September dot plot showed most officials favored a slowdown to 50 basis points in December.</p>
<p>The question for next week will be whether the Fed, led by Powell, will put into play a slower rate hike pace of 25 basis points (bps) or even a pivot.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">The Fed introduced the notion of slowing down the pace of hikes in July and the September dot plot showed support from most officials for a downshift to 50bps in December. The question today is how far Powell goes to ratify that move <a href="https://t.co/Pn8n0lh4kZ">https://t.co/Pn8n0lh4kZ</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/FinancialTimes?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@FinancialTimes</a> <a href="https://t.co/62XOqMlm3T">pic.twitter.com/62XOqMlm3T</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Colby Smith (@colbyLsmith) <a href="https://twitter.com/colbyLsmith/status/1587779692014223361?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">November 2, 2022</a></p></blockquote>
<p></p>
<h2>A Year-End Rally for Bitcoin?</h2>
<p>These two events could be the &#8220;last remaining hurdles&#8221; for a year-end rally for Bitcoin, QCP Capital <a href="https://twitter.com/QCPCapital/status/1601115933749100544" target="_blank" rel="noopener">wrote</a> in an analysis.</p>
<p>However, a higher-than-expected consumer price index and a tighter stance by the Federal Reserve could derail that rally, as was seen in the April and August reversals.</p>

<p>On the other hand, further disinflation could lead many to seek a continuation of the rally through the end of the year, according to QCP Capital&#8217;s analysis. It goes on to say that the question markets now face is where inflation will bottom.</p>
<blockquote><p><strong>Even if 2% inflation is out of reach next year, will it fall low enough such that the Fed will have room to cut rates while keeping real rates positive?</strong></p>
<p><strong>Therefore, one key market theme for next year will be the shift from &#8216;peak inflation&#8217; to &#8216;trough inflation&#8217;.</strong></p></blockquote>
<p>This is another reason why the dot plot is of paramount importance. As the last two releases show, Powell has stuck relatively strictly to projections regarding interest rates. Thus, the dot plot could reveal some insights into Powell&#8217;s thoughts about a pivot.</p>
<p>If the new data matches <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-bounces-after-cpi-dump/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CPI</a> expectations, it would be the fifth consecutive monthly decline. After peaking at 9.1% YoY in June. Next week&#8217;s reading could be even the lowest since January.</p>
<h2>Will Powell Follow His Words</h2>
<p>Given Powell&#8217;s recent comments to the Brookings Institute on November 30, it is also likely that the FED will stick to the script and raise the policy rate by only 50 basis points to 4.5%, reinforcing bullish sentiment in the market.</p>
<p>If the CPI even comes in below expectations, markets could frontrun the Fed&#8217;s decision and trigger an end-of-year rally. In any case, next week will provide blockbuster volatility in the Bitcoin and crypto markets.</p>
<p>Investors should pay close attention to the release of the FED&#8217;s dot plot.</p>
<p>At press time, Bitcoin was trading at $17,228, showing <a href="https://newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-regains-strength-17k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">signs of strength</a> ahead of the FOMC meeting.</p>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-511808 size-full" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-09_11-48-11.png" alt="Bitcoin BTC USD 2022-12-09" width="2956" height="1611" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-09_11-48-11.png 2956w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-09_11-48-11-460x251.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-09_11-48-11-860x469.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-09_11-48-11-768x419.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-09_11-48-11-1536x837.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-09_11-48-11-2048x1116.png 2048w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-09_11-48-11-750x409.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-09_11-48-11-1140x621.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 2956px) 100vw, 2956px" />
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/11/Depositphotos_300004850_s-2019-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>

<!--
Performance optimized by W3 Total Cache. Learn more: https://www.boldgrid.com/w3-total-cache/

Object Caching 188/192 objects using apc
Page Caching using disk: enhanced (Page is feed) 
Database Caching 39/45 queries in 0.008 seconds using memcached

Served from: newsbtc.com @ 2022-12-10 22:25:16 by W3 Total Cache
-->