<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	 xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" >

<channel>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://newsbtc.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://newsbtc.com</link>
	<description>Bitcoin &#38; cryptocurrency news today, price &#38; technical analysis</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 02:51:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<link>https://newsbtc.com</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Price Consolidates In Key Range, What Could Trigger Next Move</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-consolidates-16-5k/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 02:51:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xbtusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=514369</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin price is still facing resistance below $17,000. BTC could decline heavily if there is a clear move below the $16,000 support zone. Bitcoin is still showing bearish signs below the $16,800 and $17,000 resistance levels. The price is trading above $16,500 and the 100 hourly simple moving average. There was a break above a key bearish trend line with resistance near $16,550 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Kraken). The pair could resume its decline if there is a clear move below the $16,000 support. Bitcoin Price Remains In Downtrend Bitcoin price spiked below the $16,500 support zone. However, BTC bulls were active above the $16,200 level. The price traded as low as $16,325 and recently started an upside correction. There was a minor recovery wave above the $16,500 level. The price climbed above the $16,600 level and the 100 hourly simple moving average. However, the bears were active near the $16,680 zone. A high was formed near $16,683 and the price corrected lower. Bitcoin price declined below 23.6% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $16,325 low to $16,683 high. It found support near the $16,500 level. The price is trading above the 50% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $16,325 low to $16,683 high. It is also above $16,500 and the 100 hourly simple moving average. On the upside, an immediate resistance is near the $16,600 level. Source: BTCUSD on TradingView.com The first major resistance is near the $16,680 zone. The next major resistance is near the $16,800 level. The key breakout zone is still near the $17,000 level. A clear move above the $17,000 resistance might start a fresh increase in the near term. Fresh Decline in BTC? If bitcoin fails to start a recovery wave above the $16,650 resistance, it could start another decline. An immediate support on the downside is near the $16,500 level. The next major support is near the $16,350 level. A clear move below the $16,350 support might spark a move towards the $16,000 level. Any more losses might send the price towards $15,500. Technical indicators: Hourly MACD – The MACD is now losing pace in the bullish zone. Hourly RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BTC/USD is now near the 50 level. Major Support Levels – $16,500, followed by $16,350. Major Resistance Levels – $16,600, $16,800 and $17,000.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>Bitcoin price is still facing resistance below $17,000. BTC could decline heavily if there is a clear move below the $16,000 support zone.</em></p>
<ul>
<li>Bitcoin is still showing bearish signs below the $16,800 and $17,000 resistance levels.</li>
<li>The price is trading above $16,500 and the 100 hourly simple moving average.</li>
<li>There was a break above a key bearish trend line with resistance near $16,550 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could resume its decline if there is a clear move below the $16,000 support.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Bitcoin Price Remains In Downtrend</h2>
<p>Bitcoin price spiked below the <a href="https://newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-further-lower-16k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">$16,500 support zone</a>. However, BTC bulls were active above the $16,200 level. The price traded as low as $16,325 and recently started an upside correction.</p>
<p>There was a minor recovery wave above the $16,500 level. The price climbed above the $16,600 level and the 100 hourly simple moving average. However, the bears were active near the $16,680 zone. A high was formed near $16,683 and the price corrected lower.</p>
<p>Bitcoin price declined below 23.6% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $16,325 low to $16,683 high. It found support near the $16,500 level.</p>
<p>The price is trading above the 50% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $16,325 low to $16,683 high. It is also above $16,500 and the <a href="https://newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-grinds-lower-16k-2/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">100 hourly simple moving average</a>. On the upside, an immediate resistance is near the $16,600 level.</p>
<p><a href="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin.png"><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-514370" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin.png" alt="Bitcoin Price" width="1950" height="1109" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin.png 1950w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-460x262.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-860x489.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-768x437.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-1536x874.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-750x427.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-1140x648.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1950px) 100vw, 1950px" /></a></p>
<p>Source: <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BTCUSD/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">BTCUSD on TradingView.com</a></p>
<p>The first major resistance is near the $16,680 zone. The next major resistance is near the $16,800 level. The key breakout zone is still near the $17,000 level. A clear move above the $17,000 resistance might start a fresh increase in the near term.</p>
<h2>Fresh Decline in BTC?</h2>
<p>If bitcoin fails to start a recovery wave above the $16,650 resistance, it could start another decline. An immediate support on the downside is near the $16,500 level.</p>
<p>The next major support is near the $16,350 level. A clear move below the $16,350 support might spark a move towards the $16,000 level. Any more losses might send the price towards $15,500.</p>
<p>Technical indicators:</p>
<p>Hourly MACD – The MACD is now losing pace in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>Hourly RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BTC/USD is now near the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Levels – $16,500, followed by $16,350.</p>
<p>Major Resistance Levels – $16,600, $16,800 and $17,000.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/shutterstock_773873392-460x268.jpg" width="460" height="268" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Crypto Holiday Special: Past, Present, And Future With Tony Spilotro</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/interview/crypto-holiday-past-future-tony-spilotro/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reynaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 18:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Interview]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Holiday]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=514320</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[2022 is coming to an end, and our staff at NewsBTC decided to launch this Crypto Holiday Special to provide some perspective on the crypto industry. We will talk with multiple guests to understand this year’s highs and lows for crypto. Related Reading: A Crypto Holiday Special: Past, Present, And Future With Blofin In the spirit of Charles Dicken’s classic, “A Christmas Carol,” we’ll look into crypto from different angles, look at its possible trajectory for 2023 and find common ground amongst these different views of an industry that might support the future of finances. Spilotro: “As a nascent technology, crypto hasn’t been as susceptive to rate cycling in the past. But as it has become a bigger part of the financial system, it now follows by that system’s rules more than the community might like.” We close this series with an in-house guest, our Editorial Director, Tony Spilotro. Dedicated to spreading knowledge and tools for anyone willing to listen, Tony keeps tabs on the market by promoting critical thinking, going against the crowd, and developing a methodical approach to trading. Spilotro: “I am confident the mainstream media has it horribly wrong. In fact, the “magazine cover indicator” is one of the most proven ways to pick tops and bottoms in the stock market.” Tony is a proponent of the Elliot Wave Theory, which has perfectly described Bitcoin and crypto’s price trajectory since the early 2010s. The market is about to take a critical path, but in which direction? This is what he told us: Q: What’s the most significant difference for the crypto market today compared to Christmas 2021? Beyond the price of Bitcoin, Ethereum, and others, what changed from that moment of euphoria to today’s perpetual fear? Has there been a decline in adoption and liquidity? Are fundamentals still valid? A: The biggest difference today versus then are the macro conditions and money flow. The Fed tightening did its trick, taking the bull by the horns so to speak. Ned Davis Research had a rule, “Don’t Fight The Fed” and it was proven true over the last year plus. As a nascent technology, crypto hasn’t been as susceptive to rate cycling in the past. But as it has become a bigger part of the financial system, it now follows by that system’s rules more than the community might like. The industry was hurt badly by the domino-effect over the last several months, heightened by the LUNA collapse and FTX fiasco. But Bitcoin and some other cryptocurrencies feel fundamentally strong. Given how rough it is out there for many stocks, how well such a speculative asset class is holding up is remarkable. My belief in Bitcoin isn’t shaken, but like anything, will continue to have its ebbs and flows of investor enthusiasm. Q: What are the dominant narratives driving this change in market conditions? And what should be the narrative today? What are most people overlooking? We saw a major crypto exchange blowing up, a hedge fund thought to be untouchable, and an ecosystem that promised a financial utopia. Is Crypto still the future of finance, or should the community pursue a new vision? A: For me, time drives the narratives. The market will find a narrative when the time is right. The last narrative was Bitcoin as an inflation hedge and it performed horribly during the highest inflation in years. Narratives are very often false – but we all fall for it again and again. The next narrative will likely be overly-euphoric and result in its eventual destruction when the sentiment tide turns. I once again turn to a few things. Crypto is a nascent technology where we’ve barely scratched the surface of what’s possible. Even the internet is early in its design compared to the highway system or railroads. Crypto is a newborn by comparison. Much like the internet before it, when people don’t understand it fully, it is easier to fall victim to greater market sentiment and narratives. The dot com bubble is a great example. Much like all the other times Bitcoin was claimed dead, its doing nothing more than shaking out the non-believers and sucking up those that are ready to believe. Sadly, I don’t think there is a financial utopia ahead, rather Bitcoin becomes our best bet retaining ownership rights over value. I think it becomes the digital version of money in the mattress. Q: If you must choose one, what do you think was a significant moment for crypto in 2022? And will the industry feel its consequences across 2023? Where do you see the industry next Christmas? Will it survive this winter? Mainstream is once again declaring the death of the industry. Will they finally get it right? A: The most significant moment for crypto in 2022 had to be the FTX situation, although one might argue that would never have occurred without the LUNA collapse preceding it. I think the industry heavily feels the impact of the fallout for the next years and beyond. Sweeping regulation should occur, wiping out many shitcoins from existence. Rules will be put in place so no business can raise capital a’la FTT tokens. Some innovation will stifle, especially around DeFi and Ethereum. Scarcity and stronger network usage fundamentals will decouple from the rest of crypto. I am confident the mainstream media has it horribly wrong. In fact, the “magazine cover indicator” is one of the most proven ways to pick tops and bottoms in the stock market. When mainstream media starts reporting on it heavily, an extreme in sentiment is usually here. Q: What has been the best indicator to watch in 2022, and what indicators are you keeping track of for 2023? We know you based a lot of your analysis on the Elliot Wave theory; what can market participants expect next year according to this theory? A: The best indicator for 2022 was the weekly Ichimoku cloud. The moment BTCUSD fell out of the Ichimoku cloud, it was lights out for bulls and a deep decline followed. Granted, this happened after Bitcoin had fallen some in value – it was the confirmation that the bull run was finished for some time. I should have given this more weight, especially after seeing how Bitcoin behaved after losing the cloud back in March of 2020. Elliott Wave Theory matches price patterns the crowd isn’t often looking for – such as zig-zags or flats — with price extremes and, more importantly, sentiment extremes. Related Reading: A Crypto Holiday Special: Past, Present, And Future With Ex BNY Mellon David Schwed I’m a big contrarian in general, and I go by the nickname Tony “The Bull” so I lean bullish on BTC overall. If the crowd is bearish, I feel safer being bullish and vice versa. That said, I’m bullish on BTC for one last rally. I’ve been building the last 1-2 years of positions in anticipation of what I believe will be a shocking wave 5 for Bitcoin and the total crypto market cap. Just when everyone turns bullish once again and we’ve made ridiculous new highs, I’ll temporarily retire Tony “The Bull” and turn to the biggest bear in crypto –because this is what I believe to be the grand finale for some time.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>2022 is coming to an end, and our staff at NewsBTC decided to launch this Crypto Holiday Special to provide some perspective on the crypto industry. We will talk with multiple guests to understand this year’s highs and lows for crypto.</strong></p>

<p><strong>In the spirit of Charles Dicken’s classic, “A Christmas Carol,” we’ll look into crypto from different angles, look at its possible trajectory for 2023 and find common ground amongst these different views of an industry that might support the future of finances.</strong></p>
<p style="text-align: center"><strong>Spilotro: “As a nascent technology, crypto hasn’t been as susceptive to rate cycling in the past. But as it has become a bigger part of the financial system, it now follows by that system’s rules more than the community might like.”</strong></p>
<p>We close this series with an in-house guest, our Editorial Director, <a href="https://twitter.com/tonyspilotroBTC" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Tony Spilotro</a>. Dedicated to spreading knowledge and tools for anyone willing to listen, Tony keeps tabs on the market by promoting critical thinking, going against the crowd, and developing a methodical approach to trading.</p>
<p style="text-align: center"><strong>Spilotro: “I am confident the mainstream media has it horribly wrong. In fact, the “magazine cover indicator” is one of the most proven ways to pick tops and bottoms in the stock market.”</strong></p>
<p>Tony is a proponent of the Elliot Wave Theory, which has perfectly described Bitcoin and crypto’s price trajectory since the early 2010s. The market is about to take a critical path, but in which direction? This is what he told us:</p>
<p><strong>Q: What’s the most significant difference for the crypto market today compared to Christmas 2021? Beyond the price of Bitcoin, Ethereum, and others, what changed from that moment of euphoria to today’s perpetual fear? Has there been a decline in adoption and liquidity? Are fundamentals still valid? </strong></p>
<p>A: The biggest difference today versus then are the macro conditions and money flow. The Fed tightening did its trick, taking the bull by the horns so to speak. Ned Davis Research had a rule, “Don’t Fight The Fed” and it was proven true over the last year plus. As a nascent technology, crypto hasn’t been as susceptive to rate cycling in the past. But as it has become a bigger part of the financial system, it now follows by that system’s rules more than the community might like. The industry was hurt badly by the domino-effect over the last several months, heightened by the LUNA collapse and FTX fiasco. But Bitcoin and some other cryptocurrencies feel fundamentally strong. Given how rough it is out there for many stocks, how well such a speculative asset class is holding up is remarkable. My belief in Bitcoin isn’t shaken, but like anything, will continue to have its ebbs and flows of investor enthusiasm.</p>
<p><strong>Q: What are the dominant narratives driving this change in market conditions? And what should be the narrative today? What are most people overlooking? We saw a major crypto exchange blowing up, a hedge fund thought to be untouchable, and an ecosystem that promised a financial utopia. Is Crypto still the future of finance, or should the community pursue a new vision?</strong></p>
<p>A: For me, time drives the narratives. The market will find a narrative when the time is right. The last narrative was Bitcoin as an inflation hedge and it performed horribly during the highest inflation in years. Narratives are very often false – but we all fall for it again and again. The next narrative will likely be overly-euphoric and result in its eventual destruction when the sentiment tide turns. I once again turn to a few things. Crypto is a nascent technology where we’ve barely scratched the surface of what’s possible. Even the internet is early in its design compared to the highway system or railroads. Crypto is a newborn by comparison. Much like the internet before it, when people don’t understand it fully, it is easier to fall victim to greater market sentiment and narratives. The dot com bubble is a great example. Much like all the other times Bitcoin was claimed dead, its doing nothing more than shaking out the non-believers and sucking up those that are ready to believe. Sadly, I don’t think there is a financial utopia ahead, rather Bitcoin becomes our best bet retaining ownership rights over value. I think it becomes the digital version of money in the mattress.</p>
<p><strong>Q: If you must choose one, what do you think was a significant moment for crypto in 2022? And will the industry feel its consequences across 2023? Where do you see the industry next Christmas? Will it survive this winter? Mainstream is once again declaring the death of the industry. Will they finally get it right? </strong></p>
<p>A: The most significant moment for crypto in 2022 had to be the FTX situation, although one might argue that would never have occurred without the LUNA collapse preceding it. I think the industry heavily feels the impact of the fallout for the next years and beyond. Sweeping regulation should occur, wiping out many shitcoins from existence. Rules will be put in place so no business can raise capital a’la FTT tokens. Some innovation will stifle, especially around DeFi and Ethereum. Scarcity and stronger network usage fundamentals will decouple from the rest of crypto. I am confident the mainstream media has it horribly wrong. In fact, the “magazine cover indicator” is one of the most proven ways to pick tops and bottoms in the stock market. When mainstream media starts reporting on it heavily, an extreme in sentiment is usually here.</p>
<p><strong>Q: What has been the best indicator to watch in 2022, and what indicators are you keeping track of for 2023? We know you based a lot of your analysis on the Elliot Wave theory; what can market participants expect next year according to this theory?</strong></p>
<p>A: The best indicator for 2022 was the weekly Ichimoku cloud. The moment BTCUSD fell out of the Ichimoku cloud, it was lights out for bulls and a deep decline followed. Granted, this happened after Bitcoin had fallen some in value – it was the confirmation that the bull run was finished for some time. I should have given this more weight, especially after seeing how Bitcoin behaved after losing the cloud back in March of 2020. Elliott Wave Theory matches price patterns the crowd isn’t often looking for – such as zig-zags or flats — with price extremes and, more importantly, sentiment extremes.</p>



<p>I’m a big contrarian in general, and I go by the nickname Tony “The Bull” so I lean bullish on BTC overall. If the crowd is bearish, I feel safer being bullish and vice versa. That said, I’m bullish on BTC for one last rally. I’ve been building the last 1-2 years of positions in anticipation of what I believe will be a shocking wave 5 for Bitcoin and the total crypto market cap.</p>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-514198 size-large" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Crypto-holiday-BTC-BTCUSDT-Binance-CFO-Wei-Zhou-860x376.png" alt="Crypto holiday BTC BTCUSDT Binance CFO Wei Zhou" width="860" height="376" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Crypto-holiday-BTC-BTCUSDT-Binance-CFO-Wei-Zhou-860x376.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Crypto-holiday-BTC-BTCUSDT-Binance-CFO-Wei-Zhou-460x201.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Crypto-holiday-BTC-BTCUSDT-Binance-CFO-Wei-Zhou-768x336.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Crypto-holiday-BTC-BTCUSDT-Binance-CFO-Wei-Zhou-1536x672.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Crypto-holiday-BTC-BTCUSDT-Binance-CFO-Wei-Zhou-750x328.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Crypto-holiday-BTC-BTCUSDT-Binance-CFO-Wei-Zhou-1140x499.png 1140w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Crypto-holiday-BTC-BTCUSDT-Binance-CFO-Wei-Zhou.png 1813w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" />
<p>Just when everyone turns bullish once again and we’ve made ridiculous new highs, I’ll temporarily retire Tony “The Bull” and turn to the biggest bear in crypto –because this is what I believe to be the grand finale for some time.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Crypto-Holiday-Special-cover-image-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Decentraland (MANA) Sheds 90% In 2022 Despite Solid NFT Volume Performance</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/decentraland-sheds-90-in-2022/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 10:29:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[decentraland]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MANA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NFT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[non-fungible token]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Token]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=514344</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Decentraland (MANA), the cryptocurrency launched in 2020 by Ariel Meilich and Esteban Ordano, failed to take advantage of some of the positive developments that happened within its ecosystem this year as it closes 2022 in a “beaten” state. Over the last 12 months, the digital coin has shed 91% of its value, failing to recover from the massive price dumps it experienced triggered by the a series of unfortunate events that plagued the crypto space and the growing uncertainty in the market. According to latest tracking from Coingecko, at the time of writing, the digital token is changing hands at $0.2941 and has lost 10.3% of its value during the past seven days. The last 30 days have been rocky for Decentraland as well, as the altcoin ended up depreciating in value by 27.3%. This really is unfortunate, considering the crypto’s ecosystem has been making impressive progress in the NFT realm. Related Reading: Is Polkadot (DOT) A Must-Have For Your 2023 Portfolio? Decentraland: 440% Growth In Minted NFTs The metaverse-based gaming platform seemed to have focused most of its attention to the non-fungible token (NFT) space this year, as evidenced by its incredible performance pertaining to the industry. In its yearend performance report, Decentraland disclosed that for the year 2022, there were 2.7 million unique NFTs that have been released on its platform. With such a figure, on a year-over-year (YoY) basis, the project enjoyed a 440% increase in the volume of NFT assets minted on its network. Decentraland was also proud to announce that it will end 2022 with a unique active user count of 1 million after it tallied a 13% jump in that particular department over the last 12 months. Moreover, the project also managed to grow its sales volume by 510% during the same time period after it sold 143,900 wearable NFTs. However, even with this superlative showing, Decentraland’s MANA failed to catch a break from its bearish streak. Related Reading: Solana Continues Its Freefall – Will The FUD Ever Stop? Crypto total market cap at $755 billion on the daily chart &#124; Chart: TradingView.com What MANA Holders Can Expect In 2023 There’s a bit of good news for holders of the Decentraland altcoin as Coincodex predicts a possible increase in value in the coming days. According to the online cryptocurrency information provider, over the next five days, the digital asset’s trading price is expected to rise by more than 2% and will change hands at a value of $0.2977. Meanwhile, 30 days from now, the crypto is expected to hit and surpass the $0.30 mark once again as it is expected to trade at $0.3305. If these forecasts translate into reality, MANA holders and investors could finally find a little breathing room to take a break from the challenging landscape of crypto industry today. &#8211; Featured Image: Lumiere Children&#8217;s Therapy]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Decentraland (MANA), the cryptocurrency launched in 2020 by Ariel Meilich and Esteban Ordano, failed to take advantage of some of the positive developments that happened within its ecosystem this year as it closes 2022 in a “beaten” state.</p>
<p>Over the last 12 months, the digital coin has shed 91% of its value, failing to recover from the massive price dumps it experienced triggered by the a series of unfortunate events that plagued the crypto space and the growing uncertainty in the market.</p>
<p>According to latest tracking from <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/decentraland" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Coingecko</a>, at the time of writing, the digital token is changing hands at $0.2941 and has lost 10.3% of its value during the past seven days.</p>
<p>The last 30 days have been rocky for Decentraland as well, as the altcoin ended up depreciating in value by 27.3%.</p>
<p>This really is unfortunate, considering the crypto’s ecosystem has been making impressive progress in the NFT realm.</p>

<h2><b>Decentraland: 440% Growth In Minted NFTs</b></h2>
<p>The metaverse-based gaming platform seemed to have focused most of its attention to the non-fungible token (NFT) space this year, as evidenced by its <a href="https://ambcrypto.com/decentraland-closes-2022-on-a-sour-note-despite-440-growth-in-volume/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">incredible performance</a> pertaining to the industry.</p>
<p>In its yearend performance report, Decentraland disclosed that for the year 2022, there were 2.7 million unique NFTs that have been released on its platform.</p>
<p>With such a figure, on a year-over-year (YoY) basis, the project enjoyed a 440% increase in the volume of NFT assets minted on its network.</p>
<p>Decentraland was also proud to announce that it will end 2022 with a unique active user count of 1 million after it tallied a 13% jump in that particular department over the last 12 months.</p>
<p>Moreover, the project also managed to grow its sales volume by 510% during the same time period after it sold 143,900 wearable NFTs.</p>
<p>However, even with this superlative showing, Decentraland’s MANA failed to catch a break from its bearish streak.</p>


<h2><b>What MANA Holders Can Expect In 2023</b></h2>
<p>There’s a bit of good news for holders of the Decentraland altcoin as Coincodex predicts a possible increase in value in the coming days.</p>
<p>According to the <a href="https://coincodex.com/crypto/decentraland/price-prediction/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">online cryptocurrency information provider</a>, over the next five days, the digital asset’s trading price is expected to rise by more than 2% and will change hands at a value of $0.2977.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, 30 days from now, the crypto is expected to hit and surpass the $0.30 mark once again as it is expected to trade at $0.3305.</p>
<p>If these forecasts translate into reality, MANA holders and investors could finally find a little breathing room to take a break from the challenging landscape of crypto industry today.</p>
<p>&#8211;</p>
<p><em>Featured Image: Lumiere Children&#8217;s Therapy</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Decen-460x310.png" width="460" height="310" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Solana Continues Its Freefall &#8211; Will The FUD Ever Stop?</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/solana-continues-its-freefall/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2022 18:40:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sol]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Solana Ecosystem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tags: Solana]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=514336</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Solana has been on a freefall since the collapse of FTX and has not been able to move upwards because of the FUD (fear, uncertainty and doubt) surrounding the ecosystem and its connections with the former crypto exchange. According to recent news, Solana’s native token SOL has dropped 51.14% since the day FTX fell from grace.  Solana: Dead Or Not Dead?  The current situation might be confusing to investors. Based on data by CoinGeko, the token shot up by 5.4% in the past 24 hours which might be a signal that investor sentiment is reversing. However, the FUD still remains strong around the ecosystem itself.  Messari released an overview of the ecosystem back on December 15. The basic gist of the overview was that Solana is still a solid ecosystem even after the collapse of the Sam Bankman-Fried-led exchange. However, recent Santiment insight on the ecosystem shows that it might be already dead.  The most notable on-chain development for the token was the significant drop in developer activity despite a lot of projects being developed on the ecosystem. Although it is difficult to say whether Solana as a whole is dead or near it, it is easier to say that the ecosystem is struggling to keep itself afloat because of its close ties with FTX.  Image: Coincu News What This Means For Holders Of SOL The crypto community seems to be very bearish at the moment considering what transpired in the past weeks courtesy of some major macroeconomics news, including the spate of job cuts and bankruptcies by big crypto firms. Those who are bullish for the ecosystem point to ETH’s crash back in 2018 and how SOL’s movement mimics this.  For everyone that sold #ETH in 2018 for 88 USD and for everyone who is selling $SOL sub 10 USD! Fundamentals haven’t changed and Solana isn’t FTX! Just sayin! 🫡 pic.twitter.com/IBYzldEaBd — MANDO CT (@XMaximist) December 29, 2022 MANDO CT, a self-declared crypto expert, said the above on his pinned tweet. Others try to refute the claim that Solana only blew up with the help of Bankman-Fried’s dirty money with documents which show SBF supporting competitors of Solana.  SOL total market cap at $3.5 billion on the daily chart &#124; Chart: TradingView.com Related Reading: Is Polkadot (DOT) A Must-Have For Your 2023 Portfolio? However, SOL’s price movement reflects investor sentiment on the token itself &#8211; fear, uncertainty, and doubt: fear that the ecosystem would inevitably follow the path of FTX. uncertainty on what 2023 will bring for Solana. doubt regarding the ecosystem despite the amount of projects being worked on top of it.  However, with several big developments like Solana Pay and the nearing launch of its own mobile phones, we might see 2023 to become a crucial part of Solana&#8217;s recovery, or a further catalyst of its downfall.  &#8211; Featured image: Cryptopolitan]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Solana has been on a freefall since the collapse of FTX and has not been able to move upwards because of the FUD (fear, uncertainty and doubt) surrounding the ecosystem and its connections with the former crypto exchange. </p>
<p>According to recent <a href="https://cyprus-mail.com/2022/12/30/solana-crypto-token-loses-most-of-its-value-in-2022-ftx-collapse-weighs/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">news</a>, Solana’s native token SOL has dropped 51.14% since the day FTX fell from grace. </p>
<h2><strong>Solana: Dead Or Not Dead? </strong></h2>
<p>The current situation might be confusing to investors. Based on data by <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/solana" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">CoinGeko</a>, the token shot up by 5.4% in the past 24 hours which might be a signal that investor sentiment is reversing. However, the FUD still remains strong around the ecosystem itself. </p>
<p>Messari released an <a href="https://messari.io/report/solana-ecosystem-overview?referrer=asset:solana" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">overview</a> of the ecosystem back on December 15. The basic gist of the overview was that Solana is still a solid ecosystem even after the collapse of the Sam Bankman-Fried-led exchange. </p>
<p>However, recent Santiment <a href="https://insights.santiment.net/read/is-solana-s-o-l-s-outta-luck-7154?utm_source=twitter&amp;utm_medium=post&amp;utm_campaign=twitter_is_solana_sol_insight_b_122722/&amp;fpr=twitter" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">insight</a> on the ecosystem shows that it might be already dead. </p>
<p>The most notable on-chain development for the token was the <a href="https://app.santiment.net/s/OqevSPN8" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">significant drop</a> in developer activity despite a lot of projects being <a href="https://twitter.com/0xSydney/status/1608084692229820417?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">developed</a> on the ecosystem. </p>
<p>Although it is difficult to say whether Solana as a whole is dead or near it, it is easier to say that the ecosystem is struggling to keep itself afloat because of its close ties with FTX. </p>

<h2><strong>What This Means For Holders Of SOL</strong></h2>
<p>The crypto community seems to be very bearish at the moment considering what transpired in the past weeks courtesy of some major macroeconomics news, including the spate of job cuts and bankruptcies by big crypto firms.</p>
<p>Those who are bullish for the ecosystem point to ETH’s crash back in 2018 and how SOL’s movement mimics this. </p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">For everyone that sold <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/ETH?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">#ETH</a> in 2018 for 88 USD and for everyone who is selling <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24SOL&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">$SOL</a> sub 10 USD!</p>
<p>Fundamentals haven’t changed and Solana isn’t FTX!</p>
<p>Just sayin! <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1fae1.png" alt="🫡" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> <a href="https://t.co/IBYzldEaBd" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/IBYzldEaBd</a></p>
<p>— MANDO CT (@XMaximist) <a href="https://twitter.com/XMaximist/status/1608347304414658561?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">December 29, 2022</a></p></blockquote>
<p><a href="https://twitter.com/XMaximist" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">MANDO CT</a>, a self-declared crypto expert, said the above on his <a href="https://twitter.com/XMaximist/status/1608347304414658561?s=20" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">pinned</a> tweet. </p>
<p>Others try to <a href="https://twitter.com/0xMert_/status/1608503029103484928?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">refute</a> the claim that Solana only blew up with the help of Bankman-Fried’s dirty money with documents which show SBF supporting competitors of Solana. </p>


<p>However, SOL’s price movement reflects investor sentiment on the token itself &#8211; fear, uncertainty, and doubt: </p>
<ul>
<li>fear that the ecosystem would inevitably follow the path of FTX. </li>
<li>uncertainty on what 2023 will bring for Solana. </li>
<li>doubt regarding the ecosystem despite the amount of projects being worked on top of it. </li>
</ul>
<p>However, with several big developments like <a href="https://twitter.com/solana/status/1605672309137715200?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Solana Pay</a> and the <a href="https://twitter.com/solana/status/1605672307145510912?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">nearing launch</a> of its own mobile phones, we might see 2023 to become a crucial part of Solana&#8217;s recovery, or a further catalyst of its downfall. </p>
<p>&#8211;</p>
<p><em>Featured image: Cryptopolitan</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/sol-1-460x341.png" width="460" height="341" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Crypto Holiday Special: Past, Present, And Future With Material Indicators</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/interview/crypto-holiday-future-material-indicators/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reynaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2022 18:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Interview]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Holiday]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=514290</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[2022 is coming to an end, and our staff at NewsBTC decided to launch this Crypto Holiday Special to provide some perspective on the crypto industry. We will talk with multiple guests to understand this year’s highs and lows for crypto. Related Reading: A Crypto Holiday Special: Past, Present, And Future With Ex BNY Mellon David Schwed In the spirit of Charles Dicken’s classic, “A Christmas Carol,” we’ll look into crypto from different angles, look at its possible trajectory for 2023 and find common ground amongst these different views of an industry that might support the future of finances. Over the last week, we spoke with institutions about their perception of 2022 and their outlook for the coming months. We’ll begin our experts round with Material Indicators, a market data, and analytics firm dedicated to building trading tools for the nascent sector. Material Indicators: “While we have yet to see tradfi (Traditional Finances) price in earnings contraction (~Q1&#8217;23) for the last leg down, we are already close to bottoming sentiment-wise.” Material Indicators and their team of analyst gauge market sentiment and liquidity and try to read between the lines of what big players are doing to provide a clear view, absent of noise, about its conditions and possible direction. This is what they told us: Q: What’s the most significant difference for the crypto market today compared to Christmas 2021? Beyond the price of Bitcoin, Ethereum, and others, what changed from that moment of euphoria to today’s perpetual fear? Has there been a decline in adoption and liquidity? Are fundamentals still valid? A: The difference is striking! Since the FTX blowup, the influx of new people to Crypto Twitter has been reduced to a trickle. Salty Youtubers will now advise you to sell your remaining coins to avoid a total loss. Telegram communities have been shrinking. Big accounts who&#8217;ve been telling their followers to buy have either quit or rebranded. While we have yet to see tradfi (Traditional Finances) price in earnings contraction (~Q1&#8217;23) for the last leg down, we are already close to bottoming sentiment-wise. Q: What are the dominant narratives driving this change in market conditions? And what should be the narrative today? What are most people overlooking? We saw a major crypto exchange blowing up, a hedge fund thought to be untouchable, and an ecosystem that promised a financial utopia. Is Crypto still the future of finance, or should the community pursue a new vision? A: It&#8217;s the other way around. Conditions create narratives. Loose monetary policy and abundant cheap credit create bubbles and nurture fraud. It&#8217;s only after the tide recedes that we see who has been swimming naked. With an imminent rise in unemployment, people will try to hide in bonds, which actually improves credit-availability for risk assets. So, while earnings-driven assets will feel pain on higher unemployment, credit-driven assets (risk assets) will feel relatively less pain. Q: If you must choose one, what do you think was a significant moment for crypto in 2022? And will the industry feel its consequences across 2023? Where do you see the industry next Christmas? Will it survive this winter? Mainstream is once again declaring the death of the industry. Will they finally get it right? A: Terra/Luna was probably the catalyst for all the subsequent blowups and we have yet to see the full effects of contagion (DCG/Grayscale/Genesis are not fully resolved yet). As with any blowup, this will just invite more regulation that will neither protect investors, nor improve the potential for growth. We wanted institutional adoption and now we see that they had zero risk-management and gambled away their user funds. Related Reading: A Crypto Holiday Special: Past, Present, And Future With Blofin Q: Finally, across social media, you guys at Material Indicators made your bearish bias public. Are you more or less pessimistic than you were at the beginning of 2022? And what will you like to see to shift your bias and lean towards the long side of the market? We know a lot depends on the Federal Reserve, are the chances of a pivot and lower interest rates hikes higher? A: While we&#8217;re probably not quite out of the woods yet, we can already almost see the light. On poor earnings &#38; poor forecasts bonds will likely catch a bid in Q1&#8217;23, and therefore make credit available to risk assets to dampen their fall or even help them recover (especially if the Treasury manages to relieve the RRP of its ~$2T idle liquidity). Bitcoin could also benefit from this as it&#8217;s only subject to credit-availability and not earnings. However, while inflation has been and will likely continue to fall for some time, it is unlikely that we&#8217;ve seen the last of it. So, keep an eye out for potentially re-surging inflation sometime in late-&#8217;23/early-&#8217;24.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>2022 is coming to an end, and our staff at NewsBTC decided to launch this Crypto Holiday Special to provide some perspective on the crypto industry. We will talk with multiple guests to understand this year’s highs and lows for crypto.</strong></p>



<p><strong>In the spirit of Charles Dicken’s classic, “A Christmas Carol,” we’ll look into crypto from different angles, look at its possible trajectory for 2023 and find common ground amongst these different views of an industry that might support the future of finances. </strong></p>
<p>Over the last week, we spoke with institutions about their perception of 2022 and their outlook for the coming months. We’ll begin our experts round with <a href="https://twitter.com/MI_Algos" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Material Indicators</a>, a market data, and analytics firm dedicated to building trading tools for the nascent sector.</p>
<p style="text-align: center"><strong>Material Indicators: “While we have yet to see tradfi (Traditional Finances) price in earnings contraction (~Q1&#8217;23) for the last leg down, we are already close to bottoming sentiment-wise.”</strong></p>
<p>Material Indicators and their team of analyst gauge market sentiment and liquidity and try to read between the lines of what big players are doing to provide a clear view, absent of noise, about its conditions and possible direction. This is what they told us:</p>
<p><strong>Q: What’s the most significant difference for the crypto market today compared to Christmas 2021? Beyond the price of Bitcoin, Ethereum, and others, what changed from that moment of euphoria to today’s perpetual fear? Has there been a decline in adoption and liquidity? Are fundamentals still valid? </strong></p>
<p>A: The difference is striking! Since the FTX blowup, the influx of new people to Crypto Twitter has been reduced to a trickle. Salty Youtubers will now advise you to sell your remaining coins to avoid a total loss. Telegram communities have been shrinking. Big accounts who&#8217;ve been telling their followers to buy have either quit or rebranded. While we have yet to see tradfi (Traditional Finances) price in earnings contraction (~Q1&#8217;23) for the last leg down, we are already close to bottoming sentiment-wise.</p>
<p><strong>Q: What are the dominant narratives driving this change in market conditions? And what should be the narrative today? What are most people overlooking? We saw a major crypto exchange blowing up, a hedge fund thought to be untouchable, and an ecosystem that promised a financial utopia. Is Crypto still the future of finance, or should the community pursue a new vision?</strong></p>
<p>A: It&#8217;s the other way around. Conditions create narratives. Loose monetary policy and abundant cheap credit create bubbles and nurture fraud. It&#8217;s only after the tide recedes that we see who has been swimming naked. With an imminent rise in unemployment, people will try to hide in bonds, which actually improves credit-availability for risk assets. So, while earnings-driven assets will feel pain on higher unemployment, credit-driven assets (risk assets) will feel relatively less pain.</p>
<p><strong>Q: If you must choose one, what do you think was a significant moment for crypto in 2022? And will the industry feel its consequences across 2023? Where do you see the industry next Christmas? Will it survive this winter? Mainstream is once again declaring the death of the industry. Will they finally get it right? </strong></p>
<p>A: Terra/Luna was probably the catalyst for all the subsequent blowups and we have yet to see the full effects of contagion (DCG/Grayscale/Genesis are not fully resolved yet). As with any blowup, this will just invite more regulation that will neither protect investors, nor improve the potential for growth. We wanted institutional adoption and now we see that they had zero risk-management and gambled away their user funds.</p>

<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-211512 size-large" src="https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Crypto-holiday-Material-Indicators-Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-980x429.png" alt="Crypto holiday Material Indicators Bitcoin BTC BTCUSDT" width="980" height="429" />




<p><strong>Q: Finally, across social media, you guys at Material Indicators made your bearish bias public. Are you more or less pessimistic than you were at the beginning of 2022? And what will you like to see to shift your bias and lean towards the long side of the market? We know a lot depends on the Federal Reserve, are the chances of a pivot and lower interest rates hikes higher? </strong></p>
<p>A: While we&#8217;re probably not quite out of the woods yet, we can already almost see the light. On poor earnings &amp; poor forecasts bonds will likely catch a bid in Q1&#8217;23, and therefore make credit available to risk assets to dampen their fall or even help them recover (especially if the Treasury manages to relieve the RRP of its ~$2T idle liquidity). Bitcoin could also benefit from this as it&#8217;s only subject to credit-availability and not earnings. However, while inflation has been and will likely continue to fall for some time, it is unlikely that we&#8217;ve seen the last of it. So, keep an eye out for potentially re-surging inflation sometime in late-&#8217;23/early-&#8217;24.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Crypto-Holiday-Special-cover-image-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Is Polkadot (DOT) A Must-Have For Your 2023 Portfolio?</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/is-polkadot-a-must-have/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2022 05:06:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DOT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DOT Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[polkadot]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Polkadot Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=514330</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The year 2023 is said to be huge for Polkadot (DOT) as it is one of the cryptocurrencies to watch out for. Many crypto experts are very optimistic about Polkadot, and they’re saying that traders should keep an eye on the coin because its developments will be big for that year. DOT is looking bearish but can pivot to a bull run in the coming days Polkadot is said to be an attractive addition to the investment portfolio for 2023 DOT price is down by 1.43% While DOT isn’t performing well as of press time, crypto experts believe that this is the best time to buy. The coin is regarded as one of the safety nets and best bets to include in your portfolio for next year. According to CoinMarketCap, DOT price is down by 1.43% or trading at $4.28 as of this writing. And many crypto experts think that the discounted price should entice more traders to buy while the prices are still low because it’s bound to spike by next year. Polkadot: One Of The Most Liquid Assets Even though Polkadot has depreciated in value, it’s still the top-rated crypto in terms of capturing investor interest. It stands out when pitted with other cryptos as it’s also one of the popular liquid assets included in hedge fund portfolios. Indeed, there is an increasing demand for Polkadot, and it is seen to have the most potential to rise in 2023. In fact, as early as now, many top investment companies and even hedge funds are putting most of their eggs on the Polkadot basket. Related Reading: Hedera: Is 2023 The Comeback Year For HBAR NFTs? DOGE total market cap at $9.06 billion on the daily chart &#124; Chart: TradingView.com DOT May Kick Off Bullish Run Polkadot has been looking bearish as it recently dipped to as low as $4.20 in the past 24 hours. This retreat has attracted investors in the past, and it may also draw them in now. On the other hand, DOT’s technical indicators hint at some bullish movement, with its volume reached a new low as registered on December 25. Still, it is now slowly recovering from the slump. Related Reading: Dogecoin Breaking Past This Key Barrier Could Spell 10% Spike For DOGE Eco-Friendly Crypto DOT’s market capitalization shows that the bears still dominate the market for December, but its market cap has an uptick by $100 million overnight, which looks like an accumulation. More so, the development activity is also seen to nosedive, which can be worrisome, especially for investors. Meanwhile, Polkadot, along with Cardano and Algorand, is among the most eco-friendly cryptocurrencies, according to a new analysis by the Traders of Crypto. Polkadot ranks as the fourth most eco-friendly digital money, with annual carbon emissions of 50 tons. &#8211; Featured image: VOI]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The year 2023 is said to be huge for Polkadot (DOT) as it is one of the cryptocurrencies to watch out for. Many<a href="https://dailyhodl.com/2022/12/26/coin-bureau-says-2023-could-be-big-year-for-ethereum-details-forecast-for-eth-and-polkadot-dot/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow"> crypto experts</a> are very optimistic about Polkadot, and they’re saying that traders should keep an eye on the coin because its developments will be big for that year.</p>
<ul>
<li>DOT is looking bearish but can pivot to a bull run in the coming days</li>
<li>Polkadot is said to be an attractive addition to the investment portfolio for 2023</li>
<li>DOT price is down by 1.43%</li>
</ul>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="size-medium wp-image-503391 aligncenter" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/Polkadot-460x229.png" alt="Polkadot" width="460" height="229" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/Polkadot-460x229.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/Polkadot-768x383.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/Polkadot-360x180.png 360w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/Polkadot-750x374.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/Polkadot.png 772w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px" /></p>
<p>While DOT isn’t performing well as of press time, crypto experts believe that this is the best time to buy. The coin is regarded as one of the safety nets and best bets to include in your portfolio for next year.</p>
<p>According to<a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/polkadot-new/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow"> CoinMarketCap</a>, DOT price is down by 1.43% or trading at $4.28 as of this writing. And many crypto experts think that the discounted price should entice more traders to buy while the prices are still low because it’s bound to spike by next year.</p>
<h2><b>Polkadot: One Of The Most Liquid Assets</b></h2>
<p>Even though Polkadot has depreciated in value, it’s still the top-rated crypto in terms of capturing investor interest. It stands out when pitted with other cryptos as it’s also one of the popular liquid assets included in hedge fund portfolios.</p>
<p>Indeed, there is an increasing demand for Polkadot, and it is seen to have the most potential to rise in 2023. In fact, as early as now, many top investment companies and even hedge funds are putting most of their eggs on the Polkadot basket.</p>


<h2><b>DOT May Kick Off Bullish Run</b></h2>
<p>Polkadot has been looking bearish as it recently dipped to as low as $4.20 in the past 24 hours. This retreat has attracted investors in the past, and it may also draw them in now.</p>
<p>On the other hand, DOT’s technical indicators hint at some bullish movement, with its volume reached a new low as registered on December 25. Still, it is now slowly recovering from the slump.</p>

<strong>Eco-Friendly Crypto</strong>
<p><a href="https://ambcrypto.com/why-polkadot-is-still-one-of-the-best-projects-to-put-on-your-watchlist-in-2023/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">DOT’s market capitalization</a> shows that the bears still dominate the market for December, but its market cap has an uptick by $100 million overnight, which looks like an accumulation. More so, the development activity is also seen to nosedive, which can be worrisome, especially for investors.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, Polkadot, along with Cardano and Algorand, is among the most<a href="https://ambcrypto.com/polkadot-dot-price-prediction-13/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow"> eco-friendly</a> cryptocurrencies, according to a new analysis by the Traders of Crypto. Polkadot ranks as the fourth most eco-friendly digital money, with annual carbon emissions of 50 tons.</p>
<p>&#8211;</p>
<p><em>Featured image: VOI</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Dot-460x259.png" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Investor Sentiment Remains Steady As BTC Stalls At $16,000</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-investor-sentiment/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Best Owie]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 23:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin performance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=514270</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin investor sentiment has reached a standstill amid struggling prices in the market. While the digital asset continues to hold the $16,000 level, investors have backed off from the market, ensuring no significant movements either up or down, and as a result, investor sentiment hasn’t moved. Bitcoin Investors Still In Fear The crypto Fear &#38; Greed Index shows that bitcoin investor sentiment hasn’t really moved much in the last month. It closed out the month of November at a score of 29 which put it right in the fear territory but since then has been unable to break out of this trend.  Related Reading: Solana Suffers Double-Digit Losses, Is There An End In Sight? The score on this index over the month of December has staggered between 26-30 for the most part, maintaining a nearly straight-line trend during this period. Even now, the Fear &#38; Greed Index sits at a score of 28 and is up one point from last week’s close of 27. Fear &#38; Greed Index trends in an almost straight line &#124; Source: alternative.me What this trend in the Fear &#38; Greed Index shows is that bitcoin investors are not willing to take any risk. This is why the index has been unable to move into the greed territory. On the flip side, sell sentiment has not been as strong as expected during a time like this. If investors were selling more of their bitcoin, then it would have been obvious given that the index would slide further down. Instead, it continues to maintain a near-consistent score level, meaning hold sentiment now dominates the market. Will BTC See A Recovery Soon? Bitcoin is still finding a hard time regaining the momentum it has lost over the past month. This hesitancy from investors to do anything with their tokens has seen the price of the digital asset follow the same path as sentiment. BTC has now refused to move out of the $16,000 price level. BTC price maintains $16,000 level &#124; Source: BTCUSD on TradingView.com As a result of this, bitcoin volatility has fallen to historical lows. So it is likely that the last two days of the year 2022 will follow this same trend. Recovery should not be expected in any way because momentum will continue to decline as people take a break from the markets to celebrate with family. Related Reading: Dogecoin Beats Bitcoin, Ethereum For Best Performance In Crypto Top 10 Rather, it is important that BTC holds above $16,000 to close out the year. Anything below this level would be very bearish and could trigger more declines in the market as bears take control. But a finish above $16,000 strengthens investors’ resolve to hold their coins. BTC is changing hands at a price of $16,519 at the time of this writing. Its price is down 0.43% in the last 24 hours and 2.01% in the last 7 days. Featured image from Finbold, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="p2">Bitcoin investor sentiment has reached a standstill amid struggling prices in the market. While the digital asset continues to hold the $16,000 level, investors have backed off from the market, ensuring no significant movements either up or down, and as a result, investor sentiment hasn’t moved.</p>
<h2 class="p2">Bitcoin Investors Still In Fear</h2>
<p class="p2">The <a href="https://alternative.me/crypto/fear-and-greed-index/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">crypto Fear &amp; Greed Index</a> shows that bitcoin investor sentiment hasn’t really moved much in the last month. It closed out the month of November at a score of 29 which put it right in the fear territory but since then has been unable to break out of this trend. </p>

<p class="p2">The score on this index over the month of December has staggered between 26-30 for the most part, maintaining a nearly straight-line trend during this period. Even now, the Fear &amp; Greed Index sits at a score of 28 and is up one point from last week’s close of 27.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-514272 aligncenter" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Fear-Greed-index-460x279.png" alt="Bitcoin Fear &amp; Greed index" width="460" height="279" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Fear-Greed-index-460x279.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Fear-Greed-index-860x522.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Fear-Greed-index-768x466.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Fear-Greed-index-1536x933.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Fear-Greed-index-2048x1243.png 2048w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Fear-Greed-index-750x455.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Fear-Greed-index-1140x692.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px" /></p>

<p class="p2">What this trend in the Fear &amp; Greed Index shows is that bitcoin investors are not willing to take any risk. This is why the index has been unable to move into the greed territory. On the flip side, sell sentiment has not been as strong as expected during a time like this. If investors were selling more of their bitcoin, then it would have been obvious given that the index would slide further down. Instead, it continues to maintain a near-consistent score level, meaning hold sentiment now dominates the market.</p>
<h2 class="p2">Will BTC See A Recovery Soon?</h2>
<p class="p2">Bitcoin is still finding a hard time regaining the momentum it has lost over the past month. This hesitancy from investors to do anything with their tokens has seen the price of the digital asset follow the same path as sentiment. BTC has now refused to move out of the $16,000 price level.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/Zwz3MvAI/" alt="Bitcoin price chart from TradingView.com" width="3284" height="1760" /></p>

<p class="p2">As a result of this, bitcoin volatility has fallen to historical lows. So it is likely that the last two days of the year 2022 will follow this same trend. Recovery should not be expected in any way because momentum will continue to decline as people take a break from the markets to celebrate with family.</p>

<p class="p2">Rather, it is important that BTC holds above $16,000 to close out the year. Anything below this level would be very bearish and could trigger more declines in the market as bears take control. But a finish above $16,000 strengthens investors’ resolve to hold their coins.</p>
<p class="p2">BTC is changing hands at a price of $16,519 at the time of this writing. Its price is down 0.43% in the last 24 hours and 2.01% in the last 7 days.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/bitcoin-3-460x307.jpeg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Price Remains Stagnated, How Soon Can You Expect A Rebound?</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-stagnated-soon-can-you-expect-a-rebound/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[anushsamal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 23:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=514315</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[It has been a rough year for Bitcoin and most major altcoins. Over the last 24 hours, Bitcoin lost 1% of its value, which points towards consolidated price action. BTC has not made much progress over the past week either, as the coin only lost 1.6% of its market value. For multiple weeks, the coin has been oscillating between $16,400 and $18,000. The closest support line for the coin stood at $16,000. The technical outlook for Bitcoin depicted mundane price action due to a decline in the buying strength on the one-day chart. Since the price of Bitcoin has remained undecided for quite some time now, sellers have flooded the market, indicating that the coin is headed toward another round of depreciation. The trading volume of Bitcoin has declined considerably, reinforcing that bears were in charge of the asset&#8217;s price. If the selling pressure keeps mounting, BTC will soon lose its crucial price level of $16,000. Currently, BTC is down 76% from its all-time high, secured in 2021. Related Reading: Ethereum Finishes 2022 With ATH Correlation To Bitcoin, Despite The Merge Bitcoin Price Analysis: One-Day Chart BTC was trading at $16,550 at the time of writing. Bitcoin was trading close to its immediate support level of $16,000. Going by the technical outlook, the coin might undergo further depreciation before it starts to reverse its price action. Overhead resistance for Bitcoin was $16,900; clearing this could help the crypto reach $17,400 and eventually attempt to breach $18,000. On the flip side, if Bitcoin moves below the current price mark, it will fall through $16,000 and exceed $15,800. The amount of Bitcoin traded in the last session declined, indicating a fall in buying strength for the asset. Technical Analysis BTC traders might again witness a fall in asset prices over the upcoming trading sessions. The Relative Strength Index (RSI) was below the half-line, near the 40-mark, which indicates that sellers outnumbered buyers heavily. RSI had also noted a downtick, signifying further loss of value. Similarly, the BTC price was below the 20-Simple Moving Average (SMA) line, which signals that sellers were driving the price momentum in the market. The SMA also formed a death cross; it is formed when a longer moving average line crosses over a shorter moving average line; in this case, the 50-SMA line was above the 20-SMA line. This sign on the chart is accompanied by the bears strengthening in the market. Other technical indicators have also pointed out that sellers are here to stay a little longer. The Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD) indicates price momentum and reversals. MACD depicted a sell signal as the indicator noted red signal bars after undergoing a bearish crossover. The sell signal could mean that the price would depreciate further. The Directional Movement Index, which portrays the price direction, was negative. The -DI (orange) line was above the +DI (blue) line. The Average Directional Index (red) was near the 20-mark with an uptick, emphasizing that bearish action could gain momentum over the immediate trading sessions. Related Reading: A Crypto Holiday Special: Past, Present, And Future With Ex-Binance CFO Wei Zhou Featured Image From Unsplash, Charts From TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>It has been a rough year for Bitcoin and most major altcoins. Over the last 24 hours, Bitcoin lost 1% of its value, which points towards consolidated price action. BTC has not made much progress over the past week either, as the coin only lost 1.6% of its market value.</p>
<p>For multiple weeks, the coin has been oscillating between $16,400 and $18,000. The closest support line for the coin stood at $16,000. The technical outlook for Bitcoin depicted mundane price action due to a decline in the buying strength on the one-day chart.</p>
<p>Since the price of Bitcoin has remained undecided for quite some time now, sellers have flooded the market, indicating that the coin is headed toward another round of depreciation. The trading volume of Bitcoin has declined considerably, reinforcing that bears were in charge of the asset&#8217;s price.</p>
<p>If the selling pressure keeps mounting, BTC will soon lose its crucial price level of $16,000. Currently, BTC is down 76% from its all-time high, secured in 2021.</p>

<h2>Bitcoin Price Analysis: One-Day Chart</h2>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-514318 size-full" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-31_01-08-09.png" alt="Bitcoin" width="1817" height="830" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-31_01-08-09.png 1817w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-31_01-08-09-460x210.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-31_01-08-09-860x393.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-31_01-08-09-768x351.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-31_01-08-09-1536x702.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-31_01-08-09-750x343.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-31_01-08-09-1140x521.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1817px) 100vw, 1817px" />
<p>BTC was trading at $16,550 at the time of writing. Bitcoin was trading close to its immediate support level of $16,000. Going by the technical outlook, the coin might undergo further depreciation before it starts to reverse its price action.</p>
<p>Overhead resistance for Bitcoin was $16,900; clearing this could help the crypto reach $17,400 and eventually attempt to breach $18,000.</p>
<p>On the flip side, if Bitcoin moves below the current price mark, it will fall through $16,000 and exceed $15,800. The amount of Bitcoin traded in the last session declined, indicating a fall in buying strength for the asset.</p>
<h2>Technical Analysis</h2>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-514319 size-full" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-31_01-09-39.png" alt="Bitcoin" width="1877" height="743" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-31_01-09-39.png 1877w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-31_01-09-39-460x182.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-31_01-09-39-860x340.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-31_01-09-39-768x304.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-31_01-09-39-1536x608.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-31_01-09-39-750x297.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-31_01-09-39-1140x451.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1877px) 100vw, 1877px" />
<p>BTC traders might again witness a fall in asset prices over the upcoming trading sessions. The Relative Strength Index (RSI) was below the half-line, near the 40-mark, which indicates that sellers outnumbered buyers heavily. RSI had also noted a downtick, signifying further loss of value.</p>
<p>Similarly, the BTC price was below the 20-Simple Moving Average (SMA) line, which signals that sellers were driving the price momentum in the market.</p>
<p>The SMA also formed a death cross; it is formed when a longer moving average line crosses over a shorter moving average line; in this case, the 50-SMA line was above the 20-SMA line. This sign on the chart is accompanied by the bears strengthening in the market.</p>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-514321 size-full" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-31_01-10-14.png" alt="Bitcoin" width="1877" height="743" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-31_01-10-14.png 1877w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-31_01-10-14-460x182.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-31_01-10-14-860x340.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-31_01-10-14-768x304.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-31_01-10-14-1536x608.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-31_01-10-14-750x297.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-31_01-10-14-1140x451.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1877px) 100vw, 1877px" />
<p>Other technical indicators have also pointed out that sellers are here to stay a little longer. The Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD) indicates price momentum and reversals. MACD depicted a sell signal as the indicator noted red signal bars after undergoing a bearish crossover.</p>
<p>The sell signal could mean that the price would depreciate further. The Directional Movement Index, which portrays the price direction, was negative.</p>
<p>The -DI (orange) line was above the +DI (blue) line. The Average Directional Index (red) was near the 20-mark with an uptick, emphasizing that bearish action could gain momentum over the immediate trading sessions.</p>





]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/woliul-hasan-aAvzCO-B5aA-unsplash-460x460.jpg" width="460" height="460" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Polygon (MATIC) Depicts Further Downtrend, This Could Be The Next Support Level</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/matic/polygon-depicts-downtrend-next-support-level/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[anushsamal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 21:00:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[MATIC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[maticusdt]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Polygon]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=514283</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Polygon (MATIC) price has been on a downward spiral for the last couple of weeks. Over the last 24 hours, MATIC lost 4% of its value. The altcoin has also lost about 6% in the last week. Earlier in November, MATIC touched the $1.20 price mark and plunged significantly. Since the coin plummeted in November, the Polygon price has noted a freefall in its value. Going by the technical outlook on the daily chart, buyers are nowhere to be found. It will be difficult for MATIC to sustain itself above its immediate support level. The buying strength of Polygon has to increase considerably for it to remain above the local support line. Over the past month, the coin has breached several important price floors. After trading sideways for a while, MATIC lost buyers further, which made the coin fall on its chart again. For Polygon, the most important price floor currently stands at $0.74. If MATIC loses that support line, the coin can register a significant decline of 14%. The market capitalization of MATIC also declined over the past few weeks, which depicts bearishness for the coin. Currently, the coin is trading 74% below its all-time high secured one year ago. Related Reading: Most Public Crypto Firms Underperformed Bitcoin In 2022, Miners Hit Worst MATIC Price Analysis: One-Day Chart Polygon was trading at $0.76 at the time of writing. The coin was trading extremely close to the immediate support line of $0.74; one push from the sellers and the price could take another significant bearish turn. Overhead resistance for MATIC was $0.81; crossing this price level will help the altcoin reach $0.84. The $0.84 level has previously acted as a propelling point for the asset&#8217;s price, so this could mean that moving above the $0.84 level would help the coin reverse its price action. On the other hand, a fall from the present price mark will bring the altcoin to $0.67 and then to $0.63. The amount of Polygon traded in the last session was red, indicating selling dominance. Technical Analysis The coin was in the seller&#8217;s dominant zone for most of this month. The coin barely recovered after it lost the $0.84 support line. The Relative Strength Index was below the 40-mark, which depicted that the coin received more sellers than buyers. In correspondence with the same, the coin moved below the 20-Simple Moving Average (SMA) line. This meant that the sellers were driving the price momentum in the market. Usually, when the coin hovers too close to the oversold zone, the price reverses. If demand returns, the coin will move above the 200-SMA line (green), which points towards a potential rally. Regarding selling strength, the indicators pointed out that the selling spree is not over yet. The Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD) indicator depicts price momentum and reversals. MACD showed red signal bars, which are tied to a sell signal. This was an indication that the coin could dip further on the chart. The Chaikin Money Flow reads capital inflows and outflows; the indicator was below the half-line, signifying lower capital inflows than outflows. Related Reading: Santiment: Bitcoin Will Trend Lower Because Whales Are Still Selling Featured Image From Unsplash, Charts From TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Polygon (MATIC) price has been on a downward spiral for the last couple of weeks. Over the last 24 hours, MATIC lost 4% of its value. The altcoin has also lost about 6% in the last week. Earlier in November, MATIC touched the $1.20 price mark and plunged significantly.</p>
<p>Since the coin plummeted in November, the Polygon price has noted a freefall in its value. Going by the technical outlook on the daily chart, buyers are nowhere to be found. It will be difficult for MATIC to sustain itself above its immediate support level.</p>
<p>The buying strength of Polygon has to increase considerably for it to remain above the local support line. Over the past month, the coin has breached several important price floors. After trading sideways for a while, MATIC lost buyers further, which made the coin fall on its chart again.</p>
<p>For Polygon, the most important price floor currently stands at $0.74. If MATIC loses that support line, the coin can register a significant decline of 14%. The market capitalization of MATIC also declined over the past few weeks, which depicts bearishness for the coin. Currently, the coin is trading 74% below its all-time high secured one year ago.</p>

<h2>MATIC Price Analysis: One-Day Chart</h2>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-514296 size-full" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MATICUSD_2022-12-30_22-49-40.png" alt="Polygon" width="1816" height="830" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MATICUSD_2022-12-30_22-49-40.png 1816w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MATICUSD_2022-12-30_22-49-40-460x210.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MATICUSD_2022-12-30_22-49-40-860x393.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MATICUSD_2022-12-30_22-49-40-768x351.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MATICUSD_2022-12-30_22-49-40-1536x702.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MATICUSD_2022-12-30_22-49-40-750x343.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MATICUSD_2022-12-30_22-49-40-1140x521.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1816px) 100vw, 1816px" />
<p>Polygon was trading at $0.76 at the time of writing. The coin was trading extremely close to the immediate support line of $0.74; one push from the sellers and the price could take another significant bearish turn.</p>
<p>Overhead resistance for MATIC was $0.81; crossing this price level will help the altcoin reach $0.84. The $0.84 level has previously acted as a propelling point for the asset&#8217;s price, so this could mean that moving above the $0.84 level would help the coin reverse its price action.</p>
<p>On the other hand, a fall from the present price mark will bring the altcoin to $0.67 and then to $0.63. The amount of Polygon traded in the last session was red, indicating selling dominance.</p>
<h2>Technical Analysis</h2>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-514299 size-full" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MATICUSD_2022-12-30_23-01-09.png" alt="Polygon" width="1816" height="743" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MATICUSD_2022-12-30_23-01-09.png 1816w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MATICUSD_2022-12-30_23-01-09-460x188.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MATICUSD_2022-12-30_23-01-09-860x352.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MATICUSD_2022-12-30_23-01-09-768x314.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MATICUSD_2022-12-30_23-01-09-1536x628.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MATICUSD_2022-12-30_23-01-09-750x307.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MATICUSD_2022-12-30_23-01-09-1140x466.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1816px) 100vw, 1816px" />
<p>The coin was in the seller&#8217;s dominant zone for most of this month. The coin barely recovered after it lost the $0.84 support line. The Relative Strength Index was below the 40-mark, which depicted that the coin received more sellers than buyers.</p>
<p>In correspondence with the same, the coin moved below the 20-Simple Moving Average (SMA) line. This meant that the sellers were driving the price momentum in the market.</p>
<p>Usually, when the coin hovers too close to the oversold zone, the price reverses. If demand returns, the coin will move above the 200-SMA line (green), which points towards a potential rally.</p>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-514303 size-full" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MATICUSD_2022-12-30_23-01-31.png" alt="Polygon" width="1816" height="743" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MATICUSD_2022-12-30_23-01-31.png 1816w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MATICUSD_2022-12-30_23-01-31-460x188.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MATICUSD_2022-12-30_23-01-31-860x352.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MATICUSD_2022-12-30_23-01-31-768x314.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MATICUSD_2022-12-30_23-01-31-1536x628.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MATICUSD_2022-12-30_23-01-31-750x307.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MATICUSD_2022-12-30_23-01-31-1140x466.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1816px) 100vw, 1816px" />
<p>Regarding selling strength, the indicators pointed out that the selling spree is not over yet. The Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD) indicator depicts price momentum and reversals. MACD showed red signal bars, which are tied to a sell signal.</p>
<p>This was an indication that the coin could dip further on the chart. The Chaikin Money Flow reads capital inflows and outflows; the indicator was below the half-line, signifying lower capital inflows than outflows.</p>





]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/barefoot-communications-z2M7JefmTEw-unsplash-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum Finishes 2022 With ATH Correlation To Bitcoin, Despite The Merge</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/ethereum/ethereum-ath-correlation-bitcoin-merge/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hououin Kyouma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 19:00:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Stock market correlation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum Bitcoin Correlation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum Merge]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Merge]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=514285</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Data shows Ethereum&#8217;s year of high correlation with Bitcoin is coming to an end with the metric hitting ATH values. Ethereum Ends 2022 With All-Time High Correlation To Bitcoin According to the year-end report from Arcane Research, the global markets have all fallen strongly correlated this year. The &#8220;30-day correlations&#8221; is an indicator that measures how in-tune Bitcoin has been with another asset in terms of price movement over a 30-day period. When the value of this metric is greater than zero, it means there has been a positive correlation between BTC and the other asset in the past month. On the other hand, negative values imply that the price of the crypto has been reacting to changes in the value of the other asset by moving in the opposite direction. Also, the higher the metric value (in either direction), the more the degree of the correlation. Naturally, the metric has a value equal to zero suggesting the two prices aren&#8217;t tied to each other at the moment. Related Reading: Analyst Explains Why Ethereum Is Bullish Against Bitcoin Now, here is a chart that shows the trend in Bitcoin&#8217;s 30-day correlations with Ethereum, S&#38;P 500, and Nasdaq over the past year: Looks like the metric's value corresponding to ETH has been very high in recent weeks &#124; Source: Arcane Research's 2022 - Year in Review As the above graph displays, Bitcoin positively correlated with these three assets during 2022. BTC&#8217;s correlation has been around or above 0.5 for most of the year for the US equities, suggesting it has been decently tied with them. The correlation with Ethereum, however, has been at values of around 0.9 or more, implying Bitcoin has been extremely correlated with it. Even now, as the year&#8217;s end, the correlation between these cryptos stands at 0.97, around ATH levels. Back in September of this year, ETH successfully finished its much-anticipated transition to a Proof-of-Stake consensus system, an event known as the Merge. Since the Merge brought some developments unique to Ethereum, the correlation with BTC dropped, as is apparent in the chart. However, it wasn&#8217;t long before the two started moving on the same wavelength again, so even the Merge wasn&#8217;t enough to cause sufficient impact to separate the coins. Related Reading: Most Public Crypto Firms Underperformed Bitcoin In 2022, Miners Hit Worst Also, since Bitcoin is highly correlated with stocks, so is Ethereum. Though, Arcane Research expects that this correlation between the cryptos and the US equities will soften in the next year due to trading volumes in the crypto market declining substantially. ETH Price At the time of writing, Ethereum&#8217;s price floats around $1,200, down 2% in the last week. ETH seems to have gone down recently &#124; Source: ETHUSD on TradingView Featured image from Pierre Borthiry &#8211; Peiobty on Unsplash.com, charts from TradingView.com, Arcane Research]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Data shows Ethereum&#8217;s year of high correlation with Bitcoin is coming to an end with the metric hitting ATH values.</p>
<h2>Ethereum Ends 2022 With All-Time High Correlation To Bitcoin</h2>
<p>According to the year-end report from <a href="https://arcane.no/research/2022-year-in-review" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Arcane Research</a>, the global markets have all fallen strongly correlated this year. The &#8220;<a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-moves-us-stock-market-correlation-weakening/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">30-day correlations</a>&#8221; is an indicator that measures how in-tune Bitcoin has been with another asset in terms of price movement over a 30-day period.</p>
<p>When the value of this metric is greater than zero, it means there has been a positive correlation between BTC and the other asset in the past month. On the other hand, negative values imply that the price of the crypto has been reacting to changes in the value of the other asset by moving in the opposite direction.</p>
<p>Also, the higher the metric value (in either direction), the more the degree of the correlation. Naturally, the metric has a value equal to zero suggesting the two prices aren&#8217;t tied to each other at the moment.</p>

<p>Now, here is a chart that shows the trend in Bitcoin&#8217;s 30-day correlations with Ethereum, S&amp;P 500, and Nasdaq over the past year:</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone wp-image-514298 size-full aligncenter" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/chart-41.png" alt="Bitcoin And Ethereum Correlation" width="771" height="518" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/chart-41.png 771w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/chart-41-460x309.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/chart-41-768x516.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/chart-41-750x504.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 771px) 100vw, 771px" /></p>

<p>As the above graph displays, Bitcoin positively correlated with these three assets during 2022. BTC&#8217;s correlation has been around or above 0.5 for most of the year for the US equities, suggesting it has been decently tied with them.</p>
<p>The correlation with Ethereum, however, has been at values of around 0.9 or more, implying Bitcoin has been extremely correlated with it. Even now, as the year&#8217;s end, the correlation between these cryptos stands at 0.97, around ATH levels.</p>
<p>Back in September of this year, ETH successfully finished its much-anticipated transition to a Proof-of-Stake consensus system, an event known as the <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/company/the-ethereum-merge-what-is-trading-headed-towards/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Merge</a>. Since the Merge brought some developments unique to Ethereum, the correlation with BTC dropped, as is apparent in the chart.</p>
<p>However, it wasn&#8217;t long before the two started moving on the same wavelength again, so even the Merge wasn&#8217;t enough to cause sufficient impact to separate the coins.</p>

<p>Also, since Bitcoin is highly correlated with stocks, so is Ethereum. Though, Arcane Research expects that this correlation between the cryptos and the US equities will soften in the next year due to trading volumes in the crypto market declining substantially.</p>
<h2>ETH Price</h2>
<p>At the time of writing, <a href="https://newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-signals-bearish-1100/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ethereum&#8217;s price</a> floats around $1,200, down 2% in the last week.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone wp-image-514304 size-large aligncenter" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/chart-42-860x482.png" alt="Ethereum Price Chart" width="860" height="482" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/chart-42-860x482.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/chart-42-460x258.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/chart-42-768x430.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/chart-42-750x420.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/chart-42.png 973w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" /></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/pierre-borthiry-peiobty-vBCVcWUyvyM-unsplash-1-460x333.jpg" width="460" height="333" />	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
