<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"

	xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
	xmlns:geo="http://www.w3.org/2003/01/geo/wgs84_pos#"
	>

<channel>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.newsbtc.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<description>Bitcoin &#38; Cryptocurrency News Today</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 22:18:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-cropped-favicon.png?fit=32%2C32</url>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
<site xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">221170450</site>	<item>
		<title>Curve DAO Scores $5 Million Boost From Binance, Eyes BNB Chain Expansion</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/binance/curve-dao-scores-5-million-boost-from-binance-eyes-bnb-chain-expansion/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 02:00:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance Labs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CRVUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Curve DAO]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DeFi]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=546738</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[In a strategic move to bolster the decentralized finance (DeFi) sector, Binance Labs, the venture capital and incubation arm of Binance, has committed a substantial $5 million investment in Curve DAO Token (CRV).  The Ethereum-based CRV token is the backbone of the Curve ecosystem, which has established itself as the largest stable swap and second-largest decentralized exchange (DEX). Related Reading: Rising Star Hedera (HBAR) And Its 11% Climb – A Closer Look Curve and Binance&#8217;s BNB Chain Forge Strategic Alliance As part of the partnership, Curve will explore the deployment of its protocol on the BNB Chain, the thriving ecosystem powered by its native token, BNB. This strategic alignment aims to leverage the strengths of both platforms, further fueling the growth of DeFi on the BNB Chain. Yi He, Co-Founder of Binance and Head of Binance Labs, expressed enthusiasm about the collaboration, stating:  Curve is the largest stableswap, and as a key protocol in DeFi, it has contributed to the steady growth of the space in 2023. Given the recent events that have impacted the protocol, Binance Labs has offered our full support to Curve through our investment and strategic collaboration. We view this cooperation as a starting point and look forward to working together to further propel the growth of the DeFi ecosystem. Curve Founder, Michael Egorov, acknowledged the significance of the collaboration, stating: BNB Chain has earned a significant presence in DeFi and is well-positioned to deploy Curve&#8217;s current and future products on its chain. We look forward to collaboratively fostering innovation and growth across the DeFi ecosystem. According to Binance Labs’ announcement, Curve&#8217;s Automated Market Maker (AMM) platform has revolutionized liquidity provision in DeFi, offering hundreds of incentivized liquidity pools with low slippage and transaction fees.  With the support and strategic investment of Binance Labs, the protocol seems poised to accelerate its mission to transform DeFi by increasing liquidity, reducing transaction friction, and expanding its ecosystem.  Is Cross-Chain Interoperability The Key To Curve&#8217;s Success On BNB Chain? Deploying Curve to BNB Chain brings numerous advantages to both Curve and the BNB Chain ecosystem. One key benefit is enhanced scalability, as BNB Chain offers high throughput and low latency, providing a robust infrastructure for DeFi protocols like Curve. By deploying on BNB Chain, Curve can leverage the network&#8217;s capabilities to handle more transactions and accommodate the growing user demand. Another advantage is the lower transaction fees offered by BNB Chain. This cost-efficiency appeals to users seeking to minimize expenses when interacting with Curve. By deploying on BNB Chain, Curve users can enjoy reduced transaction fees, enhancing the overall affordability of using the Curve protocol. The cross-chain interoperability of BNB Chain also enables seamless integration of assets and protocols from different blockchains, creating opportunities for Curve to collaborate with other projects and protocols within the BNB Chain ecosystem.  Related Reading: Aptos (APT) Volume Remains Extremely High, More Gains Ahead? Deploying Curve to BNB Chain can expose the protocol to the extensive Binance ecosystem. Binance, one of the world&#8217;s largest cryptocurrency exchanges, operates its ecosystem on BNB Chain.  This exposure opens doors to potential partnerships, collaborations, and increased visibility among Binance users, further strengthening Curve&#8217;s position in the market. Overall, deploying the platform to BNB Chain aligns with its goal of expanding its presence across multiple chains and reaching a broader user base.  By leveraging the advantages of BNB Chain, such as enhanced scalability, lower transaction fees, access to a large user base, cross-chain interoperability, and exposure to the Binance ecosystem, the protocol can contribute to the growth and development of the DeFi ecosystem. Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com ]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In a strategic move to bolster the decentralized finance (DeFi) sector, Binance Labs, the venture capital and incubation arm of Binance, has <a href="https://www.binance.com/en/blog/ecosystem/binance-labs-invests-$5m-in-curve-dao-token-crv-and-supports-curve-deployment-to-bnb-chain-4372009526169554266" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">committed </a>a substantial $5 million investment in Curve DAO Token (CRV). </p>
<p>The Ethereum-based CRV token is the backbone of the Curve ecosystem, which has established itself as the largest stable swap and second-largest decentralized exchange (DEX).</p>

<h2>Curve and Binance&#8217;s BNB Chain Forge Strategic Alliance</h2>
<p>As part of the partnership, Curve will explore the deployment of its protocol on the BNB Chain, the thriving ecosystem powered by its native token, BNB. This strategic alignment aims to leverage the strengths of both platforms, further fueling the growth of DeFi on the BNB Chain.</p>
<p>Yi He, Co-Founder of Binance and Head of Binance Labs, expressed enthusiasm about the collaboration, stating: </p>
<blockquote><p>Curve is the largest stableswap, and as a key protocol in DeFi, it has contributed to the steady growth of the space in 2023. Given the recent events that have impacted the protocol, Binance Labs has offered our full support to Curve through our investment and strategic collaboration. We view this cooperation as a starting point and look forward to working together to further propel the growth of the DeFi ecosystem.</p></blockquote>
<p>Curve Founder, Michael Egorov, acknowledged the significance of the collaboration, stating:</p>
<blockquote><p>BNB Chain has earned a significant presence in DeFi and is well-positioned to deploy Curve&#8217;s current and future products on its chain. We look forward to collaboratively fostering innovation and growth across the DeFi ecosystem.</p></blockquote>
<p>According to Binance Labs’ announcement, Curve&#8217;s Automated Market Maker (AMM) platform has revolutionized liquidity provision in DeFi, offering hundreds of incentivized liquidity pools with low slippage and transaction fees. </p>
<p>With the support and strategic investment of Binance Labs, the protocol seems poised to accelerate its mission to transform DeFi by increasing liquidity, reducing transaction friction, and expanding its ecosystem. </p>
<h2>Is Cross-Chain Interoperability The Key To Curve&#8217;s Success On BNB Chain?</h2>
<p>Deploying Curve to BNB Chain brings numerous advantages to both Curve and the BNB Chain ecosystem. One key benefit is enhanced scalability, as BNB Chain offers high throughput and low latency, providing a robust infrastructure for DeFi protocols like Curve. </p>
<p>By deploying on BNB Chain, Curve can leverage the network&#8217;s capabilities to handle more transactions and accommodate the growing user demand.</p>
<p>Another advantage is the lower transaction fees offered by BNB Chain. This cost-efficiency appeals to users seeking to minimize expenses when interacting with Curve. By deploying on BNB Chain, Curve users can enjoy reduced transaction fees, enhancing the overall affordability of using the Curve protocol.</p>
<p>The cross-chain interoperability of BNB Chain also enables seamless integration of assets and protocols from different blockchains, creating opportunities for Curve to collaborate with other projects and protocols within the BNB Chain ecosystem. </p>

<p>Deploying Curve to BNB Chain can expose the protocol to the extensive Binance ecosystem. Binance, one of the world&#8217;s largest cryptocurrency exchanges, operates its ecosystem on BNB Chain. </p>
<p>This exposure opens doors to potential partnerships, collaborations, and increased visibility among Binance users, further strengthening Curve&#8217;s position in the market.</p>
<p>Overall, deploying the platform to BNB Chain aligns with its goal of expanding its presence across multiple chains and reaching a broader user base. </p>
<p>By leveraging the advantages of BNB Chain, such as enhanced scalability, lower transaction fees, access to a large user base, cross-chain interoperability, and exposure to the Binance ecosystem, the protocol can contribute to the growth and development of the DeFi ecosystem.</p>
<img decoding="async" fetchpriority="high" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/GEfYnLWI/" alt="Curve" width="1815" height="858" loading="lazy"/>
<p>Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Downloader.la-64d50712bc39e.jpg?fit=460%2C288" width="460" height="288" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">546738</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dogecoin Rally Ahead? This Positive Correlation Data Points To A Potential 20% Jump For DOGE</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/dogecoin-2/this-positive-correlation-data-points-to-a-potential-20-jump-for-dogecoin/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Opeyemi Sule]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 01:00:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ali Martinez]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[doge]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dogeusdt]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shiba Inu (SHIB)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=546734</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Dogecoin has been one of the cryptocurrencies to watch in the past few weeks. However, the token’s price appears to be slowing down after recording significant bullish momentum. Interestingly, there might be renewed optimism around the DOGE price, as a crypto analyst has offered insight on what to expect from the meme coin in the coming weeks. Related Reading: Dogecoin Falls While Others Rally, Is It Decoupling From The Market? Dogecoin To Experience A 20% Price Rally?   On Thursday, August 10, crypto analyst Ali Martinez shared data from IntoTheBlock, suggesting that DOGE might witness a positive price movement soon. This suggestion is based on the similarities in the price history of both Shiba Inu (SHIB) and Dogecoin.  According to his post on X (formerly Twitter), there is a “strong” positive correlation of 0.74 between the two meme coins over the past two months. This indicates that when SHIB’s price shifts, the price of DOGE often moves in the same direction.  Source: TradingView/ali_charts Interestingly, this hasn&#8217;t happened in the past few days, as the DOGE price has not taken significant action. The value of SHIB, on the other hand, has surged by 22% in the last seven days. However, Ali Martinez noted that “given their high correlation coefficient,” a bullish price movement might still be on the horizon for DOGE. So, investors might want to keep a keen eye on the token’s performance in the coming days. DOGE Price Stuck In A Range &#8211; Price Overview Dogecoin has struggled to maintain the momentum garnered from Elon Musk’s support a few weeks ago. The meme coin has been trading mainly within a range since then, recording a mere 3.1% gain in the past week. After reaching a 7-day high of $0.07658 on Saturday, August 5, the DOGE price shed all its gain to trade below $0.073. However, the token&#8217;s price is back up, hovering around its weekly high. Related Reading: Dogecoin Falls While Others Rally, Is It Decoupling From The Market? This price action underscores the meme coin’s unsuccessful attempts at breaking the $0.08 resistance level. DOGE trades about 5.5% down from the significant $0.08 zone after failing to breach it on July 31. As of this writing, the Dogecoin price is $0.075739,  having leaped by 0.3% in the last 24 hours. With a nearly $10.7 billion market cap, DOGE ranks as the 8th-largest cryptocurrency. CoinGecko data reveals that there has been a substantial boost in DOGE’s market activity, with a 17.6% increase in its daily trading volume. The cryptocurrency currently has a 24-hour trading volume of over $430.2 million. DOGEUSDT approaching the $0.08 level on the daily timeframe &#124; Source: DOGEUSDT chart from Tradingview Featured image from iStock, charts from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Dogecoin has been one of the cryptocurrencies to watch in the past few weeks. However, the token’s price appears to be slowing down after recording significant bullish momentum.</p>
<p>Interestingly, there might be renewed optimism around the DOGE price, as a crypto analyst has offered insight on what to expect from the meme coin in the coming weeks.</p>

<h2>Dogecoin To Experience A 20% Price Rally?  </h2>
<p>On Thursday, August 10, crypto analyst Ali Martinez <a href="https://twitter.com/ali_charts/status/1689579782432841728?s=46&amp;t=n3tNY_IO4dmxRzBvEYNN-w" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">shared</a> data from IntoTheBlock, suggesting that DOGE might witness a positive price movement soon. This suggestion is based on the similarities in the price history of both Shiba Inu (SHIB) and Dogecoin. </p>
<p>According to his post on X (formerly Twitter), there is a “strong” positive correlation of 0.74 between the two meme coins over the past two months. This indicates that when SHIB’s price shifts, the price of DOGE often moves in the same direction. </p>
<p><img decoding="async" class="aligncenter wp-image-546736 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/photo_2023-08-10_16-36-45.jpg?w=860&#038;resize=860%2C482" alt="Dogecoin" width="860" height="482" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/photo_2023-08-10_16-36-45.jpg?w=1280 1280w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/photo_2023-08-10_16-36-45.jpg?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/photo_2023-08-10_16-36-45.jpg?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/photo_2023-08-10_16-36-45.jpg?w=860&#038;resize=860%2C482 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/photo_2023-08-10_16-36-45.jpg?w=750 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/photo_2023-08-10_16-36-45.jpg?w=1140 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" loading="lazy" data-recalc-dims="1"/></p>

<p>Interestingly, this hasn&#8217;t happened in the past few days, as the DOGE price has not taken significant action. The value of SHIB, on the other hand, has surged by 22% in the last seven days.</p>
<p>However, Ali Martinez noted that “given their high correlation coefficient,” a bullish price movement might still be on the horizon for DOGE. So, investors might want to keep a keen eye on the token’s performance in the coming days.</p>
<h2>DOGE Price Stuck In A Range &#8211; Price Overview</h2>
<p>Dogecoin has struggled to maintain the momentum garnered from Elon Musk’s support a few weeks ago. The meme coin has been trading mainly within a range since then, recording a mere 3.1% gain in the past week.</p>
<p>After reaching a 7-day high of $0.07658 on Saturday, August 5, the DOGE price shed all its gain to trade below $0.073. However, the token&#8217;s price is back up, hovering around its weekly high.</p>

<p>This price action underscores the meme coin’s unsuccessful attempts at breaking the $0.08 resistance level. DOGE trades about 5.5% down from the significant $0.08 zone after failing to breach it on July 31.</p>
<p>As of this writing, the Dogecoin price is $0.075739,  having leaped by 0.3% in the last 24 hours. With a nearly $10.7 billion market cap, DOGE ranks as the 8th-largest cryptocurrency.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/dogecoin" rel="nofollow">CoinGecko data</a> reveals that there has been a substantial boost in DOGE’s market activity, with a 17.6% increase in its daily trading volume. The cryptocurrency currently has a 24-hour trading volume of over $430.2 million.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/WRXxqaAF/" alt="Dogecoin" width="1013" height="595" loading="lazy"/></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/iStock-1015828796-1536x878-1.jpg?fit=460%2C263" width="460" height="263" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">546734</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Bears Ran Out Of Coins? What This Analyst Forecast For BTC At Around $30,000</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-bears-ran-out-of-coins-what-this-analyst-forecast-for-btc-at-around-30000/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reynaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 00:00:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=546726</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Despite today’s macroeconomic developments, the price of Bitcoin continues to move sideways and seems likely to stay on this path. The number one crypto by market cap has seen its volatility drop to fresh lows as its price is trapped at current levels. Related Reading: Ethereum Price Prints Bullish Technical Pattern, Why Close Above $1,880 Is Critical At the time of writing, Bitcoin trades at $26,600 with sideways movement in the last 24 hours. Over the past seven days, the cryptocurrency has recorded some profits but has been unable to break above or below the $28,000 to $30,500 range. A New Normal For Bitcoin? Volatility Likely To Decline Until This Changes Analyst Dylan LeClair pointed out that operators in the derivatives sector have dominated the current Bitcoin price action. In that sense, the BTC spot-to-derivative trading volume ratio followed volatility and declined to all-time lows. As seen in the chart below, this ratio shows that the spot market has been suppressed by the derivatives sector, with traders “chopping each other to oblivion.” LeClair stated the following: (…) spot bears have mostly run out of coins &#38; spot bulls are either fully deployed or are sidelined TradFi waiting for ETF approval. With the U.S. Federal Reserve (Fed) out of session until September and low uncertainty in the short term, the price of Bitcoin seems poised to keep chopping around its current levels. In this environment, derivatives traders will likely profit from selling volatility via different financial instruments. Data from the derivatives platform Deribit shows an uptick in call (buy) contracts on the options sectors for October to December expiry. A report posted by this platform from Rogue Trader Academy highlights the need for a catalyst to push BTC out of its current range. The market is positioning itself for a Bitcoin spot Exchange Traded Fund (ETF) approval in Q4, 2023, thus why players on the options markets are accumulating calls. Selling volatility has been a profitable strategy in July. Still, as the metric hovers around historical lows, traders become more resilient to dump their contracts on the derivatives sector, further suppressing BTC’s price. Rogue Trader Academy stated: (…) those selling volatility (gamma sellers) are growing hesitant to offload at such historically low implied vol levels, especially with significant economic data like the US Consumer Price Index (CPI) on the horizon for this week. Related Reading: PEPE Coin Makes Minor Gains With 3.5% Spike – Sign Of Recovery? In this low volatility, low liquidity environment, only a catalyst will push BTC beyond $30,000 and beyond $40,000 by the end of the year. Something seems apparent in this context: Bitcoin seems ahead of any bullish narrative and likely to outperform in the sector for the remainder of 2023. Cover image from Unsplash, chart from Tradingview]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Despite today’s macroeconomic developments, the price of Bitcoin continues to move sideways and seems likely to stay on this path. The number one crypto by market cap has seen its volatility drop to fresh lows as its price is trapped at current levels. </strong></p>

<p>At the time of writing, Bitcoin trades at $26,600 with sideways movement in the last 24 hours. Over the past seven days, the cryptocurrency has recorded some profits but has been unable to break above or below the $28,000 to $30,500 range.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-546732 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-1.png?w=860&#038;resize=860%2C410" alt="Bitcoin BTC BTCUSDT" width="860" height="410" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-1.png?w=1758 1758w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-1.png?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-1.png?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-1.png?w=860&#038;resize=860%2C410 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-1.png?w=1536 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-1.png?w=750 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-1.png?w=1140 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" data-recalc-dims="1"/>
<h2>A New Normal For Bitcoin? Volatility Likely To Decline Until This Changes</h2>
<p>Analyst Dylan LeClair <a href="https://twitter.com/DylanLeClair_/status/1689632860989214720" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">pointed out</a> that operators in the derivatives sector have dominated the current Bitcoin price action. In that sense, the BTC spot-to-derivative trading volume ratio followed volatility and declined to all-time lows.</p>
<p>As seen in the chart below, this ratio shows that the spot market has been suppressed by the derivatives sector, with traders “chopping each other to oblivion.” LeClair stated the following:</p>
<blockquote><p>(…) spot bears have mostly run out of coins &amp; spot bulls are either fully deployed or are sidelined TradFi waiting for ETF approval.</p></blockquote>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-546731 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-2.jpeg?w=860&#038;resize=860%2C569" alt="Bitcoin BTC BTCUSDT Chart 2" width="860" height="569" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-2.jpeg?w=1133 1133w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-2.jpeg?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-2.jpeg?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-2.jpeg?w=860&#038;resize=860%2C569 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-2.jpeg?w=750 750w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" data-recalc-dims="1"/>
<p>With the U.S. Federal Reserve (Fed) out of session until September and low uncertainty in the short term, the price of Bitcoin seems poised to keep chopping around its current levels.</p>
<p>In this environment, derivatives traders will likely profit from selling volatility via different financial instruments. Data from the derivatives platform Deribit shows an uptick in call (buy) contracts on the options sectors for October to December expiry.</p>
<p>A report <a href="https://insights.deribit.com/industry/btc-call-premium-is-back-across-the-curve/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">posted</a> by this platform from Rogue Trader Academy highlights the need for a catalyst to push BTC out of its current range. The market is positioning itself for a Bitcoin spot Exchange Traded Fund (ETF) approval in Q4, 2023, thus why players on the options markets are accumulating calls.</p>
<p>Selling volatility has been a profitable strategy in July. Still, as the metric hovers around historical lows, traders become more resilient to dump their contracts on the derivatives sector, further suppressing BTC’s price. Rogue Trader Academy stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>(…) those selling volatility (gamma sellers) are growing hesitant to offload at such historically low implied vol levels, especially with significant economic data like the US Consumer Price Index (CPI) on the horizon for this week.</p></blockquote>

<p>In this low volatility, low liquidity environment, only a catalyst will push BTC beyond $30,000 and beyond $40,000 by the end of the year. Something seems apparent in this context: Bitcoin seems ahead of any bullish narrative and likely to outperform in the sector for the remainder of 2023.</p>
<p>Cover image from Unsplash, chart from Tradingview</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT.jpg?fit=460%2C307" width="460" height="307" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">546726</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Terra Classic (LUNC) Chances Of Revival Grow Slimmer, Here’s Why</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/lunc/terra-classic-lunc-chances-of-revival/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Best Owie]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 23:00:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[LUNC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LUNC TVL]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Terra]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Terra Classic]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[TVL]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=546691</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Terra Classic (LUNC) has suffered persistent declines since the network’s collapse back in 2022. These declines have ranged from its price through to the network’s Total Value Locked (TVL). And even while development abounds among its community members to try to restore it to its past glory, the numbers point to a low possibility of recovery. Terra Classic TVL Falls To All-Time Low After Terra’s crash in 2022, the network lost a significant chunk of its TVL due to investors pulling out their funds as well as developers moving their decentralized applications and protocols to other networks. Over time, there seemed to be a stable trend but once again, the network has lost out against its better counterparts. Related Reading: Cardano (ADA) Next In Line For A Rally Following Shark And Whale Buying Spree Data from the on-chain tracker DeFiLlama shows that as of Thursday, the total Terra Classic (LUNC) TVL is sitting at $2.11 million. This is notable because this is the lowest that the network’s TVL has ever been. It is also a long way from the over $20 billion all-time high TVL of the Terra blockchain before its tragic collapse. LUNC TVL falls to new all-time low &#124; Source: DeFiLlama The vast majority of its meager TVL is spread across just two DeFi protocols: Terraswap and Astroport Classic, with $1.07 million and $933,527 in TVL, respectively. The highest that Terra’s TVL has been in 2023 is $12 million back in April 2023. Terra’s TVL has now declined by over 83% from its 2023 peaks. In the same vein, DeFiLlama shows $0 decentralized exchange (DEX) volumes over the last week, meaning that trading activity on the network has grounded to a halt. The Road To Recovery For LUNC Over the last year, the Terra community has been consistent about trying to help the network recover. However, the kind of decline that the cryptocurrency suffered as a result of the crash is not easy and near impossible to recover from. Related Reading: Crypto Analyst Says Bitcoin Could Reach $180,000 Next Cycle If This Happens Throwing in the fact that the network’s activities are almost non-existent, the chances of recovery have become even slimmer. But perhaps the biggest hindrance to its recovery is the fact that LUNC’s supply ballooned to over 6 trillion coins. Given this, even a surge to the $1 mark is out of reach for the token, unless there is a significant reduction in its supply. LUNC’s price continues to struggle at this time, trading at $0.00007746 at the time of writing. Its market cap is currently sitting at $450 million, making it the 80th-largest cryptocurrency by market cap. LUNC price trading over 99% below all-time high &#124; Source: LUNCUSDT on Tradingview.com Follow Best Owie on Twitter for market insights, updates, and the occasional funny tweet… Featured image from Finbold, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="p2">Terra Classic (LUNC) has suffered persistent declines since the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/all/terra-luna-token-burn-proposal-greenlit-could-1-be-hittable/">network’s collapse</a> back in 2022. These declines have ranged from its price through to the network’s <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/terra-tvl-climbs-to-new-high/" rel="nofollow">Total Value Locked (TVL)</a>. And even while development abounds among its community members to try to restore it to its past glory, the numbers point to a low possibility of recovery.</p>
<h2 class="p2">Terra Classic TVL Falls To All-Time Low</h2>
<p class="p2">After Terra’s crash in 2022, the network lost a significant chunk of its TVL due to investors pulling out their funds as well as developers moving their decentralized applications and protocols to other networks. Over time, there seemed to be a stable trend but once again, the network has lost out against its better counterparts.</p>

<p class="p2">Data from the on-chain tracker DeFiLlama shows that as of Thursday, the total Terra Classic (LUNC) TVL is sitting at $2.11 million. This is notable because this is the lowest that the network’s TVL has ever been. It is also a long way from the over $20 billion all-time high <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/defi-total-value-locked-tvl-declines-35/" rel="nofollow">TVL</a> of the Terra blockchain before its tragic collapse.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-546694 aligncenter" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot-2023-08-10-at-13.39.53.png?w=460&#038;resize=460%2C161" alt="Terra Classic (LUNC) TVL" width="460" height="161" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot-2023-08-10-at-13.39.53.png?w=2894 2894w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot-2023-08-10-at-13.39.53.png?w=460&#038;resize=460%2C161 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot-2023-08-10-at-13.39.53.png?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot-2023-08-10-at-13.39.53.png?w=860 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot-2023-08-10-at-13.39.53.png?w=1536 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot-2023-08-10-at-13.39.53.png?w=2048 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot-2023-08-10-at-13.39.53.png?w=750 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot-2023-08-10-at-13.39.53.png?w=1140 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px" data-recalc-dims="1"/></p>

<p class="p2">The vast majority of its meager TVL is spread across just two DeFi protocols: Terraswap and Astroport Classic, with $1.07 million and $933,527 in TVL, respectively. The highest that Terra’s TVL has been in 2023 is $12 million back in April 2023.</p>
<p class="p2">Terra’s TVL has now declined by over 83% from its 2023 peaks. In the same vein, DeFiLlama shows <a href="https://defillama.com/dexs/chains/terra%20classic" rel="nofollow">$0 decentralized exchange (DEX) volumes over the last week</a>, meaning that trading activity on the network has grounded to a halt.</p>
<h2 class="p2">The Road To Recovery For LUNC</h2>
<p class="p2">Over the last year, the Terra community has been consistent about trying to help the network recover. However, the kind of decline that the cryptocurrency suffered as a result of the crash is not easy and near impossible to recover from.</p>

<p class="p2">Throwing in the fact that the network’s activities are almost non-existent, the chances of recovery have become even slimmer. But perhaps the biggest hindrance to its recovery is the fact that LUNC’s supply ballooned to over 6 trillion coins. Given this, even a surge to the $1 mark is out of reach for the token, unless there is a <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/all/how-terra-luna-classic-token-burn-may-drive-lunc-and-ustc-to-1/">significant reduction in its supply</a>.</p>
<p class="p2"><a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/lunc/price-of-lunc-will-land-this-august/">LUNC’s price</a> continues to struggle at this time, trading at $0.00007746 at the time of writing. Its market cap is currently sitting at $450 million, making it the 80th-largest cryptocurrency by market cap.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/SWM6IDZC/" alt="Terra Classic (LUNC) price chart from Tradingview.com" width="2884" height="1746"/></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Terra-Classic-LUNC-1.jpeg?fit=460%2C279" width="460" height="279" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">546691</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Futures Fakeout: The Price Divergence That Predicts A Phony</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-futures-fakeout-the-price-divergence/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tony "The Bull"]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 22:16:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=546776</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[This week, Bitcoin traders braced for a breakout as an important technical buy signal triggered and BTCUSD shot up over $30,000 temporarily. They came up short-handed, however, as the market took an immediate turn back down. Interestingly, the fakeout could have possibly been predicted by a divergence between two BTCUSD price charts. Why Price Patterns And Technical Signals Can Fail Price patterns are tough to trade in cryptocurrencies. Because so many eyes are on the same pattern meeting precise parameters, the market has a way of making people pay for acting on the obvious. For example, a rising wedge pattern is typically bearish, but could breakout to the upside. The same is true for technical signals that a large portion of traders are paying attention to, such as notable crossovers and changes in momentum. This is exactly the case recently with a bullish crossover of the daily BTCUSD Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD). Related Reading: Will Record Low Volatility Awaken A Behemoth Bitcoin Surge? 4,000% Signal Returns The MACD is a momentum indicator that gives a buy signal when the MACD line crosses the signal line from below. This signal not only has appeared in Bitcoin, but it confirmed on BTCUSD spot exchanges, so what gives? It was a phony signal from the “future.” Conflicting signals &#124; BTCUSD on TradingView.com Spot Possible Divergences With Bitcoin Futures By “future” we mean BTC CME Futures, also known as Chicago Mercantile Exchange’s Bitcoin derivatives product, which institutions use to speculate on the underlying price of BTCUSD. The BTC CME Futures chart doesn’t always reflect spot BTCUSD charts 1:1. Any divergences between the two platforms, has historically led to fakeouts and phony breakouts. Part of the reason for this is due to the platform shutting down for a short period each day, and for the entire weekend starting at Friday afternoon. The result is a Bitcoin chart with more traditional market traits, such as gaps. The missing price data also changes the calculation of many technical indicators. For example, moving averages are in slightly different locations from chart to chart. Related Reading: Crypto Storm Brewing: Bitcoin Vortex Indicator Flashes Buy Alert This is precisely how the recent “fakeout” higher was able to be predicted with a degree of accuracy. This discrepancy and divergence leading to false signals is nothing new and has been happening for years. When BTC CME finally participates in the same signal, the expected results often then arrive. Is this a situation similar to Dow Theory, where the DJIA and DJTA must confirm one another for a trend to be valid? Or is there some more at play? Whatever the case may be, there’s enough historical evidence at this point to pay attention to any divergences between spot and CME Futures. Tony is the author of the CoinChartist (VIP) newsletter. Sign up for free. Follow @TonyTheBullBTC &#38; @coinchartist_io on Twitter. Or join the TonyTradesBTC Telegram for daily market insights and technical analysis education. Please note: Content is educational and should not be considered investment advice. Featured image from iStockPhoto, Charts from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This week, Bitcoin traders braced for a breakout as an important technical buy signal triggered and BTCUSD shot up over $30,000 temporarily.</p>
<p>They came up short-handed, however, as the market took an immediate turn back down. Interestingly, the fakeout could have possibly been predicted by a divergence between two BTCUSD price charts.</p>
<h2>Why Price Patterns And Technical Signals Can Fail</h2>
<p>Price patterns are tough to trade in cryptocurrencies. Because so many eyes are on the same pattern meeting precise parameters, the market has a way of making people pay for acting on the obvious. For example, a rising wedge pattern is typically bearish, but could breakout to the upside.</p>
<p>The same is true for technical signals that a large portion of traders are paying attention to, such as notable crossovers and changes in momentum. This is exactly the case recently with a bullish crossover of the daily BTCUSD Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD).</p>

<p>The MACD is a momentum indicator that gives a buy signal when the MACD line crosses the signal line from below. This signal not only has appeared in Bitcoin, but it confirmed on BTCUSD spot exchanges, so what gives? It was a phony signal from the “future.”</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/IMG_5259.jpeg?w=860&#038;resize=860%2C496" alt="Bitcoin futures " width="860" height="496" class="alignnone size-large wp-image-546777" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/IMG_5259.jpeg?w=1280 1280w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/IMG_5259.jpeg?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/IMG_5259.jpeg?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/IMG_5259.jpeg?w=860&#038;resize=860%2C496 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/IMG_5259.jpeg?w=750 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/IMG_5259.jpeg?w=1140 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" data-recalc-dims="1"/></p>

<h2>Spot Possible Divergences With Bitcoin Futures</h2>
<p>By “future” we mean BTC CME Futures, also known as Chicago Mercantile Exchange’s Bitcoin derivatives product, which institutions use to speculate on the underlying price of BTCUSD. The BTC CME Futures chart doesn’t always reflect spot BTCUSD charts 1:1. Any divergences between the two platforms, <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-futures-and-spot-signals-dont-match-up/">has historically led to fakeouts and phony breakouts</a>.</p>
<p>Part of the reason for this is due to the platform shutting down for a short period each day, and for the entire weekend starting at Friday afternoon. The result is a Bitcoin chart with more traditional market traits, such as gaps. The missing price data also changes the calculation of many technical indicators. For example, moving averages are in slightly different locations from chart to chart.</p>

<p>This is precisely how the recent “fakeout” higher was able to be predicted with a degree of accuracy. This discrepancy and divergence leading to false signals is nothing new and has been happening for years. When BTC CME finally participates in the same signal, the expected results often then arrive. </p>
<p>Is this a situation similar to Dow Theory, where the DJIA and DJTA must confirm one another for a trend to be valid? Or is there some more at play? Whatever the case may be, there’s enough historical evidence at this point to pay attention to any divergences between spot and CME Futures.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/IMG_5257.jpeg?fit=460%2C307" width="460" height="307" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">546776</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Here&#8217;s Why This Analyst Foresees Hedera (HBAR) Breaking Into The Crypto Top 10</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/altcoin/heres-why-this-analyst-foresees-hedera-hbar/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samuel Edyme]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 21:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[analyst]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[HBAR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hedera]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=546702</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Hedera popularly known as HBAR, has lately been drawing attention in the world of cryptocurrencies. An influencer from the crypto-sphere recently asserted that this digital currency is poised to cement its position among the top 10 in the industry. HBAR&#8217;s Position In The Upcoming Bull Market Classy Crypto, a crypto-focused YouTube channel, hosted a discussion where the anchoring influencer laid out his reasoning, foreseeing HBAR&#8217;s substantial ascent in the near future. According to the host of Classy Crypto, HBAR is not just positioned to rise but is also primed to become one of the biggest beneficiaries in the anticipated bull run. Related Reading: HBAR Token Scores Impressive Gains As Major Cryptos Nosedive The host noted that one factor driving this optimism is the forthcoming Bitcoin and Ethereum Exchange Trust Funds (ETFs). As these ETFs come into play, they are expected to usher a wave of institutional investors into the crypto sphere. However, the influencer argues that the initial attraction toward giants like Bitcoin and Ethereum would eventually pivot. Investors, after their primary foray, would likely explore alternative digital assets. These alternatives, which the host referred to as &#8220;pseudo-centralized currencies&#8221; offering distinct use cases, especially those with tracking capabilities, would then become the focal point. Hedera, with its tracking features, according to the host, could potentially emerge as a leading contender in this narrative. Hedera Offerings And Market Dynamics Diving deeper into Hedera&#8217;s offerings, the Classy Crypto host highlighted the consensus service of the platform. The host emphasized that this plays a significant role in tracking and catering to rising global demand. Additionally, in the backdrop of an evolving global political scenario, solutions like Hedera&#8217;s are anticipated to gain traction, given their ability to address large-scale issues. The host noted: Hedera has a consensus that does a lot of tracking and it&#8217;s great for the environment which is an increasingly large issue in our world political scene. Furthermore, beyond these specifics, the influencer also shared a broader market perspective. He envisions a major market breakout before the culmination of 2023. This momentum is likely to carry forward into 2024, heralding a significant bull run. One pivotal point he made pertained to the Layer 2 blockchains prevalent in the market. A realization among investors that many of these platforms might not support sustainable transaction sizes could direct focus towards Hedera. Related Reading: Hedera (HBAR) Token Shines With 10% Weekly Gains When Market Suffers Downtrend Particularly, its attributes, including fixed gas fees and the avant-garde Hashgraph technology, might just provide the edge it needs, according to the host. Over the past 24 hours, HBAR has traded in the red, down by nearly 5%. The asset currently trades at a price of $0.058, at the time of writing. Featured image from iStock, Chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Hedera popularly known as HBAR, has lately been drawing attention in the world of cryptocurrencies. An influencer from the crypto-sphere recently <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8dPuo5PBeAM" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">asserted</a> that this digital currency is poised to cement its position among the top 10 in the industry.</p>
<h2>HBAR&#8217;s Position In The Upcoming Bull Market</h2>
<p>Classy Crypto, a crypto-focused YouTube channel, hosted a discussion where the anchoring influencer laid out his reasoning, foreseeing <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/hbar-token-scores-impressive-gains-as-major-cryptos-nosedive/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">HBAR&#8217;s substantial ascent</a> in the near future. According to the host of Classy Crypto, HBAR is not just positioned to rise but is also primed to become one of the biggest beneficiaries in the anticipated bull run.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/hbar-token-scores-impressive-gains-as-major-cryptos-nosedive/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">HBAR Token Scores Impressive Gains As Major Cryptos Nosedive</a></p>
<p>The host noted that one factor driving this optimism is the forthcoming Bitcoin and Ethereum Exchange Trust Funds (ETFs). As these ETFs come into play, they are expected to usher a wave of institutional investors into the crypto sphere.</p>
<p>However, the influencer argues that the initial attraction toward giants like Bitcoin and Ethereum would eventually pivot. Investors, after their primary foray, would likely explore alternative digital assets. </p>
<p>These alternatives, which the host referred to as &#8220;pseudo-centralized currencies&#8221; offering distinct use cases, especially those with tracking capabilities, would then become the focal point. <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/altcoin/hedera-soars-23/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Hedera</a>, with its tracking features, according to the host, could potentially emerge as a leading contender in this narrative.</p>
<h2>Hedera Offerings And Market Dynamics</h2>
<p>Diving deeper into Hedera&#8217;s offerings, the Classy Crypto host highlighted the consensus service of the platform. The host emphasized that this plays a significant role in tracking and catering to rising global demand. </p>
<p>Additionally, in the backdrop of an evolving global political scenario, solutions like <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/all/hedera-gains-24-amidst-market-losses/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Hedera&#8217;s</a> are anticipated to gain traction, given their ability to address large-scale issues.</p>
<p>The host noted:</p>
<blockquote><p>Hedera has a consensus that does a lot of tracking and it&#8217;s great for the environment which is an increasingly large issue in our world political scene.</p></blockquote>
<p>Furthermore, beyond these specifics, the influencer also shared a broader market perspective. He envisions a major market breakout before the culmination of 2023. This momentum is likely to carry forward into 2024, heralding a significant bull run.</p>
<p>One pivotal point he made pertained to the Layer 2 blockchains prevalent in the market. A realization among investors that many of these platforms might not support sustainable transaction sizes could direct focus towards Hedera.</p>

<p>Particularly, its attributes, including fixed gas fees and the avant-garde Hashgraph technology, might just provide the edge it needs, according to the host.</p>
<p>Over the past 24 hours, HBAR has traded in the red, down by nearly 5%. The asset <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/crypto/hedera-hbar-token-shines-with-10-weekly-gains-when-market-suffers-downtrend/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">currently trades</a> at a price of $0.058, at the time of writing.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/8zEAXQoK/" alt="Hedera (HBAR) price chart on TradingView" width="2770" height="1408"/>
<p>Featured image from iStock, Chart from TradingView</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/istockphoto-482730527-612x612-1.jpg?fit=460%2C345" width="460" height="345" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">546702</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Solana (SOL) Leads Gains Among Top Coins, Is $30 Milestone Possible?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/solana/solana-sol-leads-gains-among-top-coins-is-30-milestone/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Kent Glory]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 20:00:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Solana]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SOL Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Solana ( SOL)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Solana performance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SOLUSD]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=546685</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The price of Solana (SOL) has fluctuated a lot in the past week, like many other cryptocurrencies in the market. SOL is currently trading above $24, gaining 8.01% in its price in the past 7 days with over $376 million in trading volume in the past 24 hours.   The coin&#8217;s movement has now sparked speculation among investors about the imminent breach of the $30 resistance threshold.  Factors That Could Influence SOL&#8217;s Price Solana has seen significant growth in terms of its total value locked (TVL). According to Data from Messari, Solana did better than other chains, with a 14% increase in the amount of funds locked in last month. Related Reading: Whale Purchases $10 Million stETH In The past Day, Here Are Possible Reasons Why Additionally, data from DeFi Llama shows that Solana is now the 9th biggest chain in terms of locked funds. It has around $320.07 million locked, a big jump from the $205.11 million it had at the start of the year. This surge in Solana’s Total Value Locked (TVL) could attract more people to buy SOL tokens. Importantly, with rising interest, the price of Solana&#8217;s tokens might increase due to higher demand.  However, if there&#8217;s suddenly bad news about Solana&#8217;s security or performance, even with a growing TVL, people might get worried and start selling their SOL tokens. This increased supply and decreased demand could cause the price to drop.  Can SOL Hit The $30 Milestone? The daily chart shows that the asset has traded positively in the past 24-hour market circle. The coin is trading above the Simple Moving Average (SMA) indicator and is bullish, signaling a potentially strong uptrend and a positive momentum in its price movement.  Additionally, it suggests that buyers are consistently active, pushing the price higher. This often indicates sustained demand and can potentially lead to further price appreciation. Meanwhile, the SMA can act as a support level if the price dips, preventing the price from falling too much.  However, while the SMA can act as support, it can also become a resistance level if the price moves significantly above it. This is because the Relative Strength Index (RSI) at 55 suggests the coin is balanced between overbought and oversold conditions.  The Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD) is also showing an attempt to cross over the signal line, indicated by the red histogram bar fading. This could signal a potential shift in momentum, with the upward movement gaining strength.  Related Reading: US Congresswoman Raises Concerns About Paypal Stablecoin In The Absence Of Regulation Considering the analysis, SOL could potentially hit the $30 threshold in a few weeks if the bulls sustain the current market sentiment. So traders can anticipate a bullish move but should consider other indicators and market context for a more accurate assessment of the coin&#8217;s direction. Featured image from Pixabay and chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The price of Solana (SOL) has fluctuated a lot in the past week, like many other cryptocurrencies in the market. SOL is currently trading above $24, gaining 8.01% in its price in the past 7 days with over $376 million in trading volume in the past 24 hours.  </p>
<p>The coin&#8217;s movement has now sparked speculation among investors about the imminent breach of the $30 resistance threshold. </p>
<h2>Factors That Could Influence SOL&#8217;s Price</h2>
<p>Solana has seen significant growth in terms of its total value locked (TVL). According to Data from Messari, <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/solana/solana-best-performer-in-tvl/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Solana did better than other chains</a>, with a 14% increase in the amount of funds locked in last month.</p>

<p>Additionally, data from DeFi Llama shows that Solana is now the 9th biggest chain in terms of locked funds. It has around $320.07 million locked, a big jump from the $205.11 million it had at the start of the year.</p>
<p>This surge in Solana’s Total Value Locked (TVL) could attract more people to buy SOL tokens. Importantly, with rising interest, the price of Solana&#8217;s tokens might increase due to higher demand. </p>
<p>However, if there&#8217;s suddenly bad news about Solana&#8217;s security or performance, even with a growing TVL, people might get worried and start selling their SOL tokens. This increased supply and decreased demand could cause the price to drop. </p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/2u1rUnY9/" alt="SOLUSD chart" width="980" height="589"/>
<h2>Can SOL Hit The $30 Milestone?</h2>
<p>The daily chart shows that the asset has traded positively in the past 24-hour market circle. The coin is trading above the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/x/UusiUMR4/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Simple Moving Average</a> (SMA) indicator and is bullish, signaling a potentially strong uptrend and a positive momentum in its price movement. </p>
<p>Additionally, it suggests that buyers are consistently active, pushing the price higher. This often indicates sustained demand and can potentially lead to further price appreciation. Meanwhile, the SMA can act as a support level if the price dips, preventing the price from falling too much. </p>
<p>However, while the SMA can act as support, it can also become a resistance level if the price moves significantly above it. This is because the Relative Strength Index (RSI) at 55 suggests the coin is balanced between overbought and oversold conditions. </p>
<p>The <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/x/UusiUMR4/" rel="nofollow">Moving Average Convergence Divergence</a> (MACD) is also showing an attempt to cross over the signal line, indicated by the red histogram bar fading. This could signal a potential shift in momentum, with the upward movement gaining strength. </p>

<p>Considering the analysis, SOL could potentially hit the $30 threshold in a few weeks if the bulls sustain the current market sentiment. So traders can anticipate a bullish move but should consider other indicators and market context for a more accurate assessment of the coin&#8217;s direction.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SOL.jpg?fit=460%2C298" width="460" height="298" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">546685</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>New Milestone For Ethereum Could Spell Good News For ETH Price</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/ethereum/new-milestone-for-ethereum/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 19:00:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum addresses]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=546689</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The number of Ethereum non-zero addresses, meaning addresses that hold at least some amount of Ether, just reached an all-time high. According to data from Glassnode, this metric which counts only externally owned addresses just reached an all-time high of 104,127,318. But what does this mean for the price of Ethereum? Ethereum Non-Zero Addresses Reach New All-Time High More addresses mean more people are using the network and Ethereum is in the driver&#8217;s seat when it comes to most application aspects of the crypto industry. As a result, the Ethereum blockchain has seen the highest growth rate in new addresses in recent years.  Related Reading: US Congresswoman Raises Concerns About Paypal Stablecoin In The Absence Of Regulation This growth has been particularly high as more people flock to decentralized finance (DeFi) protocols and non-fungible tokens (NFTs), the majority of which are built on the Ethereum blockchain. As of the time of writing, there are now 104,127,318 Ethereum addresses holding at least one wei, the smallest unit of ETH. Just around two years ago in 2021, this metric was around 50 million addresses, showing a 100% jump during this time.  Although only a fraction of these wallets are active, the high number of non-zero addresses shows the sheer increase in ETH adoption. In the same vein, the number of non-zero Bitcoin addresses only recently reached an all-time high of 47.8 million addresses. More Addresses Means Increased Network Activity and Adoption The growing interest in trading, smart contracts, DeFi, and NFTs will continue to boost the number of Ethereum users and non-zero addresses, especially now that the industry sits on the cusp of a possible bull run.  ETH bulls continue to hold above $1,800 &#124; Source: ETHUSD on Tradingview.com According to a similar metric by Glassnode Alerts, the amount of Ethereum supply last active within a seven to 10-year timeframe also just reached n new all-time high of 4.312 million ETH. This extended state of inactivity is suggestive of HODLing and long-term faith on the part of investors. Bullish For The Price Of ETH In the past, major rallies in Ether&#8217;s price have coincided with a surge in new addresses on the network. During the 2021 bull run, Ethereum saw a flurry of new addresses and non-zero addresses, as its price reached an all-time high of $4,810. As mainstream interest and adoption of Ethereum grow, the value and price of Ether (ETH) are likely to increase. Non-zero addresses mean activity on many addresses is increasing, which can create buy pressure in addition to other factors that should push ETH’s price higher.  Related Reading: Solana Beats Out Ethereum To Emerge As Best Performer In Terms Of TVL Additionally, investment companies are looking to launch exchange-traded funds (ETFs) tied to Ethereum futures, which could propel a spike in ETH’s price. Right now, ETH is currently trading at $1,852 and is looking to break above the resistance being mounted at $2,000 by the bears. Featured image from iStock, chart from Tradingview.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The number of Ethereum non-zero addresses, meaning addresses that hold at least some amount of Ether, just reached an all-time high. According to data from Glassnode, this metric which counts only <a href="https://twitter.com/glassnodealerts/status/1689294398192775168?s=20" rel="nofollow">externally owned addresses</a> just reached an all-time high of 104,127,318. But what does this mean for the price of Ethereum?</p>
<h2>Ethereum Non-Zero Addresses Reach New All-Time High</h2>
<p>More addresses mean more people are using the network and Ethereum is in the driver&#8217;s seat when it comes to most application aspects of the crypto industry. As a result, the Ethereum blockchain has seen the highest growth rate in new addresses in recent years. </p>

<p>This growth has been particularly high as more people flock to decentralized finance (DeFi) protocols and non-fungible tokens (NFTs), the majority of which are built on the Ethereum blockchain.</p>
<p>As of the time of writing, there are now 104,127,318 Ethereum addresses holding at least one wei, the smallest unit of ETH. Just around two years ago in 2021, this metric was around 50 million addresses, showing a 100% jump during this time. </p>
<p>Although only a fraction of these wallets are active, the high number of non-zero addresses shows the sheer increase in ETH adoption. In the same vein, the number of non-zero Bitcoin addresses only recently reached an <a href="https://t.co/VtoChZbLsa%20pic.twitter.com/fgiM94KVka" rel="nofollow">all-time high</a> of 47.8 million addresses.</p>
<h2>More Addresses Means Increased Network Activity and Adoption</h2>
<p>The growing interest in trading, smart contracts, DeFi, and NFTs will continue to boost the number of Ethereum users and non-zero addresses, especially now that the industry sits on the cusp of a possible bull run. </p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/xiwh32EG/" alt="Ethereum (ETH) price chart from Tradingview.com" width="2884" height="1746"/></p>

<p>According to a similar metric by Glassnode Alerts, the amount of Ethereum supply last active within a seven to 10-year timeframe also just reached n new all-time high of 4.312 million ETH. This extended state of inactivity is suggestive of HODLing and long-term faith on the part of investors.</p>
Bullish For The Price Of ETH
<p>In the past, major rallies in Ether&#8217;s price have coincided with a surge in new addresses on the network. During the 2021 bull run, Ethereum saw a flurry of new addresses and non-zero addresses, as its price reached an all-time high of $4,810.</p>
<p>As mainstream interest and adoption of Ethereum grow, the value and price of Ether (ETH) are likely to increase. Non-zero addresses mean activity on many addresses is increasing, which can create buy pressure in addition to other factors that should push ETH’s price higher. </p>

<p>Additionally, investment companies are looking to launch exchange-traded funds (ETFs) tied to <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/ethereum/ethereum-etfs-heat-up/">Ethereum futures</a>, which could propel a spike in ETH’s price.</p>
<p>Right now, ETH is currently trading at $1,852 and is looking to break above the resistance being mounted at $2,000 by the bears.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/iStock-1389493567.jpg?fit=460%2C307" width="460" height="307" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">546689</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Shanghai Upgrade Drives 25% Boost In ETH Staking Activity</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/shanghai-upgrade-drives-25-boost-in-eth-staking-activity/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Semilore Faleti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 18:00:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH accumulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH staking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shanghai Upgrade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Token Unlocks]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=546686</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Shanghai upgrade was one of the most anticipated blockchain events of 2023, expected to introduce a higher level of speed and scalability to the Ethereum network. However, the most important feature of the Shanghai upgrade was allowing validators and stakers to finally withdraw their staked ETH from the Ethereum Beacon Chain. To explain, the Beacon Chain was created to aid the smooth transition of Ethereum from a Proof-of-Work consensus model to a Proof-of-Stake mechanism, i.e., ETH 2.0. Since its launch in 2020, many users have been staking their ETH tokens on the Beacon chain to facilitate network security and earn rewards. Albeit, those assets and the rewards they generate were inaccessible until after the Shanghai upgrade in 2023.  Prior to this network upgrade which occurred on April 12, 2023, the total number of staked ETH stood at 18.1 million, according to data by Dune Analytics. Four months later, the token analytics website Token Unlocks has offered more insight into how the Shanghai Upgrade has impacted the ETH staking activity so far. Related Reading: Ethereum: Historical Playbook Points To $3,800 In Coming Months Shanghai Upgrade Sparks Confidence In ETH Staking  On August 10, Token Unlocks posted on social media platform X that the Ethereum Shanghai upgrade has yielded a positive result on ETH staking, with a significant rise in demand for LSD protocols &#8211; a liquid staking aggregator project designed to promote maximum yields for ETH stakers.  🔥 Wrapped Up for Shanghai Upgrade 🔥 The Shanghai Upgrade fueled sector growth, and the demand for the LSD protocol keeps rising. Here&#8217;s what you can&#8217;t afford to miss: 🔐 22.99m $ETH staked, ~18.86% of circulation (Overall) ✅ 5.84m $ETH staked, ~4.8% of circulation (Since… pic.twitter.com/ZReOpNVTzD — Token Unlocks (@Token_Unlocks) August 10, 2023 According to the report by Token Unlocks, there are currently 22.99 million staked ETH on the Ethereum network, accounting for about 18.86% of ETH’s circulating supply. The report also highlights that 25% of this currently staked ETH was staked after the Shanghai upgrade in April. This means that about 5.84 million ETH, constituting about 4.8% of ETH circulating supply, has been staked in the last four months. To emphasize the impact of the Shanghai upgrade on ETH staking, Token Unlocks noted that the net ETH staking ratio is up by 147%, with about 9.82 million ETH deposited and only 3.97 million ETH withdrawn post-upgrade. It is worth stating that there were some speculations that the Shanghai upgrade would lead to a large-scale withdrawal of ETH, which could negatively affect the crypto market. Interestingly, the report above paints a different reality, with many users now willing to stake ETH as they have the freedom to withdraw at will.  ETH trading at $1,856.8 on the hourly chart &#124; Source: ETHUSD chart on Tradingview.com ETH Elites Strengthen Grip On Coin Supply In other news, on-chain analytics firm Santiment reports a wealth accumulation trend in the ETH market. According to Santiment, the top 10 ETH addresses have significantly increased their ETH holdings in the last five years. Within this period, the market intelligence firm notes that these wallets have acquired 27.86 million ETH, increasing their holdings from 11.2% to 34.6% of the token’s supply. Related Reading: Ethereum Price Prints Bullish Technical Pattern, Why Close Above $1,880 Is Critical At the time of writing, ETH is trading at $1,855.86, with a 0.68% decline in the last 24 hours based on data from CoinMarketCap. With a market cap of $222.18 billion, the Ethereum native token remains the 2nd largest cryptocurrency in the market. Featured image from Finbold, chart from Tradingview.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Shanghai upgrade was one of the most anticipated blockchain events of 2023, expected to introduce a higher level of speed and scalability to the Ethereum network.</p>
<p>However, the most important feature of the Shanghai upgrade was allowing validators and stakers to finally withdraw their staked ETH from the Ethereum Beacon Chain.</p>
<p>To explain, the Beacon Chain was created to aid the smooth transition of Ethereum from a Proof-of-Work consensus model to a Proof-of-Stake mechanism, i.e., ETH 2.0. Since its launch in 2020, many users have been staking their ETH tokens on the Beacon chain to facilitate network security and earn rewards. Albeit, those assets and the rewards they generate were inaccessible until after the Shanghai upgrade in 2023. </p>
<p>Prior to this network upgrade which occurred on April 12, 2023, the total number of staked ETH stood at 18.1 million, according to <a href="https://dune.com/arch1111/eth-staking-dashboard" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">data by Dune Analytics</a>.</p>
<p>Four months later, the token analytics website Token Unlocks has offered more insight into how the Shanghai Upgrade has impacted the ETH staking activity so far.</p>

<h2>Shanghai Upgrade Sparks Confidence In ETH Staking </h2>
<p>On August 10, Token Unlocks <a href="https://twitter.com/Token_Unlocks/status/1689526067479060481?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">posted</a> on social media platform X that the Ethereum Shanghai upgrade has yielded a positive result on ETH staking, with a significant rise in demand for LSD protocols &#8211; a liquid staking aggregator project designed to promote maximum yields for ETH stakers. </p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en"><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f525.png" alt="🔥" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> Wrapped Up for Shanghai Upgrade <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f525.png" alt="🔥" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /></p>
<p>The Shanghai Upgrade fueled sector growth, and the demand for the LSD protocol keeps rising.</p>
<p>Here&#8217;s what you can&#8217;t afford to miss:</p>
<p><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f510.png" alt="🔐" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> 22.99m <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24ETH&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$ETH</a> staked, ~18.86% of circulation (Overall)
<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2705.png" alt="✅" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> 5.84m <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24ETH&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$ETH</a> staked, ~4.8% of circulation (Since… <a href="https://t.co/ZReOpNVTzD" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/ZReOpNVTzD</a></p>
<p>— Token Unlocks (@Token_Unlocks) <a href="https://twitter.com/Token_Unlocks/status/1689526067479060481?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">August 10, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p>According to the report by Token Unlocks, there are currently 22.99 million staked ETH on the Ethereum network, accounting for about 18.86% of ETH’s circulating supply.</p>
<p>The report also highlights that 25% of this currently staked ETH was staked after the Shanghai upgrade in April. This means that about 5.84 million ETH, constituting about 4.8% of ETH circulating supply, has been staked in the last four months.</p>
<p>To emphasize the impact of the Shanghai upgrade on ETH staking, Token Unlocks noted that the net ETH staking ratio is up by 147%, with about 9.82 million ETH deposited and only 3.97 million ETH withdrawn post-upgrade.</p>
<p>It is worth stating that there were some speculations that the Shanghai upgrade would lead to a large-scale withdrawal of ETH, which could negatively affect the crypto market.</p>
<p>Interestingly, the report above paints a different reality, with many users now willing to stake ETH as they have the freedom to withdraw at will. </p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/o0FwrrZU/" alt="Shanghai upgrade" width="1479" height="906"/></p>

<h2>ETH Elites Strengthen Grip On Coin Supply</h2>
<p>In other news, on-chain analytics firm Santiment<a href="https://twitter.com/santimentfeed/status/1689349389549293568" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow"> reports</a> a wealth accumulation trend in the ETH market. According to Santiment, the top 10 ETH addresses have significantly increased their ETH holdings in the last five years.</p>
<p>Within this period, the market intelligence firm notes that these wallets have acquired 27.86 million ETH, increasing their holdings from 11.2% to 34.6% of the token’s supply.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-bullish-1880/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Ethereum Price Prints Bullish Technical Pattern, Why Close Above $1,880 Is Critical</a></p>
<p>At the time of writing, ETH is trading at $1,855.86, with a 0.68% decline in the last 24 hours based on <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">data from CoinMarketCap</a>. With a market cap of $222.18 billion, the Ethereum native token remains the 2nd largest cryptocurrency in the market.</p>



]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/5-factors-that-could-send-Ethereum-to-5000.jpg?fit=460%2C306" width="460" height="306" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">546686</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Spoils Of Victory: XRP Daily Transactions Surpass Ethereum</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/xrp-daily-transactions-surpass-ethereum/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 17:00:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrp]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP Ledger]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP transactions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrpusdt]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=546690</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[On the back of Ripple’s partial win over the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), activity on the blockchain has ramped up quickly. This increase has now seen XRP beat out market leader Ethereum when it comes to the number of daily transactions carried out on the blockchain.  Ripple Leading The Pack While the euphoria from Judge Analisa Torres’s ruling has been waning, there is still enough left to continue to drive new milestones on Ripple’s XRP Ledger. The most prominent of these has been the number of transactions that are being carried out on the Ledger since the ruling. Related Reading: Pro-XRP Lawyer John Deaton Says He Is Willing To Bet That Ripple Will Win SEC Appeal Despite ending the month of July on a low note, the transactions have picked up in August. According to data from BitInfoCharts, daily transactions on the Ripple Ledger have consistently crossed 1 million since the start of August. This puts XRPL ahead of leading blockchains such as Ethereum (ETH) and Bitcoin (BTC), both of which have seen daily transaction figures come out below 1 million this month. On August 2, which has been the best day of the month so far for Ripple, transaction figures crossed 1.3 million, compared to 1.04 million for Ethereum and 390,000 for Bitcoin. XRP daily transactions rise above Ethereum &#124; Source: BitInfoCharts The new milestone comes after XRP first experienced a sharp drop in July. But since then, the blockchain has been on an upward trajectory. According to the present data, the XRP Network carried out 1.1173 million transactions on Thursday, August 9, almost double the number of its July 29 low of 612,000. However, despite the rise in transaction numbers, XRP continues to lag behind Bitcoin and Ethereum in terms of volume. Coinmarketcap data shows Bitcoin’s volume over the last day was $14 billion, Ethereum was in second with $4.2 billion, while XRP volume came in at $1.7 billion. Token price falls from local peak following court ruling &#124; Source: XRPUDST on Tradingview.com SEC’s Appeal Brings Down The XRP Momentum  XRP had undoubtedly enjoyed a huge boost following Judge Analisa Torres’ partial summary judgment in favor of Ripple in its ongoing case against the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). Related Reading: Billionaire Investor Wishes He Bought Bitcoin Early On, Here’s Why XRP experienced a massive spike from $0.47 to $0.81 (+72%) on the 13th of July (the day the partial summary judgment was given). However, it has since then retracted to the present zone. The token has maintained its current price range since the start of August with no significant movement upwards since then.  Furthermore, the SEC’s intention to file an interlocutory appeal may also draw down XRP’s momentum. In fact, XRP has reacted negatively to the aforementioned news as it is trading at around $0.6293, down 2.24% in the last 24 hours. Featured image from iStock, chart from Tradingview.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On the back of Ripple’s partial win over the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), activity on the blockchain has ramped up quickly. This increase has now seen XRP beat out market leader Ethereum when it comes to the number of daily transactions carried out on the blockchain. </p>
<h2>Ripple Leading The Pack</h2>
<p>While the euphoria from Judge Analisa Torres’s ruling has been waning, there is still enough left to continue to drive new milestones on Ripple’s XRP Ledger. The most prominent of these has been the number of transactions that are being carried out on the Ledger since the ruling.</p>

<p>Despite ending the month of July on a low note, the transactions have picked up in August. According to <a href="https://bitinfocharts.com/comparison/transactions-btc-eth-xrp.html#1y" rel="nofollow">data</a> from BitInfoCharts, daily transactions on the Ripple Ledger have consistently crossed 1 million since the start of August.</p>
<p>This puts XRPL ahead of leading blockchains such as Ethereum (ETH) and Bitcoin (BTC), both of which have seen daily transaction figures come out below 1 million this month. On August 2, which has been the best day of the month so far for Ripple, transaction figures crossed 1.3 million, compared to 1.04 million for Ethereum and 390,000 for Bitcoin.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-546698 aligncenter" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot-2023-08-10-at-13.44.19.png?w=460&#038;resize=460%2C166" alt="XRP surpasses Ethereum" width="460" height="166" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot-2023-08-10-at-13.44.19.png?w=3456 3456w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot-2023-08-10-at-13.44.19.png?w=460&#038;resize=460%2C166 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot-2023-08-10-at-13.44.19.png?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot-2023-08-10-at-13.44.19.png?w=860 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot-2023-08-10-at-13.44.19.png?w=1536 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot-2023-08-10-at-13.44.19.png?w=2048 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot-2023-08-10-at-13.44.19.png?w=750 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot-2023-08-10-at-13.44.19.png?w=1140 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot-2023-08-10-at-13.44.19.png?w=3000 3000w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px" data-recalc-dims="1"/></p>

<p>The new milestone comes after XRP first experienced a sharp drop in July. But since then, the blockchain has been on an upward trajectory. According to the present data, the XRP Network carried out 1.1173 million transactions on Thursday, August 9, almost double the number of its July 29 low of 612,000.</p>
<p>However, despite the rise in transaction numbers, XRP continues to lag behind Bitcoin and Ethereum in terms of volume. Coinmarketcap data shows Bitcoin’s volume over the last day was $14 billion, Ethereum was in second with $4.2 billion, while XRP volume came in at $1.7 billion.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/weKEgvx9/" alt="Ripple (XRP) price chart from Tradingview.com" width="2884" height="1746"/></p>

<h2><b>SEC’s Appeal Brings Down The XRP Momentum </b></h2>
<p>XRP had undoubtedly enjoyed a huge boost following Judge Analisa Torres’ partial summary judgment in favor of Ripple in its <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/ripple-sec-update-why-ruling-take-even-longer/" rel="nofollow">ongoing case</a> against the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC).</p>

<p>XRP experienced a massive spike from $0.47 to $0.81 (+72%) on the 13th of July (the day the partial summary judgment was given). However, it has since then retracted to the present zone. The token has maintained its current price range since the start of August with no significant movement upwards since then. </p>
<p>Furthermore, the SEC’s intention to file an <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/ripple/sec-asks-file-interlocutory-appeal-ripple-xrp/">interlocutory appeal</a> may also draw down XRP’s momentum. In fact, XRP has reacted negatively to the aforementioned news as it is trading at around $0.6293, down 2.24% in the last 24 hours.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/iStock-1370115266.jpg?fit=460%2C307" width="460" height="307" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">546690</post-id>	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
