<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"

	xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
	xmlns:geo="http://www.w3.org/2003/01/geo/wgs84_pos#"
	>

<channel>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.newsbtc.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<description>Bitcoin &#38; Cryptocurrency News Today</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 17:30:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-cropped-favicon.png?fit=32%2C32</url>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
<site xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">221170450</site>	<item>
		<title>Rumors Of Robinhood Listing XRP Take Center Stage On Crypto Twitter</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/robinhood-listing-xrp/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 03:00:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ripple news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Robinhood]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Robinhood news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrp]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrp news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrpusdt]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=548459</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The crypto community is currently buzzing with excitement and curiosity following rumors of Robinhood potentially listing XRP. These rumors come as the XRP price falls to pre-judgment levels, sparking hope that it could trigger a reversal. XRP Rumors Has Crypto Twitter In A Frenzy Rumor has it that an anonymous insider has confirmed the potential listing of XRP, the native token of Ripple, on Robinhood, an American financial trading platform, before the end of 2023. The rumor was started on August 22 by a crypto user on X (formerly Twitter) who goes by the username @25hoursawake.  The whispers of Robinhood listing XRP have sent shockwaves in the crypto community and numerous crypto investors and enthusiasts have taken to Twitter to air out their respective views and opinions on the speculation. Related Reading: Diamond In The Rough: Solo Bitcoin Miner Secures $160,000 Block Reward Robinhood is renowned for its meticulous listing process, and according to an X user Crypto Asset Guy, Robinhood has a reputation for not just listing any type of cryptocurrency. The trading platform puts considerable effort and time into its crypto listing procedure to ensure only the highest-qualified cryptocurrencies according to their standards are integrated into its platform.  Alternatively, the crypto and stock trading platform is also known for delisting cryptocurrencies without a second thought, if said cryptocurrency faces any form of regulatory or significant market challenges.  As the crypto space eagerly discusses the ramifications of Robinhood potentially listing XRP, some enthusiasts argue that integrating XRP tokens into the platform would have a positive outlook, exposing the digital asset to a wider audience and increasing investments in Robinhood.  Token price falls to levels before Judge Torres's ruling &#124; Source: XRPUSD on Tradingview.com Other individuals have pointed out Robinhood&#8217;s affinity for restricting trades and transactions during high market volatility. This has led to doubts about the platform&#8217;s ability to provide uninterrupted access to XRP users’ digital assets.  Commenting on the rumors of Robinhood listing XRP, Crypto Assets Guy stated that if the speculations prove to be true, then the crypto community should look forward to a surge in investments and market trends. He emphasized that Robinhood may have insights on XRP, unbeknownst to the public.  “If the rumors are true and Robinhood lists $XRP by the end of the year then prepare for a MASSIVE uptrend. Robinhood is known for being very tedious when selecting which crypto to list. So if they are getting ready to list XRP they must know something,” he said.  Additionally, the outcome would undoubtedly increase the cryptocurrency’s mainstream adoption. Analyzing The Potential Effect Of A Robinhood Listing Ripple has been in an ongoing lawsuit with the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) for almost three years now. The lawsuit was thought to be finalized after XRP took a win following Judge Analisa Torres’s ruling which stated that programmatic XRP sales are not to be considered a security.  Related Reading: Dogecoin Proof Of Stake Discussion Heats Up As Lead Dev Chimes In However, the SEC has recently issued an interlocutory appeal to reevaluate the case. This move has pushed XRP back to a potentially red zone in terms of regulatory challenges. If the SEC were to emerge victorious, then it could impact the potential listing of XRP on a platform such as Robinhood. Featured image from Coinmarketcap, chart from Tradingview.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The crypto community is currently buzzing with excitement and curiosity following rumors of Robinhood potentially listing XRP. These rumors come as the XRP price falls to pre-judgment levels, sparking hope that it could trigger a reversal.</p>
<h2>XRP Rumors Has Crypto Twitter In A Frenzy</h2>
<p>Rumor has it that an anonymous insider has confirmed the potential listing of XRP, the native token of <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/ripple-2/xrp-pain-ripple-vs-sec-case/">Ripple</a>, on Robinhood, an American financial trading platform, before the end of 2023. The rumor was started on August 22 by a crypto user on X (formerly Twitter) who goes by the username <a href="https://twitter.com/25hoursawake/status/1693814264434249871?s=20" rel="nofollow">@25hoursawake</a>. </p>
<p>The whispers of Robinhood listing XRP have sent shockwaves in the crypto community and numerous crypto investors and enthusiasts have taken to Twitter to air out their respective views and opinions on the speculation.</p>

<p>Robinhood is renowned for its meticulous listing process, and according to an X user <a href="https://twitter.com/cryptoassetsguy/status/1693635334519533872?s=20" rel="nofollow">Crypto Asset Guy</a>, Robinhood has a reputation for not just listing any type of cryptocurrency. The trading platform puts considerable effort and time into its crypto listing procedure to ensure only the highest-qualified cryptocurrencies according to their standards are integrated into its platform. </p>
<p>Alternatively, the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/dogecoin-robinhood-16m-whale-exodus/">crypto and stock trading platform</a> is also known for delisting cryptocurrencies without a second thought, if said cryptocurrency faces any form of regulatory or significant market challenges. </p>
<p>As the crypto space eagerly discusses the ramifications of Robinhood potentially listing XRP, some enthusiasts argue that integrating XRP tokens into the platform would have a positive outlook, exposing the digital asset to a wider audience and increasing investments in Robinhood. </p>
<p><img decoding="async" fetchpriority="high" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/0hmWyvZq/" alt="XRP price chart from Tradingview.com (Robinhood)" width="2884" height="1746" loading="lazy"/></p>

<p>Other individuals have pointed out Robinhood&#8217;s affinity for restricting trades and transactions during high market volatility. This has led to doubts about the platform&#8217;s ability to provide uninterrupted access to XRP users’ digital assets. </p>
<p>Commenting on the rumors of Robinhood listing XRP, Crypto Assets Guy stated that if the speculations prove to be true, then the crypto community should look forward to a surge in investments and market trends. He emphasized that Robinhood may have insights on XRP, unbeknownst to the public. </p>
<p>“If the rumors are true and Robinhood lists $XRP by the end of the year then prepare for a MASSIVE uptrend. Robinhood is known for being very tedious when selecting which crypto to list. So if they are getting ready to list XRP they must know something,” he said. </p>
<p>Additionally, the outcome would undoubtedly increase the cryptocurrency’s <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/institutional-xrp-holdings-rise/">mainstream adoption</a>.</p>
<h2>Analyzing The Potential Effect Of A Robinhood Listing</h2>
<p>Ripple has been in an ongoing lawsuit with the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) for almost three years now. The lawsuit was thought to be finalized after XRP took a win following Judge Analisa Torres’s ruling which stated that programmatic XRP sales are not to be considered a security. </p>

<p>However, the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/ripple-2/sec-interlocutory-appeal-ripple-a-mistake/">SEC has recently issued an interlocutory appeal</a> to reevaluate the case. This move has pushed XRP back to a potentially red zone in terms of regulatory challenges. If the SEC were to emerge victorious, then it could impact the potential listing of XRP on a platform such as Robinhood.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/XRP-robinhood.jpeg?fit=460%2C328" width="460" height="328" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">548459</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Is Binance Really Selling Bitcoin To Prop The Price Of BNB?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/binance-bitcoin-bnb/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 02:00:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BNB]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BNB news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto exchange]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=548461</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Crypto exchange Binance has had a tough few months in terms of market news and pressure from regulatory bodies. Just a few days ago, Binance lost another payment processing partner after Checkout.com terminated its contract with the crypto exchange. And now, another rumor that appears to be spreading is that Binance is selling Bitcoin on the spot market to sustain the price of its native token, BNB. Is Binance Really Selling Its Bitcoin To Buy BNB? The rumor originated from a post made by @WhaleChart on X (formerly Twitter), claiming that Binance is allegedly selling Bitcoin on the spot market to support the price of its own token, BNB.  Related Reading: Shiba Inu Community Leaves Shibarium Launch Troubles Behind As Wallet Count Crossed 10 Million BREAKING: Binance is allegedly selling Bitcoin to support the price of their own token BNB — Whale (@WhaleChart) August 22, 2023 This rumor seems to be gaining ground since the tweet first went live, especially as the price of BNB continues to struggle in the market. This is because as one of the biggest holders of both Bitcoin and BNB, Binance is in a unique position to manipulate the market if it wanted.  However, this remains only a rumor as there are currently no signs the crypto exchange is manipulating the price for short-term gains in BNB.  Additionally, data from Coinmarketcap shows that the prices of both cryptocurrencies have been falling together in the past week, with Bitcoin also down by 11.20% in a 7-day timeframe. This will not be the first time such allegations are being brought against the exchange. Binance has faced similar claims in the past, with crypto analyst JW claiming Binance was selling Bitcoin to prop up the price of BNB in June of this year.  Token price falls in tandem with BTC &#124; Source: BNBUSD on Tradingview.com Binance CEO Changpeng Zhao (CZ), however, denied the allegations, dismissing them as an attempt to spread fear, uncertainty, and doubt (FUD).  4. Binance have not sold BTC or BNB. We even still have a bag of FTT. It is amazing they can know exactly who sold based on just a price chart involving millions of traders. FUD. 🤷‍♂️ pic.twitter.com/M3MUH2bFRE — CZ 🔶 Binance (@cz_binance) June 13, 2023 Whether or not the theories are true, Binance has surely been under intense scrutiny, but it continues to stand strong as the biggest exchange in the world.  BNB and other cryptocurrencies that rely on the BEP20 and BEP2 token standards are very dependent on Binance, as news surrounding the exchange has led to price pumps and dumps in the past. But there has been no solid evidence that the exchange has been manipulating the prices of any of these tokens. Related Reading: Gemini Hits Back At SEC Lawsuit With Dismissal Filing The price of BNB has seen a drastic reduction in the past few days as the entire market goes through corrections signaled by BTC falling by more than 8% in a couple of minutes last week. As a result, BNB has seen its price drop to $209.44, a reduction of 12.33% in the past few days.  To combat a further price drop, the BNB Chain had to manually liquidate a $200 million position on the Venus DEFI protocol, which would have been liquidated after BNB dropped below $220. At the time of writing, BNB is the fourth biggest crypto with a market cap of $32.2 billion. Featured image from Unsplash, chart from Tradingview.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Crypto exchange Binance has had a tough few months in terms of market news and pressure from regulatory bodies. Just a few days ago, Binance lost another payment processing partner after Checkout.com <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/binance-checkout-com-cuts-ties-citing-aml-concerns/" rel="nofollow">terminated its contract</a> with the crypto exchange. And now, another rumor that appears to be spreading is that Binance is selling Bitcoin on the spot market to sustain the price of its native token, BNB.</p>
<h2>Is Binance Really Selling Its Bitcoin To Buy BNB?</h2>
<p>The rumor originated from a post made by @WhaleChart on X (formerly Twitter), claiming that Binance is allegedly selling Bitcoin on the spot market to support the price of its own token, BNB. </p>

<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">BREAKING:</p>
<p>Binance is allegedly selling Bitcoin to support the price of their own token BNB</p>
<p>— Whale (@WhaleChart) <a href="https://twitter.com/WhaleChart/status/1693867386783375481?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">August 22, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p>This rumor seems to be gaining ground since the tweet first went live, especially as the price of BNB continues to struggle in the market. This is because as one of the biggest holders of both Bitcoin and BNB, Binance is in a unique position to manipulate the market if it wanted. </p>
<p>However, this remains only a rumor as there are currently no signs the crypto exchange is manipulating the price for short-term gains in BNB. </p>
<p>Additionally, data from Coinmarketcap shows that the prices of both cryptocurrencies have been falling together in the past week, with Bitcoin also down by 11.20% in a 7-day timeframe.</p>
<p>This will not be the first time such allegations are being brought against the exchange. Binance has faced similar <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/fud-or-real-binance-selling-bitcoin-to-prop-up-bnb/">claims in the past</a>, with crypto analyst JW claiming Binance was selling Bitcoin to prop up the price of BNB in June of this year. </p>
<p><img decoding="async" class="aligncenter" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/dyVH8TYi/" alt="BNB price chart from Tradingview.com (Binance Bitcoin)" width="2884" height="1746" loading="lazy"/></p>

<p>Binance CEO Changpeng Zhao (CZ), however, denied the allegations, dismissing them as an attempt to spread fear, uncertainty, and doubt (FUD). </p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">4. Binance have not sold BTC or BNB. We even still have a bag of FTT.</p>
<p>It is amazing they can know exactly who sold based on just a price chart involving millions of traders. FUD. <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f937-200d-2642-fe0f.png" alt="🤷‍♂️" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> <a href="https://t.co/M3MUH2bFRE" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/M3MUH2bFRE</a></p>
<p>— CZ <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f536.png" alt="🔶" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> Binance (@cz_binance) <a href="https://twitter.com/cz_binance/status/1668735411705765893?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">June 13, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p>Whether or not the theories are true, Binance has surely been under intense scrutiny, but it continues to stand strong as the biggest exchange in the world. </p>
<p>BNB and other cryptocurrencies that rely on the BEP20 and BEP2 token standards are very dependent on Binance, as news surrounding the exchange has led to price pumps and dumps in the past. But there has been no solid evidence that the exchange has been manipulating the prices of any of these tokens.</p>

<p>The price of BNB has seen a drastic reduction in the past few days as the entire market goes through corrections signaled by BTC falling by more than 8% in a couple of minutes last week. As a result, BNB has seen its price drop to $209.44, a reduction of 12.33% in the past few days. </p>
<p>To combat a further price drop, the BNB Chain had to <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/binance-coin/200-million-bnb-bridge-exploiter-liquidated/">manually liquidate a $200 million position on the Venus DEFI protocol</a>, which would have been liquidated after BNB dropped below $220.</p>
<p>At the time of writing, BNB is the fourth biggest crypto with a market cap of $32.2 billion.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/kanchanara-WLvog4WcqRU-unsplash.jpg?fit=460%2C306" width="460" height="306" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">548461</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Chicken Game: Why Losing This Level Could Send BTC Back To $20,000</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-chicken-game-why-losing-this-level-could-send-btc-back-to-20000/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reynaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 01:00:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=548443</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The price of Bitcoin has stalled again around its current levels as an explosion in downside volatility broke critical support. The cryptocurrency is trapped between major players waiting and positioning for the next move; which side will prevail in this battle? Related Reading: Bitcoin On-Chain Data Suggests Price Is Top Heavy, What It Means As of this writing, Bitcoin trades at $26,000 with sideways movement in the last 24 hours. In the previous seven days, the cryptocurrency recorded a 12% correction which has severely impacted other assets in the sector, notably XRP and Binance Coin (BNB), which recorded losses north of 15% in the same period. Retail Traders Likely To Push Bitcoin Price Lower? In a report from Bitfinex Alpha, an analyst points out the influence of the derivatives sector on the spot Bitcoin price. Last week, BTC’s volatility was compressed, declining into historical lows, but a negative delta (high selling pressure) persisted, moving the price lower. At the time, Bitcoin dropped enough to trigger a liquidation cascade, which was potentially worsened by a prominent trader being forced out of their position on a crypto exchange, the report speculated. The chart below shows that Open Interest in the derivatives sector followed BTC’s price action. This market dynamics left Bitcoin in its current state. Analysts from Material Indicators called it a “game of chicken” between prominent players waiting to see if enough liquidity will be added to support the current levels or if the selling pressure will return. The analysts indicated that the BTC price orderbook is the thinnest in 6 months while adding the following: (…) we are seeing small amounts of bid liquidity ladder up from $20k closer to the active trading zone, but no liquidity of any size (new or moved) has been stacked into the range defending price from a Lower Low. Needless to say, printing a LL in this TF has macro implications. Printing 2 LLs would push #BTC down to sub $20k levels. Material Indicators showed that when the price of Bitcoin broke below critical support, most of the selling was done by relatively small traders. However, whales likely used small selling orders to reduce slippage and push prices down to current levels. Related Reading: 3rd Biggest Bitcoin Stash Now Belongs To Unknown Wallet, Amassed In Over 3 Months A similar scenario seems likely if the BTC price slowly bleeds into critical support triggering another liquidation cascade. In the meantime, the number one cryptocurrency seems bound to carry on its game of Chicken between large players. Cover image from Unsplash, chart from Tradingview]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>The price of Bitcoin has stalled again around its current levels as an explosion in downside volatility broke critical support. The cryptocurrency is trapped between major players waiting and positioning for the next move; which side will prevail in this battle?</strong></p>

<p>As of this writing, Bitcoin trades at $26,000 with sideways movement in the last 24 hours. In the previous seven days, the cryptocurrency recorded a 12% correction which has severely impacted other assets in the sector, notably XRP and Binance Coin (BNB), which recorded losses north of 15% in the same period.</p>
<img decoding="async" class="wp-image-548454 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-price-BTC-BTCUSDT-5.png?w=860&#038;resize=860%2C410" alt="Bitcoin price BTC BTCUSDT" width="860" height="410" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-price-BTC-BTCUSDT-5.png?w=1758 1758w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-price-BTC-BTCUSDT-5.png?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-price-BTC-BTCUSDT-5.png?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-price-BTC-BTCUSDT-5.png?w=860&#038;resize=860%2C410 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-price-BTC-BTCUSDT-5.png?w=1536 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-price-BTC-BTCUSDT-5.png?w=750 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-price-BTC-BTCUSDT-5.png?w=1140 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" loading="lazy" data-recalc-dims="1"/>
<h2>Retail Traders Likely To Push Bitcoin Price Lower?</h2>
<p>In a <a href="https://blog.bitfinex.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitfinex-Alpha-68.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">report</a> from Bitfinex Alpha, an analyst points out the influence of the derivatives sector on the spot Bitcoin price. Last week, BTC’s volatility was compressed, declining into historical lows, but a negative delta (high selling pressure) persisted, moving the price lower.</p>
<p>At the time, Bitcoin dropped enough to trigger a liquidation cascade, which was potentially worsened by a prominent trader being forced out of their position on a crypto exchange, the report speculated. The chart below shows that Open Interest in the derivatives sector followed BTC’s price action.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-548451 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-price-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-2-2.jpg?w=860&#038;resize=860%2C290" alt="Bitcoin price BTC BTCUSDT Chart 2" width="860" height="290" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-price-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-2-2.jpg?w=1699 1699w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-price-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-2-2.jpg?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-price-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-2-2.jpg?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-price-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-2-2.jpg?w=860&#038;resize=860%2C290 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-price-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-2-2.jpg?w=1536 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-price-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-2-2.jpg?w=750 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-price-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-2-2.jpg?w=1140 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" data-recalc-dims="1"/>
<p>This market dynamics left Bitcoin in its current state. Analysts from Material Indicators <a href="https://twitter.com/MI_Algos/status/1693987249103532224" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">called</a> it a “game of chicken” between prominent players waiting to see if enough liquidity will be added to support the current levels or if the selling pressure will return.</p>
<p>The analysts indicated that the BTC price orderbook is the thinnest in 6 months while <a href="https://twitter.com/MI_Algos/status/1693987249103532224" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">adding</a> the following:</p>
<blockquote><p>(…) we are seeing small amounts of bid liquidity ladder up from $20k closer to the active trading zone, but no liquidity of any size (new or moved) has been stacked into the range defending price from a Lower Low. Needless to say, printing a LL in this TF has macro implications. Printing 2 LLs would push #BTC down to sub $20k levels.</p></blockquote>
<p>Material Indicators <a href="https://twitter.com/MI_Algos/status/1693637697544327590" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">showed</a> that when the price of Bitcoin broke below critical support, most of the selling was done by relatively small traders. However, whales likely used small selling orders to reduce slippage and push prices down to current levels.</p>

<p>A similar scenario seems likely if the BTC price slowly bleeds into critical support triggering another liquidation cascade. In the meantime, the number one cryptocurrency seems bound to carry on its game of Chicken between large players.</p>
<p>Cover image from Unsplash, chart from Tradingview</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-Price-BTC-BTCUSDT-8.jpg?fit=460%2C307" width="460" height="307" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">548443</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Rise In Bitcoin Outflows Suggests Institutional Investors May Be Losing Faith In The Asset</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-outflows-institutional-investors/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 00:01:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin institutional investors]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Outflows]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC news]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=548460</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[This year has been marked by significant volatility across the crypto market, including for Bitcoin, which has seen both gains and losses over the course of the year. Just a month ago in the middle of July, Bitcoin crossed over $30,000 and many investors saw this as the start of another bull run.  However, things seem to have taken a turn, as the price of Bitcoin has plateaued since then. The asset is currently struggling to find a push in price, and it would seem this sentiment has flowed into digital asset funds. According to the weekly report published by digital asset manager CoinShares, Bitcoin outflows from institutional accounts have resumed in the past week. Outflows From Digital Asset Investment Products Outflows from digital asset investment products have spiked in recent weeks to register a three-week run of outflows. This would indicate that institutional investors might be avoiding volatile cryptos. This comes two weeks after a brief period of inflows, where Ripple&#8217;s partial victory in court and recent US inflation data led to inflows in digital asset products.  Related Reading: Dogecoin Proof Of Stake Discussion Heats Up As Lead Dev Chimes In However, data shows that outflows resumed last week, and it appears that the euphoria that followed Ripple&#8217;s partial triumph against the SEC has dissipated. Digital asset investment products saw $55 million in outflows last week, with Bitcoin leading the charge with outflows of $42 million. Other cryptocurrencies like Ethereum registered $9 million outflows, while Polygon, Litecoin, and Polkadot saw outflows of $0.9 million, $0.6 million, and $0.5 million, respectively. On the other hand, XRP and Cardano saw an increase in their respective inflows of $1.2 million and $0.1 million.  In terms of region, Canada had the most outflows of $35.9. million, and Germany followed with $11 million. BTC price falls below $26,000 support &#124; Source: BTCUSD On Tradingview.com Rise In Bitcoin Outflows Bitcoin outflows from exchanges suggest big investors may be losing faith in the popular cryptocurrency. One factor that fueled this outflow is speculations going around that the SEC might not actually approve applications for spot Bitcoin ETFs in the US. As a result, total assets under management (AuM) declined by 10% to close the week at $32.3 billion.  Related Reading: Gemini Hits Back At SEC Lawsuit With Dismissal Filing The speculations come as the SEC has delayed making a decision on Spot Bitcoin ETF applications multiple times. Each postponement casts more doubt on whether they will ever approve one and an outright rejection from the SEC will most likely lead to the price of Bitcoin falling to $20,000 and digital asset investment products registering more outflows. At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading at $26,053 and is down by 11.09% in a 7-day timeframe.  Featured image from Unsplash, chart from Tradingview.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This year has been marked by significant volatility across the crypto market, including for Bitcoin, which has seen both gains and losses over the course of the year. Just a month ago in the middle of July, Bitcoin crossed over $30,000 and many investors saw this as the start of another bull run. </p>
<p>However, things seem to have taken a turn, as the price of Bitcoin has plateaued since then. The asset is currently struggling to find a push in price, and it would seem this sentiment has flowed into digital asset funds. According to the weekly report published by digital asset manager CoinShares, Bitcoin outflows from institutional accounts <a href="https://blog.coinshares.com/volume-145-digital-asset-fund-flows-weekly-report-370b18faa268" rel="nofollow">have resumed in</a> the past week.</p>
<h2>Outflows From Digital Asset Investment Products</h2>
<p>Outflows from digital asset investment products have spiked in recent weeks to register a three-week run of outflows. This would indicate that institutional investors might be avoiding volatile cryptos. This comes two weeks after a <a href="https://blog.coinshares.com/volume-144-digital-asset-fund-flows-weekly-report-7d29c8c04df5" rel="nofollow">brief period of inflows</a>, where Ripple&#8217;s partial victory in court and recent US inflation data <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/institutional-xrp-holdings-rise/#:~:text=In%20the%20days%20following%20Ripple's,of%20a%20continued%20bull%20run.">led to inflows</a> in digital asset products. </p>

<p>However, data shows that outflows resumed last week, and it appears that the euphoria that followed Ripple&#8217;s partial triumph against the SEC has dissipated. Digital asset investment products saw $55 million in outflows last week, with Bitcoin leading the charge with outflows of $42 million.</p>
<p>Other cryptocurrencies like Ethereum registered $9 million outflows, while Polygon, Litecoin, and Polkadot saw outflows of $0.9 million, $0.6 million, and $0.5 million, respectively. On the other hand, XRP and Cardano saw an increase in their respective inflows of $1.2 million and $0.1 million. </p>
<p>In terms of region, Canada had the most outflows of $35.9. million, and Germany followed with $11 million.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/81xDsSFU/" alt="Bitcoin price chart from Tradingview.com (Institutional investors)" width="2884" height="1746"/></p>

<h2>Rise In Bitcoin Outflows</h2>
<p>Bitcoin outflows from exchanges suggest big investors may be losing faith in the popular cryptocurrency. One factor that fueled this outflow is speculations going around that the SEC <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/attorney-dashes-hopes-of-spot-bitcoin-etf/#:~:text=According%20to%20him%2C%20CNBC's%20recent,requirements%2C%20and%20effective%20consumer%20protections." rel="nofollow">might not actually approve applications</a> for spot Bitcoin ETFs in the US. As a result, total assets under management (AuM) declined by 10% to close the week at $32.3 billion. </p>

<p>The speculations come as the SEC has delayed making a decision on Spot Bitcoin ETF applications multiple times. Each postponement casts more doubt on whether they will ever approve one and an outright rejection from the SEC will most likely lead to the price of Bitcoin falling to $20,000 and digital asset investment products registering more outflows.</p>
<p>At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading at $26,053 and is down by 11.09% in a 7-day timeframe. </p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/kanchanara-4KJJezDyo3M-unsplash.jpg?fit=460%2C307" width="460" height="307" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">548460</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>SHIB Burn Rate Jump 1,100% Amid Expectations Of Shibarium Relaunch</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/shib/shib-burn-rate-jump-1100-amid-expectations-of-shibarium-relaunch/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Best Owie]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 23:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[SHIB]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shib Burn]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIB burn news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIB news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shiba Inu]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shiba Inu burn]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shiba Inu news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIBUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIBUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=548386</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Off the back of the much-anticipated Shibarium launch, the SHIB burn rate has seen a tremendous rise. This surge in the burn rate comes despite the Layer 2 blockchain running into problems on the day of its launch last week, and still being in private mode. But while it could point to renewed vigor among the meme coin’s investors, something else seems to be driving this accelerated burn rate. SHIB Burn Rate Is Up 1,108% In One Day According to data from Shiba Inu burn tracking website Shibburn, there has been a remarkable increase in burn rate in the last 24 hours compared to the prior day. In total, there have been over 1.046 billion tokens burned, which translates to a 1,108.78% increase during this timeframe. Related Reading: AVAX Price Bucks Under The Pressure Of Upcoming $102 Million Token Unlock This is in stark contrast to the previous day’s figures which came out at around 100 million tokens burned. However, while the jump in burn rate is interesting, the address doing most of the SHIB burn is even more interesting. Looking at the burn addresses posted by Shibburn, one address keeps popping up and that is the 0x4be2 address. A quick look on-chain revealed that this address is actually the contract address for the MARSWAP (MSWAP) token. Burn rate up over 1,100% &#124; Source: Shibburn This token seems to dedicate a portion of fees generated from transactions toward SHIB burn and as it gains popularity, the number of SHIB tokens being burned has jumped. So far, Marswap accounts for about 40% of burnt tokens. But a single address, 0xcf6d, which is the ShibaSwap LP Token (SSLP) contract address, burned 418,719,732 tokens in what has been the single largest burn event in the last day. Token price remains highly volatile &#124; Source: SHIBUSD on Tradingview.com How Is The Token Price Responding? Despite the marked increase in the SHIB burn rate, the price of the meme coin has not responded as positively as expected. The token price seems to be keeping in line with the general crypto market sentiment and continues to trade in the red. Related Reading: Bitcoin Liquidations Top $500 Million Amid $1 Billion Crypto Decimation Although there has been a small shift in the last hour at the time of this writing, with SHIB’s price moving up a meager 0.16%, its price is still taking losses of 1.48% on the daily chart. Even more concerning is its significant loss of 21.94% on the weekly chart. Given this trend, it is unlikely that SHIB will make a break from the market and rally. Rather, a recovery from here will follow a Bitcoin rise. However, one event that could trigger a recovery is the Shibarium relaunch. According to lead developer Shytoshi Kusama, the layer 2 network could be gearing up for a relaunch in the coming days. Follow Best Owie on Twitter for market insights, updates, and the occasional funny tweet… Featured image from Analytics Insight, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="p2">Off the back of the much-anticipated <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/shib-burn-up-64-shibarium-launch/" rel="nofollow">Shibarium launch</a>, the SHIB burn rate has seen a tremendous rise. This surge in the burn rate comes despite the Layer 2 blockchain running into problems on the day of its launch last week, and still being in private mode. But while it could point to renewed vigor among the meme coin’s investors, something else seems to be driving this accelerated burn rate.</p>
<h2 class="p2">SHIB Burn Rate Is Up 1,108% In One Day</h2>
<p class="p2">According to data from <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/shiba-inu-community-ramps-up-burn/" rel="nofollow">Shiba Inu burn</a> tracking website Shibburn, there has been a remarkable increase in burn rate in the last 24 hours compared to the prior day. In total, there have been over 1.046 billion tokens burned, which translates to a 1,108.78% increase during this timeframe.</p>

<p class="p2">This is in stark contrast to the previous day’s figures which came out at around 100 million tokens burned. However, while the jump in burn rate is interesting, the address doing most of the SHIB burn is even more interesting.</p>
<p class="p2">Looking at the burn addresses posted by Shibburn, one address keeps popping up and that is the 0x4be2 address. A quick look on-chain revealed that this address is actually the <a href="https://etherscan.io/address/0x4be2b2c45b432ba362f198c08094017b61e3bdc6" rel="nofollow">contract address</a> for the <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/shib-burn-up-64-shibarium-launch/" rel="nofollow">MARSWAP (MSWAP) token</a>.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-548397 aligncenter" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot-2023-08-22-at-13.11.49.png?w=460&#038;resize=460%2C292" alt="SHIB burn" width="460" height="292" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot-2023-08-22-at-13.11.49.png?w=2514 2514w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot-2023-08-22-at-13.11.49.png?w=460&#038;resize=460%2C292 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot-2023-08-22-at-13.11.49.png?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot-2023-08-22-at-13.11.49.png?w=860 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot-2023-08-22-at-13.11.49.png?w=1536 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot-2023-08-22-at-13.11.49.png?w=2048 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot-2023-08-22-at-13.11.49.png?w=750 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot-2023-08-22-at-13.11.49.png?w=1140 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px" data-recalc-dims="1"/></p>

<p class="p2">This token seems to dedicate a portion of fees generated from transactions toward SHIB burn and as it gains popularity, the number of SHIB tokens being burned has jumped. So far, Marswap accounts for about 40% of burnt tokens. But a single address, 0xcf6d, which is the <a href="https://etherscan.io/address/0xcf6daab95c476106eca715d48de4b13287ffdeaa" rel="nofollow">ShibaSwap LP Token (SSLP)</a> contract address, burned 418,719,732 tokens in what has been the single largest burn event in the last day.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/Obdskqp2/" alt="Shiba Inu (SHIB) price chart from Tradingview.com (Shibarium launch)" width="2884" height="1746"/></p>

<h2 class="p2">How Is The Token Price Responding?</h2>
<p class="p2">Despite the marked increase in the SHIB burn rate, the price of the meme coin has not responded as positively as expected. The token price seems to be keeping in line with the general crypto market sentiment and continues to trade in the red.</p>

<p class="p2">Although there has been a <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/shib-price-surges-by-20-burn-rate-spikes-by-613/" rel="nofollow">small shift</a> in the last hour at the time of this writing, with SHIB’s price moving up a meager 0.16%, its price is still taking losses of 1.48% on the daily chart. Even more concerning is its significant loss of 21.94% on the weekly chart. Given this trend, it is unlikely that SHIB will make a break from the market and rally. Rather, a recovery from here will follow a Bitcoin rise.</p>
<p class="p2">However, one event that could trigger a recovery is the Shibarium relaunch. According to lead developer <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/shiba-inu-when-shibarium-relaunch-public/" rel="nofollow">Shytoshi Kusama</a>, the layer 2 network could be gearing up for a relaunch in the coming days.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SHIB-burn.jpeg?fit=460%2C256" width="460" height="256" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">548386</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>99.5% Of AVAX Holders In Loss, As Avalanche Bears Thirst For More Blood</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/avalanche/99-5-of-avax-holders-in-loss-as-avalanche-bears-thirst-blood/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Opeyemi Sule]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 22:00:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Avalanche]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Avalanche Bears]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AVAX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AVAX Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AVAXUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Token Unlocks]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=548384</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Avalanche token (AVAX), like most other altcoins, felt the bearish impact of the general market downturn, which resulted in a billion-dollar liquidation in the crypto market. Historical price data, however, shows that AVAX has been experiencing selling pressure long before this recent market crash. As expected, the struggling price of the Avalanche token has also been reflected in the portfolio of the cryptocurrency&#8217;s investors, who seem to be drowning in losses at the moment. AVAX Holders In Profit Reach All-Time Low: IntoTheBlock On Tuesday, August 22, market intelligence platform IntoTheBlock revealed &#8211; via a post on X (formerly Twitter) &#8211; that the number of AVAX holders in profit is at an all-time low.  According to IntoTheBlock data, approximately 99.5% of AVAX holders are at a loss. This metric implies that nearly all investors in this cryptocurrency bought at a higher price and are currently holding at a loss due to the sustained bearish trend. Related Reading: XRP About-Face Sparks Another Descent – What Lies Ahead? From a historical perspective, AVAX holders have witnessed similar levels of loss in the past, albeit not to this extent. The on-chain tracker reported that the number of AVAX holders in profit was almost as low in June and December 2022. It is worth noting that these losses are unrealized, and they only become real when the Avalanche tokens &#8211; being held &#8211; are traded off. Although a high number of crypto holders in loss is not exactly a positive signal, it can be an indication that investors are yet to lose faith in a token and may even be banking on a recovery. Avalanche Price Dips 17% In A Single Week As mentioned earlier, the AVAX price has been struggling long before the recent market downturn, down by 52% from its yearly high of 21.37%. Unfortunately, the Avalanche market has been in a steep decline since notching a swing high in April. In the past week, which coincided with the $1-billion market liquidation, AVAX has lost more than 17% of its value. Furthermore, a broader look at the market data shows that the token is on a nearly 25% decline in the last 30 days. Related Reading: XRP Price Shows Confluence Of Bearish Factors and Could Decline Again The future doesn&#8217;t look particularly bright for AVAX, especially with its upcoming token unlock event. A total of 9.54 million tokens is set to be unlocked on August 26, with a large portion of the unlocked tokens expected to hit the open market, potentially exacerbating the struggles of the Avalanche price. According to CoinGecko data, AVAX is currently valued at $10.20, registering a 3.5% price decline in the past 24 hours. With a market cap of roughly $3.52 billion, the Avalanche token ranks as the 22nd-largest cryptocurrency in the market. Avalanche price suffers further decline on daily timeframe &#124; Source: AVAXUSDT chart on TradingView Featured image from Investopedia, chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Avalanche token (AVAX), like most other altcoins, felt the bearish impact of the general market downturn, which resulted in a billion-dollar liquidation in the crypto market. Historical price data, however, shows that AVAX has been <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/all/turbulent-avax-price-trends-and-fading-trading-activity-what-to-expect/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">experiencing selling pressure</a> long before this recent market crash.</p>
<p>As expected, the struggling price of the Avalanche token has also been reflected in the portfolio of the cryptocurrency&#8217;s investors, who seem to be drowning in losses at the moment.</p>
<h2>AVAX Holders In Profit Reach All-Time Low: IntoTheBlock</h2>
<p>On Tuesday, August 22, market intelligence platform IntoTheBlock revealed &#8211; via <a href="https://twitter.com/intotheblock/status/1693925000909086796" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">a post on X</a> (formerly Twitter) &#8211; that the number of AVAX holders in profit is at an all-time low. </p>
<p>According to IntoTheBlock data, approximately 99.5% of AVAX holders are at a loss. This metric implies that nearly all investors in this cryptocurrency bought at a higher price and are currently holding at a loss due to the sustained bearish trend.</p>

<p>From a historical perspective, AVAX holders have witnessed similar levels of loss in the past, albeit not to this extent. The on-chain tracker reported that the number of AVAX holders in profit was almost as low in June and December 2022.</p>
<p>It is worth noting that these losses are unrealized, and they only become real when the Avalanche tokens &#8211; being held &#8211; are traded off. Although a high number of crypto holders in loss is not exactly a positive signal, it can be an indication that investors are yet to lose faith in a token and may even be banking on a recovery.</p>
<h2>Avalanche Price Dips 17% In A Single Week</h2>
<p>As mentioned earlier, the AVAX price has been struggling long before the recent market downturn, down by 52% from its yearly high of 21.37%. Unfortunately, the Avalanche market has been in a steep decline since notching a swing high in April.</p>
<p>In the past week, which coincided with the $1-billion market liquidation, AVAX has lost more than 17% of its value. Furthermore, a broader look at the market data shows that the token is on a nearly 25% decline in the last 30 days.</p>

<p>The future doesn&#8217;t look particularly bright for AVAX, especially with its <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/avax/avax-price-bucks-under-the-pressure-of-upcoming-102-million-token-unlock/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">upcoming token unlock event</a>. A total of 9.54 million tokens is set to be unlocked on August 26, with a large portion of the unlocked tokens expected to hit the open market, potentially exacerbating the struggles of the Avalanche price.</p>
<p>According to CoinGecko data, AVAX is currently valued at $10.20, registering a 3.5% price decline in the past 24 hours. With a market cap of roughly $3.52 billion, the Avalanche token ranks as the 22nd-largest cryptocurrency in the market.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/5Y447eRF/" alt="AVAX" width="1013" height="595"/></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/bear-market.jpeg?fit=460%2C298" width="460" height="298" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">548384</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>By The Numbers: Deciphering XRP&#8217;s Lost Momentum Amid The SEC Lawsuit</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/by-the-numbers-deciphering-xrp-lost-momentum/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samuel Edyme]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 21:00:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrp]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrpusdt]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=548441</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The US Securities and Exchange Commission&#8217;s (SEC) legal tussle with Ripple over the XRP token may have significantly set its trajectory back in the US market. Crypto lawyer John Deaton explained this in an X (formerly known as Twiter) post uploaded earlier today, shedding light on the ramifications of the SEC&#8217;s lawsuit on XRP&#8217;s potential adoption in the US. You could NEVER underestimate the damage the SEC’s lawsuit has caused &#8211; NOT ONLY AGAINST RIPPLE &#8211; BUT #XRP. THREE YEARS OF ADOPTION &#8211; that’s what it’s caused. Just how long is 3 yrs &#8211; in crypto years? People seem to forget how much Coinbase promoted #XRP before the lawsuit.… https://t.co/1fZ3r8WCSd pic.twitter.com/GLu4kFUU38 — John E Deaton (@JohnEDeaton1) August 22, 2023 The comments come when discussions about regulatory clarity in crypto are more intense than ever, with token holders striving for clearer guidelines in the North American country. Related Reading: XRP About-Face Sparks Another Descent – What Lies Ahead? The Coinbase Connection According to Deaton, Coinbase, one of the pioneering cryptocurrency exchanges in the US, was at the forefront of promoting XRP before regulatory challenges arose. Deaton pointed out that before listing XRP, Coinbase proactively reached out to the SEC for clarity. In a meeting held in January 2019, Coinbase presented its regulatory framework for evaluating digital assets – a framework that had previously garnered admiration from senior SEC staff. With no objections raised by the SEC, Coinbase proceeded to list XRP the following month. In fact, in January 2019 Coinbase asked for and got a meeting with the @SECGov to SPECIFICALLY DISCUSS THE REGULATORY STATUS OF #XRP! Coinbase explained to the SEC that Coinbase had evaluated #XRP and ran it through Coinbase’s stringent regulatory framework for digital assets. — John E Deaton (@JohnEDeaton1) August 22, 2023 Furthermore, the fact wasn&#8217;t just restricted to Coinbase. Payment processing giant MoneyGram, which had established a partnership with Ripple for remittances, disclosed its intentions to integrate with the XRP  Ledger through a formal filing with the SEC. Much like the Coinbase instance, MoneyGram didn’t receive any complaint from the regulatory body either, but the ensuing legal battle halted the company&#8217;s plans.  The Controversial Lawsuit And Its Implications For XRP Contrary to these initial interactions, the SEC filed a lawsuit against Ripple in December 2020. Deaton emphasized that several industry stakeholders, including the lawyers at MoneyGram and Coinbase, assessed XRP and determined it was not a security. Yet, the SEC&#8217;s lawsuit against Ripple painted a contrasting narrative. Amazingly, despite all the above (and so much more), on December 22, 2020, less than 2 years AFTER Coinbase met with the SEC about #XRP, and 18 months AFTER MoneyGram disclosed to the SEC it was utilizing #XRP, and despite lawyers at the SEC not concluding #XRP was a security in… — John E Deaton (@JohnEDeaton1) August 22, 2023 The following legal battle created was felt across the crypto industry. It raised questions about the regulatory landscape and brought forth discussions about the nature of cryptocurrencies and how they are classified in the US.  While Ripple has seen commendable success outside the US, Deaton underscored that the lawsuit undeniably hindered XRP&#8217;s adoption within the country. Related Reading: XRP Price Shows Confluence Of Bearish Factors and Could Decline Again From Deaton&#8217;s perspective, the evidence gathered over the past three years suggested that the lawsuit may have been part of a strategy. While it remains speculative to conclude the exact motivations behind the SEC&#8217;s actions, the impact on XRP&#8217;s US adoption and the broader crypto market has been palpable. Deaton concluded: It is so clear the lawsuit was used as a weapon. I said it only 9 days after the Ripple lawsuit in a federal pleading, when I filed the Writ of Mandamus against the SEC, and all the evidence uncovered during the last 3 years proves it to be true. Featured image from Unsplash, Chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The US Securities and Exchange Commission&#8217;s (SEC) legal tussle with Ripple over the XRP token may have significantly set its trajectory back in the US market. Crypto lawyer John Deaton <a href="https://twitter.com/JohnEDeaton1/status/1693798126371422237?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">explained</a> this in an X (formerly known as Twiter) post uploaded earlier today, shedding light on the ramifications of the SEC&#8217;s lawsuit on XRP&#8217;s <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/altcoin/xrp-whales-accumulate-can-price-recover-now/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">potential adoption</a> in the US. </p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">You could NEVER underestimate the damage the SEC’s lawsuit has caused &#8211; NOT ONLY AGAINST RIPPLE &#8211; BUT <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/XRP?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#XRP</a>. THREE YEARS OF ADOPTION &#8211; that’s what it’s caused.</p>
<p>Just how long is 3 yrs &#8211; in crypto years?</p>
<p>People seem to forget how much Coinbase promoted <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/XRP?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#XRP</a> before the lawsuit.… <a href="https://t.co/1fZ3r8WCSd" rel="nofollow">https://t.co/1fZ3r8WCSd</a> <a href="https://t.co/GLu4kFUU38" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/GLu4kFUU38</a></p>
<p>— John E Deaton (@JohnEDeaton1) <a href="https://twitter.com/JohnEDeaton1/status/1693798126371422237?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">August 22, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p>The comments come when discussions about regulatory clarity in crypto are more intense than ever, with token holders <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/wixpool-is-preparing-for-regulation-and-preparing-documents-for-reporting-to-the-sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">striving for clearer guidelines</a> in the North American country.</p>

<h2>The Coinbase Connection</h2>
<p>According to Deaton, Coinbase, one of the pioneering cryptocurrency exchanges in the US, was at the forefront of promoting XRP before regulatory challenges arose. Deaton pointed out that before listing XRP, Coinbase proactively reached out to the SEC for clarity.</p>
<p>In a meeting held in January 2019, Coinbase presented its regulatory framework for evaluating digital assets – a framework that had previously garnered admiration from senior SEC staff. With no objections raised by the SEC, Coinbase proceeded to list XRP the following month.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">In fact, in January 2019 Coinbase asked for and got a meeting with the <a href="https://twitter.com/SECGov?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">@SECGov</a> to SPECIFICALLY DISCUSS THE REGULATORY STATUS OF <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/XRP?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#XRP</a>!</p>
<p>Coinbase explained to the SEC that Coinbase had evaluated <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/XRP?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#XRP</a> and ran it through Coinbase’s stringent regulatory framework for digital assets.</p>
<p>— John E Deaton (@JohnEDeaton1) <a href="https://twitter.com/JohnEDeaton1/status/1693798194927239647?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">August 22, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p>Furthermore, the fact wasn&#8217;t just restricted to Coinbase. Payment processing giant MoneyGram, which had established a partnership with Ripple for remittances, <a href="https://twitter.com/JohnEDeaton1/status/1693798233535857025?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">disclosed</a> its intentions to integrate with the XRP  Ledger through a formal filing with the SEC. </p>
<p>Much like the Coinbase instance, MoneyGram didn’t receive any complaint from the regulatory body either, but the ensuing legal battle halted the company&#8217;s plans. </p>
<h2>The Controversial Lawsuit And Its Implications For XRP</h2>
<p>Contrary to these initial interactions, the SEC <a href="https://www.sec.gov/news/press-release/2020-338" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">filed a lawsuit</a> against Ripple in December 2020. Deaton emphasized that several<a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/ripple-2/mastercard-partners-ripple-xrp-falls-below-pre-sec-ruling/" target="_blank" rel="noopener "> industry stakeholders</a>, including the lawyers at MoneyGram and Coinbase, assessed XRP and determined it was not a security. Yet, the SEC&#8217;s lawsuit against Ripple painted a contrasting narrative.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Amazingly, despite all the above (and so much more), on December 22, 2020, less than 2 years AFTER Coinbase met with the SEC about <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/XRP?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#XRP</a>, and 18 months AFTER MoneyGram disclosed to the SEC it was utilizing <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/XRP?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#XRP</a>, and despite lawyers at the SEC not concluding <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/XRP?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#XRP</a> was a security in…</p>
<p>— John E Deaton (@JohnEDeaton1) <a href="https://twitter.com/JohnEDeaton1/status/1693798233535857025?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">August 22, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p>The following legal battle created was felt across the crypto industry. It raised questions about the regulatory landscape and brought forth discussions about the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/xrp-price-at-a-crossroad-will-0-5-support-trigger-a-correction-shift/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">nature of cryptocurrencies</a> and how they are classified in the US. </p>
<p>While Ripple has seen commendable success outside the US, Deaton underscored that the lawsuit undeniably hindered XRP&#8217;s adoption within the country.</p>

<p>From Deaton&#8217;s perspective, the evidence gathered over the past three years suggested that the lawsuit may have been part of a strategy. While it remains speculative to conclude the exact motivations behind the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/ripple-2/xrp-pain-ripple-vs-sec-case/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">SEC&#8217;s actions</a>, the impact on XRP&#8217;s US adoption and the broader crypto market has been palpable.</p>
<p>Deaton concluded:</p>
<blockquote><p>It is so clear the lawsuit was used as a weapon. I said it only 9 days after the Ripple lawsuit in a federal pleading, when I filed the Writ of Mandamus against the SEC, and all the evidence uncovered during the last 3 years proves it to be true.</p></blockquote>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/pZ63Ej89/" alt="XRP price chart on TradingView" width="2770" height="1408"/>
<p>Featured image from Unsplash, Chart from TradingView</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/XRP-2.jpeg?fit=460%2C329" width="460" height="329" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">548441</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Will Bitcoin Show A Repeat Of The March Rebound?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-show-repeat-of-the-march-rebound/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hououin Kyouma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 20:00:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin crash]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin March Rebound]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Rebound]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=548431</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Will Bitcoin observe a repeat of the rebound that took place after the crash back in March? Here&#8217;s what this on-chain metric suggests. Bitcoin Short-Term Holder SOPR Is Showing A Pattern Similar To March As an analyst in a CryptoQuant post explained, if the BTC short-term holder SOPR crosses above 1 in the coming days, a rebound might occur. The &#8220;Spent Output Profit Ratio&#8221; (SOPR) here refers to an indicator that tells us whether the investors are selling their Bitcoin at a profit or a loss right now. When the value of this metric is greater than 1, it means that the average holder is currently moving their coins at a profit. On the other hand, values under this threshold imply that loss-taking is the dominant behavior in the market. The SOPR being precisely equal to one naturally suggests that the investors are just breaking-even on their selling currently, as the total amount of profits realized in the market is precisely canceling out the losses. In the context of the current discussion, the SOPR for only a specific market segment is of interest. Namely, the short-term holder (STH) SOPR is the relevant metric. Here is a chart that shows the trend in the 7-day simple moving average (SMA) Bitcoin STH SOPR over the past few months: Looks like the 7-day SMA value of the metric has been below the 1 mark in recent days &#124; Source: CryptoQuant The STH group includes investors who purchased their BTC less than 155 days ago. This cohort makes up one of the two main segments of the market, the other side being the &#8220;long-term holders&#8221; (LTHs). As displayed in the graph, the 7-day Bitcoin STH SOPR had been floating around the neutral mark before the recent crash, but following it, the metric has plunged into the loss territory. This would suggest that the STHs have been panic-selling at a loss after they witnessed the cryptocurrency register a deep drawdown. Related Reading: Bitcoin Dip Worth Buying? What Market Sentiment Suggests The chart shows that the crash back in March of this year also pushed the STHs into selling at a loss. The lowest value that the 7-day STH SOPR has seen in the current crash so far has been similar to what the March crash observed. Historically, capitulation has allowed the asset to form bottoms, as in such events, the weak hands exit the market, and the more persistent investors may pick up their coins. This effect seems to have worked in March, as the coin hit its bottom during the STHs&#8217; capitulation. As the loss selling slowed down, Bitcoin rebounded in speculator fashion, as its price jumped below $20,000 to near the $30,000 mark. Related Reading: Will Bitcoin Retest $20,500 Again? This Pattern May Suggest So Currently, the STHs&#8217; loss selling is slowing down, as the metric&#8217;s value is gradually rising. The latest capitulation may have also allowed BTC to form a bottom this time. It remains to be seen whether that was the case, and if Bitcoin can show a rebound similar to back in March. BTC Price At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading around $26,000, down 11% in the last week. BTC has been hanging on around the $26,000 level &#124; Source: BTCUSD on TradingView Featured image from Yiğit Ali Atasoy on Unsplash.com, charts from TradingView.com, CryptoQuant.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Will Bitcoin observe a repeat of the rebound that took place after the crash back in March? Here&#8217;s what this on-chain metric suggests.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Short-Term Holder SOPR Is Showing A Pattern Similar To March</h2>
<p>As an analyst in a CryptoQuant <a href="https://cryptoquant.com/insights/quicktake/64e4763f53ebba2eeba439b4-Analysis-of-the-STH-SOPR-Short-Term-Holder-Spent-Output-Profit-Ratio" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">post</a> explained, if the BTC short-term holder SOPR crosses above 1 in the coming days, a rebound might occur. The &#8220;<a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-sopr-bounces-into-profit-zone-what-mean/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Spent Output Profit Ratio</a>&#8221; (SOPR) here refers to an indicator that tells us whether the investors are selling their Bitcoin at a profit or a loss right now.</p>
<p>When the value of this metric is greater than 1, it means that the average holder is currently moving their coins at a profit. On the other hand, values under this threshold imply that loss-taking is the dominant behavior in the market.</p>
<p>The SOPR being precisely equal to one naturally suggests that the investors are just breaking-even on their selling currently, as the total amount of profits realized in the market is precisely canceling out the losses.</p>
<p>In the context of the current discussion, the SOPR for only a specific market segment is of interest. Namely, the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-short-term-holders-exchange-inflows-price/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">short-term holder</a> (STH) SOPR is the relevant metric.</p>
<p>Here is a chart that shows the trend in the 7-day simple moving average (SMA) Bitcoin STH SOPR over the past few months:</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone aligncenter" src="https://i0.wp.com/img.cryptoquant.com/280562/quicktake/H1vvm2cl_3c088e5d30d8db877c7a485a9a7d4bd89dcdc5b567ead7964c1b3418288ecd8b.png?resize=1280%2C806&#038;ssl=1" alt="Bitcoin STH SOPR" width="1280" height="806"  data-recalc-dims="1"/></p>

<p>The STH group includes investors who purchased their BTC less than 155 days ago. This cohort makes up one of the two main segments of the market, the other side being the &#8220;<a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/litecoin/litecoin-long-term-holders-smartly-exited-before-halving-data-shows/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">long-term holders</a>&#8221; (LTHs).</p>
<p>As displayed in the graph, the 7-day Bitcoin STH SOPR had been floating around the neutral mark before the recent crash, but following it, the metric has plunged into the loss territory. This would suggest that the STHs have been panic-selling at a loss after they witnessed the cryptocurrency register a deep drawdown.</p>

<p>The chart shows that the crash back in March of this year also pushed the STHs into selling at a loss. The lowest value that the 7-day STH SOPR has seen in the current crash so far has been similar to what the March crash observed.</p>
<p>Historically, capitulation has allowed the asset to form bottoms, as in such events, the weak hands exit the market, and the more persistent investors may pick up their coins.</p>
<p>This effect seems to have worked in March, as the coin hit its bottom during the STHs&#8217; capitulation. As the loss selling slowed down, Bitcoin rebounded in speculator fashion, as its price jumped below $20,000 to near the $30,000 mark.</p>

<p>Currently, the STHs&#8217; loss selling is slowing down, as the metric&#8217;s value is gradually rising. The latest capitulation may have also allowed BTC to form a bottom this time. It remains to be seen whether that was the case, and if Bitcoin can show a rebound similar to back in March.</p>
<h2>BTC Price</h2>
<p>At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading around $26,000, down 11% in the last week.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium aligncenter" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/qbIgwN67/" alt="Bitcoin Price Chart" width="1534" height="877"/></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/yigit-ali-atasoy-z1jggXh29_Q-unsplash.jpg?fit=460%2C259" width="460" height="259" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">548431</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Optimism (OP) Continues Market Recovery As Network Whales Triple Holdings</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/optimism-2/optimism-op-continues-market-recovery-as-network-whales-triple-holdings/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Semilore Faleti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 19:00:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Optimism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum upgrade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[OP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[optimism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Whale]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=548420</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Ethereum layer 2 network Optimism (OP) has maintained its market recovery in the last few days, recording a 5.57% gain over the last 24 hours, based on data from CoinMarketCap. Since hitting the $1.31 price mark, Optimism has embarked on an upward curve, looking set to return to the high price levels seen at the start of August. Optimism Major Investors Boost Holdings By 300% In The Last Year Among many positives for Optimism, the on-chain analytics firm, Santiment has also revealed another significant development for the altcoin in terms of investors&#8217; interest. Related Reading: Optimism (OP) Rides The Wave Of Today’s Crypto Surge With 15% Rally According to a report by Santiment on August 21, whale and shark addresses on Optimism holding between 100,000-10,000,000 OP have consistently increased their amount of holdings over the last 12 months. The analytics team reported that these investors currently hold 505.91 million OP worth around $781.9 million. Remarkably, this stake constitutes a significant 69.6% of Optimism’s total market shares. In addition to this investment growth, Santiment also noted that Optimism recorded 22,900 active addresses on Monday, its fifth-highest value of their metric in 2023.  Behind the Growing OP Accumulation Trend In line with Santiment’s report on the increasing OP accumulation by Optimism major investors, Spot On Chain, another blockchain analytics platform, has recently provided a deeper insight into this trend. According to a blog post by Spot On Chain, address 0x011, which they suspect belongs to popular venture capital firm Amber Group, has purchased 3.73 million OP &#8211; valued at $5.71 million &#8211; from Binance in the last 24 hours.  The analytics team states that this particular address has accumulated 8.14 million OP, valued at $12.7 million over the last 19 days.  Interestingly, Spot On Chain proposes that the reason behind OP’s recent accumulation could be the upcoming Ethereum Cancun/Deneb upgrade. Related Reading: Altcoin Season In Limbo As Bitcoin Dominance Bounces Off Key Support In June, Christine Kim, vice president of Galaxy Digital’s research team, stated that this impending Ethereum network upgrade &#8211; slated for the second half of 2023 &#8211; could boost the network capacity of layer two solutions such as Arbitrum and Optimism by 100-fold. At the time of writing, Optimism is trading at $1.56, with a 0.29% decline in the last hour. Albeit, the token’s trading volume is up 54.83% in the last 24 hours and is valued at $137.08 million. OP trading at $1.56 on the daily chart &#124; Source: OPUSD chart on Tradingview.com Featured image from CoinMarketCap, chart from Tradingview.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ethereum layer 2 network Optimism (OP) has maintained its market recovery in the last few days, recording a 5.57% gain over the last 24 hours, based on <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/optimism-ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">data from CoinMarketCap</a>.</p>
<p>Since hitting the $1.31 price mark, Optimism has embarked on an upward curve, looking set to return to the high price levels<a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/optimism/optimism-op-climbs-over-10-on-weekly-chart-will-the-rally-last/" target="_blank" rel="noopener "> seen at the start of August</a>.</p>
<h2>Optimism Major Investors Boost Holdings By 300% In The Last Year</h2>
<p>Among many positives for Optimism, the on-chain analytics firm, Santiment has also revealed another significant development for the altcoin in terms of investors&#8217; interest.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/optimism-rides-wave-of-crypto-surge/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Optimism (OP) Rides The Wave Of Today’s Crypto Surge With 15% Rally</a></p>
<p>According to a<a href="https://twitter.com/santimentfeed/status/1693743335113109783?s=46&amp;t=JAUmthpFclo8jS4VJkm3DQ" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow"> report by Santiment</a> on August 21, whale and shark addresses on Optimism holding between 100,000-10,000,000 OP have consistently increased their amount of holdings over the last 12 months.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr"><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f433.png" alt="🐳" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f4c8.png" alt="📈" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Optimism?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#Optimism</a> is seeing some positive signs today, as its +5% pump is accompanied by 22.9K active addresses, among its best days of 2023. Additionally, key whale &amp; shark addresses with 100K-10M <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24OP&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$OP</a> continue holding a high level, currently worth $781.9M. <a href="https://t.co/VOE7uqOQpN" rel="nofollow">https://t.co/VOE7uqOQpN</a> <a href="https://t.co/Ie0oX2pJT0" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/Ie0oX2pJT0</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Santiment (@santimentfeed) <a href="https://twitter.com/santimentfeed/status/1693743335113109783?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">August 21, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p></p>
<p>The analytics team reported that these investors currently hold 505.91 million OP worth around $781.9 million. Remarkably, this stake constitutes a significant 69.6% of Optimism’s total market shares.</p>
<p>In addition to this investment growth, Santiment also noted that Optimism recorded 22,900 active addresses on Monday, its fifth-highest value of their metric in 2023. </p>
<h2>Behind the Growing OP Accumulation Trend</h2>
<p>In line with Santiment’s report on the increasing OP accumulation by Optimism major investors, Spot On Chain, another blockchain analytics platform, has recently provided a deeper insight into this trend.</p>
<p>According to a<a href="https://platform.spotonchain.ai/signal-details/amber-group-allegedly-accumulated-op-in-mass-485" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow"> blog post</a> by Spot On Chain, address 0x011, which they suspect belongs to popular venture capital firm Amber Group, has purchased 3.73 million OP &#8211; valued at $5.71 million &#8211; from Binance in the last 24 hours. </p>
<p>The analytics team states that this particular address has accumulated 8.14 million OP, valued at $12.7 million over the last 19 days. </p>
<p>Interestingly, Spot On Chain proposes that the reason behind OP’s recent accumulation could be the upcoming Ethereum Cancun/Deneb upgrade.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/altcoin-season-bitcoin-dominance-holds-key-support/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Altcoin Season In Limbo As Bitcoin Dominance Bounces Off Key Support</a></p>
<p>In June, Christine Kim, vice president of Galaxy Digital’s research team, <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/ethereum-cancun-upgrade-arbitrum-optimism-will-profit/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">stated</a> that this impending Ethereum network upgrade &#8211; slated for the second half of 2023 &#8211; could boost the network capacity of layer two solutions such as Arbitrum and Optimism by 100-fold.</p>
<p>At the time of writing, Optimism is trading at $1.56, with a 0.29% decline in the last hour. Albeit, the token’s trading volume is up 54.83% in the last 24 hours and is valued at $137.08 million.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/R6Mfn0p7/" alt="Optimism" width="1480" height="906"/></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/3a84c43c479640ccaa066b2e219e2ebe.png?fit=460%2C259" width="460" height="259" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">548420</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Shiba Inu Price Challenge: Gunning For $0.00001 After Shibarium Snag</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/all/shib-challenge-gunning-for-0-00001/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 18:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[All]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[meme coins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price action]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIB price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shiba Inu]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shibarium]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=548378</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Shiba Inu (SHIB) has recently witnessed a tumultuous journey marked by a sharp reversal from its peak at $0.00001136.  This reversal, known as a V-top, has raised significant concerns within the crypto community and the trading floors. But what exactly does this term mean, and what implications does it hold for SHIB investors and enthusiasts? A V-top reversal is a distinctive price pattern observed in technical analysis. It occurs when a cryptocurrency&#8217;s value experiences a rapid ascent to a peak, followed by an equally swift decline.   Related Reading: Polygon (MATIC) At June Lows Again – Prospects For Bullish Recovery? In SHIB&#8217;s case, this sharp reversal saw its value plummet from $0.00001136, a striking deviation from its recent surge. This downward spiral has caused the current price to stand at $0.00000789 according to CoinGecko data, reflecting a 4.5% drop within 24 hours and a staggering 23.1% slump over the past seven days. Shiba Inu: The Intersection Of FUD And Network Activity The timing of this massive price slump coincides with a period of uncertainty and anxiety within the SHIB community, centered around the Shibarium Layer 2 launch. The emergence of fear, uncertainty, and doubt (FUD) has cast shadows over the project, leading to heightened caution among SHIB holders.  Similar to Polygon, Ethereum, and other blockchains, Shibarium is open for anyone to build on. Regrettably, this also provides an avenue for bad actors to develop scam dApps and rug-pull tokens, among other things. The mere incorporation of the term &#8220;Shibarium&#8221; or &#8220;Shib&#8221; in… pic.twitter.com/AiNqORi7J2 — 𝐋𝐔𝐂𝐈𝐄 &#124; Summer of Shibarium (@LucieSHIB) August 16, 2023 Lucie Shib, a prominent figure in the Shiba Inu executive team, further accentuated these concerns by issuing warnings about potential risks of exploitation. As a result of these apprehensions, SHIB holders have noticeably scaled back their transactional engagement over the past week. A closer look at CryptoQuant data highlights a stark contrast: on August 12, the SHIB Transaction Count exceeded 16,500, pushing the price to a four-month peak.  Source: CryptoQuant However, this number dropped drastically to a mere 5,601 transactions on August 21, signifying a substantial 66% decline in network activity. This trend has been fueled not only by Shibarium FUD but also by the broader downtrend sweeping through the crypto market. Related Reading: XRP About-Face Sparks Another Descent – What Lies Ahead? Shiba Inu (SHIB) is currently trading at $0.00000795. Chart: TradingView.com A Glimpse At SHIB Demand And Potential Recovery Meanwhile, recent trading data from multiple cryptocurrency exchanges indicates that Shiba Inu enthusiasts are actively placing purchase orders, indicating their optimism for a positive market shift. This reflects their confidence in a potential bullish reversal and their active engagement in shaping Shiba Inu&#8217;s future. Source: IntoTheBlock Optimistic investors have initiated live purchase requests for nearly 2 trillion SHIB tokens, marking a rise of 400 billion compared to the 1.5 trillion SHIB orders registered the previous week. In contrast, the quantity of sell orders has maintained its position at 1.2 trillion SHIB tokens, showing little movement. Related Reading: XRP About-Face Sparks Another Descent – What Lies Ahead? This intriguing observation suggests that, despite prevailing uncertainties, market demand for SHIB remains strong, as investors potentially await the clearance of FUD clouds. Looking ahead, the resolution of challenges surrounding the Shibarium L2 network could pave the way for SHIB to regain momentum and reclaim the $0.000011 threshold.  (This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk). Featured image from Sniper Country]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Shiba Inu (SHIB) has recently witnessed a tumultuous journey marked by a sharp reversal from its peak at $0.00001136. </p>
<p>This reversal, known as a V-top, has raised significant concerns within the crypto community and the trading floors. But what exactly does this term mean, and what implications does it hold for SHIB investors and enthusiasts?</p>
<p>A V-top reversal is a distinctive price pattern observed in technical analysis. It occurs when a cryptocurrency&#8217;s value experiences a rapid ascent to a peak, followed by an equally swift decline.  </p>

<p>In SHIB&#8217;s case, this sharp reversal saw its value plummet from $0.00001136, a striking deviation from its recent surge. This downward spiral has caused the current price to stand at $0.00000789 according to <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/shiba-inu" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">CoinGecko data</a>, reflecting a 4.5% drop within 24 hours and a staggering 23.1% slump over the past seven days.</p>
<h2><strong>Shiba Inu: The Intersection Of FUD And Network Activity</strong></h2>
<p>The timing of this massive price slump coincides with a period of uncertainty and anxiety within the SHIB community, centered around the Shibarium Layer 2 launch. The emergence of fear, uncertainty, and doubt (FUD) has cast shadows over the project, leading to heightened caution among SHIB holders. </p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Similar to Polygon, Ethereum, and other blockchains, Shibarium is open for anyone to build on. Regrettably, this also provides an avenue for bad actors to develop scam dApps and rug-pull tokens, among other things.</p>
<p>The mere incorporation of the term &#8220;Shibarium&#8221; or &#8220;Shib&#8221; in… <a href="https://t.co/AiNqORi7J2" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/AiNqORi7J2</a></p>
<p>— 𝐋𝐔𝐂𝐈𝐄 | Summer of Shibarium (@LucieSHIB) <a href="https://twitter.com/LucieSHIB/status/1691784869628555764?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">August 16, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p>Lucie Shib, a prominent figure in the Shiba Inu executive team, further accentuated these concerns by <a href="https://twitter.com/LucieSHIB/status/1691784869628555764" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">issuing warnings</a> about potential risks of exploitation.</p>
<p>As a result of these apprehensions, SHIB holders have noticeably scaled back their transactional engagement over the past week. A closer look at <a href="https://cryptoquant.com/asset/shib/chart/transactions/transaction-count-total?window=DAY&amp;sma=0&amp;ema=0&amp;priceScale=log&amp;metricScale=linear&amp;chartStyle=line" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">CryptoQuant data</a> highlights a stark contrast: on August 12, the SHIB Transaction Count exceeded 16,500, pushing the price to a four-month peak. </p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-548395 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-129.png?w=860&#038;resize=860%2C420" alt="" width="860" height="420" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-129.png?w=1443 1443w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-129.png?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-129.png?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-129.png?w=860&#038;resize=860%2C420 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-129.png?w=750 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-129.png?w=1140 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" data-recalc-dims="1"/></p>

<p>However, this number dropped drastically to a mere 5,601 transactions on August 21, signifying a substantial 66% decline in network activity. </p>
<p>This trend has been fueled not only by Shibarium FUD but also by the broader downtrend sweeping through the crypto market.</p>

<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/NlSjXmbh/" width="1835" height="893"/></p>

<h2><strong>A Glimpse At SHIB Demand And Potential Recovery</strong></h2>
<p>Meanwhile, recent trading data from multiple cryptocurrency exchanges indicates that Shiba Inu enthusiasts are actively placing purchase orders, indicating their optimism for a positive market shift. This reflects their confidence in a potential bullish reversal and their active engagement in shaping Shiba Inu&#8217;s future.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-548410" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-131.png?resize=676%2C255" alt="" width="676" height="255" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-131.png?resize=676%2C255?w=676 676w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-131.png?resize=676%2C255?w=460 460w" sizes="(max-width: 676px) 100vw, 676px" data-recalc-dims="1"/></p>

<p>Optimistic investors have initiated live purchase requests for nearly 2 trillion SHIB tokens, marking a rise of 400 billion compared to the 1.5 trillion SHIB orders registered the previous week. In contrast, the quantity of sell orders has maintained its position at 1.2 trillion SHIB tokens, showing little movement.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/all/xrp-about-face-sparks-another-descent-what-lies-ahead/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">XRP About-Face Sparks Another Descent – What Lies Ahead?</a></p>
<p>This intriguing observation suggests that, despite prevailing uncertainties, market <a href="https://coingape.com/markets/shib-price-analysis-can-0-000007-withstand-market-correction/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">demand for SHIB remains strong</a>, as investors potentially await the clearance of FUD clouds. </p>
<p>Looking ahead, the resolution of challenges surrounding the Shibarium L2 network could pave the way for SHIB to regain momentum and reclaim the $0.000011 threshold. </p>
<p><em>(This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk).</em></p>
<p><em>Featured image from Sniper Country</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-130.png?fit=460%2C306" width="460" height="306" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">548378</post-id>	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
