<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	 xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" >

<channel>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://newsbtc.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://newsbtc.com</link>
	<description>Bitcoin &#38; cryptocurrency news today, price &#38; technical analysis</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 22:25:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<link>https://newsbtc.com</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Ethereum Closes Near Its Next Profit Take Region As Bullish Momentum Continues</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/ethereum/ethereum-close-profit-region-as-bullish/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[anushsamal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 23:00:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=517169</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Ethereum price has been propelling itself considerably ever since Bitcoin crossed the $20,000 price mark. Over the last 24 hours, ETH has slightly moved down on its chart, depicting consolidated price action. Last week helped the Ethereum price move up by 6%. The coin finally broke past its consolidation at the $1,500 price level and has been moving north ever since. The technical outlook of the coin has pointed towards continued bullishness on the chart. Accumulation has increased substantially ever since Ethereum breached the $1,500 price level. Related Reading: Crypto Analyst Says Bitcoin Price Could See Another 30% Rally The chance of a price reversal cannot be ruled out just yet, as ETH was overbought and overvalued. Currently, Ethereum has secured $1,600 as the support level. The next price correction could help traders with buying opportunities. A price correction might not occur over the immediate trading sessions as demand for the coin remains quite high on the chart. Ethereum&#8217;s price might continue on the upside before the coin retraces. The market capitalization of Ethereum increased, which also reflected that the buying sentiment remained high. Ethereum Price Analysis: One-Day Chart ETH was exchanging hands at $1,620 at the time of writing. Immediate resistance for the coin stood at $1,690; it even corresponds to the 50% Fibonacci retracement level. A move above $1,690 will help Ethereum touch the $1,700 price mark. The $1,700 price mark is crucial, as touching or breaching this mark could mean continued bullish momentum for the crypto. ETH could even soar to $2,000 if the $1,700 price mark is crossed. This region will act as a profit-take region for traders. On the flip side, if the bullish momentum slows down, the first fall would be at $1,600 and then at $1,520. The amount of Ethereum traded in the last session was red, signifying a downtick in buying. Technical Analysis The altcoin was still in the overbought zone, which also means that Ethereum broke a multi-month record in terms of accumulation. The Relative Strength Index was parked a little below the 80-mark, which still signified heavy buying strength and bullishness. If demand stays at this level, bullish momentum will not fade out anytime soon. ETH was also trading above the 20-Simple Moving Average line, indicating that buyers were driving the price momentum. On the contrary, the 200-SMA line crossed the 20-SMA line, which implies that the coin might be headed for southbound price movement. As accumulation has remained at a record high for the coin, chances of a price pullback still remain for the altcoin. The Awesome Oscillator, which signifies price direction, displayed red histograms, which meant that these were sell signals for the altcoin. Related Reading: Dogecoin Price Technicals Suggest DOGE Must Clear $0.920 For Another Rally Sell signals can be accompanied by a fall in price. Ethereum may briefly fall in price before resuming its upward trend. The Directional Movement Index was still positive, as the +DI line (blue) was above the -DI line (orange). The Average Directional Index (red) shot past 40, which suggested that price direction would gain further strength, which will push ETH to break past its nearest price ceiling of $1,700. Featured Image From UnSplash, Charts From TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Ethereum price has been propelling itself considerably ever since Bitcoin crossed the $20,000 price mark. Over the last 24 hours, ETH has slightly moved down on its chart, depicting consolidated price action. Last week helped the Ethereum price move up by 6%.</p>
<p>The coin finally broke past its consolidation at the $1,500 price level and has been moving north ever since. The technical outlook of the coin has pointed towards continued bullishness on the chart. Accumulation has increased substantially ever since Ethereum breached the $1,500 price level.</p>

<p>The chance of a price reversal cannot be ruled out just yet, as ETH was overbought and overvalued. Currently, Ethereum has secured $1,600 as the support level. The next price correction could help traders with buying opportunities.</p>
<p>A price correction might not occur over the immediate trading sessions as demand for the coin remains quite high on the chart. Ethereum&#8217;s price might continue on the upside before the coin retraces. The market capitalization of Ethereum increased, which also reflected that the buying sentiment remained high.</p>
<h2>Ethereum Price Analysis: One-Day Chart</h2>
<img class="wp-image-517188 size-full" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ETHUSD_2023-01-23_21-22-03.png" alt="Ethereum" width="1816" height="743" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ETHUSD_2023-01-23_21-22-03.png 1816w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ETHUSD_2023-01-23_21-22-03-460x188.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ETHUSD_2023-01-23_21-22-03-860x352.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ETHUSD_2023-01-23_21-22-03-768x314.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ETHUSD_2023-01-23_21-22-03-1536x628.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ETHUSD_2023-01-23_21-22-03-750x307.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ETHUSD_2023-01-23_21-22-03-1140x466.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1816px) 100vw, 1816px" />
<p>ETH was exchanging hands at $1,620 at the time of writing. Immediate resistance for the coin stood at $1,690; it even corresponds to the 50% Fibonacci retracement level. A move above $1,690 will help Ethereum touch the $1,700 price mark.</p>
<p>The $1,700 price mark is crucial, as touching or breaching this mark could mean continued bullish momentum for the crypto.</p>
<p>ETH could even soar to $2,000 if the $1,700 price mark is crossed. This region will act as a profit-take region for traders. On the flip side, if the bullish momentum slows down, the first fall would be at $1,600 and then at $1,520. The amount of Ethereum traded in the last session was red, signifying a downtick in buying.</p>
<h2>Technical Analysis</h2>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-517206 size-full" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ETHUSD_2023-01-23_21-21-12.png" alt="Ethereum" width="1816" height="743" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ETHUSD_2023-01-23_21-21-12.png 1816w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ETHUSD_2023-01-23_21-21-12-460x188.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ETHUSD_2023-01-23_21-21-12-860x352.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ETHUSD_2023-01-23_21-21-12-768x314.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ETHUSD_2023-01-23_21-21-12-1536x628.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ETHUSD_2023-01-23_21-21-12-750x307.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ETHUSD_2023-01-23_21-21-12-1140x466.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1816px) 100vw, 1816px" />
<p>The altcoin was still in the overbought zone, which also means that Ethereum broke a multi-month record in terms of accumulation. The Relative Strength Index was parked a little below the 80-mark, which still signified heavy buying strength and bullishness.</p>
<p>If demand stays at this level, bullish momentum will not fade out anytime soon. ETH was also trading above the 20-Simple Moving Average line, indicating that buyers were driving the price momentum.</p>
<p>On the contrary, the 200-SMA line crossed the 20-SMA line, which implies that the coin might be headed for southbound price movement.</p>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-517208 size-full" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ETHUSD_2023-01-23_20-37-25.png" alt="Ethereum" width="1816" height="743" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ETHUSD_2023-01-23_20-37-25.png 1816w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ETHUSD_2023-01-23_20-37-25-460x188.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ETHUSD_2023-01-23_20-37-25-860x352.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ETHUSD_2023-01-23_20-37-25-768x314.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ETHUSD_2023-01-23_20-37-25-1536x628.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ETHUSD_2023-01-23_20-37-25-750x307.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ETHUSD_2023-01-23_20-37-25-1140x466.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1816px) 100vw, 1816px" />
<p>As accumulation has remained at a record high for the coin, chances of a price pullback still remain for the altcoin. The Awesome Oscillator, which signifies price direction, displayed red histograms, which meant that these were sell signals for the altcoin.</p>

<p>Sell signals can be accompanied by a fall in price. Ethereum may briefly fall in price before resuming its upward trend.</p>
<p>The Directional Movement Index was still positive, as the +DI line (blue) was above the -DI line (orange). The Average Directional Index (red) shot past 40, which suggested that price direction would gain further strength, which will push ETH to break past its nearest price ceiling of $1,700.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/traxer-tUfpPnpHFoE-unsplash-460x306.jpg" width="460" height="306" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Weekly RSI Reaches Line Between Bear &#038; Bull Market</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-weekly-rsi-bear-bull-market/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tony Spilotro]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 22:23:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[j. welles wilder]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Relative Strength Index]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[RSI]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=517214</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin price continues to push higher, leaving very few pullback opportunities thus far for those that failed to buy below $20,000. Price action on BTCUSD the weekly timeframe, according to the Relative Strength Index, has reached a critical line that separates bear market from bull market. Any higher, and crypto could experience a full blown breakout. Let&#8217;s take a look. What The Relative Strength Tells Us About Cryptocurrencies The Relative Strength Index is a popular technical indicator used in cryptocurrencies, originally created by J. Welles Wilder in the 1970s. The tool measures momentum through the &#8220;velocity and magnitude of price movements,&#8221; according to Wikipedia. Readings above 70 can indicate overbought conditions, and falling below 30 suggests an oversold market. In rare instances, the RSI will remain overheated depicting an especially powerful trend. Most of the time it remains somewhere between 30 and 70 while prices consolidate or move sideways. Related Reading: Overbought Or Ready To Rip? Bitcoin Daily RSI Reaches Explosive Levels On higher timeframes, moving past the middle-zone on the RSI can send lower timeframes through the roof — or through the floor. In the case of BTCUSD weekly charts, the RSI suggests this exact line in the sand is currently separating what could be a full breakout into a bull market – or a harsh rejection. Breaching this level on the RSI led to bullish rallies &#124; BTCUSD on TradingView.com Bitcoin Reaches Critical Line In The Sand Between Bear &#38; Bull Market Looking back throughout the history of Bitcoin, pushing above roughly 55-56 on the RSI has in the past led to extraordinarily bullish moves. Falling below it lead to the the deadliest declines and bear markets. Even worse, as BTCUSD weekly finds itself at the key trigger level, rejection has resulted in some brutal moves. In 2014 a rejection from there kicked off the second phase of the bear market. In 2015, a bull market attempt was harshly rejected back to bear market lows. Related Reading: “Parabolic” Signal That Triggered Past Bitcoin Bull Runs Reappears The latest instance in 2020 a bull market was rejected and combined with the onset of COVID, resulted in the Black Thursday collapse. Considering the importance of the level and the fact some of the worst rejections ever have taken place when the RSI reached such a reading, it is no surprise investors remain skeptical and cautious. If Bitcoin can make it above the current zone on the Relative Strength Index, the bull market could be back on in a flash. Currently, BTCUSD daily charts show a wildly elevated RSI, well into overbought conditions. However, extended phases of daily RSI levels support bull market behavior, and could indicate that the weekly RSI and further higher timeframes might also approach overbought levels at some point in the future. Beware of shorting #Bitcoin when the RSI is this elevated. pic.twitter.com/YHus8lR6dG &#8212; Tony &#34;The Bull&#34; (@tonythebullBTC) January 17, 2023 Follow @TonyTheBullBTC on Twitter or join the TonyTradesBTC Telegram for exclusive daily market insights and technical analysis education. Please note: Content is educational and should not be considered investment advice. Featured image from iStockPhoto, Charts from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-puell-multiple-bear-bull-rally/">Bitcoin price</a> continues to push higher, leaving very few pullback opportunities thus far for those that failed to buy below $20,000.</p>
<p>Price action on BTCUSD the weekly timeframe, according to the Relative Strength Index, has reached a critical line that separates bear market from bull market. Any higher, and crypto could experience a full blown breakout. Let&#8217;s take a look.</p>
<h2>What The Relative Strength Tells Us About Cryptocurrencies</h2>
<p>The <a href="https://newsbtc.com/topic/relative-strength-index/">Relative Strength Index</a> is a popular technical indicator used in cryptocurrencies, originally created by J. Welles Wilder in the 1970s.</p>
<p>The tool measures momentum through the &#8220;velocity and magnitude of price movements,&#8221; according to <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Relative_strength_index" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Wikipedia</a>. Readings above 70 can indicate overbought conditions, and falling below 30 suggests an oversold market.</p>
<p>In rare instances, the RSI will remain overheated depicting <a href="https://newsbtc.com/all/bitcoin-daily-rsi-reaches-explosive-levels/">an especially powerful trend</a>. Most of the time it remains somewhere between 30 and 70 while prices consolidate or move sideways.</p>

<p>On higher timeframes, moving past the middle-zone on the RSI can send lower timeframes through the roof — or through the floor.</p>
<p>In the case of BTCUSD weekly charts, the RSI suggests this exact line in the sand is currently separating what could be a full breakout into a bull market – or a harsh rejection.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-large wp-image-517215 aligncenter" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/2023-01-23-16.09.17-860x415.jpg" alt="Bitcoin BTC RSI " width="860" height="415" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/2023-01-23-16.09.17-860x415.jpg 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/2023-01-23-16.09.17-460x222.jpg 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/2023-01-23-16.09.17-768x371.jpg 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/2023-01-23-16.09.17-750x362.jpg 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/2023-01-23-16.09.17-1140x550.jpg 1140w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/2023-01-23-16.09.17.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" /></p>
<p style="text-align: center">Breaching this level on the RSI led to bullish rallies | <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BTCUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">BTCUSD on TradingView.com</a></p>
<h2>Bitcoin Reaches Critical Line In The Sand Between Bear &amp; Bull Market</h2>
<p>Looking back throughout the history of Bitcoin, pushing above roughly 55-56 on the <a href="https://newsbtc.com/topic/relative-strength-index/">RSI</a> has in the past led to extraordinarily bullish moves. Falling below it lead to the the deadliest declines and bear markets.</p>
<p>Even worse, as BTCUSD weekly finds itself at the key trigger level, rejection has resulted in some brutal moves. In 2014 a rejection from there kicked off the second phase of the bear market. In 2015, a bull market attempt was harshly rejected back to bear market lows.</p>

<p>The latest instance in 2020 a bull market was rejected and combined with the onset of COVID, resulted in the <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/panic-pandemic-crypto-more-fearful-black-thursday/">Black Thursday</a> collapse. Considering the importance of the level and the fact some of the worst rejections ever have taken place when the RSI reached such a reading, it is no surprise investors remain skeptical and cautious.</p>
<p>If Bitcoin can make it above the current zone on the Relative Strength Index, the bull market could be back on in a flash. Currently, BTCUSD daily charts show a wildly elevated RSI, well into overbought conditions. However, extended phases of daily RSI levels <a href="https://newsbtc.com/all/bitcoin-daily-rsi-reaches-explosive-levels/">support bull market behavior</a>, and could indicate that the weekly RSI and further higher timeframes might also approach overbought levels at some point in the future.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Beware of shorting <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Bitcoin?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">#Bitcoin</a> when the RSI is this elevated. <a href="https://t.co/YHus8lR6dG" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/YHus8lR6dG</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Tony &quot;The Bull&quot; (@tonythebullBTC) <a href="https://twitter.com/tonythebullBTC/status/1615343729287614468?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">January 17, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p></p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/iStock-1206059272-460x307.jpeg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Puell Multiple Starts To Leave Bear Market Zone, Bull Rally Here?</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-puell-multiple-bear-bull-rally/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hououin Kyouma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 21:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin bear market]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Bull Rally]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Bullish]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Puell Multiple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=517147</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[On-chain data shows the annual rate of change in the Bitcoin Puell Multiple has exited the bear market zone, a sign that a bull rally may be here. Bitcoin Puell Multiple 365-Day Rate Of Change Has Shot Up As pointed out by an analyst in a CryptoQuant post, this could be one of the first indications of the return of the bull market. The &#8220;Puell Multiple&#8221; is an indicator that measures the ratio between the daily Bitcoin mining revenue (in USD) and the 365-day moving average (MA) of the same. When the value of this metric is greater than 1, miners are making more income than the yearly average right now. On the other hand, values below the threshold imply the revenues of these chain validators is less than usual. As miner revenues shift, these holders become more or less likely to sell BTC (depending on which way of the break-even mark the ratio has swung in), which is a factor that can affect the price of the crypto. Thus, when the Puell Multiple is greater than 1, BTC may be considered overvalued, while being lesser than this value might suggest the coin is undervalued. The relevant indicator here is not the Puell Multiple itself but its rate of change (RoC). The RoC displays the speed at which any metric changes its value over a defined period. Related Reading: Bitcoin Bullish Signal: Whales Go On $1.4B Buying Spree In particular, the 365-day RoC of the Puell Multiple is of interest in the current discussion. Here is a chart that shows the trend in this indicator over the course of the different Bitcoin cycles: Looks like the value of the metric has spiked in recent days &#124; Source: CryptoQuant In the above graph, the quant has marked the relevant zones for the Bitcoin Puell Multiple 365-day RoC. It seems like tops have taken place in the crypto price whenever the metric has touched the red line, while mid-cycle highs have been set around the orange line. And it would appear that bear markets have lasted while the indicator has been around the green line. It also looks like transitions to and from bear markets have generally followed the dotted line historically. Related Reading: Bearish Indicator: Are Big Players No Longer Interested In Bitcoin? Recently, as Bitcoin has sharply rallied, miner revenues have also shot up, leading to the Puell Multiple also observing a rise. As the chart displays, the 365-day RoC of the indicator has naturally seen some rapid rise in recent days. With this spike, the metric has finally crossed above the dotted line, which could mean, if the past pattern is anything to go by, that the bear market may be coming to an end, and the crypto might have started transitioning towards a bullish trend. The analyst notes, however, that it will still take some more price action before this breakout can be fully confirmed. BTC Price At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading around $22,800, up 9% in the last week. The value of the crypto seems to have been moving sideways in the last few days &#124; Source: BTCUSD on TradingView Featured image from Dylan Leagh on Unsplash.com, charts from TradingView.com, CryptoQuant.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On-chain data shows the annual rate of change in the Bitcoin Puell Multiple has exited the bear market zone, a sign that a bull rally may be here.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Puell Multiple 365-Day Rate Of Change Has Shot Up</h2>
<p>As pointed out by an analyst in a CryptoQuant <a href="https://cryptoquant.com/quicktake/63ce771c91557e00cbb25965-Annually-Adjusted-Puell-Multiple-Starts-to-Break-Out-of-Bear-Zone" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">post</a>, this could be one of the first indications of the return of the bull market. The &#8220;<a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/what-puell-multiple-say-current-bitcoin-bear/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Puell Multiple</a>&#8221; is an indicator that measures the ratio between the daily Bitcoin mining revenue (in USD) and the 365-day moving average (MA) of the same.</p>
<p>When the value of this metric is greater than 1, <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/sell-pressure-mounts-on-bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">miners</a> are making more income than the yearly average right now. On the other hand, values below the threshold imply the revenues of these chain validators is less than usual.</p>
<p>As miner revenues shift, these holders become more or less likely to sell BTC (depending on which way of the break-even mark the ratio has swung in), which is a factor that can affect the price of the crypto. Thus, when the Puell Multiple is greater than 1, BTC may be considered overvalued, while being lesser than this value might suggest the coin is undervalued.</p>
<p>The relevant indicator here is not the Puell Multiple itself but its rate of change (RoC). The RoC displays the speed at which any metric changes its value over a defined period.</p>

<p>In particular, the 365-day RoC of the Puell Multiple is of interest in the current discussion. Here is a chart that shows the trend in this indicator over the course of the different Bitcoin cycles:</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="aligncenter" src="https://img.cryptoquant.com/342335/quicktake/V4Hb9Y913_63cbd363c0938c65bcb0cda372be7fff2579f6bdf847149241e6a3726f57db9b.png" alt="Bitcoin Puell Multiple" width="1280" height="701" /></p>

<p>In the above graph, the quant has marked the relevant zones for the Bitcoin Puell Multiple 365-day RoC. It seems like tops have taken place in the crypto price whenever the metric has touched the red line, while mid-cycle highs have been set around the orange line.</p>
<p>And it would appear that bear markets have lasted while the indicator has been around the green line. It also looks like transitions to and from bear markets have generally followed the dotted line historically.</p>

<p>Recently, as Bitcoin has sharply rallied, miner revenues have also shot up, leading to the Puell Multiple also observing a rise. As the chart displays, the 365-day RoC of the indicator has naturally seen some rapid rise in recent days.</p>
<p>With this spike, the metric has finally crossed above the dotted line, which could mean, if the past pattern is anything to go by, that the bear market may be coming to an end, and the crypto might have started transitioning towards a <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/this-bitcoin-on-chain-reading-confirms-the-rally-is-getting-started/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">bullish trend</a>. The analyst notes, however, that it will still take some more price action before this breakout can be fully confirmed.</p>
<h2>BTC Price</h2>
<p>At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading around $22,800, up 9% in the last week.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone wp-image-517193 size-large aligncenter" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/chart-33-860x468.png" alt="Bitcoin Price Chart" width="860" height="468" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/chart-33-860x468.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/chart-33-460x250.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/chart-33-768x418.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/chart-33-750x408.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/chart-33.png 991w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" /></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/dylan-leagh-qnVXHhUP0xU-unsplash-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Why Bitcoin Has The Momentum To Run Beyond 23,000</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-the-momentum-to-run-beyond-23000/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reynaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 20:00:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=517175</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The price of Bitcoin keeps smashing resistance levels while reclaiming previously lost territory. Unlike other rallies into the current area, this price action might suggest a persistent trend and a new dawn for the industry following months of collapsing companies and bankruptcies.  Related Reading: Is Litecoin (LTC) Expecting A Pullback Before Soaring Again? As of this writing, Bitcoin (BTC) trades at $22,800 with sideways movement in the last 24 hours. In the previous week, the cryptocurrency records a 10% profit. Other cryptocurrencies in the top 10 by market capitalization are experiencing similar price action with substantial profits over this period.  Is Bitcoin Finally At Bottom Levels? According to an analyst at Jarvis Labs, the current Bitcoin rally results from a long period of consolidation below the 200-Day Moving Average (MA). This moving average is one of BTC’s most important levels operating as critical support during the bearish cycles.  As Bitcoin reclaims the 200-day MA at around $19,520, the analyst wants to see a consolidation above this level. The rally might extend if the cryptocurrency can hold above it, pushing BTC into further highs, solidifying “a flip of the 200-day MA from resistance to support.”  As seen in the chart below, during the 2019 bear market, BTC saw a long consolidation below its 200-day MA before reclaiming these levels later in the year. According to the analyst, the longer the consolidation, the better the improvement for BTC’s overall market structure as other moving averages rise.  The above does not imply that Bitcoin will continuously trend to the upside, back to its all-time high of $69,000. Instead, it suggests that BTC’s market health is improving, with the foundation for further gains increasing.  This new status quo makes any potential decline an opportunity for optimistic investors. The Jarvis Labs analyst wrote:  (…) And while there is still a reasonably high probability that early January price levels will be revisited again at some point in 2023, there is also a strong piece of data which suggests any such retest would present a prime buying opportunity. Accumulation Levels Hint At 2019 Like BTC Bottom In addition to this period of consolidation below the 200-day MA, which hints at a 2019-like bottom, BTC has seen “persistent accumulation.” The image below shows that Bitcoin investors have been “moderately accumulating” (Blue dots in the chart below) more of the cryptocurrency.  Similar to the 2018-2019 bear market, this accumulation period preceded market rallies. In the coming months, Bitcoin should see more aggressive accumulation (Red dots in the chart below) to support another bullish season.  The US Federal Reserve (Fed) remains the biggest obstacle to a Bitcoin rally. The financial institution is hiking interest rates to reduce inflation while hurting financial markets. Related Reading: Ethereum Staking Reaches 16.16 million ETH Ahead of Shanghai Upgrade Market participants expect the Fed to pivot its monetary policy, but gains in stocks and crypto, combined with sticky inflation, could trigger the opposite. If this happens, optimistic investors might see the buying opportunity presented by the Jarvis Labs analyst. ]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>The price of Bitcoin keeps smashing resistance levels while reclaiming previously lost territory. Unlike other rallies into the current area, this price action might suggest a persistent trend and a new dawn for the industry following months of collapsing companies and bankruptcies. </strong></p>

<p>As of this writing, Bitcoin (BTC) trades at $22,800 with sideways movement in the last 24 hours. In the previous week, the cryptocurrency records a 10% profit. Other cryptocurrencies in the top 10 by market capitalization are experiencing similar price action with substantial profits over this period. </p>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-517196 size-large" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-3-860x394.png" alt="Bitcoin BTC BTCUSDT" width="860" height="394" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-3-860x394.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-3-460x211.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-3-768x352.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-3-1536x704.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-3-750x344.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-3-1140x523.png 1140w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-3.png 1813w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" />
<h2>Is Bitcoin Finally At Bottom Levels?</h2>
<p>According to an <a href="https://jarvislabs.substack.com/p/here-comes-the-sun" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">analyst at Jarvis Labs,</a> the current Bitcoin rally results from a long period of consolidation below the 200-Day Moving Average (MA). This moving average is one of BTC’s most important levels operating as critical support during the bearish cycles. </p>
<p>As Bitcoin reclaims the 200-day MA at around $19,520, the analyst wants to see a consolidation above this level. The rally might extend if the cryptocurrency can hold above it, pushing BTC into further highs, solidifying “a flip of the 200-day MA from resistance to support.” </p>
<p>As seen in the chart below, during the 2019 bear market, BTC saw a long consolidation below its 200-day MA before reclaiming these levels later in the year. According to the analyst, the longer the consolidation, the better the improvement for BTC’s overall market structure as other moving averages rise. </p>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-517195 size-large" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-2-Jarvis-860x570.jpg" alt="Bitcoin BTC BTCUSDT Chart 2 Jarvis" width="860" height="570" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-2-Jarvis-860x570.jpg 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-2-Jarvis-460x305.jpg 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-2-Jarvis-768x509.jpg 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-2-Jarvis-750x497.jpg 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-2-Jarvis-1140x755.jpg 1140w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-2-Jarvis.jpg 1315w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" />
<p>The above does not imply that Bitcoin will continuously trend to the upside, back to its all-time high of $69,000. Instead, it suggests that BTC’s market health is improving, with the foundation for further gains increasing. </p>
<p>This new status quo makes any potential decline an opportunity for optimistic investors. The Jarvis Labs analyst wrote: </p>
<blockquote><p>(…) And while there is still a reasonably high probability that early January price levels will be revisited again at some point in 2023, there is also a strong piece of data which suggests any such retest would present a prime buying opportunity.</p></blockquote>
Accumulation Levels Hint At 2019 Like BTC Bottom
<p>In addition to this period of consolidation below the 200-day MA, which hints at a 2019-like bottom, BTC has seen “persistent accumulation.” The image below shows that Bitcoin investors have been “moderately accumulating” (Blue dots in the chart below) more of the cryptocurrency. </p>
<p>Similar to the 2018-2019 bear market, this accumulation period preceded market rallies. In the coming months, Bitcoin should see more aggressive accumulation (Red dots in the chart below) to support another bullish season. </p>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-517194 size-full" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-3.jpg" alt="Bitcoin BTC BTCUSDT Chart 3" width="861" height="462" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-3.jpg 861w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-3-460x247.jpg 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-3-768x412.jpg 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-3-750x402.jpg 750w" sizes="(max-width: 861px) 100vw, 861px" />
<p>The US Federal Reserve (Fed) remains the biggest obstacle to a Bitcoin rally. The financial institution is hiking interest rates to reduce inflation while hurting financial markets.</p>

<p>Market participants expect the Fed to pivot its monetary policy, but gains in stocks and crypto, combined with sticky inflation, could trigger the opposite. If this happens, optimistic investors might see the buying opportunity presented by the Jarvis Labs analyst. </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-1-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Vitalik Buterin Proposes A Privacy Fix for Ethereum</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/ethereum/vitalik-buterin-privacy-fix-ethereum/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dalmas Ngetich]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 19:00:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stealth Addresses]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tornado Cash]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Vitalik Buterin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=517163</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Vitalik Buterin, the co-founder of Ethereum, recognizes the privacy problem in the most active smart contracting platform. He is proposing a stealth address system as a possible fix. Vitalik Buterin&#8217;s idea radically differs from what Tornado Cash, a crypto mixer, and similar platforms offer. Instead of the sender having control, it would be the recipient in charge. This is crucially important because, in ordinary settings, the asset receiver would desire to keep transactions, financial or otherwise, private and away from the public&#8217;s prying eyes.  Related Reading: The Blockchain that Brings Privacy to the Masses By default, transactions in Ethereum and other public blockchains can be traced. This characteristic is available for all users, despite the basic levels of encryptions concealing the identity of the sender and receivers.  Ethereum Price on January 23&#124; Source: ETHUSDT on KuCoin, Trading View Vitalik Buterin Talks Stealth Addresses To counter the openness in Ethereum and cushion the privacy of asset receivers, stealth addresses would be created by the sender or receiver. However, the receiver will be the one in charge. At any point in the transfer cycle, the receiver will be free to create a spending key which he can then use to create a “stealth meta-address.” This address is then sent to the sender, who does a small computation and creates a stealth address that belongs to the recipient. The recipient will always be in charge if they send assets to this address.  Additional cryptographic data will be published on-chain to affirm that the receiver controls the stealth address. A key blinding mechanism is added to break the public link between the sending and receiving addresses due to the additional cryptographic data sent on-chain. Related Reading: Newly Discovered Monero (XMR) Glitch Will Negatively Affect Transaction’s Privacy Vitalik also proposes the integration of ZK-SNARKs to boost privacy further when using stealth addresses. Integrating ZK SNARKs would increase the difficulty of linking transactors, a benefit for the receiving address seeking more privacy. Different from Tornado Cash Vitalik explains in his research blog that the stealth address system provides a different kind of privacy offered by Tornado Cash. The co-founder notes that Tornado Cash is only suitable for individuals who want to send assets to their addresses. While Tornado Cash is widely popular and used by thousands to obscure ETH and ERC-20 transactions, it cannot hide the receiving address of assets complying with the ERC-721 standard, mainly NFTs.  In early August 2022, the United States Treasury Department barred U.S. citizens from using the mixer. The Under Secretary of the Treasury for Terrorism and Financial Intelligence, Brian Nelson, said the Tornado Cash creators had failed to add adequate controls to prevent the tool from being used to launder money. Treasury alleged that North Korean hackers and other agents had used the tool to launder billions of dollars since 2019. Most of the laundered funds came from Decentralized Finance (DeFi) and exchange hacks. ]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Vitalik Buterin, the co-founder of Ethereum, recognizes the privacy problem in the most active smart contracting platform. He is proposing a <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://vitalik.ca/general/2023/01/20/stealth.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">stealth address system</a> as a possible fix.</p>
<p>Vitalik Buterin&#8217;s idea radically differs from what Tornado Cash, a crypto mixer, and similar platforms offer. Instead of the sender having control, it would be the recipient in charge. This is crucially important because, in ordinary settings, the asset receiver would desire to keep transactions, financial or otherwise, private and away from the public&#8217;s prying eyes. </p>

<p>By default, transactions in Ethereum and other public blockchains can be traced. This characteristic is available for all users, despite the basic levels of encryptions concealing the identity of the sender and receivers. </p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-517167 size-full" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ethereum-Prices-.png" alt="Vitalik Buterin Ethereum Price on January 23" width="1267" height="494" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ethereum-Prices-.png 1267w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ethereum-Prices--460x179.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ethereum-Prices--860x335.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ethereum-Prices--768x299.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ethereum-Prices--750x292.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ethereum-Prices--1140x444.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1267px) 100vw, 1267px" /></p>
<p style="text-align: center">Ethereum Price on January 23| Source: <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">ETHUSDT on KuCoin, Trading View</a></p>
<h2>Vitalik Buterin Talks Stealth Addresses</h2>
<p>To counter the openness in Ethereum and cushion the privacy of asset receivers, stealth addresses would be created by the sender or receiver. However, the receiver will be the one in charge. At any point in the transfer cycle, the receiver will be free to create a spending key which he can then use to create a “stealth meta-address.” </p>
<p>This address is then sent to the sender, who does a small computation and creates a stealth address that belongs to the recipient. The recipient will always be in charge if they send assets to this address. </p>
<p>Additional cryptographic data will be published on-chain to affirm that the receiver controls the stealth address. A key blinding mechanism is added to break the public link between the sending and receiving addresses due to the additional cryptographic data sent on-chain.</p>

<p>Vitalik also proposes the integration of ZK-SNARKs to boost privacy further when using stealth addresses. Integrating ZK SNARKs would increase the difficulty of linking transactors, a benefit for the receiving address seeking more privacy.</p>
<h2>Different from Tornado Cash</h2>
<p>Vitalik explains in his research blog that the stealth address system provides a different kind of privacy offered by Tornado Cash. The co-founder notes that Tornado Cash is only suitable for individuals who want to send assets to their addresses. While Tornado Cash is widely popular and used by thousands to obscure ETH and ERC-20 transactions, it cannot hide the receiving address of assets complying with the ERC-721 standard, mainly NFTs. </p>
<p>In early August 2022, the United States Treasury Department barred U.S. citizens from using the mixer. The Under Secretary of the Treasury for Terrorism and Financial Intelligence, Brian Nelson, <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://home.treasury.gov/news/press-releases/jy0916" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">said</a> the Tornado Cash creators had failed to add adequate controls to prevent the tool from being used to launder money. </p>
<p>Treasury alleged that North Korean hackers and other agents had used the tool to launder billions of dollars since 2019. Most of the laundered funds came from Decentralized Finance (DeFi) and exchange hacks. </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Blockchain-Ethereum-Privacy-460x296.png" width="460" height="296" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cardano (ADA) Appears In Top Trending Crypto List, Surpassing BTC</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/cardano/cardano-top-trending-crypto-list/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samuel Edyme]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 18:00:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cardano]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=517176</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Weeks have gone by, and the crypto market is still seeing a bullish trend, and the dubbed ‘mini bull run’ for the ongoing market movement is beginning to look more prominent. Altcoins such as Cardano (ADA) have moved significantly in price breaking multiple resistance and climbing higher highs while ignoring a retrace.  In today’s news, ADA has once again proven its potential to be small but mighty as the token appeared in the top trending crypto list on the crypto analytics platform StockTwits, surpassing Bitcoin (BTC), which comes second below ADA.  ADA Obtains First Position In Top Trending Crypto List  In a series of tweets shared by StockTwits, the crypto analytics platform ranked ADA as the most trending cryptocurrency on the platform, noting; “Cardano is also trending #1 on Stocktwits!.” At the time, ADA had a trading price of $0.3774, up by 11%, and a change of $0.0382. Aside from its position on StockTwits, ADA still appears to have significant potential as it still ranks higher on other platforms such CoinGecko and Coinmarketcap, competing with the other big dogs like Bitcoin (BTC), Ethereum (ETH), and the rest. Related Reading: XRP Vs. Cardano (ADA), Which Is The Better Investment In 2023? CoinGecko and Coinmarketcap rank ADA as the eighth cryptocurrency with the highest market capitalization, having a 1.2% dominance in the global crypto market cap. Notably, ranking second below ADA on StockTwits was BTC having a trading price of $23,195, up by 8.47% at the time, with a change of $1,810.42. Other cryptocurrencies at the bottom of the top 10 trending currencies include XRP and KRL, obtaining the ninth and tenth positions, respectively. The Crypto Market Price Outlook The bullish movement wasn’t only favorable to ADA but also to other altcoins that appear in the list of largest cryptocurrencies by market cap. Altcoins such as Ethereum (ETH), Solana (SOL), Binance coin BNB, and Ripple (XRP) have so far been a part of the uptrend.  The top coin, Bitcoin, has made some significant movement since the beginning of the year, increasing by over 30% in the last 20 days and currently trading above $22,000. ETH and SOL have also been in a bullish trend since the beginning, with both up by 25% and 67%, respectively, in the last 14 days. ETH currently trades at $1613, while SOL is at $24.11 at the time of writing. Related Reading: BTC, ETH, DOGE, and ADA Are Undervalued, Report Indicates XRP began the year shakily, but the token had increased nearly 30% in the last 20 days and is currently with a trading price of $0.42 and still up by 2.7% in the past 24 hours. BNB, after surviving massive FUD late last year, has also increased 10% in the previous 14 days and currently trades above the $300 region. Overall, ADA is still one of the top gainers among the crypto tokens listed. Cardano has surged above 40% in the last 30 days. The sustained bullish trend shows the token still has higher highs to climb through before coming close to its peak and beyond. Featured image from Unsplash, Chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Weeks have gone by, and the crypto market is still seeing a bullish trend, and the dubbed ‘mini bull run’ for the ongoing market movement is beginning to look more prominent. Altcoins such as <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/cardano/cardano-up-30-since-december/">Cardano </a>(ADA) have moved significantly in price breaking multiple resistance and climbing higher highs while ignoring a retrace. </p>
<p>In today’s news, ADA has once again proven its potential to be small but mighty as the token appeared in the top trending crypto list on the crypto analytics platform StockTwits, surpassing Bitcoin (BTC), which comes second below ADA. </p>
<h2>ADA Obtains First Position In Top Trending Crypto List </h2>
<p>In a series of <a href="https://twitter.com/stocktwitsnfts/status/1616860508425953280?s=46&amp;t=kUDK4tI2Qh1sjJsypUxh3A" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">tweets</a> shared by StockTwits, the crypto analytics platform ranked ADA as the most trending cryptocurrency on the platform, noting; “Cardano is also trending #1 on Stocktwits!.” At the time, ADA had a trading price of $0.3774, up by 11%, and a change of $0.0382.</p>
<p>Aside from its position on StockTwits, ADA still appears to have significant potential as it still ranks higher on other platforms such CoinGecko and Coinmarketcap, competing with the other big dogs like Bitcoin (BTC), <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/ethereum/ethereum-staking-reaches-16-million/">Ethereum</a> (ETH), and the rest.</p>

<p>CoinGecko and Coinmarketcap rank ADA as the eighth cryptocurrency with the highest market capitalization, having a 1.2% dominance in the global crypto market cap. Notably, ranking second below ADA on StockTwits was BTC having a trading price of $23,195, up by 8.47% at the time, with a change of $1,810.42.</p>
<p>Other cryptocurrencies at the bottom of the top 10 trending currencies include XRP and KRL, obtaining the ninth and tenth positions, respectively.</p>
<h2>The Crypto Market Price Outlook</h2>
<p>The bullish movement wasn’t only favorable to <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/cardano/cardano-ada-up-nearly-20/">ADA</a> but also to other altcoins that appear in the list of largest cryptocurrencies by market cap. Altcoins such as Ethereum (ETH), Solana (SOL), Binance coin BNB, and Ripple (XRP) have so far been a part of the uptrend. </p>
<p>The top coin, <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-reaches-one-month-high/">Bitcoin</a>, has made some significant movement since the beginning of the year, increasing by over 30% in the last 20 days and currently trading above $22,000.</p>
<p>ETH and SOL have also been in a bullish trend since the beginning, with both up by 25% and 67%, respectively, in the last 14 days. ETH currently trades at $1613, while SOL is at $24.11 at the time of writing.</p>

<p>XRP began the year shakily, but the token had increased nearly 30% in the last 20 days and is currently with a trading price of $0.42 and still up by 2.7% in the past 24 hours. </p>
<p>BNB, after surviving massive FUD late last year, has also increased 10% in the previous 14 days and currently trades above the $300 region.</p>
<img loading="lazy" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/EiXM9nUR/" alt="ADA price chart on TradingView" width="1834" height="808" />
<p>Overall, ADA is still one of the top gainers among the crypto tokens listed. Cardano has surged above 40% in the last 30 days. The sustained bullish trend shows the token still has higher highs to climb through before coming close to its peak and beyond.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Cardano-1-460x259.jpg" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Analyst Says Bitcoin Price Could See Another 30% Rally</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-could-see-30-rally/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Best Owie]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 17:00:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto analyst]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=517134</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin price has already had a good week. The digital asset already rallied to two-month highs above $23,000 and is still maintaining a good portion of its bullish momentum. Despite this already impressive growth over the last few weeks, a crypto analyst known on Twitter as Kaleo is not convinced that the best of the mini-bull run has passed. Crypto Analyst Says Another 30% Rally Is Possible Analyst @CryptoKaleo took to Twitter to share his thoughts on the current bull rally. According to him, the bitcoin rally might not be over despite the price drawdown that was recorded on Sunday. Even though the digital asset has now lost about $1,000 off its local peak, Kaleo revealed that there is still room for another 30% rally. Related Reading: Bullish Indicator: Bitcoin Shakes Off Genesis Bankruptcy Filing In the chart shared by the analyst, he shows a possible path that could lead bitcoin back to the $30,000 level. Kaleo refers to the $30,000 price level as a “magnet” for the digital asset. And if his analysis were to prove through, then BTC would be looking at an over 30% rally from its current price point. BTC could rally to $30,000 &#124; Source: Twitter This bounce is expected to happen sometime between now and the beginning of February going by the timeline on this chart. However, there are possible drawdowns along the way going to this analysis but the endpoint remains right above $30,000 for the digital asset. Can The Bitcoin Price Rally This High? The kind of momentum that has been recorded in the bitcoin price in the past two weeks can serve as a basis for what is possible for the cryptocurrency. If it were to continue, then the possibility of BTC reaching $30,000 over the next two weeks grows exponentially. However, that may not be the case. BTC price holding steady above $22,800 &#124; Source: BTCUSD on TradingView.com As of Monday, the price of BTC is already feeling the heat in the market with Sunday’s slowdown. Bitcoin’s trading volume is down over 10%, although there has been some recovery in this regard. Essentially, this trading volume would need to see an uptick if BTC is to continue on its bull rally. Related Reading: Bitcoin Might Fall Below $20,000 Before Bull Rally Resumes, Analyst Says A good thing now is that bitcoin has been able to clear its 200-day moving average, one of the last important indicators to signal an established bull trend. But it remains to be seen how this will go over for the digital asset as the markets usher in another trading week. BTC is trending at $22,900 at the time of this writing. The cryptocurrency is seeing meager gains in the last days at 0.11% but is doing better in a 7-day period with 9.91% gains. Follow Best Owie on Twitter for market insights, updates, and the occasional funny tweet… Featured image from Finbold, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="p2">Bitcoin price has already had a good week. The digital asset already rallied to two-month highs above $23,000 and is still maintaining a good portion of its bullish momentum. Despite this already impressive growth over the last few weeks, a crypto analyst known on Twitter as Kaleo is not convinced that the best of the mini-bull run has passed.</p>
<h2 class="p2">Crypto Analyst Says Another 30% Rally Is Possible</h2>
<p class="p2">Analyst @CryptoKaleo took to Twitter to <a href="https://twitter.com/CryptoKaleo/status/1617368196151152641?s=20&amp;t=2S_RkUpr5CAkpiyN35aZ4g" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">share his thoughts on the current bull rally</a>. According to him, the bitcoin rally might not be over despite the price drawdown that was recorded on Sunday. Even though the digital asset has now lost about $1,000 off its local peak, Kaleo revealed that there is still room for another 30% rally.</p>

<p class="p2">In the chart shared by the analyst, he shows a possible path that could lead bitcoin back to the $30,000 level. Kaleo refers to the $30,000 price level as a “magnet” for the digital asset. And if his analysis were to prove through, then BTC would be looking at an over 30% rally from its current price point.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-517135 aligncenter" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-price-Kaleo-crypto-analyst-460x211.jpeg" alt="Bitcoin price Kaleo crypto analyst" width="460" height="211" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-price-Kaleo-crypto-analyst-460x211.jpeg 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-price-Kaleo-crypto-analyst-860x395.jpeg 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-price-Kaleo-crypto-analyst-768x353.jpeg 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-price-Kaleo-crypto-analyst-1536x706.jpeg 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-price-Kaleo-crypto-analyst-750x345.jpeg 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-price-Kaleo-crypto-analyst-1140x524.jpeg 1140w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-price-Kaleo-crypto-analyst.jpeg 1777w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px" /></p>

<p class="p2">This bounce is expected to happen sometime between now and the beginning of February going by the timeline on this chart. However, there are possible drawdowns along the way going to this analysis but the endpoint remains right above $30,000 for the digital asset.</p>
<h2 class="p2">Can The Bitcoin Price Rally This High?</h2>
<p class="p2">The kind of momentum that has been recorded in the bitcoin price in the past two weeks can serve as a basis for what is possible for the cryptocurrency. If it were to continue, then the possibility of BTC reaching $30,000 over the next two weeks grows exponentially. However, that may not be the case.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/OOeiA2EG/" alt="Bitcoin price chart from TradingView.com" width="3284" height="1646" /></p>

<p class="p2">As of Monday, the price of BTC is already feeling the heat in the market with Sunday’s slowdown. Bitcoin’s trading volume is down over 10%, although there has been some recovery in this regard. Essentially, this trading volume would need to see an uptick if BTC is to continue on its bull rally.</p>

<p class="p2">A good thing now is that bitcoin has been able to clear its 200-day moving average, one of the last important indicators to signal an established bull trend. But it remains to be seen how this will go over for the digital asset as the markets usher in another trading week.</p>
<p class="p2">BTC is trending at $22,900 at the time of this writing. The cryptocurrency is seeing meager gains in the last days at 0.11% but is doing better in a 7-day period with 9.91% gains.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/bitcoin-bull-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Is Litecoin (LTC) Expecting A Pullback Before Soaring Again?</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/litecoin/litecoin-expecting-a-pullback/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[anushsamal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 16:00:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Litecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ltc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ltc/usd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LTCUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=517148</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Litecoin price has shown bullish sentiment over the past week once it bounced off the $81 resistance zone. Over the last 24 hours, the altcoin jumped by 2%, and in the past week, the LTC price gained close to 6%. As Bitcoin continues to trot upwards and is now eyeing the $23,000 price mark, other altcoins have reflected the same price sentiments. The technical outlook of the Litecoin price has depicted that accumulation shot past the overbought region just when Litecoin breached the $81 price region. Related Reading: Bitcoin Bullish Signal: Whales Go On $1.4B Buying Spree Demand for the coin remained steady between the $81 and $88 price levels, respectively. As Litecoin traveled above the $88 price zone, the coin started to display a price correction. Going by the indicators, Litecoin continues to remain heavily bullish on its chart, with another chance of a price retracement. Bullish momentum has gained strength since it moved past the $86 price mark, which is why a move to the $90 mark was swift and easy for Litecoin. Historically, the $93 resistance mark has acted as a pullback region for the coin. LTC might reach the $93 level over the next trading session if Bitcoin continues to surge. Litecoin Price Analysis: One-Day Chart LTC was trading at $91 at the time of this writing. Over the past couple of weeks, Litecoin has pierced through several resistance levels. The coin faced stiff resistance at $81 and has been rallying since crossing that level. Overhead resistance for the coin stood at $93; this will act as a crucial price mark because LTC can experience a pullback before it tries to breach the $106 resistance mark. On the other hand, if Litecoin fails to remain above the $88 support line, it would lead to sellers exceeding buyers, causing the altcoin to fall to $80 and then $71. The amount of LTC traded in the last session was red, which signified that there was a fall in the number of buyers. Technical Analysis LTC hovered around the overvalued zone, which indicated that there would be another price correction before it started to trade upwards again. The Relative Strength Index (RSI) stood at the 70 mark, which indicated that the asset was overbought. A fall from the overvalued zone can drag the price of the asset below $88. Litecoin continued to depict extreme bullishness as the price was above the 20-Simple Moving Average line. This meant that buyers were driving the price momentum in the market. The coin was also above the 50-SMA and 200-SMA lines. However, the 50-SMA was above the 20-SMA, which is a sign of impending bearishness and indicates a price pullback. Buy signals for the asset started to show a decline, which meant that buyers might start to exit the market over the next few trading sessions. The Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD) indicates price momentum and reversal; it displayed receding green signal bars, which meant incoming bearish price action. Related Reading: Aptos Climbs 75% – What Keeps APT In The Green In Last 7 Days Bollinger Bands indicate price fluctuation and volatility; the bands were far apart, which implied forthcoming price instability. Featured Image From UnSplash, Charts From TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Litecoin price has shown bullish sentiment over the past week once it bounced off the $81 resistance zone. Over the last 24 hours, the altcoin jumped by 2%, and in the past week, the LTC price gained close to 6%.</p>
<p>As Bitcoin continues to trot upwards and is now eyeing the $23,000 price mark, other altcoins have reflected the same price sentiments. The technical outlook of the Litecoin price has depicted that accumulation shot past the overbought region just when Litecoin breached the $81 price region.</p>

<p>Demand for the coin remained steady between the $81 and $88 price levels, respectively. As Litecoin traveled above the $88 price zone, the coin started to display a price correction. Going by the indicators, Litecoin continues to remain heavily bullish on its chart, with another chance of a price retracement.</p>
<p>Bullish momentum has gained strength since it moved past the $86 price mark, which is why a move to the $90 mark was swift and easy for Litecoin. Historically, the $93 resistance mark has acted as a pullback region for the coin. LTC might reach the $93 level over the next trading session if Bitcoin continues to surge.</p>
<h2>Litecoin Price Analysis: One-Day Chart</h2>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-517151 size-full" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/LTCUSD_2023-01-23_18-18-24.png" alt="Litecoin" width="1816" height="830" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/LTCUSD_2023-01-23_18-18-24.png 1816w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/LTCUSD_2023-01-23_18-18-24-460x210.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/LTCUSD_2023-01-23_18-18-24-860x393.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/LTCUSD_2023-01-23_18-18-24-768x351.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/LTCUSD_2023-01-23_18-18-24-1536x702.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/LTCUSD_2023-01-23_18-18-24-750x343.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/LTCUSD_2023-01-23_18-18-24-1140x521.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1816px) 100vw, 1816px" />
<p>LTC was trading at $91 at the time of this writing. Over the past couple of weeks, Litecoin has pierced through several resistance levels. The coin faced stiff resistance at $81 and has been rallying since crossing that level.</p>
<p>Overhead resistance for the coin stood at $93; this will act as a crucial price mark because LTC can experience a pullback before it tries to breach the $106 resistance mark.</p>
<p>On the other hand, if Litecoin fails to remain above the $88 support line, it would lead to sellers exceeding buyers, causing the altcoin to fall to $80 and then $71. The amount of LTC traded in the last session was red, which signified that there was a fall in the number of buyers.</p>
<h2>Technical Analysis</h2>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-517154 size-full" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/LTCUSD_2023-01-23_18-19-25.png" alt="Litecoin" width="1816" height="743" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/LTCUSD_2023-01-23_18-19-25.png 1816w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/LTCUSD_2023-01-23_18-19-25-460x188.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/LTCUSD_2023-01-23_18-19-25-860x352.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/LTCUSD_2023-01-23_18-19-25-768x314.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/LTCUSD_2023-01-23_18-19-25-1536x628.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/LTCUSD_2023-01-23_18-19-25-750x307.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/LTCUSD_2023-01-23_18-19-25-1140x466.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1816px) 100vw, 1816px" />
<p>LTC hovered around the overvalued zone, which indicated that there would be another price correction before it started to trade upwards again. The Relative Strength Index (RSI) stood at the 70 mark, which indicated that the asset was overbought.</p>
<p>A fall from the overvalued zone can drag the price of the asset below $88. Litecoin continued to depict extreme bullishness as the price was above the 20-Simple Moving Average line.</p>
<p>This meant that buyers were driving the price momentum in the market. The coin was also above the 50-SMA and 200-SMA lines. However, the 50-SMA was above the 20-SMA, which is a sign of impending bearishness and indicates a price pullback.</p>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-517158 size-full" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/LTCUSD_2023-01-23_18-21-59.png" alt="Litecoin" width="1816" height="743" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/LTCUSD_2023-01-23_18-21-59.png 1816w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/LTCUSD_2023-01-23_18-21-59-460x188.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/LTCUSD_2023-01-23_18-21-59-860x352.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/LTCUSD_2023-01-23_18-21-59-768x314.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/LTCUSD_2023-01-23_18-21-59-1536x628.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/LTCUSD_2023-01-23_18-21-59-750x307.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/LTCUSD_2023-01-23_18-21-59-1140x466.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1816px) 100vw, 1816px" />
<p>Buy signals for the asset started to show a decline, which meant that buyers might start to exit the market over the next few trading sessions.</p>
<p>The Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD) indicates price momentum and reversal; it displayed receding green signal bars, which meant incoming bearish price action.</p>

<p>Bollinger Bands indicate price fluctuation and volatility; the bands were far apart, which implied forthcoming price instability.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/traxer-TLAaKG9iou0-unsplash-460x306.jpg" width="460" height="306" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum Staking Reaches 16.16 million ETH Ahead of Shanghai Upgrade</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/ethereum/ethereum-staking-reaches-16-million/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samuel Edyme]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 15:10:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[pos]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Staking]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=517153</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[According to Glassnode on-chain data, Ethereum staking has reached an all-time high of over 16.16 million ETH which has been deposited into the beacon chain.  The 16.16 million ETH figure consists of over 13.28% of the total Ether supply and represents $26.13 billion at current prices. As per the data, out of the 16 million ETH staked, about 11.408 million ETH  have been staked through staking services providers such as Lido, Coinbase, and Kraken, among others &#8211; representing 70.86% of the total staked on the Beacon chain. According to the data, Lido dominates ETH staking with 29.3%, Coinbase controls 12.8%, while Kraken holds 7.6%, and Binance controls 6.3% of total staked. BeaconScan data shows that the number of active validators stands at about 503,702 while Nansen data shows that the number of unique staking depositors is about 93,800. Related Reading: Ethereum Nears $1,600 Level – Is The $2K Mark Hittable This Week? The Upcoming Shanghai Upgrade The rising number of staked ETH is an indication of the promising signals of Ethereum adoption and security. However, this may create pressure on the network’s core developers to speed up work to enable withdrawals to maintain balance on the network. While the staked funds are locked up within the network and get accrued yield, it will be impossible to withdraw until the network’s Shanghai upgrade, which is expected to take place in March. Many participants are expected to withdraw their staked ETH after the Shanghai upgrade. However, the withdrawals are anticipated to happen in stages and validators are to be rewarded for re-staking. The mechanism is expected to ensure a balance in the chain. The increasing amounts of staked ETHs are important as it makes it more difficult for an individual actor to attack the Ethereum chain. But since the majority of staked ETH currently belongs to large wallets, the phenomenon has drawn concerns that the chain is becoming too centralized. Developers are reported to be working on making the Ethereum network less centralized as some staking providers such as Lido appear dominating in ETH staking. Related Reading: If Any Crypto Will Reach $1 Trillion, It’s Ethereum, Not Bitcoin: Dragonfly Capital The amount of staked ETH has risen 16.68% since the Merge upgrade in September when Ethereum transitioned to today’s favorite staking system (proof-of-stake consensus mechanism) from its old proof-of-work energy-intensive crypto mining process. ETH Price Seeing Uptrend                                      At the time of writing, ETH&#8217;s trading price is at $1,634.98 USD, up 0.65%, with a decrease of its trading volume by 18% to $6,947,406,035 USD in the last 24 hours. While this shows a slight reduction in interest among traders, ETH&#8217;s price analysis shows a bullish market, which has been favoring the buyers as the price currently sees significant improvements. The buyers have been able to recover the price above $1,600. The recovery has been slow as there is still selling pressure within the market. The bulls and bearish are trying to capitalize on opportunities in the market. Featured image from Unsplash, Chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>According to<a href="https://twitter.com/glassnode/status/1617294398613749761" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow"> Glassnode on-chain data</a>, Ethereum staking has reached an all-time high of over 16.16 million ETH which has been deposited into the beacon chain. </p>
<p>The 16.16 million ETH figure consists of over 13.28% of the total Ether supply and represents $26.13 billion at current prices.</p>
<p>As per the data, out of the 16 million ETH staked, about 11.408 million ETH  have been staked through staking services providers such as Lido, Coinbase, and Kraken, among others &#8211; representing 70.86% of the total staked on the Beacon chain. According to the data, Lido dominates<a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/ethereum/ethereum-staking-queue-nears-all-time-high-ahead-of-mainnet-merge/"> ETH staking </a>with 29.3%, Coinbase controls 12.8%, while Kraken holds 7.6%, and Binance controls 6.3% of total staked.</p>
<p><a href="https://beaconscan.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">BeaconScan data</a> shows that the number of active validators stands at about 503,702 while<a href="https://pro.nansen.ai/eth2-deposit-contract" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow"> Nansen data</a> shows that the number of unique staking depositors is about 93,800.</p>

<h2>The Upcoming Shanghai Upgrade</h2>
<p>The rising number of staked ETH is an indication of the promising signals of <a href="https://newsbtc.com/press-releases/ethereum-users-are-excited-about-new-erc20-pancake-swap-like-dex-called-toon-finance/">Ethereum</a> adoption and security. However, this may create pressure on the network’s core developers to speed up work to enable withdrawals to maintain balance on the network.</p>
<p>While the staked funds are locked up within the network and get accrued yield, it will be impossible to withdraw until the network’s<a href="https://www.insights.sygnum.com/post/eth-withdrawals-shanghai-upgrade-and-beyond" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow"> Shanghai upgrade</a>, which is expected to take place in March. </p>
<p>Many participants are expected to withdraw their staked<a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/ethereum/why-ethereum-will-outperform-bitcoin/"> ETH</a> after the Shanghai upgrade. However, the withdrawals are anticipated to happen in stages and validators are to be rewarded for re-staking. The mechanism is expected to ensure a balance in the chain.</p>
<p>The increasing amounts of staked ETHs are important as it makes it more difficult for an individual actor to attack the Ethereum chain. But since the majority of staked ETH currently belongs to large wallets, the phenomenon has drawn concerns that the chain is becoming too centralized. </p>
<p>Developers are reported to be working on making the Ethereum network less centralized as some staking providers such as Lido appear dominating in <a href="https://newsbtc.com/press-releases/ethereum-2-0-staking-is-taking-defi-by-storm-cocoricos-skyrockets-its-mainstream-adoption/">ETH staking</a>.</p>

<p>The amount of staked ETH has risen 16.68% since the<a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/lawrencewintermeyer/2022/09/22/the-ethereum-merge-is-over-now-what/?sh=3c32d20a4b0b" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow"> Merge upgrade</a> in September when Ethereum transitioned to today’s favorite staking system (proof-of-stake consensus mechanism) from its old proof-of-work energy-intensive crypto mining process.</p>
<h2>ETH Price Seeing Uptrend                                     </h2>
<p>At the time of writing,<a href="https://newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-consolidates-1650/"> ETH&#8217;s trading price</a> is at $1,634.98 USD, up 0.65%, with a decrease of its trading volume by 18% to $6,947,406,035 USD in the last 24 hours.</p>
<img loading="lazy" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/LVtOVua7/" alt="Ethereum price chart on TradingView" width="1834" height="808" />
<p>While this shows a slight reduction in interest among traders, ETH&#8217;s price analysis shows a bullish market, which has been favoring the buyers as the price currently sees significant improvements.</p>
<p>The buyers have been able to recover the price above $1,600. The recovery has been slow as there is still selling pressure within the market. The bulls and bearish are trying to capitalize on opportunities in the market.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ETH-460x297.jpg" width="460" height="297" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Bullish Signal: Whales Go On $1.4B Buying Spree</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-bullish-whales-1-4b-buying-spree/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hououin Kyouma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 13:10:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Bullish Signal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Whale Accumulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin whales]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=517136</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[On-chain data shows Bitcoin whales have accumulated $1.4 billion in the asset during the last two weeks, a sign that could be bullish for the coin. Bitcoin Whales Added 70,000 BTC To Their Holdings In Two Weeks As pointed out by an analyst on Twitter, BTC whales have been showing accumulation behavior recently. The relevant indicator here is the &#8220;Bitcoin Supply Distribution,&#8221; which is a metric from on-chain analytics firm Santiment that tells us which wallet groups in the market are holding what amount of the crypto right now. Wallets are divided into these groups based on the total number of coins they are holding currently. For example, the 10-100 coins cohort includes all wallets that are carrying a balance of at least 10 and at most 100 BTC. The Supply Distribution metric for this specific group would then show the combined number of coins that are present in these wallets at the moment. Related Reading: This Metric Suggests Bitcoin Could Be In Danger Of Another Selloff In the context of the topic at hand, the wallet group of interest is the 1,000-10,000 coins group. Here is a chart that shows the trend in the Supply Distribution for this Bitcoin cohort over the past month: The value of the metric seems to have observed some rise in recent days &#124; Source: Ali on Twitter The 1,000-10,000 coins wallet group is an important cohort for BTC as it includes addresses belonging to the whales. Since the balances of these investors are huge (the lower and upper bounds of the range convert to $22.9 million and $229 million, respectively, at the current exchange rate), movements from this cohort may sometimes have visible effects on the price of the crypto. As can be seen in the above graph, the amount of Bitcoin being held by the whales was going down during December, suggesting that these humongous holders were selling their coins then. At the start of this year, however, the metric bottomed out and since then this cohort has shown net accumulation behavior. Interestingly, while this buying from the whales has taken place, the price of the crypto has observed a sharp rally. Around five days ago, this BTC rally saw its first significant pullback and from the chart, it&#8217;s visible that these investors participated in some selling around it. Related Reading: Bitcoin Bulls Keeps Pushing, Why BTC Price Increase Isn’t Over Yet In the last few days, however, the 1,000-10,000 BTC wallet group has again done some buying as their Supply Distribution curve has once more spiked up. Following this latest accumulation, BTC has again caught a sharp uptrend as the price of the coin has now surged to almost $23,000. In all, these whales have added more than $1.4 billion worth of coins to their holdings in the last couple of weeks, taking their total holdings to 4.62 million BTC ($105.8 billion). BTC Price At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading around $22,900, up 10% in the last week. Looks like the value of the crypto has been moving sideways just below the $23,000 level recently &#124; Source: BTCUSD on TradingView Featured image from Todd Cravens on Unsplash.com, charts from TradingView.com, Santiment.net]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On-chain data shows Bitcoin whales have accumulated $1.4 billion in the asset during the last two weeks, a sign that could be bullish for the coin.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Whales Added 70,000 BTC To Their Holdings In Two Weeks</h2>
<p>As pointed out by an analyst on <a href="https://twitter.com/ali_charts/status/1616875069640433665" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Twitter</a>, BTC whales have been showing accumulation behavior recently. The relevant indicator here is the &#8220;Bitcoin <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/ethereum/ethereum-rallies-above-1400-as-sharks-accumulate/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Supply Distribution</a>,&#8221; which is a metric from on-chain analytics firm Santiment that tells us which wallet groups in the market are holding what amount of the crypto right now.</p>
<p>Wallets are divided into these groups based on the total number of coins they are holding currently. For example, the 10-100 coins cohort includes all wallets that are carrying a balance of at least 10 and at most 100 BTC. The Supply Distribution metric for this specific group would then show the combined number of coins that are present in these wallets at the moment.</p>

<p>In the context of the topic at hand, the wallet group of interest is the 1,000-10,000 coins group. Here is a chart that shows the trend in the Supply Distribution for this Bitcoin cohort over the past month:</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone aligncenter" src="https://pbs.twimg.com/media/FnBLThLXoAEQgZ6?format=jpg&amp;name=medium" alt="Bitcoin Whales" width="1200" height="626" /></p>

<p>The 1,000-10,000 coins wallet group is an important cohort for BTC as it includes addresses belonging to the <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/ripple/whales-move-billions-of-xrp/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">whales</a>. Since the balances of these investors are huge (the lower and upper bounds of the range convert to $22.9 million and $229 million, respectively, at the current exchange rate), movements from this cohort may sometimes have visible effects on the price of the crypto.</p>
<p>As can be seen in the above graph, the amount of Bitcoin being held by the whales was going down during December, suggesting that these humongous holders were selling their coins then. At the start of this year, however, the metric bottomed out and since then this cohort has shown net <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-bullish-small-rapid-accumulation/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">accumulation</a> behavior.</p>
<p>Interestingly, while this buying from the whales has taken place, the price of the crypto has observed a sharp rally. Around five days ago, this BTC rally saw its first significant pullback and from the chart, it&#8217;s visible that these investors participated in some selling around it.</p>

<p>In the last few days, however, the 1,000-10,000 BTC wallet group has again done some buying as their Supply Distribution curve has once more spiked up. Following this latest accumulation, BTC has again caught a sharp uptrend as the price of the coin has now surged to almost $23,000.</p>
<p>In all, these whales have added more than $1.4 billion worth of coins to their holdings in the last couple of weeks, taking their total holdings to 4.62 million BTC ($105.8 billion).</p>
<h2>BTC Price</h2>
<p>At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading around $22,900, up 10% in the last week.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone wp-image-517142 size-large aligncenter" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/chart-32-860x469.png" alt="Bitcoin Price Chart" width="860" height="469" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/chart-32-860x469.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/chart-32-460x251.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/chart-32-768x418.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/chart-32-750x409.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/chart-32.png 991w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" /></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/todd-cravens-QnBrjY-nFUs-unsplash-460x306.jpg" width="460" height="306" />	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>

<!--
Performance optimized by W3 Total Cache. Learn more: https://www.boldgrid.com/w3-total-cache/

Object Caching 214/217 objects using apc
Page Caching using disk: enhanced (Page is feed) 
Database Caching 33/43 queries in 0.009 seconds using memcached

Served from: newsbtc.com @ 2023-01-23 22:17:09 by W3 Total Cache
-->