<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
>

<channel>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.newsbtc.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<description>Bitcoin &#38; cryptocurrency news today, price &#38; technical analysis</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 20:31:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Dogecoin Expected To Experience A Further 6% Decrease Prior to Initiating Recovery</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/dogecoin/dogecoin-expected-to-experience-a-further-6-decrease-prior-to-initiating-recovery/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[anushsamal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 22:00:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[doge]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dogeusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dogeusdt]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=532409</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[In recent weeks, Dogecoin has faced a downward trend in its price momentum, largely due to the emergence of PEPE coin, which has overshadowed its popularity. Over the past 24 hours, DOGE has shown limited upward movement, with a mere 1% increase. The meme-coin has experienced a significant decline in price, indicating a prevailing bearish control. The technical outlook of Dogecoin showed that bears are currently influencing its price. Both the demand and accumulation have dipped, suggesting a decrease in buying activity. Related Reading: Key Support Levels To Monitor As Ethereum Price Slows Down Moreover, the rejection of Bitcoin at the $27,000 price mark has hurt major altcoins, including Dogecoin, resulting in a decline in their respective charts. For Dogecoin to maintain its position above its immediate support level, it needs a recovery in buying strength. If it fails to do so and loses its current support level, it could experience another significant drop in value before any signs of recovery. Additionally, the decline in the Dogecoin market capitalization further indicates a fading buying strength at the time of writing. Dogecoin Price Analysis: One-Day Chart As of the time of writing, Dogecoin (DOGE) was trading at $0.070. The meme-coin has been struggling to recover after facing rejection at $0.076, with the bulls unable to gain momentum. The current overhead resistance for DOGE is $0.073. If this level is breached, it could propel the meme-coin to $0.078. However, if the price falls from its current level, it will likely reach $0.068 and potentially drop further to $0.066, resulting in a nearly 6% decline in value. The trading volume of DOGE in the last session indicated a red signal, indicating mounting selling pressure. Technical Analysis Throughout the majority of the month, the demand for the meme-coin remained low. This was evident from the Relative Strength Index (RSI) staying below the 40-mark and nearly reaching the 30-mark, indicating oversold conditions. Additionally, the asset&#8217;s price consistently traded below the 20-Simple Moving Average line, suggesting that sellers were the driving force behind the market&#8217;s price momentum. Throughout this month, DOGE has lacked positive demand, and its chart displays sell signals. The Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD), which indicates price momentum and reversals, formed red histograms below the half-line. Related Reading: Bitcoin Plunges Below $27,000, Which Holder Groups Are Selling? This suggests a signal to sell, indicating a potential decline in price in the upcoming trading sessions. The Bollinger Bands indicator has widened regarding price volatility and fluctuation, indicating that DOGE may experience price fluctuations in the next trading session. For Dogecoin to recover shortly, it heavily relies on broader market strength. Featured Image From UnSplash, Charts From TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[









<p>In recent weeks, Dogecoin has faced a downward trend in its price momentum, largely due to the emergence of PEPE coin, which has overshadowed its popularity. Over the past 24 hours, DOGE has shown limited upward movement, with a mere 1% increase. The meme-coin has experienced a significant decline in price, indicating a prevailing bearish control.</p>
<p>The technical outlook of Dogecoin showed that bears are currently influencing its price. Both the demand and accumulation have dipped, suggesting a decrease in buying activity.</p>

<p>Moreover, the rejection of Bitcoin at the $27,000 price mark has hurt major altcoins, including Dogecoin, resulting in a decline in their respective charts.</p>




For Dogecoin to maintain its position above its immediate support level, it needs a recovery in buying strength. If it fails to do so and loses its current support level, it could experience another significant drop in value before any signs of recovery. Additionally, the decline in the Dogecoin market capitalization further indicates a fading buying strength at the time of writing.
<h2>Dogecoin Price Analysis: One-Day Chart</h2>
<img decoding="async" class="wp-image-532410 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/DOGEUSD_2023-05-13_00-51-12.png" alt="Dogecoin" width="1816" height="830" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/DOGEUSD_2023-05-13_00-51-12.png 1816w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/DOGEUSD_2023-05-13_00-51-12-460x210.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/DOGEUSD_2023-05-13_00-51-12-860x393.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/DOGEUSD_2023-05-13_00-51-12-768x351.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/DOGEUSD_2023-05-13_00-51-12-1536x702.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/DOGEUSD_2023-05-13_00-51-12-750x343.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/DOGEUSD_2023-05-13_00-51-12-1140x521.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1816px) 100vw, 1816px" />











<p>As of the time of writing, Dogecoin (DOGE) was trading at $0.070. The meme-coin has been struggling to recover after facing rejection at $0.076, with the bulls unable to gain momentum. The current overhead resistance for DOGE is $0.073. If this level is breached, it could propel the meme-coin to $0.078.</p>
<p>However, if the price falls from its current level, it will likely reach $0.068 and potentially drop further to $0.066, resulting in a nearly 6% decline in value. The trading volume of DOGE in the last session indicated a red signal, indicating mounting selling pressure.</p>
<h2>Technical Analysis</h2>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-532412 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/DOGEUSD_2023-05-13_00-52-01.png" alt="Dogecoin" width="1816" height="743" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/DOGEUSD_2023-05-13_00-52-01.png 1816w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/DOGEUSD_2023-05-13_00-52-01-460x188.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/DOGEUSD_2023-05-13_00-52-01-860x352.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/DOGEUSD_2023-05-13_00-52-01-768x314.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/DOGEUSD_2023-05-13_00-52-01-1536x628.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/DOGEUSD_2023-05-13_00-52-01-750x307.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/DOGEUSD_2023-05-13_00-52-01-1140x466.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1816px) 100vw, 1816px" />
<p>Throughout the majority of the month, the demand for the meme-coin remained low. This was evident from the Relative Strength Index (RSI) staying below the 40-mark and nearly reaching the 30-mark, indicating oversold conditions.</p>
<p>Additionally, the asset&#8217;s price consistently traded below the 20-Simple Moving Average line, suggesting that sellers were the driving force behind the market&#8217;s price momentum.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-532413 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/DOGEUSD_2023-05-13_00-52-19-1.png" alt="Dogecoin" width="1816" height="743" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/DOGEUSD_2023-05-13_00-52-19-1.png 1816w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/DOGEUSD_2023-05-13_00-52-19-1-460x188.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/DOGEUSD_2023-05-13_00-52-19-1-860x352.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/DOGEUSD_2023-05-13_00-52-19-1-768x314.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/DOGEUSD_2023-05-13_00-52-19-1-1536x628.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/DOGEUSD_2023-05-13_00-52-19-1-750x307.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/DOGEUSD_2023-05-13_00-52-19-1-1140x466.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1816px) 100vw, 1816px" />
<p>Throughout this month, DOGE has lacked positive demand, and its chart displays sell signals. The Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD), which indicates price momentum and reversals, formed red histograms below the half-line.</p>

<p>This suggests a signal to sell, indicating a potential decline in price in the upcoming trading sessions. The Bollinger Bands indicator has widened regarding price volatility and fluctuation, indicating that DOGE may experience price fluctuations in the next trading session. For Dogecoin to recover shortly, it heavily relies on broader market strength.</p>




]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/kanchanara-rfUl0Lfyays-unsplash-1-460x306.jpg" width="460" height="306" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cosmos (ATOM) Shows Price Recovery In Response To New Update Reveal</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/cosmos-atom/cosmos-atom-shows-price-recovery-in-response-to-new-update-reveal/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mudiaga Iritare]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 21:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cosmos (ATOM)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ATOM]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cosmos]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=532339</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Over the past few days, Cosmos Hub (ATOM) has demonstrated remarkable strength and resilience in its price fluctuations, despite significant downturns across the broader cryptocurrency markets due to shifts in trader sentiment. For three consecutive days, ATOM bulls have managed to bounce back and maintain the native token&#8217;s price, despite Bitcoin&#8217;s bearish momentum that has caused most altcoins to plummet. Cosmos&#8217; (ATOM) renewed strength and price stamina in the crypto markets may be linked to the fresh updates announced by the team behind the project. Related Reading: Bitcoin Bearish Chart Pattern Looms, Legendary Trader Sounds Warning Adoption Grows For Cosmos Replicated Security Model In an exciting update, the Cosmos team announced yesterday that its first Replicated Security Model went live and has gained adoption by a top smart contract and consumer chain platform. 1/ The first #Cosmos native shared security model just got adoption 💥@Neutron_org is the first Consumer Chain to leverage @cosmoshub Replicated Security. Replicated Security brings a new era of utility for #ATOM ⚛️ Appchains can now launch with the economic security of #ATOM pic.twitter.com/sMp6mXhjPC &#8212; Cosmos &#8211; Internet of Blockchains ⚛️ (@cosmos) May 11, 2023 Before this, the team had made it known in February that the launch of the Replicated security model was close and presented an opportunity for delegators and validators to earn multiple tokens from upcoming consumer chains by staking the native token ATOM. The Cosmos Replicated security model, a new and secure innovation, provides security to smart contracts and consumer chain platforms. The team announced and introduced Neutron as the first ever consumer chain and smart contracts platform to adopt and leverage its new and innovative Replicated security model. In leveraging Cosmos&#8217; Replicated security model, smart contracts and consumer chains platforms like Neutron no longer worry about platform security but can now focus on other application areas and services, according to the official announcement. As seen in an official tweet where the team made the announcement, it was also stated that the Replicated security model brings forth a new dawn and era of utility as dApps can now launch with ATOM&#8217;s native security. This fundamental news by the Cosmos team could be the backing behind ATOM&#8217;s recent show of strength and price resilience despite the bearish market outlook observed in several cryptocurrencies. Related Reading: Is This The Perfect Time To Buy Bitcoin? TD Sequential And RSI Suggests So Daily Chart Analysis For ATOM Cosmos (ATOM) trades at $11.04, a 2.02% increase from its 24-hour low at $10.55, as seen from Coingecko data trading reports. The market capitalization of ATOM is also seen to increase by 1.10%. On the daily timeframe, bulls pushed ATOM&#8217;s price above the key resistance at $10.90 and moved further to an $11.27 high before retracing. The previous resistance turned support level on the daily price chart is a good area for bulls to build momentum and push ATOM&#8217;s price to the upside. Although the 50 and 200 Exponential Moving Averages (EMA) are an immediate resistance level, bulls must contend with them to confirm further upside movements. To the downside, a break above the newfound support at $10.90 will signal further bearish movements for the asset. Cosmos (ATOM) price seen to trade at newfound support after breaking the resistance level on the daily timeframe &#124; Source: ATOMUSD on TradingView.com Featured image from Forkast News, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Over the past few days, Cosmos Hub (ATOM) has demonstrated remarkable strength and resilience in its price fluctuations, despite significant downturns across the broader cryptocurrency markets due to shifts in trader sentiment. For three consecutive days, ATOM bulls have managed to bounce back and maintain the native token&#8217;s price, despite Bitcoin&#8217;s bearish momentum that has caused most altcoins to plummet.</p>
<p>Cosmos&#8217; (ATOM) renewed strength and price stamina in the crypto markets may be linked to the fresh updates announced by the team behind the project.</p>

<h2>Adoption Grows For Cosmos Replicated Security Model</h2>
<p>In an exciting update, the Cosmos team <a href="https://twitter.com/cosmos/status/1656678298473345024?t=hyo5tGVu8TcY9EAnVB5ZCw&amp;s=19" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">announced</a> yesterday that its first Replicated Security Model went live and has gained adoption by a top smart contract and consumer chain platform.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">1/ The first <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Cosmos?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#Cosmos</a> native shared security model just got adoption <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f4a5.png" alt="💥" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><a href="https://twitter.com/Neutron_org?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">@Neutron_org</a> is the first Consumer Chain to leverage <a href="https://twitter.com/cosmoshub?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">@cosmoshub</a> Replicated Security.</p>
<p>Replicated Security brings a new era of utility for <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/ATOM?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#ATOM</a> <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/269b.png" alt="⚛" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /></p>
<p>Appchains can now launch with the economic security of <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/ATOM?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#ATOM</a> <a href="https://t.co/sMp6mXhjPC" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/sMp6mXhjPC</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Cosmos &#8211; Internet of Blockchains <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/269b.png" alt="⚛" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> (@cosmos) <a href="https://twitter.com/cosmos/status/1656678298473345024?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">May 11, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p></p>
<p>Before this, the team had made it known in February that the launch of the Replicated security model was close and presented an opportunity for delegators and validators to earn multiple tokens from upcoming consumer chains by staking the native token ATOM.</p>
<p>The Cosmos Replicated security model, a new and secure innovation, provides security to smart contracts and consumer chain platforms. The team announced and introduced Neutron as the <a href="https://neutron.org/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">first</a> ever consumer chain and smart contracts platform to adopt and leverage its new and innovative Replicated security model.</p>
<p>In leveraging Cosmos&#8217; Replicated security model, smart contracts and consumer chains platforms like Neutron no longer worry about platform security but can now focus on other application areas and services, according to the official announcement.</p>
<p>As seen in an official tweet where the team made the announcement, it was also stated that the Replicated security model brings forth a new dawn and era of utility as dApps can now launch with ATOM&#8217;s native security.</p>
<p>This fundamental news by the Cosmos team could be the backing behind ATOM&#8217;s recent show of strength and price resilience despite the bearish market outlook observed in several cryptocurrencies.</p>

<h2>Daily Chart Analysis For ATOM</h2>
<p>Cosmos (ATOM) trades at $11.04, a 2.02% increase from its 24-hour low at $10.55, as seen from Coingecko data trading reports. The market capitalization of ATOM is also seen to increase by 1.10%.</p>
<p>On the daily timeframe, bulls pushed ATOM&#8217;s price above the key resistance at $10.90 and moved further to an $11.27 high before retracing.</p>
<p>The previous resistance turned support level on the daily price chart is a good area for bulls to build momentum and push ATOM&#8217;s price to the upside. Although the 50 and 200 Exponential Moving Averages (EMA) are an immediate resistance level, bulls must contend with them to confirm further upside movements.</p>
<p>To the downside, a break above the newfound support at $10.90 will signal further bearish movements for the asset.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/dsHP7zSj/" alt="Cosmos" width="1280" height="595" /></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Cosmos-460x329.jpg" width="460" height="329" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>MakerDAO Massive Upgrade, A New Era For DeFi?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/maker-mkr/makerdao-massive-upgrade-a-new-era-for-defi/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 19:30:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Maker (MKR)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DeFi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Maker DAO (MKR)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MakerDAO]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=532358</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[MakerDAO, the decentralized finance (DeFi) project behind the popular stablecoin DAI, has announced a major update called “Endgame.” Endgame is designed to enhance efficiency, resilience, and participation by applying fine-tuned AI tools to open scalable processes. The goal is to create a strong governance equilibrium that enables the permissionless growth of SubDAOs and parallelized product development in an emergent, community-driven ecosystem. Related Reading: Is This The Perfect Time To Buy Bitcoin? TD Sequential And RSI Suggests So Revolutionizing DeFi According to the announcement, The short-term objective of Endgame is to grow MakerDAO into the largest and most widely used stablecoin project within 3 years. From there, the project aims to anchor its growth in an autonomous DAO economy that ensures its growth can accelerate and safely reach any scale level without putting the resilient governance equilibrium at risk. To achieve this goal, Endgame will be launched in five successive phases. The first phase, called Phase 0, will focus on improving the scalability and efficiency of the Maker Protocol. This will involve upgrading the system&#8217;s architecture and deploying AI tools to optimize various processes. Phase 1 will introduce the SubDAO framework, enabling the creation of specialized DAOs that can operate independently or in conjunction with the MakerDAO governance structure. This will allow for parallelized product development and the emergence of a community-driven ecosystem. The SubDAOs are further divided into Facilitator &#38; Allocator DAOs, and their genesis tokens will be distributed through the NewStable farms. This will be supported by the Smart Burn Engine, which will accumulate and burn LP tokens for NewStable against NewGovToken using protocol surplus. Phase 2 will focus on enhancing the governance mechanism of MakerDAO to ensure that it remains resilient and adaptable as the project grows. This will involve the development of a comprehensive governance framework that incorporates the SubDAOs and ensures that they are aligned with the project&#8217;s overall goals. Phase 3 will introduce new collateral types to the Maker Protocol, expanding its use case and increasing its adoption. This will include integrating real-world assets, such as real estate and stocks, as collateral, providing new opportunities for investors and borrowers. Finally, Phase 4 will focus on the project&#8217;s long-term sustainability by introducing a decentralized treasury and investment strategy that will ensure the long-term growth and stability of the MakerDAO ecosystem. MakerDAO Biggest Upgrade Yet According to the analysis by the DeFi researcher under the pseudonym “DeFi Ignas,” To further streamline governance, MakerDAO is also introducing an AI Tools system to enable users to verify governance rules and processes or generate new governance proposals. The Sagittarius Lockstake Engine (SLE) will incentivize NewGovToken holders to participate in governance by locking their tokens and delegating their voting power to receive rewards as NewStable income or SubDAO tokens.  Governance participation is gamified for accessibility, which creates earning opportunities. Furthermore, To encourage participation in governance during challenging times, MakerDAO is imposing a 15% exit fee on locked tokens. Bootstrapping rewards will also be offered to join governance. Per DeFi Ignas Analysis, the native token for gas fees will be Savings-NewStable, a tokenized version of NewStable actively earning the Savings Rate. Consensus staking will be with NewGovToken through the Sagittarius Lockstake Engine. Overall, This latest upgrade announcement from MakerDAO represents a major step forward for the DeFi ecosystem. By reducing governance complexity and increasing efficiency, MakerDAO is positioning itself to become the world&#8217;s largest and most widely used stablecoin project while maintaining its resilience and adaptability in the face of rapidly changing market conditions and potential regulatory risks. According to DeFi Ignas, the ultimate aim is to create an Unbiased World Currency that is not necessarily pegged to the USD. Related Reading: Cardano (ADA) Bounces Back From The Red Zone, Will It Continue Minting Gains? Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MakerDAO, the decentralized finance (DeFi) project behind the popular stablecoin DAI, has announced a major update called “<a href="https://forum.makerdao.com/t/the-5-phases-of-endgame/20830" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Endgame</a>.” Endgame is designed to enhance efficiency, resilience, and participation by applying fine-tuned AI tools to open scalable processes. The goal is to create a strong governance equilibrium that enables the permissionless growth of SubDAOs and parallelized product development in an emergent, community-driven ecosystem.</p>

<h2><b>Revolutionizing DeFi</b></h2>
<p>According to the announcement, The short-term objective of Endgame is to grow MakerDAO into the largest and most widely used stablecoin project within 3 years. From there, the project aims to anchor its growth in an autonomous DAO economy that ensures its growth can accelerate and safely reach any scale level without putting the resilient governance equilibrium at risk.</p>
<p>To achieve this goal, Endgame will be launched in five successive phases. The first phase, called Phase 0, will focus on improving the scalability and efficiency of the Maker Protocol. This will involve upgrading the system&#8217;s architecture and deploying AI tools to optimize various processes.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">5 phases of Endgame.</p>
<p>Endgame has been defined as an update that employs AI tools and open processes to enhance efficiency, resilience, and participation.</p>
<p>A new publication on the Maker Forum outlines its roadmap, which includes the introduction of 5 major launch phases. <a href="https://t.co/8GOkIfFADi" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/8GOkIfFADi</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Maker (@MakerDAO) <a href="https://twitter.com/MakerDAO/status/1657019717499109376?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">May 12, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p></p>
<p>Phase 1 will introduce the SubDAO framework, enabling the creation of specialized DAOs that can operate independently or in conjunction with the MakerDAO governance structure. This will allow for parallelized product development and the emergence of a community-driven ecosystem.</p>
<p>The SubDAOs are further divided into Facilitator &amp; Allocator DAOs, and their genesis tokens will be distributed through the NewStable farms. This will be supported by the Smart Burn Engine, which will accumulate and burn LP tokens for NewStable against NewGovToken using protocol surplus.</p>
<p>Phase 2 will focus on enhancing the governance mechanism of MakerDAO to ensure that it remains resilient and adaptable as the project grows. This will involve the development of a comprehensive governance framework that incorporates the SubDAOs and ensures that they are aligned with the project&#8217;s overall goals.</p>
<p>Phase 3 will introduce new collateral types to the Maker Protocol, expanding its use case and increasing its adoption. This will include integrating real-world assets, such as real estate and stocks, as collateral, providing new opportunities for investors and borrowers.</p>
<p>Finally, Phase 4 will focus on the project&#8217;s long-term sustainability by introducing a decentralized treasury and investment strategy that will ensure the long-term growth and stability of the MakerDAO ecosystem.</p>
<b>MakerDAO Biggest Upgrade Yet</b>
<p><a href="https://twitter.com/DefiIgnas/status/1656903730145689602?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">According </a>to the analysis by the DeFi researcher under the pseudonym “DeFi Ignas,” To further streamline governance, MakerDAO is also introducing an AI Tools system to enable users to verify governance rules and processes or generate new governance proposals. </p>
<p>The Sagittarius Lockstake Engine (SLE) will incentivize NewGovToken holders to participate in governance by locking their tokens and delegating their voting power to receive rewards as NewStable income or SubDAO tokens. </p>
<p>Governance participation is gamified for accessibility, which creates earning opportunities. Furthermore, To encourage participation in governance during challenging times, MakerDAO is imposing a 15% exit fee on locked tokens. Bootstrapping rewards will also be offered to join governance.</p>
<p>Per DeFi Ignas Analysis, the native token for gas fees will be Savings-NewStable, a tokenized version of NewStable actively earning the Savings Rate. Consensus staking will be with NewGovToken through the Sagittarius Lockstake Engine.</p>
<p>Overall, This latest upgrade announcement from MakerDAO represents a major step forward for the DeFi ecosystem. By reducing governance complexity and increasing efficiency, MakerDAO is positioning itself to become the world&#8217;s largest and most widely used stablecoin project while maintaining its resilience and adaptability in the face of rapidly changing market conditions and potential regulatory risks. </p>
<p>According to DeFi Ignas, the ultimate aim is to create an Unbiased World Currency that is not necessarily pegged to the USD.</p>


<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/96PjgAQj/" alt="MakerDAO" width="1813" height="858" />
<p>Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/shubham-s-web3-Z-bxe4qXXMg-unsplash-345x460.jpg" width="345" height="460" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Plunges Below $27,000, Which Holder Groups Are Selling?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-plunges-below-27000-holder-groups-selling/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hououin Kyouma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 18:07:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin long-term holders]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Plunge]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Selling]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin short-term holders]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=532354</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin has plunged below the $27,000 mark during the past day. Here are the market segments that are possibly participating in this selloff. These Bitcoin Investors Have Been Spending Their Coins Recently In a new tweet, the on-chain analytics firm Glassnode has broken down the prices at which the average coins sold today were bought. Generally, the BTC market is divided into two main segments: the long-term holders (LTHs) and the short-term holders (STHs). The STHs comprise a cohort including all investors who acquired their Bitcoin within the last 155 days. The LTHs, on the other hand, are investors who have been holding for more than this threshold amount. In the context of the current discussion, the relevant indicator is the &#8220;dormancy average spending ranges,&#8221; which finds out the periods in which the average coins being spent/transferred by these two groups were first acquired. For example, if the metric shows the 7-day spending range for the LTHs as $20,000 to $30,000, it means that the coins these investors sold in the past week were initially bought at prices in this range. Related Reading: Is Pepe Coin Ready For Another Pump? Here’s What On-Chain Data Says Here is a chart showing the data for the current 7-day dormancy average spending ranges for the STHs and LTHs, as well for the combined market. The different average spending ranges of the main segments of the sector &#124; Source: Glassnode on Twitter The graph shows that the 7-day average spending range for the STHs is quite close to the current prices at $30,400 to $27,300. Some of these sellers bought at higher prices than those observed in the past week, so they must have been selling at a loss (although not a particularly deep one). The indicator puts the LTHs&#8217; acquisition range at $67,600 to $35,000. As highlighted in the chart, the timeframe of these purchases included the lead-up to the November 2021 price all-time high, the top itself, and the period when the decline towards the bear market first started. It would appear that these holders who bought at the high bull market prices have budged because of the pressure the cryptocurrency has been under lately and have finally decided to take their losses and move on. Generally, the longer an investor holds onto their coins, the less likely they become to sell at any point. This would perhaps explain why the acquisition timeframe of the current STHs is so recent; the fickle ones are those who have only been holding a short while. For the BTC LTHs, however, the probable reason why the acquisition period of the average seller from this group is so far back, rather than nearer to 155 days ago (the cutoff of the youngest LTHs), is that a lot of the younger LTHs would be in profits currently as they bought during the lower, bear-market prices. Related Reading: Does The Bitcoin Price Dump Signal The Start Of Another Bear Market? As such, the Bitcoin investors more likely to waver in their conviction right now would be those holding the most severe losses, the 2021 bull run top buyers. The chart also includes the 7-day average spending range for the combined BTC sector, and as one may expect, this range lies in the middle of the two cohorts ($15,800 to $28,500), but the timeframe is closer to the STHs, as a lot of the sellers are bound to be recent buyers. BTC Price At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading around $26,300, down 10% in the last week. Looks like BTC has taken a plunge during the past day &#124; Source: BTCUSD on TradingView Featured image from Kanchanara on Unsplash.com, charts from TradingView.com, Glassnode.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin has plunged below the $27,000 mark during the past day. Here are the market segments that are possibly participating in this selloff.</p>
<h2>These Bitcoin Investors Have Been Spending Their Coins Recently</h2>
<p>In a new tweet, the on-chain analytics firm <a href="https://twitter.com/glassnode/status/1656993194897276929" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Glassnode</a> has broken down the prices at which the average coins sold today were bought. Generally, the BTC market is divided into two main segments: the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-long-term-holders-holding-price-decline/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">long-term holders</a> (LTHs) and the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-short-term-holder-profit-nov-2021/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">short-term holders</a> (STHs).</p>
<p>The STHs comprise a cohort including all investors who acquired their Bitcoin within the last 155 days. The LTHs, on the other hand, are investors who have been holding for more than this threshold amount.</p>
<p>In the context of the current discussion, the relevant indicator is the &#8220;dormancy average spending ranges,&#8221; which finds out the periods in which the average coins being spent/transferred by these two groups were first acquired.</p>
<p>For example, if the metric shows the 7-day spending range for the LTHs as $20,000 to $30,000, it means that the coins these investors sold in the past week were initially bought at prices in this range.</p>

<p>Here is a chart showing the data for the current 7-day dormancy average spending ranges for the STHs and LTHs, as well for the combined market.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone aligncenter" src="https://pbs.twimg.com/media/Fv7SPtyXwAAuwpK?format=png&amp;name=4096x4096" alt="Bitcoin Sellers" width="4081" height="2350" /></p>

<p>The graph shows that the 7-day average spending range for the STHs is quite close to the current prices at $30,400 to $27,300. Some of these sellers bought at higher prices than those observed in the past week, so they must have been selling at a loss (although not a particularly deep one).</p>
<p>The indicator puts the LTHs&#8217; acquisition range at $67,600 to $35,000. As highlighted in the chart, the timeframe of these purchases included the lead-up to the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin-market-dominance-hit-highest-since-november-2021-no-alt-season-in-sight/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">November 2021 price all-time high</a>, the top itself, and the period when the decline towards the bear market first started.</p>
<p>It would appear that these holders who bought at the high bull market prices have budged because of the pressure the cryptocurrency has been under lately and have finally decided to take their losses and move on.</p>
<p>Generally, the longer an investor holds onto their coins, the less likely they become to sell at any point. This would perhaps explain why the acquisition timeframe of the current STHs is so recent; the fickle ones are those who have only been holding a short while.</p>
<p>For the BTC LTHs, however, the probable reason why the acquisition period of the average seller from this group is so far back, rather than nearer to 155 days ago (the cutoff of the youngest LTHs), is that a lot of the younger LTHs would be in profits currently as they bought during the lower, bear-market prices.</p>

<p>As such, the Bitcoin investors more likely to waver in their conviction right now would be those holding the most severe losses, the 2021 bull run top buyers.</p>
<p>The chart also includes the 7-day average spending range for the combined BTC sector, and as one may expect, this range lies in the middle of the two cohorts ($15,800 to $28,500), but the timeframe is closer to the STHs, as a lot of the sellers are bound to be recent buyers.</p>
<h2>BTC Price</h2>
<p>At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading around $26,300, down 10% in the last week.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium aligncenter" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/xuu5LLIR/" alt="Bitcoin Price Chart" width="1533" height="911" /></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/kanchanara-Lta5b8mPytw-unsplash-460x306.jpg" width="460" height="306" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Is This The Perfect Time To Buy Bitcoin? TD Sequential And RSI Suggests So</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/is-this-the-perfect-time-to-buy-bitcoin/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 16:30:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=532343</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) investors have been closely monitoring the cryptocurrency market in recent days due to Bitcoin&#8217;s significant drop in price. The market&#8217;s largest cryptocurrency has shown a downtrend in its price action and has lost its key support level at $27,200, which was previously noted by the 50-day moving average (MA). Despite the bearish trend, trader and analyst Ali suggests that there may be some hope for bulls. Though the market is currently in a state of decline, Ali believes that there is still a chance for BTC to experience a reversal shortly. Related Reading: Is Pepe Coin Ready For Another Pump? Here’s What On-Chain Data Says Buy The Bitcoin Dip? Ali points to the TD Sequential indicator on the Bitcoin 4-hour chart, which has shown a buy signal. In addition, a bullish divergence is developing on the Relative Strength Index (RSI), indicating a potential reversal shortly.  Bitcoin has been experiencing a period of volatility, with the cryptocurrency facing a strong resistance level at $28,000 in the past few days, following the release of the Consumer Price Index (CPI) rates by the Federal Reserve (Fed). Although trader and analyst Ali believes that if Bitcoin can hold above the $26,000 support level, there could be an upswing to either $26,860 or $27,570. On the other hand, Ali suggests that if Bitcoin fails to hold above the $26,000 level, it could trigger a further drop to $25,200. However, there is some good news for Bitcoin bulls, as the 200-day moving average (MA) is currently placed at $24,700. This level could potentially act as a crucial threshold for BTC, serving as a bottom line for the cryptocurrency in the short term. Bitcoin And Crypto Market Vulnerable To Short Squeeze? According to the latest report by the Singapore-based digital asset trading firm, QCP Capital, this week&#8217;s sell-off has caused Bitcoin to fall through the head and shoulders trendline, but a close below $26,500 is still preventing a larger breakdown. Additionally, Bitcoin has a negative divergence on momentum indicators, leading QCP Capital to be biased towards a near-term break lower, potentially to the $25,000 mark and then to the $20,000-$22,000 level. Despite this, QCP Capital views the lower level of $20,000-$22,000 as a high-conviction medium-term buy zone. The firm has even sold physically settled puts at this level before, indicating its confidence in the cryptocurrency&#8217;s long-term prospects. Related Reading: Key Support Levels To Monitor As Ethereum Price Slows Down Furthermore, according to Chart 3 in the report, as seen below, an increase in volatility has historically led to a strengthening of the USD and a weakening of risk assets such as BTC. The report notes that while the outcome of the current political drama in Washington is uncertain, the market&#8217;s response in terms of implied volatility across assets will be key in determining the next trend direction. The report also suggests that a sharp increase in volatility could lead to a move lower for BTC and other risk assets. This could be a concern for investors who have seen BTC reach new annual highs in 2023. However, volatility can create opportunities for traders who can navigate the market&#8217;s ups and downs. As of this writing, the largest cryptocurrency in the market, BTC, is currently trading at $26,300, down by 2.1% in the last 24 hours.  Featured image from iStock, a chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin (BTC) investors have been closely monitoring the cryptocurrency market in recent days due to Bitcoin&#8217;s significant drop in price. The market&#8217;s largest cryptocurrency has shown a downtrend in its price action and has lost its key support level at $27,200, which was previously noted by the 50-day moving average (MA).</p>
<p>Despite the bearish trend, trader and analyst Ali <a href="https://twitter.com/ali_charts/status/1656972586880839680?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">suggests</a> that there may be some hope for bulls. Though the market is currently in a state of decline, Ali believes that there is still a chance for BTC to experience a reversal shortly.</p>

<h2><b>Buy The Bitcoin Dip?</b></h2>
<p>Ali points to the TD Sequential indicator on the Bitcoin 4-hour chart, which has shown a buy signal. In addition, a bullish divergence is developing on the Relative Strength Index (RSI), indicating a potential reversal shortly. </p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large wp-image-532346" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Fv6_AtZWYAAIBlz-860x588.jpg" alt="Bitcoin " width="860" height="588" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Fv6_AtZWYAAIBlz-860x588.jpg 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Fv6_AtZWYAAIBlz-460x315.jpg 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Fv6_AtZWYAAIBlz-768x525.jpg 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Fv6_AtZWYAAIBlz-1536x1051.jpg 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Fv6_AtZWYAAIBlz-2048x1401.jpg 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Fv6_AtZWYAAIBlz-750x513.jpg 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Fv6_AtZWYAAIBlz-1140x780.jpg 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" />
<p>Bitcoin has been experiencing a period of volatility, with the cryptocurrency facing a strong resistance level at $28,000 in the past few days, following the release of the Consumer Price Index (CPI) rates by the Federal Reserve (Fed). </p>
<p>Although trader and analyst Ali believes that if Bitcoin can hold above the $26,000 support level, there could be an upswing to either $26,860 or $27,570. On the other hand, Ali suggests that if Bitcoin fails to hold above the $26,000 level, it could trigger a further drop to $25,200. </p>
<p>However, there is some good news for Bitcoin bulls, as the 200-day moving average (MA) is currently placed at $24,700. This level could potentially act as a crucial threshold for BTC, serving as a bottom line for the cryptocurrency in the short term.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin And Crypto Market Vulnerable To Short Squeeze?</h2>
<p>According to the latest <a href="https://qcp.capital/featured-article/market-update-12-may-23/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">report </a>by the Singapore-based digital asset trading firm, QCP Capital, this week&#8217;s sell-off has caused Bitcoin to fall through the head and shoulders trendline, but a close below $26,500 is still preventing a larger breakdown. </p>
<p>Additionally, Bitcoin has a negative divergence on momentum indicators, leading QCP Capital to be biased towards a near-term break lower, potentially to the $25,000 mark and then to the $20,000-$22,000 level.</p>
<p>Despite this, QCP Capital views the lower level of $20,000-$22,000 as a high-conviction medium-term buy zone. The firm has even sold physically settled puts at this level before, indicating its confidence in the cryptocurrency&#8217;s long-term prospects.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/ethereum/key-support-levels-to-monitor-as-ethereum-price-slows-down/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Key Support Levels To Monitor As Ethereum Price Slows Down</a></p>
<p>Furthermore, according to Chart 3 in the report, as seen below, an increase in volatility has historically led to a strengthening of the USD and a weakening of risk assets such as BTC. </p>
<p>The report notes that while the outcome of the current political drama in Washington is uncertain, the market&#8217;s response in terms of implied volatility across assets will be key in determining the next trend direction.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large wp-image-532347" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Chart-3-2-1-860x492.jpeg" alt="Bitcoin " width="860" height="492" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Chart-3-2-1-860x492.jpeg 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Chart-3-2-1-460x263.jpeg 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Chart-3-2-1-768x439.jpeg 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Chart-3-2-1-750x429.jpeg 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Chart-3-2-1-1140x652.jpeg 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Chart-3-2-1.jpeg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" />
<p>The report also suggests that a sharp increase in volatility could lead to a move lower for BTC and other risk assets. This could be a concern for investors who have seen BTC reach new annual highs in 2023. However, volatility can create opportunities for traders who can navigate the market&#8217;s ups and downs.</p>
<p>As of this writing, the largest cryptocurrency in the market, BTC, is currently trading at $26,300, down by 2.1% in the last 24 hours. </p>

<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/Thnc6Z0p/" alt="Bitcoin " width="1813" height="858" />
<p>Featured image from iStock, a chart from TradingView.com </p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/iStock-1305769484-1-460x272.jpg" width="460" height="272" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cardano (ADA) Bounces Back From The Red Zone, Will It Continue Minting Gains?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/cardano/cardano-ada-bounces-back-from-the-red-zone-will-it-continue-minting-gains/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Eli Dambel]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 15:40:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cardano]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADAUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[api]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hydra Head]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=532336</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Cardano is gaining slightly today as the bulls seek to rally out of the bearish zone. Its trading volume is down by over 15%, but its price has entered a consolidation phase. ADA is trading above its 7-day low of $0.3512, implying that a return to the 7-day high of $0.3967 remains possible.  ADA Price Prediction ADA is in a sideways trend today, staying above its 200-day Simple Moving Average (SMA) as the bulls seek to push it to an uptrend. Its price action in the last three days shows that the bears and bulls are even in the market. However, it is below the 50-day SMA, a short-term bearish sentiment for the asset.  Related Reading: Cardano May Sink To This Level As Bears Keep Gaining Leverage Also, the Relative Strength Index (RSI) is 40.70 in the neutral zone and moving upwards. The RSI suggests that the bulls will likely reclaim control of the asset’s price action in the coming days.  ADA’s Moving Average Convergence/Divergence (MACD) is below its signal line and showing negative values. It is a bearish sentiment for the asset, although the histogram bars are fading, hinting at a possible recovery.  ADA has found strong support at the $0.3606 price level for some days, shielding it from dropping to the next support level of $0.3453. Based on its historical behavior, it will likely rally off this support level to break the $0.3767 resistance and test the next resistance level of $0.3945. Expect a positive trend soon if ADA rallies above the $0.3767 resistance.  Trends On Cardano Network Cardano is a renowned developers&#8217; hub committed to innovative network developments and trends that benefit its community. #Cardano&#39;s recent upgrades are improving interoperability, scalability and sustainability, making it an attractive blockchain for developers creating DApps. In this blog, we look at the Valentine signature changes, dynamic P2P, Hydra, and more.https://t.co/I0od7Czu38 &#8212; Input Output (@InputOutputHK) May 8, 2023 The recent Hydra upgrade is one of the trends that will likely improve its price performance moving forward.  According to the lead Cardano developers, Input Output, Hydra is a family of protocols built to improve network scalability. It functions as an off-chain mini-ledger for a small community similar to the original on-chain ledger but maximizes speed and is cost-efficient. Hydra uses smart contracts to interact with its users, processing activities like bank transfers, NFT auctions, and lightweight payments.  Hydra Head is scalable, and its applications can run off-chain relieving the main chain of load and improving throughput. Also, its transactions are faster than the main chain Cardano layer 1 (L1) transactions. Related Reading: Does The Bitcoin Price Dump Signal The Start Of Another Bear Market? Cardano has also launched the first mainnet-compatible Hydra node, version 0.10.0, a Cardano developer, Sebastian Nagel, revealed.  He noted that the API was updated to accommodate the first round of user requests. Nagel further released a link to the Hydra Head Roadmap for the community. Featured image from Pixabay and chart from Tradingview.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Cardano is <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/cardano/" rel="nofollow">gaining slightly today</a> as the bulls seek to rally out of the bearish zone. Its trading volume is down by over 15%, but its price has entered a consolidation phase.</p>
<p>ADA is trading above its 7-day low of $0.3512, implying that a return to the 7-day high of $0.3967 remains possible. </p>
<h2>ADA Price Prediction</h2>
<p>ADA is in a sideways trend today, staying above its 200-day Simple Moving Average (SMA) as the bulls seek to push it to an uptrend. Its price action in the last three days shows that the bears and bulls are even in the market. However, it is below the 50-day SMA, a short-term bearish sentiment for the asset. </p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/cardano/cardano-may-sink-to-this-level-as-bears-keep-gaining-leverage/">Cardano May Sink To This Level As Bears Keep Gaining Leverage</a></p>
<p>Also, the Relative Strength Index (RSI) is 40.70 in the neutral zone and moving upwards. The RSI suggests that the bulls will likely reclaim control of the asset’s price action in the coming days. </p>
<p>ADA’s Moving Average Convergence/Divergence (MACD) is below its signal line and showing negative values. It is a bearish sentiment for the asset, although the histogram bars are fading, hinting at a possible recovery. </p>
<p>ADA has found strong support at the $0.3606 price level for some days, shielding it from dropping to the next support level of $0.3453.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-532340 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ADAUSDT_2023-05-12_19-32-13-860x471.png" alt="Cardano (ADA) Bounces Back From The Red Zone, Will It Continue Minting Gains?" width="860" height="471" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ADAUSDT_2023-05-12_19-32-13-860x471.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ADAUSDT_2023-05-12_19-32-13-460x252.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ADAUSDT_2023-05-12_19-32-13-768x420.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ADAUSDT_2023-05-12_19-32-13-750x411.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ADAUSDT_2023-05-12_19-32-13-1140x624.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ADAUSDT_2023-05-12_19-32-13.png 1529w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" />
<p>Based on its historical behavior, it will likely rally off this support level to break the $0.3767 resistance and test the next resistance level of $0.3945. Expect a positive trend soon if ADA rallies above the $0.3767 resistance. </p>
<h2>Trends On Cardano Network</h2>
<p>Cardano is a renowned developers&#8217; hub committed to innovative network developments and trends that benefit its community.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr"><a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Cardano?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#Cardano</a>&#39;s recent upgrades are improving interoperability, scalability and sustainability, making it an attractive blockchain for developers creating DApps. In this blog, we look at the Valentine signature changes, dynamic P2P, Hydra, and more.<a href="https://t.co/I0od7Czu38" rel="nofollow">https://t.co/I0od7Czu38</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Input Output (@InputOutputHK) <a href="https://twitter.com/InputOutputHK/status/1655615561185853440?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">May 8, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p></p>
<p>The recent Hydra upgrade is one of the trends that will likely improve its price performance moving forward. </p>
<p>According to the lead Cardano developers, Input Output, Hydra is a family of protocols built to improve network scalability. It functions as an off-chain mini-ledger for a small community similar to the original on-chain ledger but maximizes speed and is cost-efficient.</p>
<p>Hydra uses smart contracts to <a href="https://t.co/LHrXHqoMiz" rel="nofollow">interact with its users</a>, processing activities like bank transfers, NFT auctions, and lightweight payments. </p>
<p>Hydra Head is <a href="https://twitter.com/InputOutputHK/status/1618592846176751621" rel="nofollow">scalable</a>, and its applications can run off-chain relieving the main chain of load and improving throughput. Also, its transactions are faster than the main chain Cardano layer 1 (L1) transactions.</p>

<p><a href="https://www.essentialcardano.io/article/cardano-advances-with-valentine-upgrade-and-zippier-p2p-nodes" rel="nofollow">Cardano</a> has also launched the first mainnet-compatible Hydra node, version 0.10.0, a Cardano developer, Sebastian Nagel, revealed. </p>
<p>He noted that the API was updated to accommodate the first round of user requests. Nagel further <a href="https://github.com/orgs/input-output-hk/projects/21/views/7" rel="nofollow">released a link</a> to the Hydra Head Roadmap for the community.</p>
<p>Featured image from Pixabay and chart from Tradingview.com</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/cardano-g57d2ba5c1_1280-460x230.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Is Pepe Coin Ready For Another Pump? Here&#8217;s What On-Chain Data Says</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/pepe/pepe-coin-ready-another-pump-on-chain-data/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hououin Kyouma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 14:50:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[PEPE]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[memecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Pepe Coin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PEPE Pump]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[pepeusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=532237</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Here&#8217;s what the different on-chain indicators from Santiment have to say about whether Pepe Coin could see another pump soon or not. The Memecoin&#8217;s On-Chain Metrics Have Been Down Since The Top PEPE has been one of the hottest topics around the cryptocurrency market recently, thanks to the explosive growth that the meme coin has enjoyed. Between the end of last month and the 5th of May, the coin saw its price rise by an extraordinary 1,200%. The uptrend, however, ended there and the cryptocurrency has been sharply plunging since then. According to Santiment, the on-chain analytics firm&#8217;s &#8220;social dominance&#8221; indicator signaled this top in advance. Social dominance tells us what percentage of the discussions happening on social media related to the top 100 cryptocurrencies by market cap are talking about a given coin. As the below chart shows, Pepe&#8217;s social dominance rose to very high values just before the top took form earlier in the month. Looks like the value of the metric has come down in recent days &#124; Source: Santiment Whenever social dominance hits high levels, it&#8217;s a sign of euphoria among investors, which is something that has historically led to top formations for cryptocurrencies. Santiment notes that the indicator still has a value of about 5%, meaning that 5% of all discussions related to the top 100 assets involve the meme coin currently. &#8220;Seeing it get down to the 1-2% range would be a good sign that traders are beginning to stray away and look for pumps from other altcoins,&#8221; the firm explains. The active addresses metric, which measures the total number of unique addresses taking part in some transaction activity on the blockchain, also saw a spike just before the top. The metric seems to have calmed down &#124; Source: Santiment When this indicator has a high value, it means a large number of investors are making trades right now. The price generally becomes more likely to get volatile when the metric shows such a trend. From the chart, it&#8217;s visible that the active addresses indicator has come down in value for PEPE in the last few days, which means that the market activity has calmed down. Related Reading: Bitcoin Rebounds From $27,100 After Spike In Bearish Sentiment An interesting trend is also visible in the data for the supply of the largest Pepe Coin holders, as the below graph displays. The holdings of the memecoin's whales &#124; Source: Santiment These humongous holders had been accumulating while the rally had been going on, but right as the top took form, they started shedding coins from their wallets. Related Reading: Does The Bitcoin Price Dump Signal The Start Of Another Bear Market? This cohort has continued to sell since then as PEPE&#8217;s value has gone downhill. &#8220;If you start seeing these lines moving up again, there is a much larger probability of PEPE going for its 2nd round of pumping (though probably a more minor one),&#8221; explains Santiment. One positive sign for the asset, however, may be that the trading volume has rebounded recently after having declined since the top (just like the other metrics). The trading volume of the asset &#124; Source: Santiment &#8220;All in all, meme coins have to be taken for what they are. They&#8217;re controlled by speculation and crowd expectations,&#8221; says the analytics firm. &#8220;In these fresh, new assets that fit this description, you&#8217;ll likely want to watch when the crowd gets too emphatic that one price direction is going to happen.&#8221; PEPE Price At the time of writing, Pepe Coin is trading around $0.000001251, down 37% in the last week. The asset continues to decline &#124; Source: PEPEUSD on TradingView Featured image from iStock.com, charts from TradingView.com, Santiment.net]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Here&#8217;s what the different on-chain indicators from Santiment have to say about whether Pepe Coin could see another pump soon or not.</p>
<h2>The Memecoin&#8217;s On-Chain Metrics Have Been Down Since The Top</h2>
<p>PEPE has been one of the hottest topics around the cryptocurrency market recently, thanks to the explosive growth that the meme coin has enjoyed. Between the end of last month and the 5th of May, the coin saw its price rise by an extraordinary 1,200%.</p>
<p>The uptrend, however, ended there and the cryptocurrency has been sharply plunging since then. According to <a href="https://twitter.com/santimentfeed/status/1656843270851555330" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Santiment</a>, the on-chain analytics firm&#8217;s &#8220;<a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/altcoin/internet-computer-icp-social-dominance-hits-top-in/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">social dominance</a>&#8221; indicator signaled this top in advance.</p>
<p>Social dominance tells us what percentage of the discussions happening on social media related to the top 100 cryptocurrencies by market cap are talking about a given coin.</p>
<p>As the below chart shows, Pepe&#8217;s social dominance rose to very high values just before the top took form earlier in the month.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone aligncenter" src="https://production-sanbase-images.s3.amazonaws.com/uploads/115a7e7cd85e4c49b693e8369b3ac1b539598e6724afa2a05303829d042cfdf5_1683854398246_Screenshot%202023-05-11%20181948.png" alt="Pepe Coin Social Dominance" width="3274" height="1671" /></p>

<p>Whenever social dominance hits high levels, it&#8217;s a sign of euphoria among investors, which is something that has historically led to top formations for cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p>Santiment notes that the indicator still has a value of about 5%, meaning that 5% of all discussions related to the top 100 assets involve the meme coin currently.</p>
<p>&#8220;Seeing it get down to the 1-2% range would be a good sign that traders are beginning to stray away and look for pumps from other altcoins,&#8221; the firm explains.</p>
<p>The <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/ethereum/ethereum-active-addresses-highest-may-2021-eth/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">active addresses</a> metric, which measures the total number of unique addresses taking part in some transaction activity on the blockchain, also saw a spike just before the top.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone aligncenter" src="https://production-sanbase-images.s3.amazonaws.com/uploads/b0d48af89836baa2ba598ba75183b8d86dcce2c0988af465d73b07c2430b6f8c_1683854415460_Screenshot%202023-05-11%20181852.png" alt="Pepe Active Addresses" width="3256" height="1669" /></p>

<p>When this indicator has a high value, it means a large number of investors are making trades right now. The price generally becomes more likely to get volatile when the metric shows such a trend.</p>
<p>From the chart, it&#8217;s visible that the active addresses indicator has come down in value for PEPE in the last few days, which means that the market activity has calmed down.</p>

<p>An interesting trend is also visible in the data for the supply of the largest Pepe Coin holders, as the below graph displays.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone aligncenter" src="https://production-sanbase-images.s3.amazonaws.com/uploads/a8801e927a52a1d62b217d6f147fc50d3384556a18bf6d71b18624ad5e3a671d_1683854471702_Screenshot%202023-05-11%20181253.png" alt="Pepe Coin Whales" width="3270" height="1669" /></p>

<p>These humongous holders had been accumulating while the rally had been going on, but right as the top took form, they started shedding coins from their wallets.</p>

<p>This cohort has continued to sell since then as PEPE&#8217;s value has gone downhill. &#8220;If you start seeing these lines moving up again, there is a much larger probability of PEPE going for its 2nd round of pumping (though probably a more minor one),&#8221; explains Santiment.</p>
<p>One positive sign for the asset, however, may be that the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/xrp-trading-volume-slumps-while-price-gains/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">trading volume</a> has rebounded recently after having declined since the top (just like the other metrics). <img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone aligncenter" src="https://production-sanbase-images.s3.amazonaws.com/uploads/3a51177020d7c96af5468b25fc140620f5a8b69143510d5f37efa191f843aa88_1683854484254_Screenshot%202023-05-11%20180821.png" alt="Trading Volume" width="3265" height="1663" /></p>

<p>&#8220;All in all, meme coins have to be taken for what they are. They&#8217;re controlled by speculation and crowd expectations,&#8221; says the analytics firm. &#8220;In these fresh, new assets that fit this description, you&#8217;ll likely want to watch when the crowd gets too emphatic that one price direction is going to happen.&#8221;</p>
<h2>PEPE Price</h2>
<p>At the time of writing, Pepe Coin is trading around $0.000001251, down 37% in the last week.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium aligncenter" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/cD4bxABV/" alt="Pepe Price Chart" width="1533" height="911" /></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/iStock-1429119108-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Key Support Levels To Monitor As Ethereum Price Slows Down</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/ethereum/key-support-levels-to-monitor-as-ethereum-price-slows-down/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[anushsamal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 13:48:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=532300</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Ethereum price consolidation weakened as the bulls lost momentum, resulting in a nearly 4% loss in the last 24 hours and a 7% decline on the weekly chart. The technical analysis indicates considerable bearish pressure. The coin&#8217;s value remained stagnant at around $1,800, leading to waning interest from buyers and a significant decrease in demand and accumulation. As Bitcoin dropped below $26,000, major altcoins also experienced significant declines on their daily charts. Related Reading: Cardano May Sink To This Level As Bears Keep Gaining Leverage To break its resistance, Ethereum requires substantial buyer participation, as failure to do so could lead to the loss of a crucial support level. Additionally, Bitcoin must recover and reach the $27,000 zone to initiate a short-term recovery for ETH. The declining market capitalization of Ethereum suggests a gradual departure of buyers from the market. Ethereum Price Analysis: One-Day Chart At the time of writing, ETH was priced at $1,770. After struggling around the $1,800 range, selling pressure eventually took over. The coin&#8217;s resistance levels were identified at $1,798 and $1,821. Conversely, if the price continues to decline, the bulls will attempt to defend ETH at $1,740. However, a failure to hold above $1,740 would push Ethereum down to $1,690. A further drop would breach the $1,540 support line. Additionally, the recent session saw a significant increase in selling strength, reflected by the red volume of Ethereum traded. Technical Analysis Following the decline from the $1,800 range, ETH has experienced a significant sell-off with a lack of recovery in buying strength. The Relative Strength Index (RSI) dipped below 40, suggesting a decrease in accumulation and nearing oversold territory. Additionally, ETH dropped below the 20-Simple Moving Average (SMA) line, indicating that sellers have been driving the market momentum. If ETH successfully surpasses the immediate resistance level, there is a possibility of moving above the 20-SMA line. Several technical indicators on the daily chart of Ethereum began showing sell signals. One of these indicators is the Awesome Oscillator, which not only reflects price momentum but also identifies potential trend reversals. In this case, the indicator displayed growing red histograms below the half-line, indicating sell signals for the altcoin. This suggests a potential decline in price before any recovery takes place. Related Reading: Does The Bitcoin Price Dump Signal The Start Of Another Bear Market? Another indicator, the Bollinger Bands, which reveal price fluctuation and volatility, started widening. This widening suggests that Ethereum could experience increased price volatility and fluctuations in the upcoming trading sessions. This heightened volatility indicates the potential for significant price movements in either direction. Ethereum has to topple over its immediate resistance in order to stall the bears. In addition to that, broader market strength will also prove to be crucial for ETH. Featured Image From UnSplash, Charts From TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Ethereum price consolidation weakened as the bulls lost momentum, resulting in a nearly 4% loss in the last 24 hours and a 7% decline on the weekly chart. The technical analysis indicates considerable bearish pressure.</p>
<p>The coin&#8217;s value remained stagnant at around $1,800, leading to waning interest from buyers and a significant decrease in demand and accumulation. As Bitcoin dropped below $26,000, major altcoins also experienced significant declines on their daily charts.</p>

<p>To break its resistance, Ethereum requires substantial buyer participation, as failure to do so could lead to the loss of a crucial support level.</p>
<p>Additionally, Bitcoin must recover and reach the $27,000 zone to initiate a short-term recovery for ETH. The declining market capitalization of Ethereum suggests a gradual departure of buyers from the market.</p>
<h2>Ethereum Price Analysis: One-Day Chart</h2>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-532308 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ETHUSD_2023-05-12_18-11-56.png" alt="Ethereum" width="1816" height="830" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ETHUSD_2023-05-12_18-11-56.png 1816w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ETHUSD_2023-05-12_18-11-56-460x210.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ETHUSD_2023-05-12_18-11-56-860x393.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ETHUSD_2023-05-12_18-11-56-768x351.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ETHUSD_2023-05-12_18-11-56-1536x702.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ETHUSD_2023-05-12_18-11-56-750x343.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ETHUSD_2023-05-12_18-11-56-1140x521.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1816px) 100vw, 1816px" />
<p>At the time of writing, ETH was priced at $1,770. After struggling around the $1,800 range, selling pressure eventually took over. The coin&#8217;s resistance levels were identified at $1,798 and $1,821. Conversely, if the price continues to decline, the bulls will attempt to defend ETH at $1,740.</p>
<p>However, a failure to hold above $1,740 would push Ethereum down to $1,690. A further drop would breach the $1,540 support line. Additionally, the recent session saw a significant increase in selling strength, reflected by the red volume of Ethereum traded.</p>
<h2>Technical Analysis</h2>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-532311 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ETHUSD_2023-05-12_18-12-27.png" alt="Ethereum" width="1816" height="743" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ETHUSD_2023-05-12_18-12-27.png 1816w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ETHUSD_2023-05-12_18-12-27-460x188.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ETHUSD_2023-05-12_18-12-27-860x352.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ETHUSD_2023-05-12_18-12-27-768x314.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ETHUSD_2023-05-12_18-12-27-1536x628.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ETHUSD_2023-05-12_18-12-27-750x307.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ETHUSD_2023-05-12_18-12-27-1140x466.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1816px) 100vw, 1816px" />
<p>Following the decline from the $1,800 range, ETH has experienced a significant sell-off with a lack of recovery in buying strength. The Relative Strength Index (RSI) dipped below 40, suggesting a decrease in accumulation and nearing oversold territory.</p>
<p>Additionally, ETH dropped below the 20-Simple Moving Average (SMA) line, indicating that sellers have been driving the market momentum. If ETH successfully surpasses the immediate resistance level, there is a possibility of moving above the 20-SMA line.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-532315 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ETHUSD_2023-05-12_18-12-50.png" alt="Ethereum" width="1816" height="743" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ETHUSD_2023-05-12_18-12-50.png 1816w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ETHUSD_2023-05-12_18-12-50-460x188.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ETHUSD_2023-05-12_18-12-50-860x352.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ETHUSD_2023-05-12_18-12-50-768x314.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ETHUSD_2023-05-12_18-12-50-1536x628.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ETHUSD_2023-05-12_18-12-50-750x307.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ETHUSD_2023-05-12_18-12-50-1140x466.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1816px) 100vw, 1816px" />
<p>Several technical indicators on the daily chart of Ethereum began showing sell signals. One of these indicators is the Awesome Oscillator, which not only reflects price momentum but also identifies potential trend reversals.</p>
<p>In this case, the indicator displayed growing red histograms below the half-line, indicating sell signals for the altcoin. This suggests a potential decline in price before any recovery takes place.</p>

<p>Another indicator, the Bollinger Bands, which reveal price fluctuation and volatility, started widening. This widening suggests that Ethereum could experience increased price volatility and fluctuations in the upcoming trading sessions.</p>
<p>This heightened volatility indicates the potential for significant price movements in either direction. Ethereum has to topple over its immediate resistance in order to stall the bears. In addition to that, broader market strength will also prove to be crucial for ETH.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/kanchanara-7cmA9ZL5dDk-unsplash-460x306.jpg" width="460" height="306" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Total Liquidation Surpasses $140 Million As Bitcoin (BTC) Continues Downtrend</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/total-liquidation-140-million-bitcoin-btc-continues-downtrend/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Edyme]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 12:40:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[OKX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PEPE]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=532291</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The crypto market experienced a significant downturn over the past 24 hours, leading to a total liquidation of over $140 million as Bitcoin (BTC) continues its downtrend. According to data from Coinglass, a record of approximately 57,585 traders have been liquidated, and the total value is still counting. Notably, traders that are currently experiencing major losses with the overall downward trend of the crypto market are those who have taken long positions, speculating that the market will eventually trend upwards. Largest Liquidations On OKX And Binance Digital asset exchanges OKX and Binance recorded the largest amount of liquidations, accounting for $48.3 million and $44.94 million, respectively. The data further reveals that long liquidations amounted to approximately $114.8 million of the total liquidations, whereas short liquidations were $29.8 million.  Long liquidations accounted for 79.39% of the total liquidations in the past 24 hours while short liquidation accounted for 25.96%. Bitcoin (BTC) was the most affected cryptocurrency, accounting for $50.97 million of the total liquidation.  Related Reading: Why This Top Financial Expert Is Saying ‘Buy Bitcoin’ Amid Looming Bank Failures Altcoins such as Ethereum (ETH) closely followed, with $30.29 million in liquidations, while the frog-themed meme coin PEPE accounted for over $7 million. Meanwhile, the largest single liquidation occurred on OKX with a BTC-USDT swap valued at $2.61 million. It is worth noting these figures confirm that the ongoing market downturn is affecting both long and short positions. Bitcoin And PEPE Plunges The global crypto market cap has also slumped below the $1.2 trillion mark with a value of $1.14 trillion at the time of writing, down by nearly 2.5% in the last 24 hours. This decline follows the plummet from Bitcoin and the recently hyped memecoin PEPE which plunged over 20% in the past 24 hours with more than $100 million subtracted from its market capitalization. Interestingly, PEPE&#8217;s trading volume has surged in the past 24 hours indicating a possible violent sell-off. Its daily trading volume has moved from $408 million as of yesterday to $647 million in the last 24 hours. Related Reading: Crypto Whale Suffers $500,000 Loss As PEPE Price Plummets Top crypto Bitcoin has also lost more than $20 billion from its market cap in the past 24 hours, down by nearly 4%, indicating selling pressure. Though Bitcoin recorded a surge in April that pushed its price to trade above $30,000, the asset has seen a bearish trend since then. The causes of the current market downturn are not entirely clear, however, it can be attributed to the US government&#8217;s recent decision to increase interest rates earlier this month may have contributed to the sell-off. Featured image from Unsplash, Chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The crypto market experienced a significant downturn over the past 24 hours, leading to a total liquidation of over $140 million as <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-btc-continues-downtrend-despite-daily-transactions/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Bitcoin (BTC) continues its downtrend</a>. According to <a href="https://www.coinglass.com/LiquidationData" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">data</a> from Coinglass, a record of approximately 57,585 traders have been liquidated, and the total value is still counting.</p>
<p>Notably, traders that are currently experiencing major losses with the overall downward trend of the crypto market are those who have taken long positions, speculating that the market will eventually trend upwards.</p>
<h2>Largest Liquidations On OKX And Binance</h2>
<p>Digital asset exchanges OKX and Binance recorded the largest amount of liquidations, accounting for $48.3 million and $44.94 million, respectively. The data further reveals that long liquidations amounted to approximately $114.8 million of the total liquidations, whereas short liquidations were $29.8 million. </p>
<p>Long liquidations accounted for 79.39% of the total liquidations in the past 24 hours while short liquidation accounted for 25.96%. Bitcoin (BTC) was the most affected cryptocurrency, accounting for $50.97 million of the total liquidation. </p>

<p>Altcoins such as <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/ethereum/ethereum-transaction-fees-hit-may-2022-highs/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Ethereum (ETH)</a> closely followed, with $30.29 million in liquidations, while the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/altcoin/discovering-the-next-pepe-and-shib-whales-to-keep-track-of/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">frog-themed meme coin PEPE</a> accounted for over $7 million. Meanwhile, the largest single liquidation occurred on OKX with a BTC-USDT swap valued at $2.61 million.</p>
<p>It is worth noting these figures confirm that the ongoing market downturn is affecting both long and short positions.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin And PEPE Plunges</h2>
<p>The global crypto market cap has also slumped below the $1.2 trillion mark with a value of $1.14 trillion at the time of writing, down by nearly 2.5% in the last 24 hours.</p>
<p>This decline follows the plummet from <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/all/top-financial-expert-bernstein-says-buy-bitcoin/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Bitcoin</a> and the recently hyped memecoin PEPE which plunged over 20% in the past 24 hours with more than $100 million subtracted from its market capitalization.</p>
<p>Interestingly, PEPE&#8217;s trading volume has surged in the past 24 hours indicating a possible violent sell-off. Its daily trading volume has moved from $408 million as of yesterday to $647 million in the last 24 hours.</p>

<p>Top crypto Bitcoin has also lost more than $20 billion from its market cap in the past 24 hours, down by nearly 4%, indicating selling pressure. Though Bitcoin recorded a surge in April that pushed its price to trade above $30,000, the asset has seen a bearish trend since then.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/PPDvG5yY/" alt="Bitcoin’s (BTC) price chart on TradingView" width="2768" height="1556" />
<p>The causes of the current market downturn are not entirely clear, however, it can be attributed to the US government&#8217;s recent decision to <a href="https://money.com/current-mortgage-rates/#:~:text=Mortgage%20rate%20trends&amp;text=The%20current%20rate%20for%20a,higher%20over%20the%20past%20week." target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">increase interest rates</a> earlier this month may have contributed to the sell-off. </p>
<p>Featured image from Unsplash, Chart from TradingView</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Optimism-460x259.jpeg" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Lisk Foundation To Convert 1,000 Bitcoin To ETH, Reason To Worry?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/lisk-foundation-to-convert-1000-bitcoin-to-eth/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jake Simmons]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 11:50:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=532261</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Max Kordek, the co-founder and CEO of Lisk recently announced via Twitter that the Lisk Foundation will convert 1,000 Bitcoin (BTC) to Ethereum (ETH) in the next 10 weeks, which will be held as part of the foundation&#8217;s long-term treasury. As Kordek explained in a commentary, the Lisk Foundation wants to stake its ETH, &#8220;but it won&#8217;t happen right away.&#8221; The project gained wider notoriety during the Initial Coin Offering (ICO) craze in 2016 and 2017. At the time, the decentralized apps platform raised 14,000 Bitcoin. That sum was worth about $5.7 million at the time, making the campaign the second most successful cryptocurrency crowdfunding to that point. With a market cap of $106 million, the Lisk Token (LSK) ranks 195th among the largest cryptocurrencies according to CoinMarketCap today. At press time, LSK was trading at $0.828 and is down 5.7% in the last 24 hours. Reasons Why Lisk Is Converting Bitcoin To ETH Lisk Foundation will sell 1,000 BTC in chunks of 100 BTC per week to reduce risks with related third parties. Subsequently, the purchased ETH will be deposited into a 2-of-3 multisig account, with each Lisk Foundation board member holding one key each. Related Reading: Why Is Bitcoin And The Crypto Market Down Today? Notably, the project will keep 500 BTC, which the co-founder said will be used to pay expenses in 2024 and 2025. Moreover, Kordek added that the Lisk Foundation has &#8220;about enough fiat until the next Bitcoin halving.&#8221; According to Kordek, there are three reasons for this move: first, the tweet states that Ethereum is the largest blockchain platform in the world. &#8220;Treasury-wise we want to go where blockchain applications are being built,&#8221; Kordek wrote, emphasizing as a second reason that ETH has &#8220;acceptable risks&#8221; from a Treasury wise point of view. Related Reading: Winner Takes All: Bitcoin And DXY Compete For Global Financial Dominance Third, he said, it allows for a sustainable, long-term return (via staking). &#8220;Treasury-wise it makes sense to go into an appreciating, deflationary, yield-generating asset,&#8221; Kordek said. The Lisk Foundation is exchanging 1000 BTC into ETH over the next 10 weeks and will hold onto them as part of its long-term treasury. 🧵 Continue reading to learn more.. How: The 1000 BTC are being sold in chunks of 100 BTC per week to reduce risks with associated… &#8212; Max Kordek (@maxkordek) May 11, 2023 Will It Have An Impact On BTC Price? Even though the Bitcoin and crypto market is very illiquid due to Operation Choke Point 2.0 in the United States at the moment, the impact on the Bitcoin price should be marginal due to the 1,000 BTC split over 10 weeks. 100 BTC is an order size that the market can easily digest. In the last 24 hours, the trading volume of BTC was approximately 19.4 billion. At press time, the Bitcoin price was at $26,388. For now, the key support is at the 100-day Exponential Moving Average (EMA), located at $26,227. Over the next few hours, it remains to be seen if this support can be held, if not, the area at $25,200 comes into focus. Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Max Kordek, the co-founder and CEO of Lisk recently <a href="https://twitter.com/maxkordek/status/1656629386689363970?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">announced</a> via Twitter that the Lisk Foundation will convert 1,000 Bitcoin (BTC) to Ethereum (ETH) in the next 10 weeks, which will be held as part of the foundation&#8217;s long-term treasury. As Kordek explained in a commentary, the Lisk Foundation wants to stake its ETH, &#8220;but it won&#8217;t happen right away.&#8221;</p>
<p>The project gained wider notoriety during the Initial Coin Offering (ICO) craze in 2016 and 2017. At the time, the decentralized apps platform raised 14,000 Bitcoin. That sum was worth about $5.7 million at the time, making the campaign the second most successful cryptocurrency crowdfunding to that point.</p>
<p>With a market cap of $106 million, the Lisk Token (LSK) ranks 195th among the largest cryptocurrencies according to CoinMarketCap today. At press time, LSK was trading at $0.828 and is down 5.7% in the last 24 hours.</p>
<h2>Reasons Why Lisk Is Converting Bitcoin To ETH</h2>
<p>Lisk Foundation will sell 1,000 BTC in chunks of 100 BTC per week to reduce risks with related third parties. Subsequently, the purchased ETH will be deposited into a 2-of-3 multisig account, with each Lisk Foundation board member holding one key each.</p>

<p>Notably, the project will keep 500 BTC, which the co-founder said will be used to pay expenses in 2024 and 2025. Moreover, Kordek added that the Lisk Foundation has &#8220;about enough fiat until the next Bitcoin halving.&#8221;</p>
<p>According to Kordek, there are three reasons for this move: first, the tweet states that Ethereum is the largest blockchain platform in the world. &#8220;Treasury-wise we want to go where blockchain applications are being built,&#8221; Kordek wrote, emphasizing as a second reason that ETH has &#8220;acceptable risks&#8221; from a Treasury wise point of view.</p>

<p>Third, he said, it allows for a sustainable, long-term return (via staking). &#8220;Treasury-wise it makes sense to go into an appreciating, deflationary, yield-generating asset,&#8221; Kordek said.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">The Lisk Foundation is exchanging 1000 BTC into ETH over the next 10 weeks and will hold onto them as part of its long-term treasury.</p>
<p><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f9f5.png" alt="🧵" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> Continue reading to learn more..</p>
<p>How:</p>
<p>The 1000 BTC are being sold in chunks of 100 BTC per week to reduce risks with associated…</p>
<p>&mdash; Max Kordek (@maxkordek) <a href="https://twitter.com/maxkordek/status/1656629386689363970?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">May 11, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p></p>
<h2>Will It Have An Impact On BTC Price?</h2>
<p>Even though the Bitcoin and crypto market is very <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin-price-threatened-by-liquidity-crisis/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">illiquid</a> due to Operation Choke Point 2.0 in the United States at the moment, the impact on the Bitcoin price should be marginal due to the 1,000 BTC split over 10 weeks.</p>
<p>100 BTC is an order size that the market can easily digest. In the last 24 hours, the trading volume of BTC was approximately 19.4 billion.</p>
<p>At press time, the Bitcoin price was at $26,388. For now, the key support is at the 100-day Exponential Moving Average (EMA), located at $26,227. Over the next few hours, it remains to be seen if this support can be held, if not, the area at $25,200 comes into focus.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-532272 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSD_2023-05-12_12-34-13.png" alt="Bitcoin price" width="3625" height="1672" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSD_2023-05-12_12-34-13.png 3625w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSD_2023-05-12_12-34-13-460x212.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSD_2023-05-12_12-34-13-860x397.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSD_2023-05-12_12-34-13-768x354.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSD_2023-05-12_12-34-13-1536x708.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSD_2023-05-12_12-34-13-2048x945.png 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSD_2023-05-12_12-34-13-750x346.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSD_2023-05-12_12-34-13-1140x526.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 3625px) 100vw, 3625px" />

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/iStock-912157946-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
