<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	 xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" >

<channel>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://newsbtc.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://newsbtc.com</link>
	<description>Bitcoin &#38; cryptocurrency news today, price &#38; technical analysis</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 23:46:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<link>https://newsbtc.com</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Shiba Inu Devs Set To Unveil Shibarium L2 Network Beta</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/shiba-inu-devs-unveil-shibarium-l2-network-beta/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[anvisaini]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 01:00:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Shiba Inu]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shiba Inu BONE]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shiba Inu holders]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=516255</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The beta testnet of Shibarium will soon release, benefiting the entire Shiba Inu community. Shibarium is a layer-2 network operable on the Ethereum mainnet. After the release of Shibarium, the Shina Inu community can build and grow projects. The release of Shibarium will address the scalability, speed, and expense challenges facing the existing projects on Ethereum.  Shiba Inu Shibarium Beta Testnet Release Shiba Inu developers will only release a beta testnet version in the coming months. A testnet mimics the use cases and applications of real-world functions. Its release aims to test the network for any gaps or performance issues and assess its capabilities. Moreover, the layer two testnet aims to address the issues faced with scalability and data.  Related Reading: Whale Moves Huge Amount Of Shiba Inu Tokens As SHIB Unveils To Metaverse With this release, Shiba Inu developers wish to educate the community about a blockchain’s development process from scratch. Before its release, some experts claimed Shibarium was a marketing move and a price &#8220;increase gimmick.&#8221; But the development team refutes such claims.  After its release, Shibarium is also expected to improve the platform’s transaction speed and lower its costs. The users will be able to interact with a metaverse solution, DEX, and several blockchain games.  The ultimate goal of Shibrium is to facilitate a solution that leads to innovation and improves the DeFi security aspects of the project. Today, Shiba Inu has over a $5 billion market cap, collectively obtained by SHIB, LEASH, and BONE.  The project lead and developer announced recently that the World Economic Forum wishes to work with the ecosystem. The purpose of this collaboration is to work on a global metaverse policy. Other IT giants like Facebook, Sand, and Decentraland will also be present in this global policymaking.  I just want to say that I appreciate the updates. That&#39;s all I asked for. Now, this is transparent. Second, anyone asking in the comment section when shibarium is coming out, read the first 2 paragraphs. You guys nailed it. &#8212; Burrito (@Burrito02353106) January 15, 2023 Shiba Inu Tokenomics Depends On Shibarium’s Working Mechanism In Shibarium, the validators play an essential role. Moreover, some SHIB tokens will be burned with every transaction. The validators on Shiba Inu will lock BONE and give fuel to the Heimdall Validator.  Related Reading: Whale Moves Huge Amount Of Shiba Inu Tokens As SHIB Unveils To Metaverse According to the Shiba Inu developers: The onboarding of these Validators will be done taking into account the experience, trust, knowledge and ensuring that these validators are committed to the health and integrity of Shibarium. To become a validator, a user needs to lock 10,000 BONE. They will get rewards in the form of this token.  New network layer and collaboration with WEF, it seems that Shiba Inu is working rigorously on its development.  Featured Image from Traxer/ Unsplash, the chart from Tradingview.com.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The beta testnet of Shibarium will soon release, benefiting the entire Shiba Inu community. Shibarium is a layer-2 network operable on the Ethereum mainnet. After the release of Shibarium, the Shina Inu community can build and grow projects. The release of Shibarium will address the scalability, speed, and expense challenges facing the existing projects on <a href="https://newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-accelerates-higher-1720/">Ethereum.</a> </p>
<h2><b>Shiba Inu Shibarium Beta Testnet Release</b></h2>
<p>Shiba Inu developers will only release a beta testnet version in the coming months. A testnet mimics the use cases and applications of real-world functions. Its release aims to test the network for any gaps or performance issues and assess its capabilities. Moreover, the layer two testnet aims to address the issues faced with scalability and data. </p>

<p>With this release, Shiba Inu developers wish to educate the community about a blockchain’s development process from scratch. Before its release, some experts claimed Shibarium was a marketing move and a price &#8220;increase gimmick.&#8221; But the development team refutes such claims. </p>
<p>After its release, <a href="https://twitter.com/Shibtoken/status/1614754575604400132?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw%7Ctwcamp%5Etweetembed%7Ctwterm%5E1614759181411815424%7Ctwgr%5Efddc485de3843db0819aca837b3dd8eb213593f8%7Ctwcon%5Es2_&amp;ref_url=https%3A%2F%2Fcointelegraph.com%2Fnews%2Fshiba-inu-devs-to-launch-shibarium-l2-network-beta" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">Shibarium </a>is also expected to improve the platform’s transaction speed and lower its costs. The users will be able to interact with a metaverse solution, DEX, and several blockchain games. </p>
<img class="wp-image-516258 size-jnews-featured-750" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Shiba-Inu-Graph-750x319.png" alt="Shiba Inu Graph" width="750" height="319" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Shiba-Inu-Graph-750x319.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Shiba-Inu-Graph-460x195.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Shiba-Inu-Graph-860x365.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Shiba-Inu-Graph-768x326.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Shiba-Inu-Graph-1536x653.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Shiba-Inu-Graph-1140x484.png 1140w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Shiba-Inu-Graph.png 1756w" sizes="(max-width: 750px) 100vw, 750px" />
<p>The ultimate goal of Shibrium is to facilitate a solution that leads to innovation and improves the DeFi security aspects of the project. Today, Shiba Inu has over a $5 billion market cap, collectively obtained by SHIB, LEASH, and BONE. </p>
<p>The project lead and developer announced recently that the World Economic Forum wishes to work with the ecosystem. The purpose of this collaboration is to work on a global metaverse policy. Other IT giants like Facebook, <a href="https://newsbtc.com/press-releases/decentraland-mana-and-the-sandbox-sand-surge-over-20-orbeon-protocol-orbn-set-to-gain-6000-in-its-presale/">Sand, and Decentraland</a> will also be present in this global policymaking. </p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">I just want to say that I appreciate the updates. That&#39;s all I asked for. Now, this is transparent. Second, anyone asking in the comment section when shibarium is coming out, read the first 2 paragraphs. You guys nailed it.</p>
<p>&mdash; Burrito (@Burrito02353106) <a href="https://twitter.com/Burrito02353106/status/1614759181411815424?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">January 15, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p></p>
<h2><b>Shiba Inu Tokenomics Depends On Shibarium’s Working Mechanism</b></h2>
<p>In Shibarium, the validators play an essential role. Moreover, some SHIB tokens will be burned with every transaction. The validators on Shiba Inu will <a href="https://newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/why-is-shiba-inus-bone-on-the-rise-and-is-it-time-to-get-in/">lock BONE</a> and give fuel to the Heimdall Validator. </p>

<p>According to the Shiba Inu developers:</p>
<blockquote><p><i>The onboarding of these Validators will be done taking into account the experience, trust, knowledge and ensuring that these validators are committed to the health and integrity of Shibarium.</i></p></blockquote>
<p>To become a validator, a user needs to lock 10,000 BONE. They will get rewards in the form of this token.  New network layer and collaboration with WEF, it seems that Shiba Inu is working rigorously on its development. </p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Shiba-Inu-460x306.jpg" width="460" height="306" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>VET Price Retraces, But Sellers Should Short At These Levels</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/altcoin/vet-price-retraces-sellers-short-these-levels/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[anushsamal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 00:00:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[VeChain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[VET]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[VETUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[VETUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=516277</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The price momentum of VeChain (VET) registered a halt over the last 24 hours after the altcoin started to trade laterally. In the same time frame, the coin dipped 0.9%, which is minor meaning that VeChain was in consolidation. The coin had picked up bullish momentum at the beginning of this year, but the bears could not sustain the price above the $0.021 mark. The technical outlook of VeChain still points towards bullishness. The altcoin was overvalued at the time of writing, which emphasizes that a price correction is on the way. Related Reading: Glassnode Points Out This Bizarre Consistency In Bitcoin Cycles A price correction also presents a shorting opportunity for traders. The accumulation on the chart also noted a downtick, but despite the downtick, demand for VET was substantial. However, VET will soon lose its current price level if buyers continue to lose interest. At the moment, VeChain has secured the $0.019 price level as its current support mark. Moving below the price above the mark will make VeChain come under the influence of bears again. The VET price is 92% lower than its all-time high secured in 2021. VET Price Analysis: One-Day Chart VeChain was trading at $0.0207 at the time of writing. The altcoin was trading within an upward parallel channel, which showed bullishness. However, VET traded outside the parallel chain over the past trading sessions. As the coin moved outside of the parallel chain, the bulls failed to cross the $0.0212 price level, which acts as the current resistance price level for the coin. Local support for the coin stood at $0.020, and as VeChain depicted a correction, it is expected to fall below the $0.0193 level. Both the $0.020 and the $0.0193 price levels can act as shorting levels for the coin. The amount of VeChain traded in the last session declined, which meant a slight fall in demand. Technical Analysis The altcoin was overvalued on the daily chart, and although demand for the coin registered a fall, the bulls were still hovering in the market. The Relative Strength Index was a few points below 80, indicating that the coin was under the influence of buyers. With a price correction, VET can dip to $0.0193 before it starts to pick up momentum. On the same note, the VET price was above the 20-Simple Moving Average line (SMA), which meant that buyers were driving the price momentum in the market. It was also above the 50-SMA line (yellow); however, another pull from the bears will drag VET below the 50-SMA line. Technical indicators continued to suggest that VET hasn&#8217;t lost its bullish steam. The Moving Average Convergence Divergence, which indicates price momentum and reversals, showed green signal bars. Related Reading: Crypto.com Decides To Let Go 20% Of Its Current Workforce Green signal bars are tied to a buy signal, but the recent bar was declining in strength, implying that traders should skip buying the asset right away. The Chaikin Money Flow was above the half-line and registered a fall; the capital inflows were far higher than capital outflows despite the fall. Overall, the market remains on the bulls&#8217; side, but VET has to stay above its crucial support line to keep the bears from returning. Featured Image From UnSplash, Charts From TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The price momentum of VeChain (VET) registered a halt over the last 24 hours after the altcoin started to trade laterally. In the same time frame, the coin dipped 0.9%, which is minor meaning that VeChain was in consolidation.</p>
<p>The coin had picked up bullish momentum at the beginning of this year, but the bears could not sustain the price above the $0.021 mark. The technical outlook of VeChain still points towards bullishness. The altcoin was overvalued at the time of writing, which emphasizes that a price correction is on the way.</p>

<p>A price correction also presents a shorting opportunity for traders. The accumulation on the chart also noted a downtick, but despite the downtick, demand for VET was substantial. However, VET will soon lose its current price level if buyers continue to lose interest.</p>
<p>At the moment, VeChain has secured the $0.019 price level as its current support mark. Moving below the price above the mark will make VeChain come under the influence of bears again. The VET price is 92% lower than its all-time high secured in 2021.</p>
<h2>VET Price Analysis: One-Day Chart</h2>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-516299 size-full" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/VETUSD_2023-01-16_22-19-41.png" alt="VET" width="1816" height="830" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/VETUSD_2023-01-16_22-19-41.png 1816w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/VETUSD_2023-01-16_22-19-41-460x210.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/VETUSD_2023-01-16_22-19-41-860x393.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/VETUSD_2023-01-16_22-19-41-768x351.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/VETUSD_2023-01-16_22-19-41-1536x702.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/VETUSD_2023-01-16_22-19-41-750x343.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/VETUSD_2023-01-16_22-19-41-1140x521.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1816px) 100vw, 1816px" />
<p>VeChain was trading at $0.0207 at the time of writing. The altcoin was trading within an upward parallel channel, which showed bullishness. However, VET traded outside the parallel chain over the past trading sessions.</p>
<p>As the coin moved outside of the parallel chain, the bulls failed to cross the $0.0212 price level, which acts as the current resistance price level for the coin. Local support for the coin stood at $0.020, and as VeChain depicted a correction, it is expected to fall below the $0.0193 level.</p>
<p>Both the $0.020 and the $0.0193 price levels can act as shorting levels for the coin. The amount of VeChain traded in the last session declined, which meant a slight fall in demand.</p>
<h2>Technical Analysis</h2>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-516300 size-full" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/VETUSD_2023-01-16_22-20-09.png" alt="VET" width="1816" height="743" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/VETUSD_2023-01-16_22-20-09.png 1816w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/VETUSD_2023-01-16_22-20-09-460x188.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/VETUSD_2023-01-16_22-20-09-860x352.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/VETUSD_2023-01-16_22-20-09-768x314.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/VETUSD_2023-01-16_22-20-09-1536x628.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/VETUSD_2023-01-16_22-20-09-750x307.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/VETUSD_2023-01-16_22-20-09-1140x466.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1816px) 100vw, 1816px" />
<p>The altcoin was overvalued on the daily chart, and although demand for the coin registered a fall, the bulls were still hovering in the market. The Relative Strength Index was a few points below 80, indicating that the coin was under the influence of buyers.</p>
<p>With a price correction, VET can dip to $0.0193 before it starts to pick up momentum. On the same note, the VET price was above the 20-Simple Moving Average line (SMA), which meant that buyers were driving the price momentum in the market.</p>
<p>It was also above the 50-SMA line (yellow); however, another pull from the bears will drag VET below the 50-SMA line.</p>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-516304 size-full" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/VETUSD_2023-01-16_22-21-01.png" alt="VET" width="1816" height="743" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/VETUSD_2023-01-16_22-21-01.png 1816w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/VETUSD_2023-01-16_22-21-01-460x188.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/VETUSD_2023-01-16_22-21-01-860x352.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/VETUSD_2023-01-16_22-21-01-768x314.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/VETUSD_2023-01-16_22-21-01-1536x628.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/VETUSD_2023-01-16_22-21-01-750x307.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/VETUSD_2023-01-16_22-21-01-1140x466.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1816px) 100vw, 1816px" />
<p>Technical indicators continued to suggest that VET hasn&#8217;t lost its bullish steam. The Moving Average Convergence Divergence, which indicates price momentum and reversals, showed green signal bars.</p>

<p>Green signal bars are tied to a buy signal, but the recent bar was declining in strength, implying that traders should skip buying the asset right away. The Chaikin Money Flow was above the half-line and registered a fall; the capital inflows were far higher than capital outflows despite the fall.</p>
<p>Overall, the market remains on the bulls&#8217; side, but VET has to stay above its crucial support line to keep the bears from returning.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/wance-paleri-Uo40KRVStJo-unsplash-460x223.jpg" width="460" height="223" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cronos (CRO) Prints Over 9% Gains In A Day While Market Sees Correction</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/analysis/cro/cronos-cro-prints-10-gains-in-a-day/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jammy Hunts]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 23:00:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[CRO]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CRO analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CRO price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cronos]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=516279</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[As crypto assets recover from the 2022 crypto winter, Cronos (CRO) has recorded massive gains in 24 hours. Cronos&#8217; trading volume has spiked by 301.28%, showing that the coin has attracted more trading activity. Generally, the crypto market has seen a slight price increase. Bitcoin, the number one cryptocurrency, has enjoyed a positive rally and has influenced the rise of altcoins such as CRO.  Related Reading: Lazarus Group Transfers $64M ETH From Harmony Bridge Hack Cronos&#8217; price surged by over 9% in 24 hours, continuing its impressive price action into 2023. The cryptocurrency&#8217;s wide range of applications in various spheres has also helped to push this crypto revival. What Is Behind This Rally? Cronos is an open-source blockchain that facilitates Crypto.com’s Pay mobile app payments. However, the Cronos blockchain, which is Ethereum compatible, has upgraded and redesigned the project focus to integrate Web 3 and NFTs.  The asset&#8217;s price has benefitted from increased adoption, evident in the more than 100% spike in trading activity. Cronos network now supports activities on the Metaverse. NFTs and Games are part of the new projects adopted to keep up with modern trends. The network has also maintained its core objective of providing decentralized finance (DeFi) solutions. Crypto users can carry out financial transactions on the blockchain fast and anonymously. Cronos has built a strong followership that interacts on social media channels. The launch of Cronos Chain, compatible with Ethereum, has put the project on the front foot. The Cronos chain allows the migration of DApps built on the Ethereum blockchain and supports the Inter Blockchain Communications (IBC) protocol. The IBC protocol lets Cronos connect to the Cosmos ecosystem and interact with its DApps.  Cronos (CRO) Price Prediction What To Expect CRO is gaining in the market today, currently trading at $0.0806. The support levels for CRO are $0.070164, $0.071703, and $0.072919, while the resistance levels are $0.075674, $0.077213, and $0.078429.  Cronos is currently trading above its 50-day Simple Moving Average (SMA) but is below its 200-day SMA. It implies that this price action could operate as a short-lived rally. On the price chart, the candles are in an ascending pattern. However, the candle for today has a long upper wick implying that the bears are trying to push the price down. The Relative Strength Index (RSI) is bullish and in the overbought zone, at 79.27. It represents the massive spike in trading volume in Cronos. However, the RSI might retrace into the channel in the coming days. The Moving Average Convergence/Divergence (MACD is above its signal line, which is also a buy signal. But, the MACD is showing minimal divergence, implying that there might be a trend reversal in the short term. Cronos will likely continue to trade in the green for a few days before slightly retracing. Related Reading: What Matters In Crypto This Week: Will Bitcoin Keep Pumping? A conservative approach to trading the asset might be the best option. More importantly, understand that a digital asset that declines in value by 50% will need to rally to 100% to return to its former value. This feat is difficult for altcoins and meme coins to accomplish.  Featured image from Pixabay and chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>As crypto assets recover from the <a href="https://twitter.com/crypto/status/1605552933952700416" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">2022 crypto winter</a>, Cronos (CRO) has recorded massive gains in 24 hours. Cronos&#8217; <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/cronos/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">trading volume has spiked by 301.28%,</a> showing that the coin has attracted more trading activity.</p>
<p>Generally, the <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">crypto market</a> has seen a slight price increase. <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Bitcoin</a>, the number one cryptocurrency, has enjoyed a positive rally and has influenced the rise of altcoins such as CRO. </p>

<p>Cronos&#8217; price surged by over 9% in 24 hours, continuing its impressive price action into 2023. The cryptocurrency&#8217;s wide range of applications in various spheres has also helped to push this crypto revival.</p>
<h2><b>What Is Behind This Rally?</b></h2>
<p>Cronos is an open-source blockchain that facilitates <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/chart/nmZAKHKT/?symbol=COINBASE%3ACROUSD" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Crypto.com’s</a> Pay mobile app payments. However, the Cronos blockchain, which is Ethereum compatible, has upgraded and redesigned the project focus to integrate Web 3 and NFTs. </p>
<p>The asset&#8217;s price has benefitted from <a href="https://twitter.com/chainalysis/status/1514212186591219716?lang=en" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">increased adoption</a>, evident in the more than 100% spike in trading activity. Cronos network now supports activities on the Metaverse. <a href="https://mobile.twitter.com/cryptocomnft" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">NFTs and Games</a> are part of the new projects adopted to keep up with modern trends.</p>
<p>The network has also maintained its core objective of <a href="https://twitter.com/cronos_chain/status/1614985864777719810?ref_src=twsrc%5Egoogle%7Ctwcamp%5Eserp%7Ctwgr%5Etweet" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">providing decentralized finance</a> (DeFi) solutions. Crypto users can carry out financial transactions on the blockchain fast and anonymously. Cronos has built a strong followership that interacts on <a href="https://twitter.com/cronos_chain/status/1612436161984860160" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">social media channels</a>.</p>
<p>The launch of <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/cronos/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Cronos Chain</a>, compatible with Ethereum, has put the project on the front foot. The Cronos chain allows the migration of DApps built on the Ethereum blockchain and supports the <a href="https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLdQIb0qr3pnAFvKNxbmxhW0RHcEG1OdMe" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Inter Blockchain Communications (IBC)</a> protocol. The IBC protocol lets Cronos connect to the <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/cosmos/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Cosmos ecosystem</a> and interact with its DApps.</p>
<img loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-516282" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/CROUSD_2023-01-16_22-22-39.png" alt="CROUSD" width="856" height="538" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/CROUSD_2023-01-16_22-22-39.png 856w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/CROUSD_2023-01-16_22-22-39-460x289.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/CROUSD_2023-01-16_22-22-39-768x483.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/CROUSD_2023-01-16_22-22-39-750x471.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 856px) 100vw, 856px" />
 <b>Cronos (CRO) Price Prediction What To Expect</b>
<p>CRO is gaining in the market today, currently trading at $0.0806. The support levels for CRO are $0.070164, $0.071703, and $0.072919, while the resistance levels are $0.075674, $0.077213, and $0.078429. </p>
<p>Cronos is currently trading above its 50-day <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Moving_average" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Simple Moving Average (SMA)</a> but is below its 200-day SMA. It implies that this price action could operate as a short-lived rally. On the price chart, the candles are in an <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pmrfys4oX3U" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">ascending pattern</a>. However, the candle for today has a <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=B_nGSgJZ04w" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">long upper wick</a> implying that the bears are trying to push the price down.</p>
<p>The <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Relative_strength_index" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Relative Strength Index (RSI)</a> is bullish and in the overbought zone, at 79.27. It represents the massive spike in trading volume in Cronos. However, the RSI might retrace into the channel in the coming days.</p>
<p>The <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/MACD" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Moving Average Convergence/Divergence</a> (MACD is above its signal line, which is also a buy signal. But, the MACD is showing minimal divergence, implying that there might be a trend reversal in the short term. Cronos will likely continue to trade in the green for a few days before slightly retracing.</p>

<p>A <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3sL4-ySSJiE" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">conservative approach</a> to trading the asset might be the best option. More importantly, understand that a digital asset that declines in value by 50% will need to rally to 100% to return to its former value. This feat is difficult for altcoins and meme coins to accomplish. </p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Cronos-1-460x345.png" width="460" height="345" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Why A Morning Star Reversal Could Awaken A Monster Bitcoin Rally</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/morning-star-reversal-bitcoin-bull-run-2/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tony Spilotro]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 22:08:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fisher Transform]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[morning star]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=516309</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin price is already turning heads after reclaiming $20,000 per coin, but if the current monthly candle closes on BTCUSD price charts, the top cryptocurrency will satisfy the conditions of a morning star reversal pattern.  The last time the signal occurred at the bottom of a major downtrend, Bitcoin began a two-year-long bull run in cryptocurrencies and went on to climb more than 6,000% after the morning star confirmed. Bitcoin Reclaims $20,000: A Wake Up Call For The Bull Market Bitcoin is once again above $20,000, but a lot has changed since 2020 when it passed the key level for the first time. The number one cryptocurrency by market cap has declined by 78%, and altcoins have dramatically collapsed by as much as 99%.  But markets are cyclical, and some signs are beginning to point to the end of a bearish phase in crypto and the possibility of a new bull trend blossoming. Top analysts are starting to wake up and take notice, and are now calling for a bottom and a cyclical low.  Related Reading: Bitcoin Price Touches $20,000 For First Time Post-FTX Collapse Reaching above $21,000 has put BTCUSD above pre-FTX crash levels from two months prior. More importantly, the three-month period has resulted in a three-candlestick reversal pattern called a morning star.  The morning star reversal pattern is a bullish Japanese candlestick reversal pattern, than when confirmed should result in three to five months worth of follow-through. A substantial shift from bearish to bullish would return Bitcoin to its previously bullish state. A morning star reversal pattern has formed &#124; BTCUSD on TradingView.com What A Morning Star Reversal Could Mean For Crypto According to Investopedia, “a morning star is a visual pattern made up of a tall black candlestick,” a black or white doji, “and a third tall white candlestick.” “The middle candle of the morning star captures a moment of market indecision where the bears begin to give way to bulls. The third candle confirms the reversal and can mark a new uptrend,” an excerpt reads. Related Reading: “Parabolic” Signal That Triggered Past Bitcoin Bull Runs Reappears Analysts and traders should look toward technical indicators to confirm the signal.  For example, the Fisher Transform is crossing bullish from extreme negative deviations, and could help provide confirmation of extended upside to follow.  Is this confirmation of a new bull trend? &#124; BTCUSD on TradingView.com Historically, the Fisher Transform turning up combined with a 20% monthly bullish candle was enough to end each bear market in the past. The most direct comparison, took place in 2015, when another morning star reversal pattern helped trigger a new bull trend.  In that instance, BTCUSD went on to climb by 6,000% in 24 months — after the signal appeared. Confirmation requires this month’s candle to engulf at least 50% of the black, November down candle. The more this month engulfs the November candle, the stronger the signal. Currently, the entire candle has been engulfed.  Follow @TonySpilotroBTC on Twitter or join the TonyTradesBTC Telegram for exclusive daily market insights and technical analysis education. Please note: Content is educational and should not be considered investment advice. Featured image from iStockPhoto, Charts from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin price is already turning heads after <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-price-touches-20000-for-first-time-post-ftx-collapse/">reclaiming $20,000 per coin</a>, but if the current monthly candle closes on BTCUSD price charts, the top cryptocurrency will satisfy the conditions of a morning star reversal pattern. </p>
<p>The last time the signal occurred at the bottom of a major downtrend, Bitcoin began a two-year-long bull run in cryptocurrencies and went on to climb more than 6,000% after the morning star confirmed.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Reclaims $20,000: A Wake Up Call For The Bull Market</h2>
<p>Bitcoin is once again <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-price-touches-20000-for-first-time-post-ftx-collapse/">above $20,000</a>, but a lot has changed since 2020 when it passed the key level for the first time. The number one cryptocurrency by market cap has declined by 78%, and altcoins have dramatically collapsed by as much as 99%. </p>
<p>But markets are cyclical, and some signs are beginning to point to the end of a bearish phase in crypto and the possibility of a new bull trend blossoming. <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-peter-l-brandt/">Top analysts are starting to wake up</a> and take notice, and are now calling for a bottom and a cyclical low. </p>

<p>Reaching above $21,000 has put BTCUSD above pre-FTX crash levels from two months prior. More importantly, the three-month period has resulted in a three-candlestick reversal pattern called a morning star. </p>
<p>The morning star reversal pattern is a bullish Japanese candlestick reversal pattern, than when confirmed should result in three to five months worth of follow-through. A substantial shift from bearish to bullish would return Bitcoin to its previously bullish state.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-large wp-image-516310 aligncenter" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/IMG_1449-860x531.png" alt="" width="860" height="531" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/IMG_1449-860x531.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/IMG_1449-460x284.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/IMG_1449-768x474.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/IMG_1449-1536x949.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/IMG_1449-2048x1265.png 2048w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/IMG_1449-750x463.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/IMG_1449-1140x704.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" /></p>
<p style="text-align: center">A morning star reversal pattern has formed | BTCUSD on TradingView.com</p>
<h2>What A Morning Star Reversal Could Mean For Crypto</h2>
<p>According to <a href="https://www.investopedia.com/terms/m/morningstar.asp" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Investopedia</a>, “a morning star is a visual pattern made up of a tall black candlestick,” a black or white doji, “and a third tall white candlestick.” “The middle candle of the morning star captures a moment of market indecision where the bears begin to give way to bulls. The third candle confirms the reversal and can mark a new uptrend,” an excerpt reads.</p>

<p>Analysts and traders should look toward technical indicators to confirm the signal.  For example, the Fisher Transform is crossing bullish from extreme negative deviations, and could help provide confirmation of extended upside to follow. </p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="size-large wp-image-516311 aligncenter" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/IMG_1450-860x531.png" alt="" width="860" height="531" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/IMG_1450-860x531.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/IMG_1450-460x284.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/IMG_1450-768x474.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/IMG_1450-1536x949.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/IMG_1450-2048x1265.png 2048w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/IMG_1450-750x463.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/IMG_1450-1140x704.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" /></p>

<p>Historically, the Fisher Transform turning up combined with a 20% monthly bullish candle was enough to end each bear market in the past. The most direct comparison, took place in 2015, when another morning star reversal pattern helped trigger a new bull trend. </p>
<p>In that instance, BTCUSD went on to climb by 6,000% in 24 months — after the signal appeared. Confirmation requires this month’s candle to engulf at least 50% of the black, November down candle. The more this month engulfs the November candle, the stronger the signal. Currently, the entire candle has been engulfed. </p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/abstract-image-bull-in-the-form-of-a-starry-sky-or-space-consisting-of-points-lines-and.jpg_s1024x1024wisk20coungdqkdWmyq2cHLKk28-eo8ER_uDaDNhzDkoUCNr5g-460x313.jpg" width="460" height="313" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>MANA Soared 75% This Week, Entering The Top 100</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/mana/mana-soared-75-this-week-entering-the-top-100/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Muhammad Ali]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 20:00:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[MANA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AOmetaverse]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CPI]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Decentraland token]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Metaverse]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SAND]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=516280</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[According to CoinMarketCap’s data, Decentraland&#8217;s native token, MANA, has gained 17.59% in the last 24 hours, following the stellar performance of metaverse tokens since the start of the new year. MANA is one of the top 100 cryptocurrencies and has grown by 95% in the last month. In addition, it has been in the green for 14 of the previous 16 days. Related Reading: Decentraland (MANA) And The Sandbox (SAND) Surge Over 20%, Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) Set To Gain 6000% In Its Presale What Pushed MANA To The Sky? At the time of writing, MANA is trading at $0.6887. Since last week, the token&#8217;s price has increased by approximately 70%, bringing its market capitalization to $1,2 million. As investor opinion in the crypto markets has improved in response to positive macroeconomic news, smaller market cap cryptocurrencies have outperformed their larger competitors.  #mana pump was inevitable, @decentraland is the platform of the future. NOW 😍 pic.twitter.com/x2LLJrCWO1 — jasonx.eth (@DCLjasonx) January 15, 2023 The recent U.S. economic data is also why the increase in MANA price. According to data released last week, US inflation has been trending downward over the past few months. From its all-time high of 9.1% in 2022 down to 6.5% in December of that year, the Bureau of Labor Statistics reports a dramatic decline in the consumer price index (CPI) for the United States. The U.S. Federal Reserve (Fed) has been hiking interest rates to bring down inflation. This data suggest their efforts are working, and the market is feeling more optimistic as the chances of a monetary policy pivot are increasing, according to their expectations. According to additional data, MANA is one of the most popular &#8220;metaverse&#8221; platforms, with roughly 8,000 unique daily users. Improvements to avatars, profiles, and friend requests have recently been released for Decentraland users. It works toward making the platform more user-friendly. However, it was a time-consuming process before the platform started to recover. These essential factors have led to the price increase and burst in investor interest. New Year, More About You 📢 A few new features came out today that will help #DCLcitizens connect with each other better than ever—and this is only the beginning! 🖍️Highlighting Avatars 👩‍🦱New User Profile 🔗Links in Profile 💌New Friend Request Flow 🏷️Differentiated Nametags pic.twitter.com/8cMUXVLpiT — Decentraland (@decentraland) January 12, 2023 Various tokens used in video games and the metaverse saw dramatic price spikes last week. For example, SAND, The Sandbox&#8217;s native, has surged by 33% during the past week, while GALA, the currency of Gala Games, has increased by 31%. Related Reading: Decentraland (MANA) Sheds 90% In 2022 Despite Solid NFT Volume Performance Australian Open Metaverse Tournament Back At Decentraland According to a tweet below, the Australian Open metaverse has returned to Decentraland. Game, Set, Match!@AOmetaverse has returned to Decentraland! 🎾 On the big screens: #AO23 Practice courts, 24/7 Classic matches 🎾 New AO Tennis Club, Beach Bar 🎾 Rod Laver Tennis Challenge 🎾 Daily quests for Wearables Now-Jan 29 -143, 74 pic.twitter.com/Z3VOICGmOU — Decentraland (@decentraland) January 15, 2023 From January 16-29, 2023, Melbourne Park will host the first round of the 2023 Australian Open, a Grand Slam tennis tournament. This year&#8217;s Australian Open will be the 111th in the tournament&#8217;s history and the 55th in the Open Era and could contribute to the bullish price action by onboarding new users on MANA.  AOmetaverse and Vegas City, the metaverse&#8217;s entertainment platform and the largest commercial zone in Decentraland, have reserved a Twitter spot for January 17 to announce the activation of the Australian Open 2023 for 14 days. Featured Image from CoinMarketCap, Chart from Tradingview.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>According to CoinMarketCap’s <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/decentraland/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">data</a>, Decentraland&#8217;s native token, MANA, has gained 17.59% in the last 24 hours, following the stellar performance of metaverse tokens since the start of the new year. MANA is one of the top 100 cryptocurrencies and has grown by 95% in the last month. In addition, it has been in the green for 14 of the previous 16 days.</p>

<h2>What Pushed MANA To The Sky?</h2>
<p>At the time of writing, MANA is trading at $0.6887. Since last week, the token&#8217;s price has increased by approximately 70%, bringing its market capitalization to $1,2 million. As investor opinion in the crypto markets has improved in response to positive macroeconomic news, smaller market cap cryptocurrencies have outperformed their larger competitors. </p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en"><a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/mana?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">#mana</a> pump was inevitable, <a href="https://twitter.com/decentraland?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">@decentraland</a> is the platform of the future. NOW <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f60d.png" alt="😍" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> <a href="https://t.co/x2LLJrCWO1" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/x2LLJrCWO1</a></p>
<p>— jasonx.eth (@DCLjasonx) <a href="https://twitter.com/DCLjasonx/status/1614771104769540096?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">January 15, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p>The recent U.S. economic data is also why the increase in MANA price. According to data released last week, US inflation has been trending downward over the past few months. From its all-time high of 9.1% in 2022 down to 6.5% in December of that year, the Bureau of Labor Statistics reports a dramatic decline in the consumer price index (CPI) for the United States.</p>
<p>The U.S. Federal Reserve (Fed) has been hiking interest rates to bring down inflation. This data suggest their efforts are working, and the market is feeling more optimistic as the chances of a monetary policy pivot are increasing, according to their expectations.</p>
<p><a href="https://decentraland.org/blog/announcements/how-many-dau-does-decentraland-have/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">According to additional data</a>, MANA is one of the most popular &#8220;metaverse&#8221; platforms, with roughly 8,000 unique daily users.</p>
<p>Improvements to avatars, profiles, and friend requests have recently been released for Decentraland users. It works toward making the platform more user-friendly. However, it was a time-consuming process before the platform started to recover. These essential factors have led to the price increase and burst in investor interest.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">New Year, More About You <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f4e2.png" alt="📢" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /></p>
<p>A few new features came out today that will help <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/DCLcitizens?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">#DCLcitizens</a> connect with each other better than ever—and this is only the beginning!</p>
<p><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f58d.png" alt="🖍" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />Highlighting Avatars
<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f469-200d-1f9b1.png" alt="👩‍🦱" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />New User Profile
<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f517.png" alt="🔗" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />Links in Profile
<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f48c.png" alt="💌" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />New Friend Request Flow
<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f3f7.png" alt="🏷" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />Differentiated Nametags <a href="https://t.co/8cMUXVLpiT" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/8cMUXVLpiT</a></p>
<p>— Decentraland (@decentraland) <a href="https://twitter.com/decentraland/status/1613329205969969152?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">January 12, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p>Various tokens used in video games and the metaverse saw dramatic price spikes last week. For example, SAND, The Sandbox&#8217;s native, has surged by 33% during the past week, while GALA, the currency of Gala Games, has increased by 31%.</p>

Australian Open Metaverse Tournament Back At Decentraland
<p>According to a tweet below, the Australian Open metaverse has returned to Decentraland.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Game, Set, Match!<a href="https://twitter.com/AOmetaverse?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">@AOmetaverse</a> has returned to Decentraland!</p>
<p><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f3be.png" alt="🎾" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> On the big screens: <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/AO23?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">#AO23</a> Practice courts, 24/7 Classic matches
<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f3be.png" alt="🎾" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> New AO Tennis Club, Beach Bar
<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f3be.png" alt="🎾" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> Rod Laver Tennis Challenge
<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f3be.png" alt="🎾" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> Daily quests for Wearables</p>
<p>Now-Jan 29
-143, 74 <a href="https://t.co/Z3VOICGmOU" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/Z3VOICGmOU</a></p>
<p>— Decentraland (@decentraland) <a href="https://twitter.com/decentraland/status/1614671781754990592?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">January 15, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p>From January 16-29, 2023, Melbourne Park will host the first round of the 2023 Australian Open, a Grand Slam tennis tournament. This year&#8217;s Australian Open will be the 111th in the tournament&#8217;s history and the 55th in the Open Era and could contribute to the bullish price action by onboarding new users on MANA. </p>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-516283 size-large" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/MANAUSDT_2023-01-16_22-27-02-860x494.png" alt="" width="860" height="494" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/MANAUSDT_2023-01-16_22-27-02-860x494.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/MANAUSDT_2023-01-16_22-27-02-460x264.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/MANAUSDT_2023-01-16_22-27-02-768x441.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/MANAUSDT_2023-01-16_22-27-02-1536x882.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/MANAUSDT_2023-01-16_22-27-02-750x431.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/MANAUSDT_2023-01-16_22-27-02-1140x655.png 1140w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/MANAUSDT_2023-01-16_22-27-02.png 1996w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" />
<p>AOmetaverse and Vegas City, the metaverse&#8217;s entertainment platform and the largest commercial zone in Decentraland, have reserved a Twitter spot for January 17 to announce the activation of the Australian Open 2023 for 14 days.</p>
<p><em>Featured Image from CoinMarketCap, Chart from Tradingview.com</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/MANA-Soared-75-This-Week-Entering-The-Top-100-460x307.jpeg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto.com Decides To Let Go 20% Of Its Current Workforce</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/crypto-com-let-go-20-of-its-current-workforce/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[anushsamal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 19:00:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto.com]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=516273</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The crypto industry continues to stagger under a massive wave of layoffs that have been occurring in recent times. Among the recent companies from the sector, Crypto.com has planned on axing 20% of its workforce. The Singapore-based company, Crypto.com, has confirmed its decision via a blog post. According to Co-Founder and CEO Kris Marszalek, the platform must let go of 20% of its current employees. Related Reading: What Matters In Crypto This Week: Will Bitcoin Keep Pumping? Crypto.com has faced significant criticism after attempting to reassure investors that the crypto exchange is in good financial health and has nothing to worry about. The reason for the layoffs is the current economic headwinds and industry situation. This will be the second major layoff carried out by the company. Crypto.com laid off nearly 260 employees in 2022, accounting for nearly 5% of its workforce. Crypto.com CEO Kris Marszalek stated: We grew ambitiously at the start of 2022, building on our incredible momentum and aligning with the trajectory of the broader industry. That trajectory changed rapidly with a confluence of negative economic developments. The exchange platform has not specifically mentioned the positions that were laid off. The decision to fire employees has been attributed to broader market weakness and the FTX crash. The crash caused a misappropriation of customer funds and eventually bankruptcy, which has gone on to affect the industry considerably. Crypto.com Says That It Continues To Perform Well Kriz Marszalek had initially mentioned that the exchange platform maintained adequate reserves for every single coin which the platform held. Two months after that statement, the exchange could not withstand the collapse of FTX without adopting measures to cut costs. Marszalek quoted: Today we made the difficult decision to reduce our global workforce by approximately 20 per cent. All impacted personnel have already been notified. These reductions were in no way related to performance, and we extend our deepest gratitude for all their contributions to Crypto.com. He additionally stated: Several factors played into our decision to reduce headcount. While we continue to perform well, growing to more than 70 million users worldwide and maintaining a strong balance sheet, we’ve had to navigate ongoing economic headwinds and unforeseeable industry events. Crypto.com Admits To Not Navigating Well After FTX Crash The Founder of Crypto.com has mentioned that even though Crypto.com was doing well, there has been a change in trajectory with a &#8216;confluence&#8217; of negative economic developments. He spoke about the layoffs in July last year as the exchange could not navigate the macroeconomic downturn. It also could not gauge the damage the FTX collapse would have caused to the industry. Related Reading: Polkadot: Why Recent On-Chain Feats Could Trigger Strong Investor Sentiment The fall of FTX has been terrible for investors&#8217; sentiments. The exchange now wants to focus on making prudent financial decisions to manage the company better, and layoffs are among such necessary measures. The exchange states that these additional reductions were mandatory to ensure that the company&#8217;s position remains profitable in the long term. At the moment, Crypto.com has 2,450 employees, and a 20 percent layoff from that population will mean that close to 490 employees lose their jobs. Featured Image From UnSplash, Chart From TradingView.Com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The crypto industry continues to stagger under a massive wave of layoffs that have been occurring in recent times. Among the recent companies from the sector, Crypto.com has planned on axing 20% of its workforce.</p>
<p>The Singapore-based company, Crypto.com, has confirmed its decision via a <a href="https://crypto.com/company-news/company-update" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">blog post</a>. According to Co-Founder and CEO Kris Marszalek, the platform must let go of 20% of its current employees.</p>


<p>Crypto.com has faced significant criticism after attempting to reassure investors that the crypto exchange is in good financial health and has nothing to worry about.</p>
<p>The reason for the layoffs is the current economic headwinds and industry situation. This will be the second major layoff carried out by the company. Crypto.com laid off nearly 260 employees in 2022, accounting for nearly 5% of its workforce.</p>
<p>Crypto.com CEO Kris Marszalek stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>We grew ambitiously at the start of 2022, building on our incredible momentum and aligning with the trajectory of the broader industry. That trajectory changed rapidly with a confluence of negative economic developments.</p></blockquote>
<p>The exchange platform has not specifically mentioned the positions that were laid off. The decision to fire employees has been attributed to broader market weakness and the FTX crash. The crash caused a misappropriation of customer funds and eventually bankruptcy, which has gone on to affect the industry considerably.</p>
<h2>Crypto.com Says That It Continues To Perform Well</h2>
<p>Kriz Marszalek had initially mentioned that the exchange platform maintained adequate reserves for every single coin which the platform held. Two months after that statement, the exchange could not withstand the collapse of FTX without adopting measures to cut costs.</p>
<p>Marszalek quoted:</p>
<blockquote><p>Today we made the difficult decision to reduce our global workforce by approximately 20 per cent. All impacted personnel have already been notified. These reductions were in no way related to performance, and we extend our deepest gratitude for all their contributions to Crypto.com.</p></blockquote>
<p>He additionally stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>Several factors played into our decision to reduce headcount. While we continue to perform well, growing to more than 70 million users worldwide and maintaining a strong balance sheet, we’ve had to navigate ongoing economic headwinds and unforeseeable industry events.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Crypto.com Admits To Not Navigating Well After FTX Crash</h2>
<p>The Founder of Crypto.com has mentioned that even though Crypto.com was doing well, there has been a change in trajectory with a &#8216;confluence&#8217; of negative economic developments.</p>
<p>He spoke about the layoffs in July last year as the exchange could not navigate the macroeconomic downturn. It also could not gauge the damage the FTX collapse would have caused to the industry.</p>


<p>The fall of FTX has been terrible for investors&#8217; sentiments. The exchange now wants to focus on making prudent financial decisions to manage the company better, and layoffs are among such necessary measures.</p>
<p>The exchange states that these additional reductions were mandatory to ensure that the company&#8217;s position remains profitable in the long term. At the moment, Crypto.com has 2,450 employees, and a 20 percent layoff from that population will mean that close to 490 employees lose their jobs.</p>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-516274 size-full" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD_2023-01-16_20-44-32.png" alt="Crypto" width="1817" height="830" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD_2023-01-16_20-44-32.png 1817w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD_2023-01-16_20-44-32-460x210.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD_2023-01-16_20-44-32-860x393.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD_2023-01-16_20-44-32-768x351.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD_2023-01-16_20-44-32-1536x702.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD_2023-01-16_20-44-32-750x343.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD_2023-01-16_20-44-32-1140x521.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1817px) 100vw, 1817px" />



]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/joanna-kosinska-8gYCAkMuvsY-unsplash-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Will New Interchain Station Wallet Launch Spike LUNC Price, Any Possibility?</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/will-new-interchain-station-wallet-launch-spike-lunc-price-any-possibility/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[David Atlee]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 18:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blockchains]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LUNCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Terra Classic]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=516209</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[After the collapse of the popular blockchain network Terra, developers have been trying to revive it; many reforms have already taken place to sustain the Terra Classic (LUNC and prevent further collapse). Terra Classic, the original blockchain, was forked to create Terra (LUNA). Among these reforms is a recent integration with Interchain Station. The news boosted the Terra Classic (LUNC) price. According to Jared, lead developer at Terraform Labs, more integrations and reforms are coming to Terra soon. The sudden crash of Terra LUNA sent a cascade effect across the crypto industry, leading several firms to bankruptcy. Many investors are yet to recover from the loss incurred from the Terra implosion. There are still uncleared controversies surrounding the ecosystem&#8217;s sudden collapse. Some say Terra LUNA was a rug pull scheme by Do Kwon, founder of Terraform Labs, to launder and steal people&#8217;s money. Meanwhile, Do Kwon and his executives are still on the run from South Korean prosecutors. Related Reading: Bitcoin Funding Rates Hit 14-Month High – What Could This Mean For The Market Leader? More Integrations Coming To Terra Classic Network In a Twitter announcement, Jared revealed that the Terra Network would partner with other blockchains, including SEI, Juno, Osmosis, Mars, Pisco, and many more. He said the integrations aim to protect the network in the right direction and allow seamless cross-chain communication between Terra and other blockchains. Jared also told the Terra community to expect a rollout of more features while their main focus is to launch the wallet on mobile devices. The current station supports many mainnets including LUNC, LUNA, Osmosis, Juno, Kujira, Carbon, HuaHua, and Cresent. Terra’s interchain station wallet would simplify the complex process of interacting with multiple blockchain networks. The wallet would allow users to stake, vote, send, receive tokens, and interact with decentralized applications (dApps) across supported chains. LUNC price soared by 3% on January 10 when Jared first shared news of the interchain wallet feature via his Twitter handle. Jared referred to the development as a breakthrough in chain integrations. This move comes after several attempts by the Terra Classic community to revive the sinking Terra Classic project. With the new station wallet, DeFi developers can now access oracle data from several chains through the interchain facility. Why New Governance Implementation Is Important To LUNC Community The Terra Classic blockchain saw a rough start in 2023 after being impacted by crypto exchange KuCoin’s December 30 move. On December 30, 2022, KuCoin removed (undelegated) 48 billion Terra Classic (LUNC) tokens from circulation. This issue reduced the voting power of KuCoin’s Terra Classic Validator by 0.25%, taking it up to the 44th position. The exchange later said it would continue pledging LUNC tokens after a 14-day lock period. However, the move caused a drastic reduction in on-chain activity and stirred much anxiety in the LUNC community, causing the price to fall. After Kucoin’s move, the community responded by approving and implementing new governance proposals to improve the overall operation of the chain. The Terra ecosystem also started burning tokens to stir up on-chain activity. The new governance proposals got overwhelming votes from the community with the support of major crypto exchanges. As a result, one of the new implementations is governance proposal 11242, which aims to stop the reminting of already destroyed LUNC tokens. Once the implementation is complete, it will ensure the effective elimination of tokens from LUNC&#8217;s circulating supply which will also boost its price. Presently, the amount of Terra Classic tokens in circulation is nearly 6 trillion. Related Reading: Bitcoin Disciples: Only 43.5 Million Own The Crypto Globally, Study Shows After the reduction in on-chain activity in the past month, the developers published proposal 11242 at the beginning of January. The aim of proposal 11242 is to stop the reminting burnt LUNC tokens and effectively reduce the seigniorage reward policy to zero. LUNC price is trading at $0.000177 with a minor decline. The token has gained up to 15.50% in the past week.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>After the collapse of the popular blockchain network Terra, developers have been trying to revive it; many <a href="https://www.terrarebels.net/roadmap" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">reforms</a> have already taken place to sustain the Terra Classic (LUNC and prevent further collapse). Terra Classic, the original blockchain, was forked to create Terra (LUNA).</p>
<p>Among these reforms is a recent integration with Interchain Station. The <a href="https://twitter.com/Jared_TFL/status/1614288469098127360" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">news</a> boosted the Terra Classic (LUNC) price. According to Jared, lead developer at Terraform Labs, more integrations and reforms are coming to Terra soon.</p>
<p>The sudden crash of Terra LUNA sent a cascade effect across the crypto industry, leading several firms to bankruptcy. Many investors are yet to recover from the loss incurred from the Terra implosion.</p>
<p>There are still uncleared controversies surrounding the ecosystem&#8217;s sudden collapse. Some say Terra LUNA was a rug pull scheme by Do Kwon, founder of Terraform Labs, to launder and steal people&#8217;s money. Meanwhile, Do Kwon and his executives are still on the run from South Korean prosecutors.</p>

<h2>More Integrations Coming To Terra Classic Network</h2>
<p>In a <a href="https://twitter.com/Jared_TFL/status/1614288469098127360" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Twitter announcement</a>, Jared revealed that the Terra Network would partner with other blockchains, including SEI, Juno, Osmosis, Mars, Pisco, and many more. He said the integrations aim to protect the network in the right direction and allow seamless cross-chain communication between Terra and other blockchains.</p>
<p>Jared also told the Terra community to expect a rollout of more features while their main focus is to launch the wallet on mobile devices. The current station supports many mainnets including LUNC, LUNA, Osmosis, Juno, Kujira, Carbon, HuaHua, and Cresent.</p>
<p>Terra’s interchain station wallet would simplify the complex process of interacting with multiple blockchain networks. The wallet would allow users to stake, vote, send, receive tokens, and interact with decentralized applications (dApps) across supported chains.</p>
<p>LUNC price soared by 3% on January 10 when Jared first shared news of the interchain wallet feature via his Twitter handle. Jared referred to the development as a breakthrough in chain integrations.</p>
<p>This move comes after several attempts by the Terra Classic community to revive the sinking Terra Classic project. With the new station wallet, DeFi developers can now access oracle data from several chains through the interchain facility.</p>
<h2>Why New Governance Implementation Is Important To LUNC Community</h2>
<p>The Terra Classic blockchain saw a rough start in 2023 after being impacted by crypto exchange <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vf9UbnuXT0w" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">KuCoin’s December 30 move</a>. On December 30, 2022, KuCoin removed (undelegated) 48 billion Terra Classic (LUNC) tokens from circulation. This issue reduced the voting power of KuCoin’s Terra Classic Validator by 0.25%, taking it up to the 44th position.</p>
<p>The exchange later said it would continue pledging LUNC tokens after a 14-day lock period. However, the move caused a drastic reduction in on-chain activity and stirred much anxiety in the LUNC community, causing the price to fall.</p>
<p>After Kucoin’s move, the community responded by approving and implementing new governance proposals to improve the overall operation of the chain. The Terra ecosystem also started burning tokens to stir up on-chain activity.</p>
<p>The new governance proposals got overwhelming votes from the community with the support of major crypto exchanges. As a result, one of the new implementations is <a href="https://www.binance.com/en/feed/post/158844" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">governance proposal 11242</a>, which aims to stop the reminting of already destroyed LUNC tokens.</p>
<p>Once the implementation is complete, it will ensure the effective elimination of tokens from LUNC&#8217;s circulating supply which will also boost its price. Presently, the amount of Terra Classic tokens in circulation is nearly 6 trillion.</p>

<p>After the reduction in on-chain activity in the past month, the developers published proposal 11242 at the beginning of January. The aim of proposal 11242 is to stop the reminting burnt LUNC tokens and effectively reduce the seigniorage reward policy to zero.</p>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-516225 size-large" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/LUNCUSDT_2023-01-16_18-50-35-860x499.png" alt="Will New Interchain Station Wallet Launch, Spike LUNC Price" width="860" height="499" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/LUNCUSDT_2023-01-16_18-50-35-860x499.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/LUNCUSDT_2023-01-16_18-50-35-460x267.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/LUNCUSDT_2023-01-16_18-50-35-768x446.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/LUNCUSDT_2023-01-16_18-50-35-750x435.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/LUNCUSDT_2023-01-16_18-50-35.png 1116w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" />
<p>LUNC price is trading at $0.000177 with a minor decline. The token has gained up to 15.50% in the past week.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/cape-gd883d7642_1280-460x368.jpg" width="460" height="368" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum Hits Monthly High And Turns Deflationary Again</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/ethereum-hits-monthly-high-and-turns-deflationary-again/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[anvisaini]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 17:03:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum (ETH)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum (ETH) Price Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=516242</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Ethereum price rally is on an upward trajectory since the last fortnight. Performing a little over Bitcoin’s growth, Ethereum gained 30%. On the morning of 16th January, Ethereum woke up to exciting news as Ethereum is riding high on the $1600 market price.  This comes after several contributory factors play a role in the price increase. From the accumulation of assets, particularly by Shark Addresses, it crossed above $1400 for the first time since 7th November on 12th January.  Related Reading: ETH Whales Scoop Up SAND – Up Nearly 80% – For Its Highly Bought Crypto Menu Shark Addresses are also the highest in this period, with Santiment observing 3000 new Shark Addresses, taking the total tally to the highest since February 2021.  Ethereum Bullish Momentum Before The Shanghai Upgrade Ethereum is two months away from the Shanghai Upgrade, and the prices have surged to the highest in ten weeks. After this upgrade, Ethereum will implement EIP Proposal 4895, enabling consensus layer withdrawals.  Following the Shanghai Upgrade, the users can withdraw staked ETH tokens on the Beacon chain for over 2 years. This upgrade is going to streamline the ETH withdrawal and will improve the exit process.  This upgrade is going to benefit ETH liquid staking platforms. Simply put, liquid staking is locking up funds to generate rewards. However, in this, the users can still access their locked funds. Given the fact that with the upgrade, the users can withdraw their staked amounts, subject to the correct exit process, which will be an attractive factor.  Lido is one of the platforms allowing liquid staking, and its performance is great. The amount of ETH staked on Lido crosses a cumulative value of $22.5 billion. Crypto experts believe that after the new upgrade, ETH will be staked to leverage better yield opportunities.  More Ethereum Is Burning Than Produced Ethereum’s performance in 2022 was not good. However, come 2023, the ETH holders are in a celebratory mood as the coin’s price increases amidst a deflationary trend. As the on-chain fundamentals strengthen ETH issue goes into a deflationary mood as the current supply growth reduces by -0.10%, according to the latest trends by Ultrasound Money. According to the same source, 732,000 ETH was burned, and 622,000 ETH was issued. The overall trend in the market is still bearish, but seeing the current upward trend in ETH and its price increase, the market is expected to take a bullish turn. Moreover, with the gas price increase, the burn rate will increase further.  Consequently, the higher deflation rate will lead to a shrinking supply. As compared to Bitcoin, Ethereum has a higher value settlement. This is an interesting trend for the future as ETH holders stand to gain more than BTC holders in the future when the contracts mature.  Related Reading: Bitcoin Hash Ribbons Trigger Buy Signal, Has Miner Capitulation Concluded? Observing the growth in ETH, the loss of momentum in the crypto market facilitated by the FTX crash is coming back. Moreover, across the crypto market, trends are rising with an overall gain of 1.3%, totalling a value of $1.3 trillion.  Featured image from Kanchanara / Unsplash, Chart from TradingView.com &#160; &#160; &#160;]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Ethereum price rally is on an upward trajectory since the last fortnight. Performing a little over Bitcoin’s growth, Ethereum gained 30%. On the morning of 16th January, Ethereum woke up to exciting news as Ethereum is riding high on the $1600 market price. </p>
<p>This comes after several contributory factors play a role in the price increase. From the accumulation of assets, particularly by <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/ethereum/ethereum-rallies-above-1400-as-sharks-accumulate/">Shark Addresses</a>, it crossed above $1400 for the first time since 7th November on 12th January. </p>

<p>Shark Addresses are also the highest in this period, with <a href="https://twitter.com/santimentfeed/status/1613359474710048768?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw%7Ctwcamp%5Etweetembed%7Ctwterm%5E1613359474710048768%7Ctwgr%5E8246cd8137b113a652ae6a25635a7bbd61c3d5bc%7Ctwcon%5Es1_&amp;ref_url=https%3A%2F%2Fbeincrypto.com%2Fethereum-tops-1400-eth-accumulation-accelerates%2F" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">Santiment observing</a> 3000 new Shark Addresses, taking the total tally to the highest since February 2021. </p>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-516244 size-jnews-featured-1140" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Etherum-Graph-1140x605.png" alt="Ethereum Graph" width="1140" height="605" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Etherum-Graph-1140x605.png 1140w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Etherum-Graph-460x244.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Etherum-Graph-860x456.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Etherum-Graph-768x408.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Etherum-Graph-1536x815.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Etherum-Graph-750x398.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Etherum-Graph.png 1920w" sizes="(max-width: 1140px) 100vw, 1140px" />
<h2><b>Ethereum Bullish Momentum Before The Shanghai Upgrade</b></h2>
<p>Ethereum is two months away from the Shanghai Upgrade, and the prices have surged to the highest in ten weeks. After this upgrade, Ethereum will implement <a href="https://eips.ethereum.org/EIPS/eip-4895" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">EIP Proposal 4895</a>, enabling consensus layer withdrawals. </p>
<p>Following the<a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/ethereum-investors-gain-4-5/"> Shanghai Upgrade,</a> the users can withdraw staked ETH tokens on the Beacon chain for over 2 years. This upgrade is going to streamline the ETH withdrawal and will improve the exit process. </p>
<p>This upgrade is going to benefit ETH liquid staking platforms. Simply put, liquid staking is locking up funds to generate rewards. However, in this, the users can still access their locked funds. Given the fact that with the upgrade, the users can withdraw their staked amounts, subject to the correct exit process, which will be an attractive factor. </p>
<p><a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/lido-dao-ldo-token-outperforms/">Lido</a> is one of the platforms allowing liquid staking, and its performance is great. The amount of ETH staked on Lido crosses a cumulative value of $22.5 billion. Crypto experts believe that after the new upgrade, ETH will be staked to leverage better yield opportunities. </p>
<h2><b>More Ethereum Is Burning Than Produced</b></h2>
<p>Ethereum’s performance in 2022 was not good. However, come 2023, the ETH holders are in a celebratory mood as the coin’s price increases amidst a deflationary trend. As the on-chain fundamentals strengthen ETH issue goes into a deflationary mood as the current supply growth reduces by -0.10%, according to the latest trends by <a href="https://ultrasound.money/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">Ultrasound Money</a>.</p>
<p>According to the same source, 732,000 ETH was burned, and 622,000 ETH was issued. The overall trend in the market is still bearish, but seeing the current upward trend in ETH and its price increase, the market is expected to take a bullish turn. Moreover, with the gas price increase, the burn rate will increase further. </p>
<p>Consequently, the higher deflation rate will lead to a shrinking supply. As compared to <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-miners-signs-dumping-bad-rally/">Bitcoin</a>, Ethereum has a higher value settlement. This is an interesting trend for the future as ETH holders stand to gain more than BTC holders in the future when the contracts mature. </p>

<p>Observing the growth in ETH, the loss of momentum in the crypto market facilitated by the <a href="https://newsbtc.com/crypto/ftx-ftt-token-spikes-43-a-revival-happening/">FTX crash</a> is coming back. Moreover, across the crypto market, trends are rising with an overall gain of 1.3%, totalling a value of $1.3 trillion. </p>



<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ethereum-1-460x306.jpg" width="460" height="306" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Lazarus Group Transfers $64M ETH From Harmony Bridge Hack</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/crypto/lazarus-group-transfers-64m-eth/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Muhammad Ali]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 17:00:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Harmony Bridge Hack]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[huobi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Lazarus]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ZachXBT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=516249</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[During the weekend, the notorious North Korean hacking gang Lazarus Group started transferring stolen money in the Harmony Bridge attack. Notably, the organization transferred over $63.5 million, or approximately 41,000 ETH.  Related Reading: FTX Hacker Mobilizes Ethereum Again, Lock And Loaded For The Dump? On January 16, blockchain detective ZachXBT published information about the transfer of a significant amount of Ethereum. The cryptocurrency assets which originated from Tornado Cash were transferred via Railgun. Railgun is a private smart contract platform that uses zero-knowledge proofs to hide financial transactions. Related Reading: Bitcoin Price Is Facing A ‘Pump And Whack’ Ranging Market According to the analyst who followed the trail of more than 350 addresses, some 41,000 ETH worth about $63.5 million were sent through Railgun and deposited on three different exchanges. 1/2 North Korea’s Lazarus Group had a very busy weekend moving $63.5m (~41000 ETH) from the Harmony bridge hack through Railgun before consolidating funds and depositing on three different exchanges. pic.twitter.com/huDumaJeSh — ZachXBT (@zachxbt) January 15, 2023 Funds Frozen By Binance And Huobi Binance&#8217;s CEO, CZ, tweeted that the exchange had previously uncovered suspicious money transfers from the Harmony One hackers when they attempted to launder money through Binance. As a result, the accounts were frozen by the exchange.  We detected Harmony One hacker fund movement. They previously tried to launder through Binance and we froze his accounts. This time he used Huobi. We assisted Huobi team to freeze his accounts. Together, 124 BTC have been recovered. CeFi helping to keep DeFi #SAFU! 🙏 — CZ 🔶 Binance (@cz_binance) January 16, 2023 The Group had been keeping its money in Tornado Cash, a service that helps keep people&#8217;s identities secret and is used by criminals to launder money in the crypto industry. The experts followed the funds through more than three hundred addresses. They concluded that Railgun had spread around 41,000 ETH among multiple receivers before the cryptocurrencies were deposited at various exchanges. He did not name the exchanges, but he did say that the Lazarus Group routinely makes rapid withdrawals from such platforms. Connections Between Lazarus And Harmony&#8217;s Attack Lazarus is now quite skilled at hiding their movements from law enforcement agencies while transferring illegal cryptocurrencies. For example, they were suspected of being behind the attack on Harmony Bridge in June 2022. In-depth information about the attack was published by Elliptic, a blockchain analytics service, at the time it occurred. Multiple large crypto heists, totaling over $2 billion, have been linked to the Lazarus Group. DeFi and cross-chain bridges became a new target in 2022, and the group was also suspected of being behind the $600 million Ronin Bridge attack. According to a recent report by cybersecurity firm Kaspersky, another North Korean hacker group BlueNoroff has expanded its illegal activities by posing as venture capitalists looking to invest in cryptocurrency startups. Kaspersky&#8217;s report shows the global attacks by BlueNoroff against cryptocurrency businesses were uncovered in January 2022 but slowed down until the fall. Theft of cryptocurrency has become a profitable business for North Korean hackers. According to information about their operations, South Korean spying services estimate that over $1.2 billion in cryptocurrency has been stolen from the global community since 2017. In 2022, numerous companies, including FTX, were victims of cyberattacks. At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading around $20,800, up 21% in the last week. It is currently trading above its 50-day Simple Moving Average (SMA), which indicates that the price will remain bullish in the short term. Featured image from Euronews, Chart from Tradingview.com.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>During the weekend, the notorious North Korean hacking gang Lazarus Group started transferring stolen money in the Harmony Bridge attack. Notably, the organization transferred over $63.5 million, or approximately 41,000 ETH. </p>

<p>On January 16, blockchain detective ZachXBT published information about the transfer of a significant amount of Ethereum. The cryptocurrency assets which originated from Tornado Cash were transferred via Railgun. Railgun is a private smart contract platform that uses zero-knowledge proofs to hide financial transactions.
</p>



<p>According to the analyst who followed the trail of more than 350 addresses, some 41,000 ETH worth about $63.5 million were sent through Railgun and deposited on three different exchanges.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">1/2 North Korea’s Lazarus Group had a very busy weekend moving $63.5m (~41000 ETH) from the Harmony bridge hack through Railgun before consolidating funds and depositing on three different exchanges. <a href="https://t.co/huDumaJeSh" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/huDumaJeSh</a></p>
<p>— ZachXBT (@zachxbt) <a href="https://twitter.com/zachxbt/status/1614771861266792449?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">January 15, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<h2>Funds Frozen By Binance And Huobi</h2>
<p>Binance&#8217;s CEO, CZ, tweeted that the exchange had previously uncovered suspicious money transfers from the Harmony One hackers when they attempted to launder money through Binance. As a result, the accounts were frozen by the exchange. </p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">We detected Harmony One hacker fund movement. They previously tried to launder through Binance and we froze his accounts. This time he used Huobi. We assisted Huobi team to freeze his accounts. Together, 124 BTC have been recovered. CeFi helping to keep DeFi <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/SAFU?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">#SAFU</a>! <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f64f.png" alt="🙏" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /></p>
<p>— CZ <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f536.png" alt="🔶" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> Binance (@cz_binance) <a href="https://twitter.com/cz_binance/status/1614887319177428992?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">January 16, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p>The Group had been keeping its money in Tornado Cash, a service that helps keep people&#8217;s identities secret and is used by criminals to launder money in the crypto industry.</p>
<p>The experts followed the funds through more than three hundred addresses. They concluded that Railgun had spread around 41,000 ETH among multiple receivers before the cryptocurrencies were deposited at various exchanges. He did not name the exchanges, but he did say that the Lazarus Group routinely makes rapid withdrawals from such platforms.</p>
Connections Between Lazarus And Harmony&#8217;s Attack
<p>Lazarus is now quite skilled at hiding their movements from law enforcement agencies while transferring illegal cryptocurrencies. For example, they were suspected of being behind the attack on Harmony Bridge in June 2022. In-depth information about the attack was published by Elliptic, a blockchain analytics service, at the time it occurred.</p>
<p>Multiple large crypto heists, totaling over $2 billion, have been linked to the Lazarus Group. DeFi and cross-chain bridges became a new target in 2022, and the group was also suspected of being behind the $600 million Ronin Bridge attack.</p>
<p>According to a recent <a href="https://securelist.com/bluenoroff-methods-bypass-motw/108383/?reseller=usa_regular-sm_acq_ona_smm__onl_b2c_twi_post_sm-team______&amp;utm_source=twitter&amp;utm_medium=social&amp;utm_campaign=us_regular-sm_en0177&amp;utm_content=sm-post&amp;utm_term=us_twitter_organic_vome177wjgciy7v" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">report </a>by cybersecurity firm Kaspersky, another North Korean hacker group BlueNoroff has expanded its illegal activities by posing as venture capitalists looking to invest in cryptocurrency startups.</p>
<p>Kaspersky&#8217;s report shows the global attacks by BlueNoroff against cryptocurrency businesses were uncovered in January 2022 but slowed down until the fall.</p>
<p>Theft of cryptocurrency has become a profitable business for North Korean hackers. According to information about their operations, South Korean spying services estimate that over $1.2 billion in cryptocurrency has been stolen from the global community since 2017. In 2022, numerous companies, including FTX, were victims of cyberattacks.</p>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-516260 size-large" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD_2023-01-16_20-14-46-860x517.png" alt="" width="860" height="517" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD_2023-01-16_20-14-46-860x517.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD_2023-01-16_20-14-46-460x276.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD_2023-01-16_20-14-46-768x462.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD_2023-01-16_20-14-46-750x451.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD_2023-01-16_20-14-46-1140x685.png 1140w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD_2023-01-16_20-14-46.png 1248w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" />
<p>At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading around $20,800, up 21% in the last week. It is currently trading above its 50-day <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=o1hgPoasCzA" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Simple Moving Average (SMA)</a>, which indicates that the price will remain bullish in the short term.</p>
<p>Featured image from Euronews, Chart from Tradingview.com.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/1440x810_cmsv2_d1b69a80-e612-5065-a4df-c9d62b0ee6fc-6578322-460x259.jpg" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>What Matters In Crypto This Week: Will Bitcoin Keep Pumping?</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/what-matters-crypto-this-week-bitcoin/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jake Simmons]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 16:00:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=516199</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Even though the next FOMC meeting of the U.S. Federal Reserve is still more than two weeks away, there are significant macroeconomic as well as crypto and Bitcoin-intrinsic events this week that investors should keep an eye on. As in previous weeks and months, it is very likely that the macro environments will steer the sentiment in the crypto market. After the December 2022 CPI was released last Thursday at 6.5%, the crypto market turned strongly bullish. Bitcoin rallied more than 18% after the publication and stopped just short of the $21,450 level. The entire crypto is about to recapture the $1 trillion dollar market cap in the wake of this recovery. What Marcoevents Will Guide Bitcoin This Week? This week, China will announce the economic data for 2022, which probably won&#8217;t have that big of an impact unless there is a big surprise that affects the U.S. dollar. Still, it&#8217;s worth keeping an eye on China this Monday when the GDP growth rate year-over-year (YoY) is announced at 9:00 pm EST. Also, the Bank of Japan&#8217;s (BoJ) interest rate decision could only become relevant if there is a surprise like last time. On Tuesday at 10:00 pm EST, the BoJ will announce its interest rate decision. The expectation here is that it will leave interest rates unchanged. When the Japanese central bank surprisingly decided to raise the benchmark interest rate from 0.25% to 0.5% on December 20, BTC experienced a green daily candle. Related Reading: Bitcoin Hash Ribbons Trigger Buy Signal, Has Miner Capitulation Concluded? In the U.S., the Producer Price Index (PPI) is likely to be the most important data point this week. Even though the PPI hasn&#8217;t had much of an impact on the overall financial market and Bitcoin in particular lately, the PPI could reaffirm bullish sentiment on rising inflation or provide a damper. The PPI data for December 2022 will be released on Wednesday, January 18 at 8:30 am EST. Watch Out For The DXY Perhaps the most important indicator at the moment of whether Bitcoin and crypto will continue to rally is the U.S. Dollar Index (DXY). The inverse correlation between Bitcoin and the DXY has been particularly high in recent weeks. Related Reading: Ethereum Price Accelerates Higher as The Bulls Aim $1,720 The latest Bitcoin rally was fueled by a weakening U.S. dollar. However, the DXY has fallen into a historically important support zone. If the DXY experiences a bounce out of the support zone, it is likely that BTC will experience a retracement &#8211; which would be healthy given its current oversold state with an RSI of 89 on the daily chart. Should the DXY fall below 101, the doors would be wide open for a sustained Bitcoin rally. In this respect, the macroeconomic situation probably remains the all-determining factor for the BTC price, provided there is no crypto-instinct catastrophic news. First and foremost, Digital Currency Group (DCG), Grayscale, and Gemini remain in the spotlight with their unresolved conflict over Gemini Earn client funds at Genesis Trading, which could derail a rally even if the DXY continues to fall. At press time, the BTC price stood at $20,861. Featured image from Kanchanara / Unsplash, Charts from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Even though the next FOMC meeting of the U.S. Federal Reserve is still more than two weeks away, there are significant macroeconomic as well as crypto and Bitcoin-intrinsic events this week that investors should keep an eye on. As in previous weeks and months, it is very likely that the <a href="https://tradingeconomics.com/calendar" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">macro environments</a> will steer the sentiment in the crypto market.</p>
<p>After the December 2022 CPI was released last Thursday at 6.5%, the crypto market turned strongly bullish. Bitcoin rallied more than 18% after the publication and stopped just short of the $21,450 level. The entire crypto is about to recapture the $1 trillion dollar market cap in the wake of this recovery.</p>
<h2>What Marcoevents Will Guide Bitcoin This Week?</h2>
<p>This week, China will announce the economic data for 2022, which probably won&#8217;t have that big of an impact unless there is a big surprise that affects the U.S. dollar. Still, it&#8217;s worth keeping an eye on China this Monday when the GDP growth rate year-over-year (YoY) is announced at 9:00 pm EST.</p>
<p>Also, the Bank of Japan&#8217;s (BoJ) interest rate decision could only become relevant if there is a surprise like last time. On Tuesday at 10:00 pm EST, the BoJ will announce its interest rate decision.</p>
<p>The expectation here is that it will leave interest rates unchanged. When the Japanese central bank surprisingly decided to raise the benchmark interest rate from 0.25% to 0.5% on December 20, BTC <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-bounces-reason-is-a-windfall/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">experienced</a> a green daily candle.</p>

<p>In the U.S., the Producer Price Index (PPI) is likely to be the most important data point this week. Even though the PPI hasn&#8217;t had much of an impact on the overall financial market and Bitcoin in particular lately, the PPI could reaffirm bullish sentiment on rising inflation or provide a damper.</p>
<p>The PPI data for December 2022 will be released on Wednesday, January 18 at 8:30 am EST.</p>
<h2>Watch Out For The DXY</h2>
<p>Perhaps the most important indicator at the moment of whether Bitcoin and crypto will continue to rally is the U.S. Dollar Index (DXY). The inverse <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-stable-gold-dxy-nasdaq-happen/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">correlation</a> between Bitcoin and the DXY has been particularly high in recent weeks.</p>

<p>The latest Bitcoin rally was fueled by a weakening U.S. dollar. However, the DXY has fallen into a historically important support zone.</p>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-516212 size-full" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/DXY_2023-01-16_14-28-17.png" alt="DXY" width="2962" height="1616" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/DXY_2023-01-16_14-28-17.png 2962w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/DXY_2023-01-16_14-28-17-460x251.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/DXY_2023-01-16_14-28-17-860x469.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/DXY_2023-01-16_14-28-17-768x419.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/DXY_2023-01-16_14-28-17-1536x838.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/DXY_2023-01-16_14-28-17-2048x1117.png 2048w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/DXY_2023-01-16_14-28-17-750x409.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/DXY_2023-01-16_14-28-17-1140x622.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 2962px) 100vw, 2962px" />
<p>If the DXY experiences a bounce out of the support zone, it is likely that BTC will experience a retracement &#8211; which would be healthy given its current oversold state with an RSI of 89 on the daily chart.</p>
<p>Should the DXY fall below 101, the doors would be wide open for a sustained Bitcoin rally. In this respect, the macroeconomic situation probably remains the all-determining factor for the BTC price, provided there is no crypto-instinct catastrophic news.</p>
<p>First and foremost, Digital Currency Group (DCG), Grayscale, and Gemini remain in the spotlight with their <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/firm-warns-bitcoin-eth-investors-over-dcg/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">unresolved conflict</a> over Gemini Earn client funds at Genesis Trading, which could derail a rally even if the DXY continues to fall.</p>
<p>At press time, the BTC price stood at $20,861.</p>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-516217 size-full" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD_2023-01-16_14-33-11.png" alt="Bitcoin price BTC USD" width="2954" height="1612" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD_2023-01-16_14-33-11.png 2954w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD_2023-01-16_14-33-11-460x251.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD_2023-01-16_14-33-11-860x469.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD_2023-01-16_14-33-11-768x419.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD_2023-01-16_14-33-11-1536x838.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD_2023-01-16_14-33-11-2048x1118.png 2048w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD_2023-01-16_14-33-11-750x409.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD_2023-01-16_14-33-11-1140x622.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 2954px) 100vw, 2954px" />
<p>Featured image from Kanchanara / Unsplash, Charts from TradingView.com</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/kanchanara-dRgxo-ujT2U-unsplash-460x306.jpg" width="460" height="306" />	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>

<!--
Performance optimized by W3 Total Cache. Learn more: https://www.boldgrid.com/w3-total-cache/

Object Caching 217/220 objects using apc
Page Caching using disk: enhanced (Page is feed) 
Database Caching 34/43 queries in 0.008 seconds using memcached

Served from: newsbtc.com @ 2023-01-16 22:11:34 by W3 Total Cache
-->