<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	 xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" >

<channel>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://newsbtc.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://newsbtc.com</link>
	<description>Bitcoin &#38; cryptocurrency news today, price &#38; technical analysis</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2022 02:34:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<link>https://newsbtc.com</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Exploiter Of &#8220;Highly Profitable Trading Strategy&#8221; Arrested In Puerto Rico</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/exploiter-arrested-in-puerto-rico/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Taylor Scott]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2022 02:31:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exploiter]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mango Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MNGOUSD]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=513928</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A few months can feel like a lifetime in crypto. However, it probably hasn&#8217;t felt like long enough for Mango Markets exploiter Avraham Eisenberg, who was taken into custody in Puerto Rico this week. Eisenberg gained notoriety on crypto Twitter after describing his nine-figure exploit of the Solana-based protocol as &#8220;a highly profitable trading strategy.&#8221; On Twitter and across other outlets, Eisenberg was insistent that his exploit was simply taking advantage of the protocol&#8217;s code, and that his actions weren&#8217;t illegal or even immoral. However, U.S. federal prosectors seem to disagree. An Exploiter&#8217;s Endeavor In October, Eisenberg exploited Solana-based Mango Markets and made headlines not just for the exploit &#8211; which was essentially a &#8216;looping&#8217; exploit, manipulating the price of the MNGO token &#8211; but also for the outlandishly-sized &#8216;bug bounty&#8217; that Eisenberg managed to walk away with. B ug bounties are commonplace for exploiters &#8211; often &#8216;white hat&#8217; exploiters who look to take advantage of code for the &#8216;better of society&#8217; &#8211; but never have amounted to a payout this large. While Eisenberg attempted to include language in a Mango protocol proposal that could shield him from &#8220;criminal investigations,&#8221; that didn&#8217;t slow the U.S. DoJ and FBI from looking into his activity. At the time of our October publishing on the matter, it was unclear if Mango would be able to make a recovery; little did we know how much damage the Solana ecosystem would face in the 60 days following that event. Since the exploiter&#8217;s endeavor, Solana&#8217;s defi landscape has crumbled, FTX fallout has impacted the chain drastically, and it&#8217;s once flagship NFT community is facing intense pressure with the departure of signature projects DeGods and y00ts. Mango Markets (MNGO) was taken advantage of by an exploiter who has been arrested this week. &#124; Source: MNGO-USD on TradingView.com Related Reading: Dogecoin Among Most Searched Cryptos Of The Year, Will It Keep Its Spot In 2023? Mango Madness, Continued Court documents have been unveiled this week, shedding light on Eisenberg&#8217;s arrest in Puerto Rico. An initial filing, dated December 23, 2022 and released this week, federal prosecutors outline two separate charges surrounding Eisenberg&#8217;s &#8220;scheme involving the intentional and artificial manipulation of the price of perpetual futures contracts&#8221; on Mango. The 14-page filing details how Eisenberg manipulated MNGO perps, detailing his movement between wallets. The filing closes by mentioning that Eisenberg attempted to flee law enforcement by swiftly departing the U.S. to Israel, and highlights the belief that Eisenberg was well aware of the illegality of his actions, based on Twitter activity. The document is rounded out by a request from the FBI agent to issue a warrant for Eisenberg&#8217;s arrest. A second filing, dated December 27, confirms his arrest in Puerto Rico. Crypto Twitter rejoiced with memes surrounding Eisenberg&#8217;s arrest. Related Reading: Cardano Price Consolidates, When Should You Short Again?]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A few months can feel like a lifetime in crypto. However, it probably hasn&#8217;t felt like long enough for Mango Markets exploiter Avraham Eisenberg, who was taken into custody in Puerto Rico this week. Eisenberg gained notoriety on crypto Twitter after describing his nine-figure exploit of the Solana-based protocol as &#8220;a highly profitable trading strategy.&#8221; On Twitter and across other outlets, Eisenberg was insistent that his exploit was simply taking advantage of the protocol&#8217;s code, and that his actions weren&#8217;t illegal or even immoral.</p>
<p>However, U.S. federal prosectors seem to disagree.</p>
An Exploiter&#8217;s Endeavor
<p>In October, <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/mango-madness-exploiter-could-walk-away-with-unparalleled-50m-bug-bounty/">Eisenberg exploited Solana-based Mango Markets</a> and made headlines not just for the exploit &#8211; which was essentially a &#8216;looping&#8217; exploit, manipulating the price of the MNGO token &#8211; but also for the outlandishly-sized &#8216;bug bounty&#8217; that Eisenberg managed to walk away with. B</p>
<p>ug bounties are commonplace for exploiters &#8211; often &#8216;white hat&#8217; exploiters who look to take advantage of code for the &#8216;better of society&#8217; &#8211; but never have amounted to a payout this large. While Eisenberg attempted to include language in a Mango protocol proposal that could shield him from &#8220;criminal investigations,&#8221; that didn&#8217;t slow the U.S. DoJ and FBI from looking into his activity.</p>
<p>At the time of our October publishing on the matter, it was unclear if Mango would be able to make a recovery; little did we know how much damage the Solana ecosystem would face in the 60 days following that event. Since the exploiter&#8217;s endeavor, Solana&#8217;s defi landscape has crumbled, FTX fallout has impacted the chain drastically, and it&#8217;s once flagship NFT community is facing intense pressure with the <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/is-sol-about-to-crumble/">departure of signature projects DeGods and y00ts</a>.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-513932 aligncenter" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Screen-Shot-2022-12-27-at-6.26.06-PM-460x243.png" alt="" width="971" height="513" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Screen-Shot-2022-12-27-at-6.26.06-PM-460x243.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Screen-Shot-2022-12-27-at-6.26.06-PM-860x453.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Screen-Shot-2022-12-27-at-6.26.06-PM-768x405.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Screen-Shot-2022-12-27-at-6.26.06-PM-1536x810.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Screen-Shot-2022-12-27-at-6.26.06-PM-750x395.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Screen-Shot-2022-12-27-at-6.26.06-PM-1140x601.png 1140w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Screen-Shot-2022-12-27-at-6.26.06-PM.png 1580w" sizes="(max-width: 971px) 100vw, 971px" /></p>
























Mango Madness, Continued
<p>Court documents have been unveiled this week, shedding light on Eisenberg&#8217;s arrest in Puerto Rico. <a href="https://storage.courtlistener.com/recap/gov.uscourts.nysd.591629/gov.uscourts.nysd.591629.1.0.pdf" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">An initial filing</a>, dated December 23, 2022 and released this week, federal prosecutors outline two separate charges surrounding Eisenberg&#8217;s &#8220;scheme involving the intentional and artificial manipulation of the price of perpetual futures contracts&#8221; on Mango. The 14-page filing details how Eisenberg manipulated MNGO perps, detailing his movement between wallets.</p>
<p>The filing closes by mentioning that Eisenberg attempted to flee law enforcement by swiftly departing the U.S. to Israel, and highlights the belief that Eisenberg was well aware of the illegality of his actions, based on Twitter activity. The document is rounded out by a request from the FBI agent to issue a warrant for Eisenberg&#8217;s arrest.</p>
<p><a href="https://storage.courtlistener.com/recap/gov.uscourts.nysd.591629/gov.uscourts.nysd.591629.3.0.pdf" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">A second filing</a>, dated December 27, confirms his arrest in Puerto Rico. Crypto Twitter rejoiced with memes surrounding Eisenberg&#8217;s arrest.</p>





















]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/pexels-kindel-media-7773260-460x345.jpeg" width="460" height="345" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cardano Price Consolidates, When Should You Short Again?</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/analysis/ada/cardano-price-consolidates-should-you-short-again/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[anushsamal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2022 01:00:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[ADA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[adausd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADAUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=513883</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Cardano price had increased over the weekend, but the coin showed lateral price movement at press time. Over the last 24 hours, ADA has dipped about 0.2%. The ADA has gained 4% in the last week, indicating a positive trend. According to the technical outlook, the Cardano price has not yet reversed its price action. The downtrend continues despite the coin securing minor gains over the last few days. The buying strength remained low, which depicted lower accumulation as well. Cardano bounced back from oversold territory, but the selling momentum was still strong. With the Bitcoin price falling and fluctuating between $16,900 and $16,600, altcoins have also seen choppy and undecided price movements. Following major market movers, ADA traded between $0.26 and $0.27, with the altcoin falling below the $0.25 price mark in the last 24 hours. The market has presented signs where buyers can make an entry to make some gains over the shorter trading timeframe. The trading volume of Cardano was low, indicating a lack of buyers. ADA is trading 91% below its all-time high secured in the last year. Related Reading: Terra Classic (LUNC) Beats The Odds With 16% Rally, More Gains Ahead Cardano Price Analysis: One-Day Chart ADA was trading at $0.25 at the time of writing. Because of the recent depreciation, ADA has lost its $0.26 support line. If buyers push harder, Cardano can be expected to trade above the $0.26 level again. The major mark of resistance for ADA stood at $0.28. As per the technical indicators, Cardano price might lose the $0.25 level before it starts to make upward strides again. That would mark an entry point for buyers and an appropriate shorting opportunity for traders. If the Cardano price fell below the $0.25 mark, the first support stood at $0.24 and then at $0.22. The amount of Cardano traded in the last session declined, signifying bearish price action. Technical Analysis Despite Cardano recovering from the undervalued zone, it still hovered close to the selling dominance zone. The Relative Strength Index was below the 40-mark with a downtick, which could lead to another fall in price before the altcoin makes a comeback. The Cardano price was below the 20-Simple Moving Average (SMA) line, which meant sellers continued to drive the price momentum in the market. Traders shorting will make gains over the next trading sessions as ADA prepares to topple past the 20-SMA line. Bearish conditions prevailed for Cardano, as the other indicators also pointed in the same direction. The Directional Movement Index (DMI), which demonstrates the price direction and strength, was negative. The -DI line (orange) was above the -DI line (blue), indicating that sellers had more strength in the market. The Average Directional Index (red) was at 40, depicting increased strength in the current price direction. This reiterated that the bears were strong, which would mean another fall for ADA, which could benefit sellers. The Moving Average Convergence Divergence portrays the price momentum. The indicator just painted one small green signal bar, indicating that buyers could find an entry point now to log gains over the immediate trading session. Related Reading: Bitcoin Miner Selling Power Plunges, Green Signal For Price? Featured Image From UnSplash, Charts From TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Cardano price had increased over the weekend, but the coin showed lateral price movement at press time. Over the last 24 hours, ADA has dipped about 0.2%. The ADA has gained 4% in the last week, indicating a positive trend. According to the technical outlook, the Cardano price has not yet reversed its price action.</p>
<p>The downtrend continues despite the coin securing minor gains over the last few days. The buying strength remained low, which depicted lower accumulation as well. Cardano bounced back from oversold territory, but the selling momentum was still strong.</p>
<p>With the Bitcoin price falling and fluctuating between $16,900 and $16,600, altcoins have also seen choppy and undecided price movements. Following major market movers, ADA traded between $0.26 and $0.27, with the altcoin falling below the $0.25 price mark in the last 24 hours.</p>
<p>The market has presented signs where buyers can make an entry to make some gains over the shorter trading timeframe. The trading volume of Cardano was low, indicating a lack of buyers. ADA is trading 91% below its all-time high secured in the last year.</p>

<h2>Cardano Price Analysis: One-Day Chart</h2>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-513901 size-full" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ADAUSD_2022-12-27_22-43-34.png" alt="Cardano Price" width="1816" height="830" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ADAUSD_2022-12-27_22-43-34.png 1816w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ADAUSD_2022-12-27_22-43-34-460x210.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ADAUSD_2022-12-27_22-43-34-860x393.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ADAUSD_2022-12-27_22-43-34-768x351.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ADAUSD_2022-12-27_22-43-34-1536x702.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ADAUSD_2022-12-27_22-43-34-750x343.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ADAUSD_2022-12-27_22-43-34-1140x521.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1816px) 100vw, 1816px" />
<p>ADA was trading at $0.25 at the time of writing. Because of the recent depreciation, ADA has lost its $0.26 support line. If buyers push harder, Cardano can be expected to trade above the $0.26 level again. The major mark of resistance for ADA stood at $0.28.</p>
<p>As per the technical indicators, Cardano price might lose the $0.25 level before it starts to make upward strides again.</p>
<p>That would mark an entry point for buyers and an appropriate shorting opportunity for traders. If the Cardano price fell below the $0.25 mark, the first support stood at $0.24 and then at $0.22. The amount of Cardano traded in the last session declined, signifying bearish price action.</p>
<h2>Technical Analysis</h2>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-513903 size-full" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ADAUSD_2022-12-27_22-44-17.png" alt="Cardano Price" width="1816" height="743" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ADAUSD_2022-12-27_22-44-17.png 1816w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ADAUSD_2022-12-27_22-44-17-460x188.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ADAUSD_2022-12-27_22-44-17-860x352.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ADAUSD_2022-12-27_22-44-17-768x314.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ADAUSD_2022-12-27_22-44-17-1536x628.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ADAUSD_2022-12-27_22-44-17-750x307.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ADAUSD_2022-12-27_22-44-17-1140x466.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1816px) 100vw, 1816px" />
<p>Despite Cardano recovering from the undervalued zone, it still hovered close to the selling dominance zone. The Relative Strength Index was below the 40-mark with a downtick, which could lead to another fall in price before the altcoin makes a comeback.</p>
<p>The Cardano price was below the 20-Simple Moving Average (SMA) line, which meant sellers continued to drive the price momentum in the market. Traders shorting will make gains over the next trading sessions as ADA prepares to topple past the 20-SMA line.</p>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-513906 size-full" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ADAUSD_2022-12-27_22-44-55.png" alt="Cardano Price" width="1816" height="743" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ADAUSD_2022-12-27_22-44-55.png 1816w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ADAUSD_2022-12-27_22-44-55-460x188.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ADAUSD_2022-12-27_22-44-55-860x352.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ADAUSD_2022-12-27_22-44-55-768x314.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ADAUSD_2022-12-27_22-44-55-1536x628.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ADAUSD_2022-12-27_22-44-55-750x307.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ADAUSD_2022-12-27_22-44-55-1140x466.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1816px) 100vw, 1816px" />
<p>Bearish conditions prevailed for Cardano, as the other indicators also pointed in the same direction. The Directional Movement Index (DMI), which demonstrates the price direction and strength, was negative. The -DI line (orange) was above the -DI line (blue), indicating that sellers had more strength in the market.</p>
<p>The Average Directional Index (red) was at 40, depicting increased strength in the current price direction. This reiterated that the bears were strong, which would mean another fall for ADA, which could benefit sellers.</p>
<p>The Moving Average Convergence Divergence portrays the price momentum. The indicator just painted one small green signal bar, indicating that buyers could find an entry point now to log gains over the immediate trading session.</p>





]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/traxer-rTzVFtl3FCI-unsplash-306x460.jpg" width="306" height="460" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dogecoin Among Most Searched Cryptos Of The Year, Will It Keep Its Spot In 2023?</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/dogecoin/dogecoin-searched-crypto-spot-in-2023/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reynaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2022 01:00:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[doge]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dogeusdt]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=513861</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The price of Dogecoin (DOGE) follows the general trend in the crypto market and only records sideways activity. Due to the holiday season, the trading volume across global markets decreased, leading to stagnation in the nascent sector.  Related Reading: Chiliz (CHZ) Finds Cover At This Level For Some Temporary Relief As of this writing, Dogecoin trades at $0.074 with a 1% loss in the last 24 hours. In the previous seven days, DOGE has seen some small profits with a 5% gain. Other cryptocurrencies in the top ten by market cap are similarly performing.  Dogecoin Shares Spot With Bitcoin And Shiba Inu As Most Popular Cryptocurrencies Per a report from DollarGeek, cryptocurrencies remain some of the most searched digital financial assets of 2022. According to data from Google, cryptocurrencies total over 7 million monthly searches in the United States and over 40 million global searches.  Despite the persistent downside trend in its prices and unfavorable macroeconomic conditions, the digital asset class remained popular. The report claims. Bitcoin preserved its spot as the most popular cryptocurrency.  Over the past two years, several new sectors emerged from the crypto industry. However, people are still attracted to Bitcoin due to its decentralized nature. 2022 has been a year of declining trust in a central authority.  In this environment, people take more interest in alternatives, such as Bitcoin and other cryptocurrencies. The benchmark crypto recorded about 4,500,000 monthly searches in the U.S. and 28,400,000 global searches.  Further down the line of popular cryptocurrencies, Dogecoin and Shiba Inu took the number two and three positions. The meme coins continued to take over market share from other significant projects.  In the last months of 2022, Dogecoin and Shiba Inu claimed the previous positions in the crypto top 10 by market cap and often competed. In terms of Google searches, SHIBA and DOGE showed mixed results. According to the report, the meme coin recorded around 1,290,000 monthly searches in the U.S., but in terms of global monthly searches, Dogecoin took the crown. This cryptocurrency recorded around 6,000,000 monthly searches compared to the 4,400,000 million from SHIBA.  DOGE To See Further Growth In Popularity Per the report, the dominant trends in the crypto industry can be divided into meme coins, represented by Dogecoin and Shiba Inu, non-fungible tokens (NFTs), and innovative contract platforms, represented by Ethereum and Avalanche.  Finally, people took an interest in old cryptocurrencies revamping their ecosystem with new features, represented by Cardano and Litecoin. As seen in the chart below, Ethereum was the most popular in the group after DOGE and SHIB. Related Reading: Bitcoin Miner Selling Power Plunges, Green Signal For Price? In this group, Dogecoin has a high chance of preserving its place on this ranking in 2023. The meme coin might see more utility if Elon Musk, owner of Twitter, integrates it with this platform. ]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>The price of Dogecoin (DOGE) follows the general trend in the crypto market and only records sideways activity. Due to the holiday season, the trading volume across global markets decreased, leading to stagnation in the nascent sector. </strong></p>

<p>As of this writing, Dogecoin trades at $0.074 with a 1% loss in the last 24 hours. In the previous seven days, DOGE has seen some small profits with a 5% gain. Other cryptocurrencies in the top ten by market cap are similarly performing. </p>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-513882 size-large" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Dogecoin-DOGE-DOGEUSDT-860x376.png" alt="Dogecoin DOGE DOGEUSDT" width="860" height="376" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Dogecoin-DOGE-DOGEUSDT-860x376.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Dogecoin-DOGE-DOGEUSDT-460x201.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Dogecoin-DOGE-DOGEUSDT-768x336.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Dogecoin-DOGE-DOGEUSDT-1536x672.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Dogecoin-DOGE-DOGEUSDT-750x328.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Dogecoin-DOGE-DOGEUSDT-1140x499.png 1140w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Dogecoin-DOGE-DOGEUSDT.png 1813w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" />
<h2>Dogecoin Shares Spot With Bitcoin And Shiba Inu As Most Popular Cryptocurrencies</h2>
<p>Per a <a href="https://www.dollargeek.com/cryptocurrency/the-most-googled-cryptocurrencies-of-2022/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">report</a> from DollarGeek, cryptocurrencies remain some of the most searched digital financial assets of 2022. According to data from Google, cryptocurrencies total over 7 million monthly searches in the United States and over 40 million global searches. </p>
<p>Despite the persistent downside trend in its prices and unfavorable macroeconomic conditions, the digital asset class remained popular. The report claims. Bitcoin preserved its spot as the most popular cryptocurrency. </p>
<p>Over the past two years, several new sectors emerged from the crypto industry. However, people are still attracted to Bitcoin due to its decentralized nature. 2022 has been a year of declining trust in a central authority. </p>
<p>In this environment, people take more interest in alternatives, such as Bitcoin and other cryptocurrencies. The benchmark crypto recorded about 4,500,000 monthly searches in the U.S. and 28,400,000 global searches. </p>
<p>Further down the line of popular cryptocurrencies, Dogecoin and Shiba Inu took the number two and three positions. The meme coins continued to take over market share from other significant projects. </p>
<p>In the last months of 2022, Dogecoin and Shiba Inu claimed the previous positions in the crypto top 10 by market cap and often competed. In terms of Google searches, SHIBA and DOGE showed mixed results.</p>
<p>According to the report, the meme coin recorded around 1,290,000 monthly searches in the U.S., but in terms of global monthly searches, Dogecoin took the crown. This cryptocurrency recorded around 6,000,000 monthly searches compared to the 4,400,000 million from SHIBA. </p>
<strong>DOGE To See Further Growth In Popularity</strong>
<p>Per the report, the dominant trends in the crypto industry can be divided into meme coins, represented by Dogecoin and Shiba Inu, non-fungible tokens (NFTs), and innovative contract platforms, represented by Ethereum and Avalanche. </p>
<p>Finally, people took an interest in old cryptocurrencies revamping their ecosystem with new features, represented by Cardano and Litecoin. As seen in the chart below, Ethereum was the most popular in the group after DOGE and SHIB.</p>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-513881 size-full" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Dogecoin-DOGE-DOGEUSDT-Chart-1.jpg" alt="Dogecoin DOGE DOGEUSDT Chart 1" width="807" height="401" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Dogecoin-DOGE-DOGEUSDT-Chart-1.jpg 807w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Dogecoin-DOGE-DOGEUSDT-Chart-1-460x229.jpg 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Dogecoin-DOGE-DOGEUSDT-Chart-1-768x382.jpg 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Dogecoin-DOGE-DOGEUSDT-Chart-1-360x180.jpg 360w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Dogecoin-DOGE-DOGEUSDT-Chart-1-750x373.jpg 750w" sizes="(max-width: 807px) 100vw, 807px" />

<p>In this group, Dogecoin has a high chance of preserving its place on this ranking in 2023. The meme coin might see more utility if Elon Musk, owner of Twitter, integrates it with this platform. </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Dogecoin-Reutersjpg-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Why The Bitcoin Mining Hashrate May Not Be Out Of The Woods Just Yet</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-hashrate-not-out-of-the-woods/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Best Owie]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 23:00:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin hashrate]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin miners]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hashrate]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mining hashrate]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=513833</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The bitcoin mining hashrate took a sharp nosedive as a historical storm tore through multiple US states. This saw power grids consolidate power to be able to provide enough energy for residents to heat their homes and some mining operations had to wind down to free up more of the electrical. There has been an increase in the hashrate since then but the worst may not be over yet. Bitcoin Hashrate Takes A Beating Electricity grids across the United States came under immense pressure as the country recorded one of its coldest winters yet. Temperatures dropped drastically across various states and the electricity grid was stretched thin to provide enough energy to heat homes. As a result, a number of bitcoin miners decided to pause their operations to free up some energy and this affected the hashrate contributed by the country. Related Reading: Litecoin (LTC) Tops List Of Christmas Gainers, Is $100 Still Possible? By Christmas Day, the global hashrate had tanked almost 40%, dropping from its Dec. 24 peak of 276 exahashes per second (EH/s) to 175 EH/s. However, there was a 39% increase in hashrate on the same day which brought it back up to around 244 EH/s. BTC mining hashrate sees sharp decline on Christmas Day &#124; Source: CoinWarz Since then, the hashrate has continued to wobble day to day and has now dropped back to the 212 EH/s level once more. This shows that while miners may have turned some of their machines back on, they may be shutting them down once more as the extremely cold weather persists. How Long Will This Last? Winter storm expert for Atmospheric Environmental Research Judah Cohen said that the Arctic blast currently being experienced in the United States should be short-lived and last about a week before temperatures begin to return to normal.  BTC price maintains momentum above $16,800 &#124; Source: BTCUSD on TradingView.com However, this still leaves a couple of days before it is expected to completely subside. This is evidenced by the zig-zag recovery and dips in the bitcoin hashrate in the last two days following Dec. 25. Miners who have taken their operations offline to help stabilize the electricity grid will likely leave them offline for a while longer until authorities are convinced the weather has stabilized. An example of this was back in July when Riot Blockchain had to shut off its mining machines in Texas as the state faced a heat wave. Related Reading: Bearish Indicator: Bitcoin Volatility Hits All-Time Low Given this, the bitcoin mining hashrate is expected to trend low for another couple of days before bouncing back up. As for the miners, given that Riot had received $9.5 million in energy credits for turning off operations in July, it is possible that some sort of recompense will be offered to the miners. Featured image from Crypto News, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="p2">The bitcoin mining hashrate took a sharp nosedive as a historical storm tore through multiple US states. This saw power grids consolidate power to be able to provide enough energy for residents to heat their homes and some mining operations had to wind down to free up more of the electrical. There has been an increase in the hashrate since then but the worst may not be over yet.</p>
<h2 class="p2">Bitcoin Hashrate Takes A Beating</h2>
<p class="p2">Electricity grids across the United States came under immense pressure as the country recorded one of its coldest winters yet. Temperatures dropped drastically across various states and the electricity grid was stretched thin to provide enough energy to heat homes. As a result, a number of bitcoin miners decided to pause their operations to free up some energy and this affected the hashrate contributed by the country.</p>

<p class="p2">By Christmas Day, the <a href="https://www.coinwarz.com/mining/bitcoin/hashrate-chart" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">global hashrate had tanked almost 40%</a>, dropping from its Dec. 24 peak of 276 exahashes per second (EH/s) to 175 EH/s. However, there was a 39% increase in hashrate on the same day which brought it back up to around 244 EH/s.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-513838 aligncenter" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-mining-hashrate-460x174.png" alt="Bitcoin mining hashrate" width="460" height="174" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-mining-hashrate-460x174.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-mining-hashrate-860x325.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-mining-hashrate-768x291.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-mining-hashrate-1536x581.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-mining-hashrate-2048x775.png 2048w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-mining-hashrate-750x284.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-mining-hashrate-1140x431.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px" /></p>

<p class="p2">Since then, the hashrate has continued to wobble day to day and has now dropped back to the 212 EH/s level once more. This shows that while miners may have turned some of their machines back on, they may be shutting them down once more as the extremely cold weather persists.</p>
<h2 class="p2">How Long Will This Last?</h2>
<p class="p2">Winter storm expert for Atmospheric Environmental Research Judah Cohen said that the Arctic blast currently being experienced in the United States should be short-lived and last about a week before temperatures begin to return to normal. </p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/bGSJsx1X/" alt="Bitcoin price chart from TradingView.com" width="3284" height="1760" /></p>

<p class="p2">However, this still leaves a couple of days before it is expected to completely subside. This is evidenced by the zig-zag recovery and dips in the bitcoin hashrate in the last two days following Dec. 25. Miners who have taken their operations offline to help stabilize the electricity grid will likely leave them offline for a while longer until authorities are convinced the weather has stabilized. An example of this was back in July when Riot Blockchain had to shut off its mining machines in Texas as the state faced a heat wave.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-volatility-hits-all-time-low/">Bearish Indicator: Bitcoin Volatility Hits All-Time Low</a></p>
<p class="p2">Given this, the bitcoin mining hashrate is expected to trend low for another couple of days before bouncing back up. As for the miners, given that Riot had received $9.5 million in energy credits for turning off operations in July, it is possible that some sort of recompense will be offered to the miners.</p>



]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-hashrate-460x307.jpeg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Analyst Explains Why Ethereum Is Bullish Against Bitcoin</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/ethereum/analyst-ethereum-bullish-against-bitcoin/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hououin Kyouma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 19:00:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin miners]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethbtc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum Bullish]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=513886</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[An analyst has explained that the absence of miners on the Ethereum network could be bullish for the ETHBTC ratio. Miners Provide A Persistent Selling Pressure On Bitcoin As explained in a tweet by Tom Dunleavy, a Messari research analyst, BTC miners sell almost all the coins they mine. The below chart contains data about the top ten public Bitcoin mining companies, displaying information such as how much each of them mined this year, the amounts that they sold, and the size of their current holdings: Looks like Marathon is holding the largest reserve right now &#124; Source: Tom Dunleavy on Twitter In total, the ten largest mining companies in the space mined a collective 40.7 BTC this year and sold 40.3 BTC. This means that they roughly dumped the entire supply that they mined in 2022 and in the process, applied constant selling pressure on the network. Earlier in the year, Ethereum successfully transitioned to a Proof-of-Stake (PoS) consensus mechanism, which means the blockchain no longer uses miners for handling transactions, and rather uses stakers (investors that have locked 32 ETH in the PoS contract) to act as validating nodes. Related Reading: Bitcoin Selling Pressure Becoming Exhausted? This Metric May Hint So In a Proof-of-Work (PoW) system, miners compete with each other using large amounts of computing power. Therefore, many expenses are involved in getting up their facilities, but one cost, in particular, stays with them as long as they continue to operate: the electricity bills. It is because of these electricity bills that miners have to continuously sell what they mine to keep their business sustainable. Some miners try to hold onto their reserves for as long as possible, like Marathon, and Hut8 can be seen doing in the chart. Still, in a market like right now, where electricity prices have shot up while the BTC price has plummeted due to the bear, margins are fine for the already debt-ridden public miners, and thus most of them can&#8217;t afford to accumulate. In the case of a PoS chain, however, stakers don&#8217;t incur such expenses and thus don&#8217;t have any particular need to sell the rewards they earn while staking. This implies that the type of selling pressure that miners put on Bitcoin isn&#8217;t present on the Ethereum blockchain. Related Reading: Ethereum Price Downtrend Intact for this Reason, Market Muted The analyst believes that this fact provides a good thesis to be bullish on the ETHBTC ratio. Ethereum Price At the time of writing, ETH is trading around $1,200, down 1% in the last week. The value of the crypto doesn't seem to have moved much during the last few days &#124; Source: ETHUSD on TradingView Featured image from Pierre Borthiry &#8211; Peiobty on Unsplash.com, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>An analyst has explained that the absence of miners on the Ethereum network could be bullish for the ETHBTC ratio.</p>
<h2>Miners Provide A Persistent Selling Pressure On Bitcoin</h2>
<p>As explained in a <a href="https://twitter.com/dunleavy89/status/1607495480677699585" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">tweet</a> by Tom Dunleavy, a Messari research analyst, BTC miners sell almost all the coins they mine. The below chart contains data about the top ten public Bitcoin mining companies, displaying information such as how much each of them mined this year, the amounts that they sold, and the size of their current holdings:</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone aligncenter" src="https://pbs.twimg.com/media/Fk74nbPWAAI_yQZ?format=png&amp;name=small" alt="Bitcoin Public Miners" width="443" height="424" /></p>

<p>In total, the ten largest mining companies in the space mined a collective 40.7 BTC this year and sold 40.3 BTC. This means that they roughly dumped the entire supply that they mined in 2022 and in the process, applied constant selling pressure on the network.</p>
<p>Earlier in the year, Ethereum successfully transitioned to a <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/company/the-ethereum-merge-what-is-trading-headed-towards/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Proof-of-Stake</a> (PoS) consensus mechanism, which means the blockchain no longer uses miners for handling transactions, and rather uses stakers (investors that have locked 32 ETH in the PoS contract) to act as validating nodes.</p>

<p>In a Proof-of-Work (PoW) system, miners compete with each other using large amounts of computing power. Therefore, many expenses are involved in getting up their facilities, but one cost, in particular, stays with them as long as they continue to operate: the electricity bills. It is because of these electricity bills that miners have to continuously sell what they mine to keep their business sustainable.</p>
<p>Some miners try to hold onto their reserves for as long as possible, like <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/u-s-mining-company-marathon-now-holds-8133-btc-and-theyre-not-selling-it/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Marathon</a>, and Hut8 can be seen doing in the chart. Still, in a market like right now, where electricity prices have shot up while the BTC price has plummeted due to the bear, margins are fine for the already <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/why-most-public-bitcoin-miners-have-performed-terribly-in-their-lifetimes/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">debt-ridden public miners</a>, and thus most of them can&#8217;t afford to accumulate.</p>
<p>In the case of a PoS chain, however, stakers don&#8217;t incur such expenses and thus don&#8217;t have any particular need to sell the rewards they earn while staking. This implies that the type of selling pressure that miners put on Bitcoin isn&#8217;t present on the Ethereum blockchain.</p>

<p>The analyst believes that this fact provides a good thesis to be bullish on the ETHBTC ratio.</p>
<h2>Ethereum Price</h2>
<p>At the time of writing, ETH is trading around $1,200, down 1% in the last week.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-513895 size-large" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/chart-32-860x481.png" alt="Ethereum Price Chart" width="860" height="481" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/chart-32-860x481.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/chart-32-460x257.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/chart-32-768x430.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/chart-32-750x420.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/chart-32.png 972w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" /></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/pierre-borthiry-peiobty-vBCVcWUyvyM-unsplash-460x333.jpg" width="460" height="333" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Terra Classic (LUNC) Beats The Odds With 16% Rally, More Gains Ahead</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/terra-luna/terra-classic-lunc-beats-odds-with-rally/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Best Owie]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 17:00:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Terra (LUNA)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LUNC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LUNC performance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LUNC price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Terra]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Terra Classic]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=513832</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Terra Classic (LUNC) continues to show strength in the market despite losing over 99.9% of its value about 8 months prior. The digital asset which has now been reduced to the meme coin level still produces massive gains. Presently, LUNC is seeing double-digit gains even at a time when the majority of the market remains muted in terms of price performance. Terra Classic Pulls Big Gains Terra Classic (LUNC) saw a massive rally on Boxing Day that solidified massive gains for investors. Over the last 24 hours, LUNC has been able to rally more than 16% and has successfully broken resistance at the $0.00018 price level.  The price recovery follows a return of positive sentiment in the community as a new developer task force called the “Joint L1 Task Force” has proposed to build a Layer 1 Terra Classic blockchain. This comes as the community looks to move on from “Terra Rebels,” the first LUNC developer task force that is now plagued by various accusations. The community has already called for a return of $150,000 that was allocated to the task force previously. Related Reading: Bearish Indicator: Bitcoin Volatility Hits All-Time Low In addition, the Terra Classic community has also voted in favor of Proposal 11111. This proposal reduces the allocation of burned LUNC tokens within an epoch to the community to 10%, revoking the 50% that was previously proposed in Proposal 10983. This effectively reduces the number of tokens that would be brought back into circulation after being burned. Terra Classic price jumps above $0.00018 &#124; Source: LUNCUSD on TradingView.com The proposal passed with 83.35% of votes being in favor and only 11.31% being against. The excitement from this news has also contributed to the rally in the price of the digital asset. More Gains For LUNC? Terra Classic (LUNC) is currently sitting at the top of the list of top gainers on Coinmarketcap over the past 24 hours. With an approximately 17% jump in the last day, the digital asset defies a market that has seen slow movement, especially with bitcoin volatility dropping to all-time lows. Terra Classic tops lists of gainers &#124; Source: Coinmarketcap LUNC, on the other hand, tends to thrive in times like these. This is because, with the low momentum, larger assets such as bitcoin and ethereum are unlikely to move much, but with low-price cryptocurrencies such as LUNC, it presents an opportunity for investors since it is easier to move the needle. Couple this with the recent rise in positive sentiment in the community and it is a recipe for success. Related Reading: Litecoin (LTC) Tops List Of Christmas Gainers, Is $100 Still Possible? Its price has now reached its second-highest level for the month of December after successfully touching above $0.00018 in the early hours of Tuesday. If the momentum holds, then the cryptocurrency will see $0.0002 before the end of the day. LUNC was changing hands at $0.0001801 at the time of this writing, according to data from Coinmarketcap. Trading volume is up 157% in the last 24 hours and is sitting at $239.8 million. Featured image from Criptokio, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="p2">Terra Classic (LUNC) continues to show strength in the market despite losing over 99.9% of its value about 8 months prior. The digital asset which has now been reduced to the meme coin level still produces massive gains. Presently, LUNC is seeing double-digit gains even at a time when the majority of the market remains muted in terms of price performance.</p>
<h2 class="p2">Terra Classic Pulls Big Gains</h2>
<p class="p2">Terra Classic (LUNC) saw a massive rally on Boxing Day that solidified massive gains for investors. Over the last 24 hours, LUNC has been able to rally more than 16% and has successfully broken resistance at the $0.00018 price level. </p>
<p class="p2">The price recovery follows a return of positive sentiment in the community as a new developer task force called the “Joint L1 Task Force” has <a href="https://classic-agora.terra.money/t/joint-l1-task-force/49108" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">proposed to build a Layer 1 Terra Classic blockchain</a>. This comes as the community looks to move on from “Terra Rebels,” the first LUNC developer task force that is now plagued by various accusations. The community has already called for a return of $150,000 that was allocated to the task force previously.</p>

<p class="p2">In addition, the Terra Classic community has also voted in favor of Proposal 11111. This proposal reduces the allocation of burned LUNC tokens within an epoch to the community to 10%, revoking the 50% that was previously proposed in Proposal 10983. This effectively reduces the number of tokens that would be brought back into circulation after being burned.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/soMltjyu/" alt="LUNA Classic (LUNC) price chart from TradingView.com" width="3284" height="1760" /></p>

<p class="p2">The proposal passed with 83.35% of votes being in favor and only 11.31% being against. The excitement from this news has also contributed to the rally in the price of the digital asset.</p>
<h2 class="p2">More Gains For LUNC?</h2>
<p class="p2">Terra Classic (LUNC) is currently sitting at the top of the list of top gainers on Coinmarketcap over the past 24 hours. With an approximately 17% jump in the last day, the digital asset defies a market that has seen slow movement, especially with <a href="https://newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-volatility-hits-all-time-low/">bitcoin volatility dropping to all-time lows</a>.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-513839 aligncenter" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Screen-Shot-2022-12-27-at-11.58.13-460x249.png" alt="LUNA Classic (LUNC) tops list of gainers" width="460" height="249" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Screen-Shot-2022-12-27-at-11.58.13-460x249.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Screen-Shot-2022-12-27-at-11.58.13-860x465.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Screen-Shot-2022-12-27-at-11.58.13-768x415.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Screen-Shot-2022-12-27-at-11.58.13-750x405.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Screen-Shot-2022-12-27-at-11.58.13-1140x616.png 1140w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Screen-Shot-2022-12-27-at-11.58.13.png 1406w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px" /></p>

<p class="p2">LUNC, on the other hand, tends to thrive in times like these. This is because, with the low momentum, larger assets such as bitcoin and ethereum are unlikely to move much, but with low-price cryptocurrencies such as LUNC, it presents an opportunity for investors since it is easier to move the needle. Couple this with the recent rise in positive sentiment in the community and it is a recipe for success.</p>

<p class="p2">Its price has now reached its second-highest level for the month of December after successfully touching above $0.00018 in the early hours of Tuesday. If the momentum holds, then the cryptocurrency will see $0.0002 before the end of the day.</p>
<p class="p2">LUNC was changing hands at $0.0001801 at the time of this writing, according to data from Coinmarketcap. Trading volume is up 157% in the last 24 hours and is sitting at $239.8 million.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/LUNA-Classic-LUNC-460x258.jpeg" width="460" height="258" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Miner Selling Power Plunges, Green Signal For Price?</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-miner-selling-plunges-green-price/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hououin Kyouma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 14:30:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Bullish]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Miner Selling Power]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Miner Selling Pressure]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin miners]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=513817</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[On-chain data shows the Bitcoin miner selling power has plunged recently, a sign that could be positive for the crypto&#8217;s price. Bitcoin Miner Selling Power Has Plummeted In Recent Days As pointed out by an analyst in a CryptoQuant post, there has been less selling pressure from the miners recently. There are two relevant indicators here, the miner supply and the miner outflow. The first of these, the miner supply, is simply a measure of the total amount of Bitcoin currently sitting in the wallets of miners. The other one, the miner outflow, is a metric that keeps track of the total number of coins that miners are transferring out of their supply at the moment. Now, the &#8220;miner selling power&#8221; is defined as this miner outflow divided by the miner supply (30-day moving average, log-scaled). When the value of this indicator is high, it means miners are transferring out large amounts compared to their total supply right now. Since miners usually take out their BTC for dumping purposes, this trend can be bearish for the value of the crypto. On the other hand, low values suggest miners are spending relatively little amounts currently. Related Reading: Bitcoin Bullish Signal? Small Investors Show Rapid Accumulation The below chart shows the trend in the Bitcoin miner selling power over the last few years: The value of the metric seems to have taken a plunge in recent days &#124; Source: CryptoQuant As the above graph displays, whenever the Bitcoin miner selling power has reached high values and set a local peak, the price of the crypto has seen some downtrend. This trend makes sense as highs in the metric suggest increased selling pressure from these chain validators. Recently, the indicator again showed such a formation, and BTC reacted with a decline this time as well, as its price went from more than $18,000 to the current $16,000 level. However, since this recent peak, the miner selling power has been rapidly going down and has now set a new low. Related Reading: Bitcoin Selling Pressure Becoming Exhausted? This Metric May Hint So This muted selling pressure from miners may not necessarily be bullish by itself, but it does mean that if Bitcoin shows any bullish momentum now, miners wouldn&#8217;t provide any impedance to it for the time being. An interesting long-term trend to notice in the miner selling power chart is that the metric has been on an overall downtrend in the last five years or so. This means that over time, miners have been selling lesser and lesser BTC compared to their reserves, suggesting that they have been accumulating and growing their supply instead. BTC Price At the time of writing, Bitcoin&#8217;s price floats around $16,800, up 1% in the last week. BTC continues to display boring price action &#124; Source: BTCUSD on TradingView Featured image from Jievani Weerasinghe on Unsplash.com, charts from TradingView.com, CryptoQuant.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On-chain data shows the Bitcoin miner selling power has plunged recently, a sign that could be positive for the crypto&#8217;s price.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Miner Selling Power Has Plummeted In Recent Days</h2>
<p>As pointed out by an analyst in a CryptoQuant <a href="https://cryptoquant.com/quicktake/63aab61ec8ccf515a9a62aa0-Bitcoin-miners-update" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">post</a>, there has been less selling pressure from the miners recently. There are two relevant indicators here, the miner supply and the miner outflow. The first of these, the <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-miners-hold-selling-reserves-2021-high/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">miner supply</a>, is simply a measure of the total amount of Bitcoin currently sitting in the wallets of miners.</p>
<p>The other one, the <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-on-chain-huge-outflow-miners/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">miner outflow</a>, is a metric that keeps track of the total number of coins that miners are transferring out of their supply at the moment. Now, the &#8220;miner selling power&#8221; is defined as this miner outflow divided by the miner supply (30-day moving average, log-scaled).</p>
<p>When the value of this indicator is high, it means miners are transferring out large amounts compared to their total supply right now. Since miners usually take out their BTC for dumping purposes, this trend can be bearish for the value of the crypto. On the other hand, low values suggest miners are spending relatively little amounts currently.</p>

<p>The below chart shows the trend in the Bitcoin miner selling power over the last few years:</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone aligncenter" src="https://img.cryptoquant.com/35320/quicktake/9QOoBbf_1965879f68feb44bb7775bf4cfb623a3c0797db0739fdfa781e0b77f8e68603b.png" alt="Bitcoin Miner Selling Power" width="1280" height="806" /></p>

<p>As the above graph displays, whenever the Bitcoin miner selling power has reached high values and set a local peak, the price of the crypto has seen some downtrend. This trend makes sense as highs in the metric suggest increased selling pressure from these chain validators.</p>
<p>Recently, the indicator again showed such a formation, and BTC reacted with a decline this time as well, as its price went from more than $18,000 to the current $16,000 level. However, since this recent peak, the miner selling power has been rapidly going down and has now set a new low.</p>

<p>This muted selling pressure from miners may not necessarily be bullish by itself, but it does mean that if Bitcoin shows any bullish momentum now, miners wouldn&#8217;t provide any impedance to it for the time being.</p>
<p>An interesting long-term trend to notice in the miner selling power chart is that the metric has been on an overall downtrend in the last five years or so. This means that over time, miners have been selling lesser and lesser BTC compared to their reserves, suggesting that they have been accumulating and growing their supply instead.</p>
<h2>BTC Price</h2>
<p>At the time of writing, <a href="https://newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-keeps-fighting-17k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin&#8217;s price</a> floats around $16,800, up 1% in the last week.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone wp-image-513827 size-large aligncenter" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/chart-31-860x452.png" alt="Bitcoin Price Chart" width="860" height="452" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/chart-31-860x452.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/chart-31-460x242.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/chart-31-768x404.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/chart-31-750x394.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/chart-31.png 978w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" /></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/jievani-weerasinghe-NHRM1u4GD_A-unsplash-1-460x282.jpg" width="460" height="282" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Chiliz (CHZ) Finds Cover At This Level For Some Temporary Relief</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/chiliz-chz-finds-cover-at-this-level/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 14:25:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[chiliZ]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Chiliz price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CHZ]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CHZ Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FIFA World Cup]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=513872</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Chiliz (CHZ) looks bearish as it shaved off as much as 64% in 50 days. This entertainment- and sport-based blockchain platform is built on Socios and allows fans to interact with sporting brands and teams. Here&#8217;s a quick glance at how the crypto is performing so far: Chiliz plunges by 0.70% Sellers are seen to dominate the bearish market CHZ has trimmed down as much as 64% in just 50 days With that said, users can fully take advantage of the platform to stake and dish out exclusive information and news tidbits from their favorite sporting teams, plus also freely share their opinions on the latest news. The 2022 FIFA World Cup gave Chiliz a boost as it pumped up the orders. However, Chiliz can’t seem to keep up with the rest of the cryptocurrencies and has been lagging behind or going downward spiral. CHZ Currently Trades At $0.1085 According to CoinMarketCap, CHZ is down by 0.70% or trading at $0.1085 as of this writing. With this scenario, the sellers clearly have the upper hand while the buyers need to hang on and wait for the market to switch to bullish and stabilize in terms of demand before placing any bids. Chiliz is a crypto exchange with the CHZ token explicitly designed for buying fan tokens that give users the ability to decide and govern regarding certain policies, stadium names, team lineups, franchises, and selection of players. In addition, the CHZ token also functions similarly to BEP2 on Binance and ERC20 token on Ethereum. Related Reading: Why USDT Is Plunging While Other Stablecoins Are Not CHZ total market cap at nearly $666 million on the daily chart &#124; Chart: TradingView.com Hitting The Oversold Zone Chiliz was seen wading along the lines of $0.1637 to $0.29 since August. Now, when the lows in this range were breached and then retested as resistance in December, this has shown how sellers have the evident upper hand in the market. RSI for CHZ is seen to have dipped below the neutral range of 50 on November 20. It is currently sitting at 9.2, which means it has reached the oversold zone. Considerably, the CMF also moved down in the same period with sizeable capital flushed out of the market. Chart: CHZ/USDT on TradingView Over the past few days, the Fibonacci extension level, which acted as support, was spotted at 24.3% across the $0.107. Sellers can shoot towards going short, given the 21-period MA, which worked as resistance this month. Sellers can then target $0.088 and $0.073 rendered as take-profit levels. Related Reading: Is SOL About To Crumble? Major NFT Projects Plan To Switch To Other Blockchains Chiliz Price Prediction Meanwhile, Anton Kharitonov, a Traders Union crypto analyst, has a different forecast for the price of Chiliz. According to Kharitonov, Chiliz will fluctuate between $0.00558 (the low end of the projection) and $0.0167 (the high end of the forecast) between now and the end of 2023. Kharitonov&#8217;s analysis suggests that the price of CHZ will rise to $0.20 by then.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.analyticsinsight.net/big-eyes-coin-chiliz-and-bitcoin-are-decentralizing-the-financial-ecosystem/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">Chiliz (CHZ)</a> looks bearish as it shaved off as much as 64% in 50 days. This entertainment- and sport-based blockchain platform is built on Socios and allows fans to interact with sporting brands and teams.</p>
<p>Here&#8217;s a quick glance at how the crypto is performing so far:</p>
<ul>
<li>Chiliz plunges by 0.70%</li>
<li>Sellers are seen to dominate the bearish market</li>
<li>CHZ has trimmed down as much as 64% in just 50 days</li>
</ul>
<p>With that said, users can fully take advantage of the platform to stake and dish out exclusive information and news tidbits from their favorite sporting teams, plus also freely share their opinions on the latest news.</p>
<p>The 2022 FIFA World Cup gave Chiliz a boost as it pumped up the orders. However, Chiliz can’t seem to keep up with the rest of the cryptocurrencies and has been lagging behind or going downward spiral.</p>
<h2><b>CHZ Currently Trades At $0.1085</b></h2>
<p>According to<a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/chiliz/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"> CoinMarketCap</a>, CHZ is down by 0.70% or trading at $0.1085 as of this writing. With this scenario, the sellers clearly have the upper hand while the buyers need to hang on and wait for the market to switch to bullish and stabilize in terms of demand before placing any bids.</p>
<p>Chiliz is a crypto exchange with the CHZ token explicitly designed for buying <a href="https://capital.com/chiliz-chz-price-prediction" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">fan tokens</a> that give users the ability to decide and govern regarding certain policies, stadium names, team lineups, franchises, and selection of players.</p>
<p>In addition, the CHZ token also functions similarly to BEP2 on Binance and ERC20 token on Ethereum.</p>

<p><img loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/ynvnmLbN/" width="2047" height="979" /></p>

<h2><b>Hitting The Oversold Zone</b></h2>
<p>Chiliz was seen <a href="https://ambcrypto.com/chiliz-finds-support-at-0-105-but-another-move-downward-remains-likely/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">wading</a> along the lines of $0.1637 to $0.29 since August. Now, when the lows in this range were breached and then retested as resistance in December, this has shown how sellers have the evident upper hand in the market.</p>
<p>RSI for CHZ is seen to have dipped below the neutral range of 50 on November 20. It is currently sitting at 9.2, which means it has reached the oversold zone. </p>
<p>Considerably, the CMF also moved down in the same period with sizeable capital flushed out of the market.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-513876 size-full" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/a-17.png" alt="" width="665" height="368" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/a-17.png 665w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/a-17-460x255.png 460w" sizes="(max-width: 665px) 100vw, 665px" /></p>

<p>Over the past few days, the Fibonacci extension level, which acted as support, was spotted at 24.3% across the $0.107. </p>
<p>Sellers can shoot towards going short, given the 21-period MA, which worked as resistance this month. Sellers can then target $0.088 and $0.073 rendered as take-profit levels.</p>

<strong>Chiliz Price Prediction</strong>
<p>Meanwhile, Anton Kharitonov, a Traders Union crypto analyst, has a different forecast for the price of Chiliz.</p>
<p>According to Kharitonov, Chiliz will fluctuate between<a href="https://tradersunion.com/currencies/forecast/chiliz/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow"> $0.00558</a> (the low end of the projection) and $0.0167 (the high end of the forecast) between now and the end of 2023.</p>
<p>Kharitonov&#8217;s analysis suggests that the price of CHZ will rise to $0.20 by then.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Chiliz-2-460x307.png" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Is SOL About To Crumble? Major NFT Projects Plan To Switch To Other Blockchains</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/is-sol-about-to-crumble/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 13:51:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum killer]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NFT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sol]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Solana]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=513865</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[In the preceding 24 hours, the sentiment of the cryptocurrency market as a whole was mixed, as the majority of top cryptocurrencies experienced mixed price changes. Solana is in a difficult position, since two of the ecosystem&#8217;s most prominent NFT projects are abandoning its network for rivals.  The outlook on the crypto remains bearish in 2022. On Monday, DeGods announced that the NFT collection will bridge to Ethereum in the first quarter of next year. The y00ts NFT collection, which is part of the same cohort, will move to Polygon. The official explanation for the transition to these blockchains has not been announced. Related Reading: VeChain Jumps By 4% As VET Investors Look To Profit Before Christmas Image: The Crypto Times What&#8217;s Going On With SOL? Due to bearish signal readings and unfavorable news, the crypto&#8217;s price could resume its freefall toward $10. Strong bearish momentum allowed the bears to push its price below the $12.00 threshold. As of writing, SOL was trading at $11.16, down 6.5% in the last seven days, data from Coingecko shows. The crypto&#8217;s price has retreated by 23.15% since December 15. Nonetheless, the bulls established support at the level, which stabilized the price activity. Regardless, bearish pressure persists as it continues to decline, although at a much slower rate. Concerns over the crypto&#8217;s exposure to the cryptocurrency exchange FTX increased as cryptocurrencies took a severe battering this year and its stock performance plummeted. Image: Business2Community Glory Days No More SOL&#8217;s price dropped by roughly 90% in 2022 after being a sparkling gem in 2021. It has fallen from a peak of $260 to its current price of $11.16. Solana established itself as a frontrunner in the rapidly growing field of decentralized finance (DeFi), a key application area for blockchain technology. In its zenith, DeFi&#8217;s total value locked (TVL) soared beyond $12 billion. Although Solana is regarded as the second-largest NFT ecosystem in the world, developers and projects are departing the network. According to data provided by DappRadar, the ecosystem&#8217;s NFT marketplace ranks fourth in terms of trade volume. The departure of DeGods and y00ts from the ecosystem is anticipated to drop the coin completely out of the top 10 in terms of sales volume. Related Reading: Why USDT Is Plunging While Other Stablecoins Are Not SOL total market cap at nearly $4.06 billion on the daily chart &#124; Chart: TradingView.com What Now &#8216;Ethereum Killer?&#8217; There are speculations that both projects requested funding from the Solana foundation in order to continue on the blockchain, although this has not been proven. Solana is a blockchain platform that competes with Ethereum. The proof-of-stake (PoS) system upon which it was founded is both quicker and less taxing on the environment than Ethereum&#8217;s. And while Ethereum can only process 20 transactions per second, Solana can process thousands. In the meantime, the price of SOL risks falling to the weekly and monthly lows of $11.00 and $10.90 respectively. If the &#8220;Ethereum Killer&#8221; breaks out of its downtrend and closes above the trendline, the bearish narrative could be invalidated.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In the preceding 24 hours, the sentiment of the cryptocurrency market as a whole was mixed, as the majority of top cryptocurrencies experienced mixed price changes.</p>
<p>Solana is in a difficult position, since two of the ecosystem&#8217;s most prominent NFT projects are abandoning its network for rivals.  The outlook on the crypto remains bearish in 2022.</p>
<p>On Monday, DeGods announced that the NFT collection will bridge to Ethereum in the first quarter of next year. The y00ts NFT collection, which is part of the same cohort, will move to Polygon.</p>
<p>The official explanation for the transition to these blockchains has not been announced.</p>


<h2>What&#8217;s Going On With SOL?</h2>
<p>Due to bearish signal readings and unfavorable news, the <a href="https://ambcrypto.com/is-solana-at-the-brink-of-a-downfall-this-final-nail-in-sols-coffin-could-spell-harm/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">crypto&#8217;s price</a> could resume its freefall toward $10.</p>
<p>Strong bearish momentum allowed the bears to push its price below the $12.00 threshold.</p>
<p>As of writing, SOL was <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">trading at $11.16</a>, down 6.5% in the last seven days, data from Coingecko shows. The crypto&#8217;s price has retreated by 23.15% since December 15.</p>
<p>Nonetheless, the bulls established support at the level, which stabilized the price activity. Regardless, <a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/solana-price-analysis-2022-12-24/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">bearish pressure</a> persists as it continues to decline, although at a much slower rate.</p>
<p>Concerns over the crypto&#8217;s exposure to the cryptocurrency exchange FTX increased as cryptocurrencies took a severe battering this year and its stock performance plummeted.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="size-medium wp-image-510578 aligncenter" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Solana-2-460x288.png" alt="Solana" width="460" height="288" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Solana-2-460x288.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Solana-2-768x480.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Solana-2-750x469.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Solana-2.png 785w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px" /></p>

<h2>Glory Days No More</h2>
<p><a href="https://www.fxstreet.com/cryptocurrencies/news/solana-nft-projects-abandon-the-network-for-ethereum-degods-and-y00ts-announce-their-departure-202212261113" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">SOL&#8217;s price</a> dropped by roughly 90% in 2022 after being a sparkling gem in 2021. It has fallen from a peak of $260 to its current price of $11.16.</p>
<p>Solana established itself as a frontrunner in the rapidly growing field of decentralized finance (DeFi), a key application area for blockchain technology. In its zenith, DeFi&#8217;s total value locked (TVL) soared beyond $12 billion.</p>
<p>Although Solana is regarded as the second-largest NFT ecosystem in the world, developers and projects are departing the network.</p>
<p>According to data provided by DappRadar, the ecosystem&#8217;s NFT marketplace ranks fourth in terms of trade volume.</p>
<p>The departure of DeGods and y00ts from the ecosystem is anticipated to drop the coin completely out of the top 10 in terms of sales volume.</p>

<p><img loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/n7TjbnQV/" width="2047" height="979" /></p>

What Now &#8216;Ethereum Killer?&#8217;
<p>There are speculations that both projects requested funding from the Solana foundation in order to continue on the blockchain, although this has not been proven.</p>
<p>Solana is a blockchain platform that competes with Ethereum.</p>
<p>The <a href="https://www.banklesstimes.com/news/2022/12/26/solana-price-prediction-for-2023-will-sol-get-its-groove-back/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">proof-of-stake</a> (PoS) system upon which it was founded is both quicker and less taxing on the environment than Ethereum&#8217;s.</p>
<p>And while Ethereum can only process 20 transactions per second, Solana can process thousands.</p>
<p>In the meantime, the price of SOL risks falling to the weekly and monthly lows of $11.00 and $10.90 respectively. If the &#8220;Ethereum Killer&#8221; breaks out of its downtrend and closes above the trendline, the bearish narrative could be invalidated.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/sol-460x307.png" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Shiba Inu Lead Dev Ignites Buzz About New Partnership, SHIB Price Stagnates</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/shiba-inu-lead-ignites-buzz-partnership/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jake Simmons]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 13:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Shiba Inu]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIB]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shibarium]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=513824</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[While the Shiba Inu (SHIB) price has been stagnant since mid-November, the latest cryptic news from the meme cryptocurrency&#8217;s lead developer could provide fresh fuel for a rally. As the SHIB community observed, Shytoshi Kusama has once again updated his profile. The Shiba Inu lead developer&#8217;s status now reads &#8220;We Are Not Alone.&#8221; In addition, Kusama&#8217;s current Twitter location says, &#8220;With a new fren&#8230;guess who?&#8221; The SHIB community is now puzzling over whether the mysterious announcement could have to do with a new partnership or the launch of Shibarium, a layer 2 solution. Hey $SHIB Family @ShytoshiKusama has once again updated his profile. &#34;We Are Not Alone&#34; and &#34;With a new fren&#8230;Guess Who&#34; Could it have anything to with a new partnershib or maybe even #SHIBARIUM? I am stumped. Help me out here family. pic.twitter.com/fX6AAhTpUB &#8212; Shib Dream * Shiba Inu News * Shib Army Social 💎 (@theshibdream) December 27, 2022 As recently as Christmas Eve, Kusama tweeted that Shibarium will be released very soon, emphasizing the importance of next year for the project: Happy Holidays to more than half the world. Wen Shibarium? Please know it will come very soon*, but not during a crucial time for people to spend with their family (or the resulting New Years party time). Enjoy these next days, next year is an important one for humanity. Therefore, probably the hottest bet for the mysterious announcement could be Shibarium. The Shiba Inu community is currently eagerly anticipating its launch. Shibarium is a layer-2 blockchain solution for Shiba Inu that targets Ethereum&#8217;s high transaction cost and low transaction speed problem. Related Reading: Shiba Inu Welcomes 10,000 New Holders, Can SHIB Keep Up The Momentum? The goal of the layer-2 blockchain is to lay the groundwork for building the Shiba Inu ecosystem, which will consist of a metaverse, a DEX, and blockchain games. Shibarium has been in development for quite some time. Another developer, Trophias, put the brakes on the release recently. He said that Shibarium needs more time because the launch has to be done carefully. On the other hand, the SHIB community speculates that the announcement could be a new partnership with another blockchain company. However, there are no conclusive indications as to who the company could be. Shiba Inu (SHIB) Price Caught In Downtrend A new boost for the Shiba Inu price would be a welcoming gift for investors in the meme coin. Since the beginning of the bear market, SHIB has lost about 90% of its value. The all-time high was $0.00008819 and was reached on October 28, 2021. The deep fall of Shiba Inu also happened despite the fact that the token enjoys very high popularity. As Binance made public on December 19, SHIB is one of the top 3 most watched crypto assets on the exchange in 2022, alongside Bitcoin and Ethereum. Related Reading: Institutional Crypto Predictions For 2023: Ethereum, BTC, L2s, NFTs However, even the recent announcement of the Shiba Inu lead developer has not been able to move the price. Within the last 24 hours, SHIB is posting a marginal gain of 0.04%, and over the last seven days, a loss of 1.1%. The trading volume is down to $59 million in the last 24 hours, an 8% drop from the previous day. A look at the 4-hour chart of SHIB reveals that the token has been stagnating in a sideways trend since mid-November, trending slightly lower. Just last week, SHIB marked a 6-month low at $0.00000794. The 1-week chart also paints a dark picture and reveals the massive crash in the Shiba Inu price. To build momentum, the $0.00001029 resistance would be key. Featured image from VOI, Charts from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>While the Shiba Inu (SHIB) price has been stagnant since mid-November, the latest cryptic news from the meme cryptocurrency&#8217;s lead developer could provide fresh fuel for a rally. As the SHIB community observed, Shytoshi Kusama has once again updated his profile.</p>
<p>The Shiba Inu lead developer&#8217;s status now <a href="https://twitter.com/ShytoshiKusama/with_replies" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">reads</a> &#8220;We Are Not Alone.&#8221; In addition, Kusama&#8217;s current Twitter location says, &#8220;With a new fren&#8230;guess who?&#8221; The SHIB community is now puzzling over whether the mysterious announcement could have to do with a new partnership or the launch of Shibarium, a layer 2 solution.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Hey <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24SHIB&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">$SHIB</a> Family <a href="https://twitter.com/ShytoshiKusama?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">@ShytoshiKusama</a> has once again updated his profile. &quot;We Are Not Alone&quot; and &quot;With a new fren&#8230;Guess Who&quot; Could it have anything to with a new partnershib or maybe even <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/SHIBARIUM?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">#SHIBARIUM</a>? I am stumped. Help me out here family. <a href="https://t.co/fX6AAhTpUB" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/fX6AAhTpUB</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Shib Dream * Shiba Inu News * Shib Army Social <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f48e.png" alt="💎" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> (@theshibdream) <a href="https://twitter.com/theshibdream/status/1607545022433345536?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">December 27, 2022</a></p></blockquote>
<p></p>
<p>As recently as Christmas Eve, Kusama tweeted that Shibarium will be released very soon, emphasizing the importance of next year for the project:</p>
<blockquote><p><strong>Happy Holidays to more than half the world. Wen Shibarium? Please know it will come very soon*, but not during a crucial time for people to spend with their family (or the resulting New Years party time). Enjoy these next days, next year is an important one for humanity.</strong></p></blockquote>
<p>Therefore, probably the hottest bet for the mysterious announcement could be Shibarium. The Shiba Inu community is currently eagerly anticipating its launch. Shibarium is a layer-2 blockchain solution for Shiba Inu that targets Ethereum&#8217;s high transaction cost and low transaction speed problem.</p>

<p>The goal of the layer-2 blockchain is to lay the groundwork for building the Shiba Inu ecosystem, which will consist of a <a href="https://newsbtc.com/axs/metaverse-token-axie-infinity-axs-suddenly-pumps-25/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">metaverse</a>, a DEX, and blockchain games. Shibarium has been in development for quite some time.</p>
<p>Another developer, Trophias, put the brakes on the release recently. He said that Shibarium needs more time because the launch has to be done carefully.</p>
<p>On the other hand, the SHIB community speculates that the announcement could be a new partnership with another blockchain company. However, there are no conclusive indications as to who the company could be.</p>
<h2>Shiba Inu (SHIB) Price Caught In Downtrend</h2>
<p>A new boost for the Shiba Inu price would be a welcoming gift for investors in the meme coin. Since the beginning of the bear market, SHIB has lost about 90% of its value. The all-time high was $0.00008819 and was reached on October 28, 2021.</p>
<p>The deep fall of Shiba Inu also happened despite the fact that the token enjoys very high <a href="https://newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/shiba-inu-welcomes-new-holders/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">popularity</a>. As Binance made <a href="https://twitter.com/Shibtoken/status/1604627098299256833" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">public</a> on December 19, SHIB is one of the top 3 most watched crypto assets on the exchange in 2022, <a href="https://newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-keeps-fighting-17k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">alongside Bitcoin</a> and Ethereum.</p>

<p>However, even the recent announcement of the Shiba Inu lead developer has not been able to move the price. Within the last 24 hours, SHIB is posting a marginal gain of 0.04%, and over the last seven days, a loss of 1.1%. The trading volume is down to $59 million in the last 24 hours, an 8% drop from the previous day.</p>
<p>A look at the 4-hour chart of SHIB reveals that the token has been stagnating in a sideways trend since mid-November, trending slightly lower. Just last week, SHIB marked a 6-month low at $0.00000794.</p>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-513844 size-full" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/SHIBUSD_2022-12-27_12-58-43.png" alt="Shiba Inu SHIB USD 2022-12-27" width="2958" height="1613" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/SHIBUSD_2022-12-27_12-58-43.png 2958w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/SHIBUSD_2022-12-27_12-58-43-460x251.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/SHIBUSD_2022-12-27_12-58-43-860x469.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/SHIBUSD_2022-12-27_12-58-43-768x419.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/SHIBUSD_2022-12-27_12-58-43-1536x838.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/SHIBUSD_2022-12-27_12-58-43-2048x1117.png 2048w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/SHIBUSD_2022-12-27_12-58-43-750x409.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/SHIBUSD_2022-12-27_12-58-43-1140x622.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 2958px) 100vw, 2958px" />
<p>The 1-week chart also paints a dark picture and reveals the massive crash in the Shiba Inu price. To build momentum, the $0.00001029 resistance would be key.</p>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-513845 size-full" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/SHIBUSD_2022-12-27_13-01-27.png" alt="SHIB USD 2022-12-27" width="2956" height="1613" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/SHIBUSD_2022-12-27_13-01-27.png 2956w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/SHIBUSD_2022-12-27_13-01-27-460x251.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/SHIBUSD_2022-12-27_13-01-27-860x469.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/SHIBUSD_2022-12-27_13-01-27-768x419.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/SHIBUSD_2022-12-27_13-01-27-1536x838.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/SHIBUSD_2022-12-27_13-01-27-2048x1118.png 2048w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/SHIBUSD_2022-12-27_13-01-27-750x409.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/SHIBUSD_2022-12-27_13-01-27-1140x622.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 2956px) 100vw, 2956px" />

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/202108121258-main.cropped_1628777443-460x259.jpg" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
