<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"

	xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
	xmlns:geo="http://www.w3.org/2003/01/geo/wgs84_pos#"
	>

<channel>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.newsbtc.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<description>Bitcoin &#38; Cryptocurrency News Today</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 20:51:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-cropped-favicon.png?fit=32%2C32</url>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
<site xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">221170450</site>	<item>
		<title>RUNE Beyond Swaps: THORChain Introduces New Lending Protocol</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/rune/rune-beyond-swaps-thorchain-introduces-new-lending-protocol/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 01:00:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Rune]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[RUNE Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[RUNEUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thorchain]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=548295</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[In a recent development, THORChain (RUNE), the liquidity network, has unveiled its lending feature, enabling users to leverage their native Layer-1 (L1) assets, such as Bitcoin (BTC) and Ethereum (ETH), to secure loans denominated in TOR, a USD equivalent stablecoin.  According to the announcement, this move opens up new avenues for financial participation, allowing users to borrow funds without the “burdens” of interest, liquidations, or expiration. THORChain Introduces Interest-Free Loans The lending process is designed to be user-friendly and “straightforward,” focusing on minimizing cognitive burden.  Depending on prevailing market conditions, borrowers can collateralize their assets within a range of collateralization ratios (CR), ranging from 200% to 500%. The CR determines the amount of debt borrowers can receive in proportion to their collateral. Related Reading: Bitcoin Price Follows This 1930’s Chart, Why BTC Could Keep On Falling One of the critical advantages of THORChain&#8217;s lending protocol is the absence of interest charges. By eliminating interest, the protocol encourages borrowers to hold onto their loans for extended periods, thereby increasing the equity value of the protocol.  This approach aims to align the interests of borrowers with the protocol itself, fostering a mutually beneficial ecosystem. Furthermore, THORChain&#8217;s lending system does not involve liquidations. In traditional lending models, borrowers risk having their collateral forcibly sold if its value falls below a certain threshold. However, THORChain&#8217;s design eliminates this risk by treating the collateral as equity (RUNE IOU).  Consequently, if the collateral falls below the debt value, it does not pose a problem, as the stored equity acts as the liability. Per the report, this approach ensures a more user-friendly experience and eliminates the need for borrowers to monitor asset prices constantly. The loans issued through THORChain&#8217;s lending feature have a minimum period of 30 days, providing borrowers with flexibility.  Repayment can occur anytime after the initial 30-day period, allowing borrowers to manage their debt according to their circumstances. Partial repayments are also possible, although the collateral is not released until the debt is fully repaid. THORChain&#8217;s Circuit Breaker System To enhance security and protect against inflation, THORChain has implemented a circuit breaker mechanism.  In the event of a drastic drop in RUNE’s price-native token of the THORchain network- against collateral assets such as BTC and ETH, which could lead to net inflation of RUNE, the system will pause new loans and disable the lending feature.  At this point, no further inflation of RUNE can occur, and the protocol&#8217;s reserve will cover the remaining collateral payouts. Initially, the lending feature will support BTC and ETH collateral, with plans to expand to other Layer 1 gas assets, including Binance Coin (BNB), Litecoin (LTC), Avalanche (AVAX), and DOGE.  According to the announcement, this expansion will further diversify borrowing options, accommodating a broader range of users and assets. Related Reading: Gemini Hits Back At SEC Lawsuit With Dismissal Filing Overall, with the introduction of the lending feature, THORChain takes a significant step toward expanding financial opportunities within its liquidity network. As of the latest update, THORChain&#8217;s native token, RUNE, has experienced a decline of nearly 8% within the past 24 hours, currently trading at $1.694, despite the anticipation surrounding the announcement of the new lending protocol. Nevertheless, the token has successfully maintained substantial gains of 20% and 80% over the past seven and fourteen days, respectively, attributed to a simultaneous increase in the social volume of the THORChain cryptocurrency. Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In a recent development, THORChain (RUNE), the liquidity network, has <a href="https://medium.com/thorchain/lending-on-thorchain-646bbf2e6e1b" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">unveiled </a>its lending feature, enabling users to leverage their native Layer-1 (L1) assets, such as Bitcoin (BTC) and Ethereum (ETH), to secure loans denominated in TOR, a USD equivalent stablecoin. </p>
<p>According to the announcement, this move opens up new avenues for financial participation, allowing users to borrow funds without the “burdens” of interest, liquidations, or expiration.</p>
<h2>THORChain Introduces Interest-Free Loans</h2>
<p>The lending process is designed to be user-friendly and “straightforward,” focusing on minimizing cognitive burden. </p>
<p>Depending on prevailing market conditions, borrowers can collateralize their assets within a range of collateralization ratios (CR), ranging from 200% to 500%. The CR determines the amount of debt borrowers can receive in proportion to their collateral.</p>

<p>One of the critical advantages of THORChain&#8217;s lending protocol is the absence of interest charges. By eliminating interest, the protocol encourages borrowers to hold onto their loans for extended periods, thereby increasing the equity value of the protocol. </p>
<p>This approach aims to align the interests of borrowers with the protocol itself, fostering a mutually beneficial ecosystem.</p>
<p>Furthermore, THORChain&#8217;s lending system does not involve liquidations. In traditional lending models, borrowers risk having their collateral forcibly sold if its value falls below a certain threshold. However, THORChain&#8217;s design eliminates this risk by treating the collateral as equity (RUNE IOU). </p>
<p>Consequently, if the collateral falls below the debt value, it does not pose a problem, as the stored equity acts as the liability. Per the report, this approach ensures a more user-friendly experience and eliminates the need for borrowers to monitor asset prices constantly.</p>
<p>The loans issued through THORChain&#8217;s lending feature have a minimum period of 30 days, providing borrowers with flexibility. </p>
<p>Repayment can occur anytime after the initial 30-day period, allowing borrowers to manage their debt according to their circumstances. Partial repayments are also possible, although the collateral is not released until the debt is fully repaid.</p>
<h2>THORChain&#8217;s Circuit Breaker System</h2>
<p>To enhance security and protect against inflation, THORChain has implemented a circuit breaker mechanism. </p>
<p>In the event of a drastic drop in RUNE’s price-native token of the THORchain network- against collateral assets such as BTC and ETH, which could lead to net inflation of RUNE, the system will pause new loans and disable the lending feature. </p>
<p>At this point, no further inflation of RUNE can occur, and the protocol&#8217;s reserve will cover the remaining collateral payouts.</p>
<p>Initially, the lending feature will support BTC and ETH collateral, with plans to expand to other Layer 1 gas assets, including Binance Coin (BNB), Litecoin (LTC), Avalanche (AVAX), and DOGE. </p>
<p>According to the announcement, this expansion will further diversify borrowing options, accommodating a broader range of users and assets.</p>

<p>Overall, with the introduction of the lending feature, THORChain takes a significant step toward expanding financial opportunities within its liquidity network.</p>
<img decoding="async" fetchpriority="high" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/iMSaofRC/" alt="THORchain " width="1815" height="858" loading="lazy"/>
<p>As of the latest update, THORChain&#8217;s native token, RUNE, has experienced a decline of nearly 8% within the past 24 hours, currently trading at $1.694, despite the anticipation surrounding the announcement of the new lending protocol.</p>
<p>Nevertheless, the token has successfully maintained substantial gains of 20% and 80% over the past seven and fourteen days, respectively, attributed to a simultaneous increase in the social volume of the THORChain cryptocurrency.</p>
<p>Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Downloader.la-64e3b7bb38573.jpg?fit=460%2C322" width="460" height="322" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">548295</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>AVAX Price Bucks Under The Pressure Of Upcoming $102 Million Token Unlock</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/avax/avax-price-bucks-under-the-pressure-of-upcoming-102-million-token-unlock/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Best Owie]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 00:00:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AVAX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Avalanche]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AVAX news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AVAX Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AVAX token]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AVAXUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AVAXUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Token unlock]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=548219</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[While most altcoins are looking toward a recovery from the recent market crash, the AVAX price seems to be gearing up for the opposite. The reason behind this is the massive token unlock that is set to occur this week, which will undoubtedly place more sell pressure on the already struggling price of the digital asset. $102 Million In AVAX Set To Be Unlocked The Avalanche network, like a lot of others, has locked a portion of its total token supply to be released into circulation on a periodic basis. Given that these unlock events can put bearish pressure on a token, they can often be a signal to exit. Related Reading: Bitcoin Liquidations Top $500 Million Amid $1 Billion Crypto Decimation For AVAX, the next token unlock event is set to take place on August 26, five days from now. But the most interesting thing about this event is the number of tokens set to be brought into circulation. According to the token tracking website Token Unlocks, a total of 9.54 million tokens are set to be unlocked on Saturday. This accounts for 2.77% of the total circulating supply of the asset, worth $102.29 million at current prices. 2.77% of token supply set to be unlocked &#124; Source: Token Unlocks The website also shows that the unlocked tokens are being distributed in four allocations. These include 1.13 million tokens ($12.06 million) for airdrop, 1.67 million tokens (17.87 million) for Foundation, 2.25 million tokens ($24.12 million) for strategic partners, and 4.5 million tokens ($48.24 million) for the team. With this unlock, over 55% of the total token supply will be unlocked, leaving less than 45% of the supply locked. And as these 9.54 million tokens make their way to the market, it could be very bad for investors. Will AVAX Price Be Impacted? Given the allocation of the $102 million in tokens set to be unlocked, it is likely that a large chunk of it is going to hit the open market. As a result of such a large amount of selling, the AVAX price will certainly be impacted, making an already bad situation worse. This will likely see the price of the digital asset fall below $10 for the first time since July 2021. Trading in the single-digit will see AVAX holders plunged further into losses, even though the vast majority are already sitting in the red, according to data from IntoTheBlock. Related Reading: Why Is Dogecoin Price Down Today? AVAX’s indicators are also incredibly bearish at this point with the price sitting below the 100-day and 200-day simple moving averages. This rules out a recovery for the digital asset in the short term, especially with the unlock event coming up. At the time of writing, the AVAX price is sitting tentatively at $10.56, down 13.15% in the last week. Avalanche price crashes to $10.5 &#124; Source: AVAXUSD on Tradingview.com Follow Best Owie on Twitter for market insights, updates, and the occasional funny tweet… Featured image from FXLeaders, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="p2">While most altcoins are looking toward a recovery from the recent market crash, the AVAX price seems to be gearing up for the opposite. The reason behind this is the massive token unlock that is set to occur this week, which will undoubtedly place more sell pressure on the already struggling price of the digital asset.</p>
<h2 class="p2">$102 Million In AVAX Set To Be Unlocked</h2>
<p class="p2">The <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/avalanche/avalanche-foundation-commits-50-million-to-tokenized-asset-purchases/">Avalanche network</a>, like a lot of others, has locked a portion of its total token supply to be released into circulation on a periodic basis. Given that these unlock events can put bearish pressure on a token, they can often be a signal to exit.</p>

<p class="p2">For AVAX, the next token unlock event is set to take place on August 26, five days from now. But the most interesting thing about this event is the number of tokens set to be brought into circulation. According to the token tracking website <a href="https://token.unlocks.app/avalanche-2" rel="nofollow">Token Unlocks</a>, a total of 9.54 million tokens are set to be unlocked on Saturday. This accounts for 2.77% of the total circulating supply of the asset, worth $102.29 million at current prices.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-548225 aligncenter" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot-2023-08-21-at-11.17.21.png?w=460&#038;resize=460%2C215" alt="AVAX token unlock" width="460" height="215" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot-2023-08-21-at-11.17.21.png?w=2960 2960w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot-2023-08-21-at-11.17.21.png?w=460&#038;resize=460%2C215 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot-2023-08-21-at-11.17.21.png?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot-2023-08-21-at-11.17.21.png?w=860 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot-2023-08-21-at-11.17.21.png?w=1536 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot-2023-08-21-at-11.17.21.png?w=2048 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot-2023-08-21-at-11.17.21.png?w=750 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot-2023-08-21-at-11.17.21.png?w=1140 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px" loading="lazy" data-recalc-dims="1"/></p>

<p class="p2">The website also shows that the unlocked tokens are being distributed in four allocations. These include 1.13 million tokens ($12.06 million) for <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/altcoin/sei-takes-a-hit-price-suffers-plunge-amid-airdrop/">airdrop</a>, 1.67 million tokens (17.87 million) for Foundation, 2.25 million tokens ($24.12 million) for strategic partners, and 4.5 million tokens ($48.24 million) for the team.</p>
<p class="p2">With this unlock, over 55% of the total token supply will be unlocked, leaving less than 45% of the supply locked. And as these 9.54 million tokens make their way to the market, it could be very bad for investors.</p>
<h2 class="p2">Will AVAX Price Be Impacted?</h2>
<p class="p2">Given the allocation of the $102 million in tokens set to be unlocked, it is likely that a large chunk of it is going to hit the open market. As a result of such a large amount of selling, the AVAX price will certainly be impacted, <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/all/turbulent-avax-price-trends-and-fading-trading-activity-what-to-expect/">making an already bad situation worse</a>.</p>
<p class="p2">This will likely see the price of the digital asset fall below $10 for the first time since July 2021. Trading in the single-digit will see AVAX holders plunged further into losses, even though the vast majority are already sitting in the red, according to data from <a href="https://app.intotheblock.com/coin/AVAX" rel="nofollow">IntoTheBlock</a>.</p>

<p class="p2">AVAX’s indicators are also incredibly bearish at this point with the price sitting below the 100-day and 200-day <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/exponential-moving-average-ema-how-to-ride-massive-trends/">simple moving averages</a>. This rules out a recovery for the digital asset in the short term, especially with the unlock event coming up.</p>
<p class="p2">At the time of writing, the AVAX price is sitting tentatively at $10.56, down 13.15% in the last week.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/PvNtn3Q4/" alt="AVAX price chart from Tradingview.com" width="2884" height="1746" loading="lazy"/></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/AVAX-price.png?fit=460%2C262" width="460" height="262" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">548219</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Glassnode Co-Founder&#8217;s Prediction: DXY Set To Peak, Fueling Potential Bitcoin Rally To $37,000</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/glassnode-co-founders-prediction-dxy-set-to-peak-fueling-potential-bitcoin-rally-to-37000/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 22:00:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dxy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=548286</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The largest cryptocurrency by market cap, Bitcoin (BTC), dropped after a prolonged period of consolidation around the $29,000 mark. The failure to sustain this level has resulted in a decline to $26,000. Interestingly, Bitcoin&#8217;s recent reversal has coincided with speculations of an imminent bull run, with many believing that the cryptocurrency winter is over and that lower price levels will not be revisited.  Nonetheless, this sentiment shifted on July 14th when the US Dollar Index (DXY) initiated a robust rally, surging from 99 points to its current level of 103. As the DXY began its ascent, Bitcoin&#8217;s trajectory turned downward, leading to a downtrend that caused the cryptocurrency to relinquish a significant portion of its 2023 gains. Conversely, before July, BTC experienced a surge to its yearly high of $31,800, while the DXY declined. Despite this development, Glassnode co-founder Yan Allemann suggests that in the coming months, it will be Bitcoin&#8217;s turn to reclaim the spotlight and assert its dominance once again. BTC’s Last Consolidation Phase? Glassnode co-founder Yan Allemann has shared insights on the current market conditions and predicts an imminent surge in Bitcoin&#8217;s value as the autumn approaches. Allemann&#8217;s analysis suggests that the US Dollar is expected to reach a peak level of 106, which will catalyze a prime environment for Bitcoin.  Historically, the inverse correlation between the Dollar and Bitcoin has been observed, where a stronger Dollar tends to put downward pressure on the cryptocurrency&#8217;s price. Conversely, a peak in the Dollar often coincides with a favorable environment for Bitcoin to thrive. Related Reading: Dogecoin Proof Of Stake Discussion Heats Up As Lead Dev Chimes In This said, Allemann believes that Bitcoin is projected to reach the $37,000 level before embarking on a significant upward movement during the autumn season.  This anticipated surge in value aligns with the patterns observed in previous market cycles, where Bitcoin has experienced notable price rallies during the latter part of the year. It remains to be seen how this narrative unfolds, but one thing is clear: the dynamics between Bitcoin and the US dollar continue to shape the cryptocurrency landscape.  Historical Data Reveals September Struggles For Bitcoin According to data by CoinGlass, August, and September have historically presented challenges for Bitcoin, making them notorious months for the cryptocurrency&#8217;s performance.  With 10 days remaining until the monthly close, August has already proven to be a difficult month for Bitcoin, experiencing a 12% decline over the past 30 days. However, this downtrend may not come to a halt just yet, as historical data indicates that September could pose additional obstacles to Bitcoin&#8217;s price trajectory. Examining the chart above, it becomes evident that September has historically been a challenging period for Bitcoin.  In some instances, the cryptocurrency has witnessed substantial price drops, reaching as high as 19%. This suggests that the coming month could potentially be characterized by further downward pressure on Bitcoin&#8217;s price. However, it is important to note that historical trends also indicate the possibility of more modest declines. In 2013, for example, Bitcoin&#8217;s price only decreased by 1% during September, defying the broader negative sentiment associated with the month.  This demonstrates that while September has a historical reputation for difficulty, it does not guarantee a significant downturn for Bitcoin in every instance. Related Reading: Gemini Hits Back At SEC Lawsuit With Dismissal Filing While Bitcoin has faced headwinds in August and historically in September, it is worth remembering that the cryptocurrency has demonstrated resilience and the ability to recover from downturns in the past.  Market conditions, macroeconomic factors, and regulatory developments can all contribute to the price fluctuations of Bitcoin and other cryptocurrencies. Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The largest cryptocurrency by market cap, Bitcoin (BTC), dropped after a prolonged period of consolidation around the $29,000 mark. The failure to sustain this level has resulted in a decline to $26,000.</p>
<p>Interestingly, Bitcoin&#8217;s recent reversal has coincided with speculations of an imminent bull run, with many believing that the cryptocurrency winter is over and that lower price levels will not be revisited. </p>
<p>Nonetheless, this sentiment shifted on July 14th when the US Dollar Index (DXY) initiated a robust rally, surging from 99 points to its current level of 103.</p>
<p>As the DXY began its ascent, Bitcoin&#8217;s trajectory turned downward, leading to a downtrend that caused the cryptocurrency to relinquish a significant portion of its 2023 gains. Conversely, before July, BTC experienced a surge to its yearly high of $31,800, while the DXY declined.</p>
<p>Despite this development, Glassnode co-founder Yan Allemann suggests that in the coming months, it will be Bitcoin&#8217;s turn to reclaim the spotlight and assert its dominance once again.</p>
<h2>BTC’s Last Consolidation Phase?</h2>
<p>Glassnode co-founder Yan Allemann has shared <a href="https://twitter.com/Negentropic_/status/1693578160460181743?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">insights </a>on the current market conditions and predicts an imminent surge in Bitcoin&#8217;s value as the autumn approaches.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/4vbnwe42/" alt="Bitcoin " width="1815" height="858"/>
<p>Allemann&#8217;s analysis suggests that the US Dollar is expected to reach a peak level of 106, which will catalyze a prime environment for Bitcoin. </p>
<p>Historically, the inverse correlation between the Dollar and Bitcoin has been observed, where a stronger Dollar tends to put downward pressure on the cryptocurrency&#8217;s price. Conversely, a peak in the Dollar often coincides with a favorable environment for Bitcoin to thrive.</p>

<p>This said, Allemann believes that Bitcoin is projected to reach the $37,000 level before embarking on a significant upward movement during the autumn season. </p>
<p>This anticipated surge in value aligns with the patterns observed in previous market cycles, where Bitcoin has experienced notable price rallies during the latter part of the year.</p>
<p>It remains to be seen how this narrative unfolds, but one thing is clear: the dynamics between Bitcoin and the US dollar continue to shape the cryptocurrency landscape. </p>
<h2>Historical Data Reveals September Struggles For Bitcoin</h2>
<p>According to <a href="https://twitter.com/coinglass_com/status/1693523533874516254?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">data </a>by CoinGlass, August, and September have historically presented challenges for Bitcoin, making them notorious months for the cryptocurrency&#8217;s performance. </p>
<p>With 10 days remaining until the monthly close, August has already proven to be a difficult month for Bitcoin, experiencing a 12% decline over the past 30 days. However, this downtrend may not come to a halt just yet, as historical data indicates that September could pose additional obstacles to Bitcoin&#8217;s price trajectory.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large wp-image-548288" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F4CaGO5aQAAJ2ht.jpeg?w=860&#038;resize=860%2C397" alt="Bitcoin " width="860" height="397" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F4CaGO5aQAAJ2ht.jpeg?w=1345 1345w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F4CaGO5aQAAJ2ht.jpeg?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F4CaGO5aQAAJ2ht.jpeg?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F4CaGO5aQAAJ2ht.jpeg?w=860&#038;resize=860%2C397 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F4CaGO5aQAAJ2ht.jpeg?w=750 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F4CaGO5aQAAJ2ht.jpeg?w=1140 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" data-recalc-dims="1"/>
<p>Examining the chart above, it becomes evident that September has historically been a challenging period for Bitcoin. </p>
<p>In some instances, the cryptocurrency has witnessed substantial price drops, reaching as high as 19%. This suggests that the coming month could potentially be characterized by further downward pressure on Bitcoin&#8217;s price.</p>
<p>However, it is important to note that historical trends also indicate the possibility of more modest declines. In 2013, for example, Bitcoin&#8217;s price only decreased by 1% during September, defying the broader negative sentiment associated with the month. </p>
<p>This demonstrates that while September has a historical reputation for difficulty, it does not guarantee a significant downturn for Bitcoin in every instance.</p>

<p>While Bitcoin has faced headwinds in August and historically in September, it is worth remembering that the cryptocurrency has demonstrated resilience and the ability to recover from downturns in the past. </p>
<p>Market conditions, macroeconomic factors, and regulatory developments can all contribute to the price fluctuations of Bitcoin and other cryptocurrencies.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/Jf3Lbi0r/" alt="Bitcoin " width="1814" height="858"/>
<p>Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Downloader.la-64e3a5be091b7.jpg?fit=460%2C305" width="460" height="305" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">548286</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Reaches Most “Oversold” Record Since 2020: What This Means</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-reaches-most-oversold-record-since-2020-what-this-means/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tony "The Bull"]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 20:51:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xbt]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xbtusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=548299</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin price just experienced one of its fastest and sharpest corrections in over a year, dropping 10% in a matter of minutes. The mass liquidations and panic from the selloff caused BTCUSD daily charts to reach the most oversold level since the COVID crash in early 2020. BTC Panic-Selling Reaches Extremes Not Seen Since COVID Crash As much as people try to fight it, investing and trading is an emotion-driven process. Few emotions cause humans to take action more urgently than those associated with fear and panic. This is precisely why selloffs tend to be sharper and scarier than bull markets. “Bulls take the stairs, bears ride the elevator” is just one adage that symbolizes this noted market behavior. Related Reading: This Bitcoin Continuation Pattern Points To 3-6 Months Of Uptrend Ahead For example, the COVID collapse in March 2020 took only a matter of days to erase 70% of Bitcoin’s price. This instance was the last time the Relative Strength Index technical indicator on the daily timeframe became this oversold. After Bitcoin’s recently drop this week, the daily RSI is back at a similar extreme for the first time in more than three years. What isn’t clear quite yet, is if the extreme represents another ideal buying opportunity, or if this is the onset of a deeper decline. The RSI has reached the deepest reading in years &#124; BTCUSD on TradingView.com Bitcoin Daily RSI Plunges To Most Oversold Level Since 2020 The Relative Strength Index is a momentum indicator that tells investors and traders when an asset is overbought and oversold on a relative basis. When the tool reaches extremes above 70 or below 30, it can present an opportunity to buy or sell. The RSI is now lower than the LUNA or FTX collapse, or at any point since March 2020. During especially strong moves, however, the RSI can remain elevated for extended phases despite reaching such overheated readings. Such was the case in December 2018, the previous instance of the daily Bitcoin RSI reaching such a low. Related Reading: This Long-Term Bitcoin Price Average Is Setting ATHs In that case, the RSI stayed hot for two full weeks, cutting down BTCUSD price by another 40% before it was all said and done. A 40% correction in Bitcoin would take prices back to the November 2022 bottom. If Bitcoin instead rebounds and reacts more akin to 2020, new all-time highs could be just months away. If not, a deeper reset is possible. #Bitcoin daily RSI is now the most oversold in all of 2023 Act accordingly pic.twitter.com/GpKFAvsonc &#8212; Tony &#34;The Bull&#34; (@tonythebullBTC) August 17, 2023 Tony is the author of the CoinChartist (VIP) newsletter. Sign up for free. Follow @TonyTheBullBTC &#38; @coinchartist_io on Twitter. Or join the TonyTradesBTC Telegram for daily market insights and technical analysis education. Please note: Content is educational and should not be considered investment advice. Featured image from iStockPhoto, Charts from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin price just experienced one of its fastest and sharpest corrections in over a year, dropping 10% in a matter of minutes.</p>
<p>The mass liquidations and panic from the selloff caused BTCUSD daily charts to reach the most oversold level since the COVID crash in early 2020.</p>
<h2>BTC Panic-Selling Reaches Extremes Not Seen Since COVID Crash</h2>
<p>As much as people try to fight it, investing and trading is an emotion-driven process. Few emotions cause humans to take action more urgently than those associated with fear and panic.</p>
<p>This is precisely why selloffs tend to be sharper and scarier than bull markets. “Bulls take the stairs, bears ride the elevator” is just one adage that symbolizes this noted market behavior.</p>

<p>For example, the COVID collapse in March 2020 took only a matter of days to erase 70% of Bitcoin’s price. This instance was the last time the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/topic/relative-strength-index/">Relative Strength Index</a> technical indicator on the daily timeframe became this oversold.</p>
<p>After Bitcoin’s recently drop this week, the daily RSI is back at a similar extreme for the first time in more than three years. What isn’t clear quite yet, is if the extreme represents another ideal buying opportunity, or if this is the onset of a deeper decline.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large wp-image-548301 aligncenter" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD_2023-08-21_09-03-46.png?w=860&#038;resize=860%2C497" alt="BTCUSD_2023-08-21_09-03-46" width="860" height="497" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD_2023-08-21_09-03-46.png?w=4078 4078w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD_2023-08-21_09-03-46.png?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD_2023-08-21_09-03-46.png?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD_2023-08-21_09-03-46.png?w=860&#038;resize=860%2C497 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD_2023-08-21_09-03-46.png?w=1536 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD_2023-08-21_09-03-46.png?w=2048 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD_2023-08-21_09-03-46.png?w=750 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD_2023-08-21_09-03-46.png?w=1140 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD_2023-08-21_09-03-46.png?w=3000 3000w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" data-recalc-dims="1"/></p>

<h2>Bitcoin Daily RSI Plunges To Most Oversold Level Since 2020</h2>
<p>The Relative Strength Index is a momentum indicator that tells investors and traders when an asset is overbought and oversold on a relative basis. When the tool reaches extremes above 70 or below 30, it can present an opportunity to buy or sell. The RSI is now lower than the LUNA or FTX collapse, or at any point since March 2020.</p>
<p>During especially strong moves, however, the RSI can remain elevated for extended phases despite reaching such overheated readings. Such was the case in December 2018, the previous instance of the daily Bitcoin RSI reaching such a low.</p>

<p>In that case, the RSI stayed hot for two full weeks, cutting down BTCUSD price by another 40% before it was all said and done. A 40% correction in Bitcoin would take prices back to the November 2022 bottom.</p>
<p>If Bitcoin instead rebounds and reacts more akin to 2020, new all-time highs could be just months away. If not, a deeper reset is possible.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr"><a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Bitcoin?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#Bitcoin</a> daily RSI is now the most oversold in all of 2023</p>
<p>Act accordingly <a href="https://t.co/GpKFAvsonc" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/GpKFAvsonc</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Tony &quot;The Bull&quot; (@tonythebullBTC) <a href="https://twitter.com/tonythebullBTC/status/1692210737530253756?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">August 17, 2023</a></p></blockquote>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/BTC-oversold.jpeg?fit=460%2C345" width="460" height="345" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">548299</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Whale Purchases $38 Million Worth Of SHIB, A Rebound On The Horizon?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/shib/whale-purchases-shib-rebound-on-the-horizon/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samuel Edyme]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 20:30:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[SHIB]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[memecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shiba Inu]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIBUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=548261</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Shiba Inu (SHIB) token has witnessed high-value transactions again, leading to intrigue among its community. As significant amounts of SHIB change hands, many wonder if these moves signal a forthcoming positive shift in its market position or a rebound, as the asset is currently in a downtrend. Whale Alert, a renowned blockchain tracking platform, disclosed that a transaction of 4.65 trillion SHIB tokens, equating to approximately $38.39 million, moved from Bitvavo to an unidentified wallet. 🚨 🚨 4,653,778,173,637 #SHIB (38,391,343 USD) transferred from #Bitvavo to unknown wallethttps://t.co/KFZzJIvU5q — Whale Alert (@whale_alert) August 21, 2023 High-Value Transactions Coincide With Shibarium’s Developments It&#8217;s worth noting that this isn’t an isolated event. A similar transaction occurred just a day prior, where an almost equivalent amount of 4.6 trillion SHIB tokens (around $38.70 million) was transferred from one undisclosed wallet to another. 🚨 🚨 4,669,778,173,637 #SHIB (38,707,791 USD) transferred from unknown wallet to unknown wallethttps://t.co/c6LPXZFq2h — Whale Alert (@whale_alert) August 20, 2023 These high-value transfers correlate with the start of Shibarium, the Ethereum-based layer-2 blockchain, which has been the cause of a spike in SHIB transactions. The surging activity, especially after introducing the Shibarium blockchain, naturally raised eyebrows within the Shiba Inu community. Related Reading: Shibarium Launch Saga: Block Production Resumes Despite Stuck ETH To address rising concerns about the safety of assets, the Shiba Inu team came forward in its &#8220;All Is Well&#8221; blog post, offering clarity on the technical issues, and emphasizing the security of the users’ assets. SHIB Rebound On The Horizon? While it&#8217;s undeniable that there may be growing attention on Shiba Inu, especially after these whale activities and the Shibarium blockchain&#8217;s developments. It may be too soon to forecast the exact trajectory SHIB will take. However, analyzing the Shiba Inu price chart suggests there could be a potential rebound, though it might not be imminent. On the 4-hour chart, Shiba Inu displays a pronounced downward wick. This indicates the presence of more liquidity in this downside range, which could suggest further decline as market makers may seek to capture this liquidity. To clarify, a wick refers to the thin line/vertical line above or below the main body of a candlestick. The wick represents an asset&#8217;s highest and lowest prices during a specific time frame, such as the candle marked above. Related Reading: How High Can Shiba Inu (SHIB) Rise When Shibarium Restarts? Regardless of the above analysis, significant whale purchases highlight the commitment of Shiba Inu&#8217;s investors. Such activities underscore their interest in adding to their SHIB holdings. This growing attention on SHIB is especially noteworthy given its recent Shibarium project launch. Featured image from Unsplash, Chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w g0rxnol2" dir="ltr">Shiba Inu (SHIB) token has witnessed high-value transactions again, leading to intrigue among its community. As significant amounts of SHIB change hands, many wonder if these moves signal a forthcoming positive shift in its market position or a rebound, as the asset is currently in a downtrend.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Whale Alert, a renowned blockchain tracking platform, <a href="https://twitter.com/whale_alert/status/1693535279078838692?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">disclosed</a> that a transaction of 4.65 trillion SHIB tokens, equating to approximately $38.39 million, moved from Bitvavo to an unidentified wallet.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en"><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f6a8.png" alt="🚨" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f6a8.png" alt="🚨" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> 4,653,778,173,637 <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/SHIB?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#SHIB</a> (38,391,343 USD) transferred from <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Bitvavo?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#Bitvavo</a> to unknown wallet<a href="https://t.co/KFZzJIvU5q" rel="nofollow">https://t.co/KFZzJIvU5q</a></p>
<p>— Whale Alert (@whale_alert) <a href="https://twitter.com/whale_alert/status/1693535279078838692?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">August 21, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<h2 dir="ltr">High-Value Transactions Coincide With Shibarium’s Developments</h2>
<p>It&#8217;s worth noting that this isn’t an isolated event. A <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/shiba-inu-whale-transfers-4-6-trillion-tokens-after-a-24-hour-safekeeping/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">similar transaction occurred</a> just a day prior, where an almost equivalent amount of 4.6 trillion SHIB tokens (around $38.70 million) was transferred from one undisclosed wallet to another.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en"><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f6a8.png" alt="🚨" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f6a8.png" alt="🚨" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> 4,669,778,173,637 <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/SHIB?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#SHIB</a> (38,707,791 USD) transferred from unknown wallet to unknown wallet<a href="https://t.co/c6LPXZFq2h" rel="nofollow">https://t.co/c6LPXZFq2h</a></p>
<p>— Whale Alert (@whale_alert) <a href="https://twitter.com/whale_alert/status/1693301237255389310?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">August 20, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p>These high-value transfers correlate with the start of Shibarium, the Ethereum-based layer-2 blockchain, which has been the cause of a spike in SHIB transactions. The surging activity, especially after introducing the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/shibarium-launch-stuck-eth/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Shibarium blockchain</a>, naturally raised eyebrows within the Shiba Inu community.</p>

<p>To address rising concerns about the safety of assets, the Shiba Inu team came forward in its &#8220;All Is Well&#8221; <a href="https://blog.shib.io/shibarium-insane-influx/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">blog post</a>, offering clarity on the technical issues, and emphasizing the security of the users’ assets.</p>
<h2>SHIB Rebound On The Horizon?</h2>
<p>While it&#8217;s undeniable that there may be growing attention on Shiba Inu, especially after these <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/buying-the-dip-shiba-inu-whale-activity-surges/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">whale activities</a> and the Shibarium blockchain&#8217;s developments. It may be too soon to forecast the exact trajectory SHIB will take. </p>
<p>However, analyzing the Shiba Inu price chart suggests there could be a <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/shiba-inu-price-resilience-shibarium-reboot/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">potential rebound</a>, though it might not be imminent. On the 4-hour chart, Shiba Inu displays a pronounced downward wick. This indicates the presence of more liquidity in this downside range, which could suggest further decline as market makers may seek to capture this liquidity.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/ScmhUq36/" alt="Shiba Inu (SHIB)’s price chart on TradingView" width="2770" height="1408"/>
<p>To clarify, a wick refers to the thin line/vertical line above or below the main body of a candlestick. The wick represents an asset&#8217;s highest and lowest prices during a specific time frame, such as the candle marked above.</p>

<p>Regardless of the above analysis, significant whale purchases highlight the commitment of Shiba Inu&#8217;s investors. Such activities underscore their interest in adding to their SHIB holdings. This growing attention on SHIB is especially noteworthy given its recent <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/how-high-shiba-inu-shib-rise-shibarium-restarts/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Shibarium project</a> launch.</p>
<p>Featured image from Unsplash, Chart from TradingView</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/todd-cravens-QnBrjY-nFUs-unsplash-2.jpg?fit=460%2C305" width="460" height="305" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">548261</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Price Follows This 1930&#8217;s Chart, Why BTC Could Keep On Falling</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-price-follows-this-1930s-chart-why-btc-could-keep-on-falling/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reynaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 19:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=548265</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Volatility is back for the Bitcoin price and the crypto market, but it currently favors the bears as value tumbles in the past few days. The nascent sector was moving sideways, but a liquidation cascade forced prices into critical support levels, but the worse might yet come if BTC fulfills a prophecy. Related Reading: Bitcoin Weekly Chart Completes Double Top: Market Shifts Ahead? As of this writing, the Bitcoin price trades at $26,100 with sideways movement in the last 24 hours. Over the past week, the price of BTC corrected back to $26,000 after its lost support at the high of its current levels. Is The Worst Yet To Come For The Bitcoin Price? Bloomberg Intelligence’s Senior Commodity Analyst Mike McGlone shared an analysis on social media platform X. Therein, the analyst classified Bitcoin as one of the “best-performing assets in history,” the cryptocurrency rose from $100 to around $70,000 in less than ten years. At the same time, McGlone pointed out the similarities between the Bitcoin price chart and the 1930s stock market chart. During this period, the US economy went through one of its worse history leading to a series of economic reforms. Comparing both sectors, McGlone forecasted a potential drop in the Bitcoin price once the US Federal Reserve (Fed) turns its monetary policy around. As seen in the chart below, the financial institution has raised interest rates to slow down inflation. As a result, BTC’s price has declined as liquidity leaves financial markets and uncertainty increases. Unlike popular belief, the Bloomberg Intelligence analyst expects the cryptocurrency to dip further if the Fed loses its monetary policy. McGlone explained: One of the best-performing assets in history and a leading indicator &#8212; Bitcoin &#8212; appears similar to the stock market in 1930. Statistician and entrepreneur Roger Babson began warning about elevated equity prices well before economist Irving Fisher proclaimed a &#8220;permanently high plateau&#8221; in 1929. The Fed tilts our bias toward a stance similar to Babson&#8217;s. The analyst above focuses on the increasing potential benefits for investors getting out of BTC and into government-based financial instruments, such as US Treasury notes which are currently yielding 5%. As long as this environment continues, BTC shows “mostly downward biases,” as the analyst concluded. Related Reading: Diamond In The Rough: Solo Bitcoin Miner Secures $160,000 Block Reward On short timeframes, the price of BTC continues to trade sideways, licking its wounds from last week’s liquidation cascades. The last time the cryptocurrency experienced a similar price action was in late 2022, and it took several weeks of sideways price action before a recovery was possible. Cover image from Unsplash, chart from Tradingview]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Volatility is back for the Bitcoin price and the crypto market, but it currently favors the bears as value tumbles in the past few days. The nascent sector was moving sideways, but a liquidation cascade forced prices into critical support levels, but the worse might yet come if BTC fulfills a prophecy. </strong></p>

<p>As of this writing, the Bitcoin price trades at $26,100 with sideways movement in the last 24 hours. Over the past week, the price of BTC corrected back to $26,000 after its lost support at the high of its current levels.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-548281 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-price-BTC-BTCUSDT-4.png?w=860&#038;resize=860%2C410" alt="Bitcoin price BTC BTCUSDT" width="860" height="410" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-price-BTC-BTCUSDT-4.png?w=1758 1758w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-price-BTC-BTCUSDT-4.png?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-price-BTC-BTCUSDT-4.png?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-price-BTC-BTCUSDT-4.png?w=860&#038;resize=860%2C410 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-price-BTC-BTCUSDT-4.png?w=1536 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-price-BTC-BTCUSDT-4.png?w=750 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-price-BTC-BTCUSDT-4.png?w=1140 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" data-recalc-dims="1"/>
<h2><strong>Is The Worst Yet To Come For The Bitcoin Price?</strong></h2>
<p>Bloomberg Intelligence’s Senior Commodity Analyst Mike McGlone shared an analysis on social media platform X. Therein, the analyst classified Bitcoin as one of the “best-performing assets in history,” the cryptocurrency rose from $100 to around $70,000 in less than ten years.</p>
<p>At the same time, McGlone pointed out the similarities between the Bitcoin price chart and the 1930s stock market chart. During this period, the US economy went through one of its worse history leading to a series of economic reforms.</p>
<p>Comparing both sectors, McGlone forecasted a potential drop in the Bitcoin price once the US Federal Reserve (Fed) turns its monetary policy around. As seen in the chart below, the financial institution has raised interest rates to slow down inflation.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-548280 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-price-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-2-2.jpeg?w=745&#038;resize=745%2C860" alt="Bitcoin price BTC BTCUSDT Chart 2" width="745" height="860" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-price-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-2-2.jpeg?w=781 781w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-price-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-2-2.jpeg?w=399 399w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-price-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-2-2.jpeg?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-price-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-2-2.jpeg?w=745&#038;resize=745%2C860 745w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-price-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-2-2.jpeg?w=750 750w" sizes="(max-width: 745px) 100vw, 745px" data-recalc-dims="1"/>
<p>As a result, BTC’s price has declined as liquidity leaves financial markets and uncertainty increases. Unlike popular belief, the Bloomberg Intelligence analyst expects the cryptocurrency to dip further if the Fed loses its monetary policy. McGlone explained:</p>
<blockquote><p>One of the best-performing assets in history and a leading indicator &#8212; Bitcoin &#8212; appears similar to the stock market in 1930. Statistician and entrepreneur Roger Babson began warning about elevated equity prices well before economist Irving Fisher proclaimed a &#8220;permanently high plateau&#8221; in 1929. The Fed tilts our bias toward a stance similar to Babson&#8217;s.</p></blockquote>
<p>The analyst above focuses on the increasing potential benefits for investors getting out of BTC and into government-based financial instruments, such as US Treasury notes which are currently yielding 5%. As long as this environment continues, BTC shows “mostly downward biases,” as the analyst concluded.</p>

<p>On short timeframes, the price of BTC continues to trade sideways, licking its wounds from last week’s liquidation cascades. The last time the cryptocurrency experienced a similar price action was in late 2022, and it took several weeks of sideways price action before a recovery was possible.</p>
<p>Cover image from Unsplash, chart from Tradingview</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-Price-BTC-BTCUSDT-7.jpg?fit=460%2C305" width="460" height="305" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">548265</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Will Bitcoin Retest $20,500 Again? This Pattern May Suggest So</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-retest-20500-again-this-pattern-suggest/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hououin Kyouma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 18:00:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Pattern]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Realized Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Retest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=548237</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin is forming a pattern that has historically led to the asset retesting a specific line. At present, this level would be found at $20,500. Bitcoin Has Dropped Below The 200-Day SMA With The Recent Crash A few days back, Bitcoin observed a sharp crash that took the cryptocurrency&#8217;s price toward the $26,000 mark. As this plummet was already significant, many have wondered whether this was it or if the drawdown will continue. An analyst on X, Ali, shared a chart that may provide hints about where the asset could be heading next. The trend in the realized price and the 200-day SMA for BTC &#124; Source: @ali_charts on X The analyst has attached the data for two Bitcoin-related metrics in the graph: the 200-day simple moving average (SMA) and the realized price. The chart shows that the BTC price has dropped below the 200-day SMA (colored in purple) with the latest crash. According to the analyst, when the cryptocurrency&#8217;s price has crossed below this level during the past ten years, it has often retested the realized price (colored in orange). The &#8220;realized price&#8221; here refers to the cost basis or the buying price of the average investor in the BTC market. This means that whenever the cryptocurrency dips below this level, the average holder enters a state of loss. On the other hand, breaks above the line imply a return to profits for most of the market. Historically, this metric has had some interesting interactions with the spot price of the coin. During bullish periods, the line has generally supported the asset, while during bearish periods, it has acted as resistance. Related Reading: Bitcoin Price Consolidates Losses and At Risk of Fresh Decline To $25K The explanation behind these curious interactions may lie in how the investors&#8217; minds work in each period. In bull markets, the average investor may think that the price will only go up, so whenever the asset drops to its buying price, they accumulate more of the asset. Similarly, in bearish trends, the holders may believe the cryptocurrency will only go down, so the price they bought in (their break-even mark) would be the ideal exit opportunity. This buying and selling may cause the level to act as support and resistance in the respective regimes. The latest example of this behavior was seen earlier in the year when Bitcoin rebounded off the line back in March. As the asset now appears to have broken below the 200-day SMA, it may be heading towards a retest, as has often happened many times in the past. Related Reading: Here Are The Factors That Could Be Behind The Latest Bitcoin Wipeout Right now, the cost basis of the average investor is $20,500, which means that if BTC is going to touch this line again, a significant drawdown would need to occur. If this scenario indeed plays out, then it&#8217;s possible that Bitcoin could find a rebound at the realized price once again. A retest failure, however, would be a very concerning sign, as it might signal the return of the bear market. BTC Price At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading around $26,000, down 11% in the last week. BTC has been moving sideways since the crash &#124; Source: BTCUSD on TradingView Featured image from Maxim Hopman on Unsplash.com, charts from TradingView.com, Glassnode.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin is forming a pattern that has historically led to the asset retesting a specific line. At present, this level would be found at $20,500.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Has Dropped Below The 200-Day SMA With The Recent Crash</h2>
<p>A few days back, Bitcoin observed a <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-investors-fall-fear-btc-crashes-26500/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">sharp crash</a> that took the cryptocurrency&#8217;s price toward the $26,000 mark. As this plummet was already significant, many have wondered whether this was it or if the drawdown will continue.</p>
<p>An analyst on X, Ali, <a href="https://twitter.com/ali_charts/status/1693392465607406020" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">shared</a> a chart that may provide hints about where the asset could be heading next.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone aligncenter" src="https://pbs.twimg.com/media/F3-c7UQWcAA2-cG?format=jpg&amp;name=medium" alt="Bitcoin Realized Price" width="1199" height="675"/></p>

<p>The analyst has attached the data for two Bitcoin-related metrics in the graph: the 200-day simple moving average (SMA) and the realized price. The chart shows that the BTC price has dropped below the 200-day SMA (colored in purple) with the latest crash.</p>
<p>According to the analyst, when the cryptocurrency&#8217;s price has crossed below this level during the past ten years, it has often retested the realized price (colored in orange).</p>
<p>The &#8220;<a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-under-realized-price-163-days/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">realized price</a>&#8221; here refers to the cost basis or the buying price of the average investor in the BTC market. This means that whenever the cryptocurrency dips below this level, the average holder enters a state of loss. On the other hand, breaks above the line imply a return to profits for most of the market.</p>
<p>Historically, this metric has had some interesting interactions with the spot price of the coin. During bullish periods, the line has generally supported the asset, while during bearish periods, it has acted as resistance.</p>

<p>The explanation behind these curious interactions may lie in how the investors&#8217; minds work in each period. In bull markets, the average investor may think that the price will only go up, so whenever the asset drops to its buying price, they accumulate more of the asset.</p>
<p>Similarly, in bearish trends, the holders may believe the cryptocurrency will only go down, so the price they bought in (their break-even mark) would be the ideal exit opportunity.</p>
<p>This buying and selling may cause the level to act as support and resistance in the respective regimes. The latest example of this behavior was seen earlier in the year when Bitcoin rebounded off the line back in March.</p>
<p>As the asset now appears to have broken below the 200-day SMA, it may be heading towards a retest, as has often happened many times in the past.</p>

<p>Right now, the cost basis of the average investor is $20,500, which means that if BTC is going to touch this line again, a significant drawdown would need to occur.</p>
<p>If this scenario indeed plays out, then it&#8217;s possible that Bitcoin could find a rebound at the realized price once again. A retest failure, however, would be a very concerning sign, as it might signal the return of the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/crypto-trading-volumes-fall-to-lowest-level-in-2023/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">bear market</a>.</p>
<h2>BTC Price</h2>
<p>At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading around $26,000, down 11% in the last week.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium aligncenter" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/4joko3De/" alt="Bitcoin Price Chart" width="1534" height="877"/></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/maxim-hopman-fiXLQXAhCfk-unsplash-2.jpg?fit=460%2C307" width="460" height="307" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">548237</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Gemini Hits Back At SEC Lawsuit With Dismissal Filing</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/crypto/gemini-sec-lawsuit-dismissal-filing/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 17:00:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gemini]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gemini Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Unregistered security]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=548273</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Gemini, an American cryptocurrency exchange, has taken a stand against the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), deeming the lawsuit brought forth by the regulator as “absurd.” Gemini Pushes Back Against SEC Lawsuit In the ongoing legal battle between Gemini Exchange and the US SEC, co-founders Cameron Winklevoss and Tyler Winklevoss have contested the validity of the SEC’s case by submitting a comprehensive brief to oppose the SEC’s claims on the Gemini Earn program.  Related Reading: Experts Explain Why SEC’s Interlocutory Appeal In Ripple Case Was A Mistake In the filing, Gemini stated that the SEC had failed to establish a clear definition of what the regulatory body regards as securities. The exchange also highlighted the absence of well-defined requirements for violating regulatory laws. As a result, the lack of specification in the SEC’s argument hampers the exchange&#8217;s ability to respond properly to the allegations put forward.  In the Judicial presentation, the exchange urged the court to ignore the “convoluted analysis” provided by the SEC. The exchange has instead advocated for direct questions which would determine if the cryptocurrency in question qualifies as a security.  Gemini has also stated that the SEC should provide an identification of the unregistered security and information on the specific sale, highlighting that treating all cryptocurrencies as unregistered security is prejudiced.  The company&#8217;s lawyer, Jack Baughman also publicly refuted the SEC’s claims in a Twitter post, saying: The SEC is floundering. They can’t even decide what the security is. On the one hand, they claim that the Loan Agreement was a security. On the other hand, they claim that the entire Gemini Earn program was itself a security — an argument absurd on its face. GUSD market cap at $361 million &#124; Source: GUSD Market Capitalization on Tradingview.com Background On The SEC Lawsuit Earlier this year, on January 13, the US SEC filed a lawsuit against Gemini and Genesis, a crypto lender affiliated with Gemini Trust Company. According to the SEC, Genesis loaned the exchange&#8217;s users unregistered securities through the Gemini Earn program, allowing the exchange and Genesis to accumulate billions of dollars worth of crypto assets from thousands of investors.  Related Reading: Ethereum Whale Avoids Market Crash, Do They Know Something You Don’t? At the beginning of February 2021, Genesis and Gemini initiated a partnership that would offer the Gemini Earn program to retail investors allowing them to loan their crypto assets to Genesis, while the exchange acts as a middleman. Genesis would then invest the crypto assets, and pay users in interest.   The SEC alleged that the company, alongside Genesis, violated federal laws via the Gemini Earn program by not registering its offerings and sales with the Commission. The lawsuit was received with an unfavorable response from the exchange&#8217;s legal team, which resulted in the dismissal motion submitted on August 18.  Featured image from Unsplash, chart from Tradingview.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Gemini, an American cryptocurrency exchange, has taken a stand against the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), deeming the lawsuit brought forth by the regulator as “absurd.”</p>
<h2>Gemini Pushes Back Against SEC Lawsuit</h2>
<p>In the ongoing legal battle between Gemini Exchange and the US SEC, co-founders Cameron Winklevoss and Tyler Winklevoss have contested the validity of the SEC’s case by submitting a comprehensive brief to oppose the SEC’s claims on the Gemini Earn program. </p>

<p><a href="https://jfblegal.egnyte.com/dl/AEuO1xtt7t/2023-08-18_(Dkt._042)_Gemini_Reply_ISO_MTD.pdf_" rel="nofollow">In the filing</a>, Gemini stated that the SEC had failed to establish a clear definition of what the regulatory body regards as securities. The exchange also highlighted the absence of well-defined requirements for violating regulatory laws. As a result, the lack of specification in the SEC’s argument hampers the exchange&#8217;s ability to respond properly to the allegations put forward. </p>
<p>In the Judicial presentation, the exchange urged the court to ignore the “convoluted analysis” provided by the SEC. The exchange has instead advocated for direct questions which would determine if the cryptocurrency in question qualifies as a security. </p>
<p>Gemini has also stated that the SEC should provide an identification of the unregistered security and information on the specific sale, highlighting that treating all cryptocurrencies as unregistered security is prejudiced. </p>
<p>The company&#8217;s lawyer, Jack Baughman also publicly refuted the SEC’s claims in a <a href="https://twitter.com/JackBaughman27/status/1692639161734369755?s=20" rel="nofollow">Twitter post</a>, saying:</p>
<blockquote><p>The SEC is floundering. They can’t even decide what the security is. On the one hand, they claim that the Loan Agreement was a security. On the other hand, they claim that the entire Gemini Earn program was itself a security — an argument absurd on its face.</p></blockquote>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/XMOsjRBN/" alt="Gemini USD (GUSD) price chart from Tradingview.com" width="2884" height="1746"/></p>

<h2>Background On The SEC Lawsuit</h2>
<p>Earlier this year, on January 13, the US SEC filed a lawsuit against Gemini and Genesis, a crypto lender affiliated with Gemini Trust Company. According to the SEC, Genesis loaned the exchange&#8217;s users unregistered securities through the Gemini Earn program, allowing the exchange and Genesis to accumulate billions of dollars worth of crypto assets from thousands of investors. </p>

<p>At the beginning of February 2021, Genesis and Gemini initiated a partnership that would offer the Gemini <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/sponsored/gemini-earn-users-want-justice-exchange-ignores-them-to-buy-ledgerx/">Earn program</a> to retail investors allowing them to loan their crypto assets to Genesis, while the exchange acts as a middleman. Genesis would then invest the crypto assets, and pay users in interest.  </p>
<p>The SEC <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/gemini-and-genesis-file-motion-to-earn-offering/" rel="nofollow">alleged</a> that the company, alongside Genesis, violated federal laws via the Gemini Earn program by not registering its offerings and sales with the Commission. The lawsuit was received with an unfavorable response from the exchange&#8217;s legal team, which resulted in the dismissal motion submitted on August 18. </p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/piggybank-hkbOeLYxUZo-unsplash.jpg?fit=460%2C368" width="460" height="368" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">548273</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dogecoin Proof Of Stake Discussion Heats Up As Lead Dev Chimes In</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/dogecoin/dogecoin-proof-of-stake-discussion/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 16:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[doge]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DOGE news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Doge price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin developer]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Proof of Stake]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[proof of work]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=548241</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Dogecoin Lead Developer, Mishaboar has expressed his doubts about a possible move to a Proof of Stake (PoS) blockchain consensus. The developer has stated that the transition to a POS mechanism is not a “sensible approach” and has highlighted several issues that could develop from the change. Mishaboar Objects To PoS Transition Mishaboar took to social media on August 20, to express his concerns about the potential impacts a PoS transformation could have on Dogecoin’s network and decentralized nature. In a recent Twitter post, he staunchly refuted the transition and stated that if the conversion pulls through, he may leave Dogecoin for another cryptocurrency network with a PoW consensus.  Related Reading: Ethereum Whale Avoids Market Crash, Do They Know Something You Don’t? “If this refers to a remote possibility of Doge ever switching to PoS, after what I have seen over the past 2 years, I would probably then move to another PoW crypto and customize the logo in my wallet to have a dog in it,” Mishaboar commented in a Twitter post.  Mishaboar has highlighted the possibilities of power imbalances that could result from a PoS switch since a significant amount of a cryptocurrency’s supply is controlled by exchanges.  He stated that the change to a PoS consensus could increase the control and influence of exchanges over a network. The developer also pointed out that Dogecoin may face increased regulatory challenges with the transition.  Furthermore, Mishaboar explained that cryptocurrencies that have transitioned to a PoS consensus have been overhyped, with most falling short of expectations and failing considerably or becoming so centralized that it contradicts the foundational structure of cryptocurrencies which is in its decentralized system.  Mishaboar concludes that transitioning into a PoS consensus does not align with Dogecoin’s futuristic goals and objectives. He mentioned that the benefits of a PoS consensus which is fast transactions can easily be achieved in the Dogecoin network with other solutions like integration of multiple payment channels. DOGE price struggles to recover &#124; Source: DOGEUSD on Tradingview.com PoS Versus PoW Consensus For Dogecoin Ecosystem The broader cryptocurrency community is presently at loggerheads on the merits of a PoS and PoW consensus and Mishaboar’s rejection of a possible Dogecoin transition has sparked debates about the future of Dogecoin cryptocurrency among crypto enthusiasts.  Proof of Work (PoW) and Proof of Stake (POS) are two distinct blockchain consensus mechanisms used to validate transactions and improve the general performance of a blockchain network. And these two consensuses have their different advantages and disadvantages.  The advantages of a PoS are seen in its energy conservation and fast transactions. In contrast, a PoW consensus is considered more secure and more decentralized but is energy-intensive.  Related Reading: Elon Musk Shows Public Support For Pro-Crypto Presidential Candidate Some crypto investors argue that a PoS consensus would offer greater energy utilization and scalability. Whereas, others have sided with Mishaboar, strongly refuting the idea of centralization and security risks that follow a PoS transition. Mishaboar has been a prominent part of Dogecoin’s development, yet recent statements made by the enigmatic figure have led to speculations about the impact his rejection of Dogecoin’s possible PoS consensus could have on the project&#8217;s direction and development. Featured image from Unsplash, chart from Tradingview.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Dogecoin Lead Developer, Mishaboar has expressed his doubts about a possible move to a Proof of Stake (PoS) blockchain consensus. The developer has stated that the transition to a POS mechanism is not a “sensible approach” and has highlighted several issues that could develop from the change.</p>
<h2>Mishaboar Objects To PoS Transition</h2>
<p><a href="https://bitcoinist.com/dogecoin-lead-dev-opposes-proof-of-stake/" rel="nofollow">Mishaboar</a> took to social media on August 20, to express his concerns about the potential impacts a PoS transformation could have on Dogecoin’s network and decentralized nature. In a recent <a href="https://twitter.com/mishaboar/status/1693120622048555422?s=20" rel="nofollow">Twitter post</a>, he staunchly refuted the transition and stated that if the conversion pulls through, he may leave Dogecoin for another cryptocurrency network with a PoW consensus. </p>

<p>“If this refers to a remote possibility of Doge ever switching to PoS, after what I have seen over the past 2 years, I would probably then move to another PoW crypto and customize the logo in my wallet to have a dog in it,” Mishaboar commented in a Twitter post. </p>
<p>Mishaboar has highlighted the possibilities of power imbalances that could result from a PoS switch since a significant amount of a cryptocurrency’s supply is controlled by exchanges. </p>
<p>He stated that the change to a <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/human-rights-foundation-says-there-will-be-pressure-for-bitcoin-to-use-proof-of-stake-like-ethereum/">PoS consensus</a> could increase the control and influence of exchanges over a network. The developer also pointed out that Dogecoin may face increased regulatory challenges with the transition. </p>
<p>Furthermore, Mishaboar explained that cryptocurrencies that have transitioned to a PoS consensus have been overhyped, with most falling short of expectations and failing considerably or becoming so centralized that it contradicts the foundational structure of cryptocurrencies which is in its decentralized system. </p>
<p>Mishaboar concludes that transitioning into a PoS consensus does not align with Dogecoin’s futuristic goals and objectives. He mentioned that the benefits of a PoS consensus which is fast transactions can easily be achieved in the Dogecoin network with other solutions like <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/breaking-news-ticker/dogecoin-surges-6-after-elon-musk-unveils-crypto-payment-master-plan/">integration of multiple payment channels</a>.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/cgSSy50h/" alt="Dogecoin price chart from Tradingiew.com" width="2884" height="1746"/></p>

<h2>PoS Versus PoW Consensus For Dogecoin Ecosystem</h2>
<p>The broader cryptocurrency community is presently at loggerheads on the merits of a PoS and PoW consensus and Mishaboar’s rejection of a possible Dogecoin transition has sparked debates about the future of Dogecoin cryptocurrency among crypto enthusiasts. </p>
<p>Proof of Work (PoW) and Proof of Stake (POS) are two distinct blockchain consensus mechanisms used to validate transactions and improve the general performance of a blockchain network. And these two consensuses have their different advantages and disadvantages. </p>
<p>The advantages of a PoS are seen in its energy conservation and fast transactions. In contrast, a PoW consensus is considered more secure and more decentralized but is energy-intensive. </p>

<p>Some crypto investors <a href="https://twitter.com/supremebeme/status/1693130905735569752?s=20" rel="nofollow">argue</a> that a PoS consensus would offer greater energy utilization and scalability. Whereas, others have sided with Mishaboar, <a href="https://twitter.com/Pilsner_Maxwell/status/1693255261216006275?s=20" rel="nofollow">strongly refuting </a>the idea of centralization and security risks that follow a PoS transition.</p>
<p>Mishaboar has been a prominent part of Dogecoin’s development, yet recent statements made by the enigmatic figure have led to speculations about the impact his rejection of Dogecoin’s possible PoS consensus could have on the project&#8217;s direction and development.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/kanchanara-r9dG85a7E_U-unsplash.jpg?fit=460%2C306" width="460" height="306" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">548241</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance Coin Falls Below $210 As BNB Bridge Hacker&#8217;s Health Rate Sinks To 0.99</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/binance-coin-drops-below-210-bnb-bridge-hacker-in-trouble/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jake Simmons]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 15:01:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance Coin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BNB]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BNB Bridge Hacker]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Venus Protocol]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=548238</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[In a complex tangle of smart contracts, governance proposals, and fluctuating crypto prices, the financial health rate of the infamous Binance BNB Bridge exploiter address (0x48…9bec) has fallen below the critical value of 1, hovering at 0.99. This development is of particular interest, given that the address holds a significant collateral of 784,616.10 BNB and a debt position in the form of USDT and USDC totaling $124 million. The plummeting health rate comes amidst the fall of Binance Coin (BNB) to $207.9, well below the pre-determined liquidation price of $210.80, leading to increased speculation about potential liquidation scenarios. As per a tweet from blockchain security firm PeckShield: &#8220;The health rate of the BNB Bridge Exploiter on Venus is 0.99. BNB has dropped to $207.9. The Venus community has passed a governance proposal to whitelist liquidation of the BNB Bridge exploiter&#8217;s position before.&#8221; Liquidation Contingency: The Binance Plan He Yi, the co-founder of Binance, alleviated some concerns stating, &#8220;The BNB collateral of Venus is covered by Binance. When the price of BNB falls, Binance will liquidate it in time. These BNB will not affect the secondary market price, and Binance will be responsible for burning these additional BNB.&#8221; Related Reading: Binance In Murky Waters? Analyst Explains Why BNB Must Stay Above This Price Nevertheless, the crypto community and analysts alike are closely following the situation, speculating on whether Binance CEO Changpeng Zhao, commonly known as CZ, intends to execute the liquidation to remove the illegitimate BNB from the ecosystem. Renowned analyst Skew remarked regarding the currently ongoing price movements: &#8220;&#8221;BNB Shorts going at it again + -24% APR (24hr). BNB Aggregate CVDs show takers are net sellers on the day so far. BNB Binance Spot: Quite a lot of spot bids below down to $200, so there will need to be a frenzy of spot selling in order to cause price dislocation or a crash. Large limit buyer has been trying to absorb the sell pressure.&#8221; Crypto influencer MartyParty brought this hypothesis into the limelight, stating, &#8220;Is CZ trying to liquidate the Venus loan to burn the 900k illegal BNB? Based on the Venus protocol documentation, the loan would have to be liquidated to burn the illegal BNB. That is the only way to remove it from the ecosystem.&#8221; This liquidity and governance issue comes after an &#8220;exploiter&#8221; illegally minted 2 million $BNB through a vulnerability in BNB Bridge, which has since been repaired. Of this illegally minted BNB, 900,000 BNB was used as collateral on Venus Protocol to obtain a loan exceeding $150 million in stablecoins, which was then dispersed across multiple blockchains. On June 12, 2023, a potential liquidation was averted when Binance stepped in to add $30 million in USDT margin, bringing the liquidation price down to $212. Again on August 17, another liquidation was sidestepped, pulling the liquidation threshold down to $210.80 and consequently the health rate to 1.02. Related Reading: Curve DAO Scores $5 Million Boost From Binance, Eyes BNB Chain Expansion In an earlier reaction to MartyParty&#8217;s query, CZ seemed unfazed: &#8220;Took me a while to understand (IF I even vaguely understand now). So, Marty is worried about a $30-120m worth re-buy of #BNB? Maybe he should check the last BNB burn? or the #SAFU insurance fund size?&#8221; He also commented on the volatility of BNB, adding, &#8220;And where did the $212 magic number come from? #BNB price is determined by the market. A $30m re-buy is less than 4% of a single day&#8217;s volume.&#8221; As of this writing, the market is still uncertain, waiting for further signals from CZ, who hasn&#8217;t commented on the latest developments. Meanwhile, Arkham Intelligence&#8217;s dashboard remains a focal point for real-time updates on the loan status and the health rate of the exploiter&#8217;s account. At press time, no liquidation took place yet. At press time, the BNB price was at $210.5. Featured image from Metal Pay, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In a complex tangle of smart contracts, governance proposals, and fluctuating crypto prices, the financial health rate of the infamous Binance BNB Bridge exploiter address (0x48…9bec) has fallen below the critical value of 1, hovering at 0.99. This development is of particular interest, given that the address holds a significant collateral of 784,616.10 BNB and a debt position in the form of USDT and USDC totaling $124 million.</p>
<p>The plummeting health rate comes amidst the fall of Binance Coin (BNB) to $207.9, well below the pre-determined liquidation price of $210.80, leading to increased speculation about potential liquidation scenarios.</p>
<p>As per a <a href="https://twitter.com/PeckShieldAlert/status/1693579519247131015" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">tweet</a> from blockchain security firm PeckShield: &#8220;The health rate of the BNB Bridge Exploiter on Venus is 0.99. BNB has dropped to $207.9. The Venus community has passed a governance proposal to whitelist liquidation of the BNB Bridge exploiter&#8217;s position before.&#8221;</p>
<h2>Liquidation Contingency: The Binance Plan</h2>
<p>He Yi, the co-founder of Binance, alleviated some concerns stating, &#8220;The BNB collateral of Venus is covered by Binance. When the price of BNB falls, Binance will liquidate it in time. These BNB will not affect the secondary market price, and Binance will be responsible for burning these additional BNB.&#8221;</p>

<p>Nevertheless, the crypto community and analysts alike are closely following the situation, speculating on whether Binance CEO Changpeng Zhao, commonly known as CZ, intends to execute the liquidation to remove the illegitimate BNB from the ecosystem.</p>
<p>Renowned analyst Skew <a href="https://twitter.com/52kskew/status/1693574204371894509" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">remarked</a> regarding the currently ongoing price movements: &#8220;&#8221;BNB Shorts going at it again + -24% APR (24hr). BNB Aggregate CVDs show takers are net sellers on the day so far. BNB Binance Spot: Quite a lot of spot bids below down to $200, so there will need to be a frenzy of spot selling in order to cause price dislocation or a crash. Large limit buyer has been trying to absorb the sell pressure.&#8221;</p>
<p>Crypto influencer MartyParty <a href="https://twitter.com/martypartymusic/status/1693509886662029733" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">brought</a> this hypothesis into the limelight, stating, &#8220;Is CZ trying to liquidate the Venus loan to burn the 900k illegal BNB? Based on the Venus protocol documentation, the loan would have to be liquidated to burn the illegal BNB. That is the only way to remove it from the ecosystem.&#8221;</p>
<p>This liquidity and governance issue comes after an &#8220;exploiter&#8221; illegally minted 2 million $BNB through a vulnerability in BNB Bridge, which has since been repaired. Of this illegally minted BNB, 900,000 BNB was used as collateral on Venus Protocol to obtain a loan exceeding $150 million in stablecoins, which was then dispersed across multiple blockchains.</p>
<p>On June 12, 2023, a potential liquidation was averted when Binance stepped in to add $30 million in USDT margin, bringing the liquidation price down to $212. Again on August 17, another liquidation was sidestepped, pulling the liquidation threshold down to $210.80 and consequently the health rate to 1.02.</p>

<p>In an earlier reaction to MartyParty&#8217;s query, CZ seemed <a href="https://twitter.com/cz_binance/status/1692935987670774088" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">unfazed</a>: &#8220;Took me a while to understand (IF I even vaguely understand now). So, Marty is worried about a $30-120m worth re-buy of #BNB? Maybe he should check the last BNB burn? or the #SAFU insurance fund size?&#8221;</p>
<p>He also commented on the volatility of BNB, adding, &#8220;And where did the $212 magic number come from? #BNB price is determined by the market. A $30m re-buy is less than 4% of a single day&#8217;s volume.&#8221;</p>
<p>As of this writing, the market is still uncertain, waiting for further signals from CZ, who hasn&#8217;t commented on the latest developments. Meanwhile, Arkham Intelligence&#8217;s dashboard remains a focal point for real-time updates on the loan status and the health rate of the exploiter&#8217;s account. At press time, no liquidation took place yet.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-548246 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot-2023-08-21-135113.png?resize=3774%2C2986" alt="Binance BNB Bridge Exploiter" width="3774" height="2986" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot-2023-08-21-135113.png?resize=3774%2C2986?w=3774 3774w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot-2023-08-21-135113.png?resize=3774%2C2986?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot-2023-08-21-135113.png?resize=3774%2C2986?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot-2023-08-21-135113.png?resize=3774%2C2986?w=860 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot-2023-08-21-135113.png?resize=3774%2C2986?w=1536 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot-2023-08-21-135113.png?resize=3774%2C2986?w=2048 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot-2023-08-21-135113.png?resize=3774%2C2986?w=750 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot-2023-08-21-135113.png?resize=3774%2C2986?w=1140 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot-2023-08-21-135113.png?resize=3774%2C2986?w=3000 3000w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" data-recalc-dims="1"/>
<p>At press time, the BNB price was at $210.5.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-548248 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BNBUSD_2023-08-21_13-58-23.png?resize=3628%2C1672" alt="Binance BNB price" width="3628" height="1672" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BNBUSD_2023-08-21_13-58-23.png?resize=3628%2C1672?w=3628 3628w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BNBUSD_2023-08-21_13-58-23.png?resize=3628%2C1672?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BNBUSD_2023-08-21_13-58-23.png?resize=3628%2C1672?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BNBUSD_2023-08-21_13-58-23.png?resize=3628%2C1672?w=860 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BNBUSD_2023-08-21_13-58-23.png?resize=3628%2C1672?w=1536 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BNBUSD_2023-08-21_13-58-23.png?resize=3628%2C1672?w=2048 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BNBUSD_2023-08-21_13-58-23.png?resize=3628%2C1672?w=750 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BNBUSD_2023-08-21_13-58-23.png?resize=3628%2C1672?w=1140 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BNBUSD_2023-08-21_13-58-23.png?resize=3628%2C1672?w=3000 3000w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" data-recalc-dims="1"/>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/binance-coin-bnb-profile_5f17283e82dd6.jpg?fit=460%2C259" width="460" height="259" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">548238</post-id>	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
