<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
>

<channel>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.newsbtc.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<description>Bitcoin &#38; Cryptocurrency News Today</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 02:48:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Is Reportedly Trading At a $2k Premium on Binance.US</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-is-reportedly-trading-at-a-2k-premium-on-binance-us/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dalmas Ngetich]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 03:00:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance US]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=536951</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[According to sources on June 6, Bitcoin is trading at a $2,000 premium on Binance US, an exchange the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) claims is controlled by Changpeng Zhao and Binance Global. According to screenshots widely circulated on Twitter, BTC, at one point, was reportedly trading at $28,505, a price level that was roughly $2,000 higher than the global BTC average of around $26,500 at the time. Bitcoin Trading At A $2,000 Premium on Binance US From price charts, Bitcoin remains volatile even at spot rates. Less than 24 hours after slumping to as low as $25,900 on June 5, the coin reversed losses on June 6.  Yesterday, the price of BTC surged, reaching levels as high as $27,000. This upward movement contradicted the bearish forecasts that analysts had previously made for June 5. Additionally, this positive price movement helped alleviate concerns that the SEC lawsuit against Binance would hurt the value of BTC. Related Reading: Bitcoin 24-Hour Volatility Soars, Why Bulls Could Win Fight In Short-Term Tumbling Bitcoin and crypto prices on June 5 coincided with accusations from the US regulator. The SEC listed 13 charges against Binance, including that together with the Binance US, the exchange allegedly enabled US citizens to illegally trade a wide range of cryptocurrencies. Moreover, the SEC pressed that Binance and Binance US were unregistered trading platforms that continue to offer “multiple unregistered offers and investment schemes” aimed at “defrauding equity, retail, and institutional investors about purported surveillance and controls over manipulative trading.” In response to the SEC’s lawsuit, on-chain data from Nansen shows that investors have continued to pull billions worth of crypto assets from Binance Global and Binance US.  The analytics platform observes that over $3 billion of assets from multiple chains have been withdrawn from Binance. Out of this, over $1.3 billion was from Ethereum.  Intervention Fueling Bitcoin’s Demand Meanwhile, Binance.US has suspended its over-the-counter (OTC) trading platform and reduced the number of supported trading pairs.  The announcement of Binance US’ changes affects roughly 90 pairs of the USDT, BTC, and BUSD pairs. It is also unclear when Binance US will resume its OTC trading services. Related Reading: Shiba Inu (SHIB) Price Could Soar To Major Highs Soon, Here’s Why Furthermore, Binance US has reduced the trade and convert options to USDC, USDT, Bitcoin, Ethereum, and some of the top crypto assets, including Cardano’s ADA. However, while there is a limitation on which assets existing clients can convert to, Binance US has placed caps on the maximum buy, sell, and convert options to USD at $10,000.  The suspension of the Binance US OTC platform and caps on USD conversion and assets could explain why Bitcoin is a highly sought asset and trading at a $2k premium in the United States for clients who used Binance US.  SEC and the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) have previously stated that Bitcoin is a commodity. Feature Image From Canva, Chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>According to sources on June 6, Bitcoin is trading at a $2,000 premium on Binance US, an exchange the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) claims is controlled by Changpeng Zhao and Binance Global.</p>
<p> According to <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://twitter.com/stackhodler/status/1666443985752141828" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">screenshots</a> widely circulated on Twitter, BTC, at one point, was reportedly trading at $28,505, a price level that was roughly $2,000 higher than the global BTC average of around $26,500 at the time.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Trading At A $2,000 Premium on Binance US</h2>
<p>From price charts, Bitcoin remains volatile even at spot rates. Less than 24 hours after slumping to as low as $25,900 on June 5, the coin reversed losses on June 6. </p>
<a href="https://www.tradingview.com/x/KgoXOhO5/" rel="nofollow"><img decoding="async" class="size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/KgoXOhO5/" alt="Bitcoin Price on June 7| Source: BTCUSDT On Binance, TradingView" width="1225" height="595" loading="lazy"/></a>
<p>Yesterday, the price of BTC surged, reaching levels as high as $27,000. This upward movement contradicted the bearish forecasts that analysts had previously made for June 5. Additionally, this positive price movement helped alleviate concerns that the SEC lawsuit against Binance would hurt the value of BTC.</p>

<p>Tumbling Bitcoin and crypto prices on June 5 coincided with accusations from the US regulator. The SEC <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.docdroid.net/I02zzqT/sec-v-binance-4-pdf#page=3" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">listed</a> 13 charges against Binance, including that together with the Binance US, the exchange allegedly enabled US citizens to illegally trade a wide range of cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p>Moreover, the SEC pressed that Binance and Binance US were unregistered trading platforms that continue to offer “multiple unregistered offers and investment schemes” aimed at “defrauding equity, retail, and institutional investors about purported surveillance and controls over manipulative trading.”</p>
<p>In response to the SEC’s lawsuit, on-chain data from Nansen <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://twitter.com/nansen_ai/status/1666145240603058179" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">shows</a> that investors have continued to pull billions worth of crypto assets from Binance Global and Binance US. </p>
<p>The analytics platform observes that over $3 billion of assets from multiple chains have been withdrawn from Binance. Out of this, over $1.3 billion was from Ethereum. </p>
<h2>Intervention Fueling Bitcoin’s Demand</h2>
<p>Meanwhile, Binance.US has suspended its over-the-counter (OTC) trading platform and reduced the number of supported trading pairs. </p>
<p>The <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://support.binance.us/hc/en-us/articles/15133607064983-Binance-US-Will-Remove-Select-Trading-Pairs-Has-Paused-OTC-Trading" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">announcement</a> of Binance US’ changes affects roughly 90 pairs of the USDT, BTC, and BUSD pairs. It is also unclear when Binance US will resume its OTC trading services.</p>

<p>Furthermore, Binance US has reduced the trade and convert options to USDC, USDT, Bitcoin, Ethereum, and some of the top crypto assets, including Cardano’s ADA.</p>
<p>However, while there is a limitation on which assets existing clients can convert to, Binance US has placed caps on the maximum buy, sell, and convert options to USD at $10,000. </p>
<p>The suspension of the Binance US OTC platform and caps on USD conversion and assets could explain why Bitcoin is a highly sought asset and trading at a $2k premium in the United States for clients who used Binance US. </p>
<p>SEC and the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) have previously stated that Bitcoin is a commodity.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-Premium-Binance-US-460x260.jpg" width="460" height="260" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum Price Consolidates Below $1,900: What Could Trigger A Sharp Decline?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-consolidates-below-1900/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 02:48:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=536959</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Ethereum price is moving lower from the $1,900 resistance against the US Dollar. ETH could decline heavily if there is a clear move below the $1,800 support. Ethereum is still struggling to clear the $1,900 and $1,920 resistance levels. The price is trading below $1,880 and the 100-hourly Simple Moving Average. There is a major bearish trend line forming with resistance near $1,855 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD (data feed via Kraken). The pair could still struggle to clear the $1,900 resistance zone. Ethereum Price Dips Again Ethereum’s price started a fresh increase from the $1,775 zone. ETH climbed above the $1,850 resistance but the bears were again active near the $1,900 zone, similar to Bitcoin. A high is formed near $1,898 and the price is now moving lower. There was a break below the $1,850 support zone. The bears pushed the price below the 50% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $1,777 swing low to the $1,898 high. Ether is now trading below $1,880 and the 100-hourly Simple Moving Average. There is also a major bearish trend line forming with resistance near $1,855 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD. It is now holding the $1,820 support and the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $1,777 swing low to the $1,898 high. Immediate resistance is near the $1,855 zone and the trend line. The next major resistance is near the $1,900 level or the recent high. Source: ETHUSD on TradingView.com A proper move above the $1,895 and $1,900 resistance levels might send Ether toward $1,920. The next resistance sits near $1,950, above which Ethereum could rise toward $2,000. Any more gains above the $2,000 resistance zone might send the price toward the $2,040 resistance. More Downsides in ETH? If Ethereum fails to clear the $1,855 resistance, it could continue to move down. Initial support on the downside is near the $1,820 level. The next major support is near the $1,800 level. If there is a break below the $1,800 support, the price could decline toward the $1,740 support. Any more losses may perhaps send the price toward the $1,700 level or even $1,660 in the coming sessions. Technical Indicators Hourly MACD – The MACD for ETH/USD is gaining momentum in the bearish zone. Hourly RSI &#8211; The RSI for ETH/USD is below the 50 level. Major Support Level – $1,800 Major Resistance Level – $1,900]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>Ethereum price is moving lower from the $1,900 resistance against the US Dollar. ETH could decline heavily if there is a clear move below the $1,800 support.</em></p>
<ul>
<li>Ethereum is still struggling to clear the $1,900 and $1,920 resistance levels.</li>
<li>The price is trading below $1,880 and the 100-hourly Simple Moving Average.</li>
<li>There is a major bearish trend line forming with resistance near $1,855 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD (data feed via Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could still struggle to clear the $1,900 resistance zone.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Ethereum Price Dips Again</h2>
<p>Ethereum’s price started a <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-strength-1840/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">fresh increase</a> from the $1,775 zone. ETH climbed above the $1,850 resistance but the bears were again active near the $1,900 zone, similar to <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-could-increase-26600/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Bitcoin</a>.</p>
<p>A high is formed near $1,898 and the price is now moving lower. There was a break below the $1,850 support zone. The bears pushed the price below the 50% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $1,777 swing low to the $1,898 high.</p>
<p>Ether is now trading below $1,880 and the 100-hourly Simple Moving Average. There is also a major bearish trend line forming with resistance near $1,855 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD.</p>
<p>It is now holding the $1,820 support and the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $1,777 swing low to the $1,898 high. Immediate resistance is near the $1,855 zone and the trend line. The next major resistance is near the $1,900 level or the recent high.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-536960" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Ethereum-5.png" alt="Ethereum Price" width="1950" height="1109" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Ethereum-5.png 1950w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Ethereum-5-460x262.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Ethereum-5-860x489.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Ethereum-5-768x437.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Ethereum-5-1536x874.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Ethereum-5-750x427.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Ethereum-5-1140x648.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1950px) 100vw, 1950px"/></p>
<p>Source: <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/ETHUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">ETHUSD on TradingView.com</a></p>
<p>A proper move above the $1,895 and $1,900 resistance levels might send Ether toward $1,920. The next resistance sits near $1,950, above which Ethereum could rise toward $2,000. Any more gains above the $2,000 resistance zone might send the price toward the $2,040 resistance.</p>
<h2>More Downsides in ETH?</h2>
<p>If Ethereum fails to clear the $1,855 resistance, it could continue to move down. Initial support on the downside is near the $1,820 level.</p>
<p>The next major support is near the $1,800 level. If there is a break below the $1,800 support, the price could decline toward the $1,740 support. Any more losses may perhaps send the price toward the $1,700 level or even $1,660 in the coming sessions.</p>
<p>Technical Indicators</p>
<p>Hourly MACD<strong> – </strong>The MACD for ETH/USD is gaining momentum in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>Hourly RSI<strong> &#8211; </strong>The RSI for ETH/USD is below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Level – $1,800</p>
<p>Major Resistance Level – $1,900</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/shutterstock_146143109-460x315.jpg" width="460" height="315" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Price Could Restart Increase If It Clears This Resistance</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-could-increase-26600/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 02:17:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xbtusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=536956</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin price is correcting lower from the $27,400 resistance. BTC could start a fresh increase if it is able to clear the $26,600 resistance zone. Bitcoin started a fresh decline after it failed to clear the $27,400 resistance. The price is trading below $26,600 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average. There is a key declining channel forming with resistance near $26,580 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Kraken). The pair could attempt a fresh increase if it clears the $26,580 and $26,600 levels. Bitcoin Price Holds Support Bitcoin price was able to climb back above the $27,000 level. BTC even climbed above $27,200 before the bears appeared near the $27,400 zone. A high was formed near $27,368 before the price started a fresh decline. There was a move below the $27,000 support zone. The price declined below the 50% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $25,368 swing low to the $27,368 high. Bitcoin price is now trading below $26,600 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average. There is also a key declining channel forming with resistance near $26,580 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair. However, it is holding the $26,200 support and the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $25,368 swing low to the $27,368 high. Immediate resistance is near the $26,580 level and the channel zone. The next major resistance is near the $26,600 level. A close above $26,600 might send the price further higher. Source: BTCUSD on TradingView.com The next key resistance is near the $27,000 level. A clear move above the $27,000 resistance might call for a move toward the $27,400 resistance. Any more gains above the $27,400 resistance zone might send the price toward the $28,500 resistance zone. More Losses in BTC? If Bitcoin’s price fails to clear the $26,600 resistance, it could continue to move down. another decline. Immediate support on the downside is near the $26,200 level. The next major support is near the $25,840 level, below which the price might gain bearish momentum. In the stated case, the price could drop toward the $25,400 support. Technical indicators: Hourly MACD – The MACD is now gaining pace in the bearish zone. Hourly RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BTC/USD is below the 50 level. Major Support Levels – $26,200, followed by $25,840. Major Resistance Levels – $26,600, $27,000, and $27,400.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>Bitcoin price is correcting lower from the $27,400 resistance. BTC could start a fresh increase if it is able to clear the $26,600 resistance zone.</em></p>
<ul>
<li>Bitcoin started a fresh decline after it failed to clear the $27,400 resistance.</li>
<li>The price is trading below $26,600 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average.</li>
<li>There is a key declining channel forming with resistance near $26,580 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could attempt a fresh increase if it clears the $26,580 and $26,600 levels.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Bitcoin Price Holds Support</h2>
<p>Bitcoin price was able to climb back above the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-trims-losses-27400/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">$27,000 level</a>. BTC even climbed above $27,200 before the bears appeared near the $27,400 zone.</p>
<p>A high was formed near $27,368 before the price started a fresh decline. There was a move below the $27,000 support zone. The price declined below the 50% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $25,368 swing low to the $27,368 high.</p>
<p>Bitcoin price is now trading below $26,600 and the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-nosedives-25k/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">100 hourly Simple moving average</a>. There is also a key declining channel forming with resistance near $26,580 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair.</p>
<p>However, it is holding the $26,200 support and the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $25,368 swing low to the $27,368 high. Immediate resistance is near the $26,580 level and the channel zone. The next major resistance is near the $26,600 level. A close above $26,600 might send the price further higher.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-536957" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-5.png" alt="Bitcoin Price" width="1950" height="1109" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-5.png 1950w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-5-460x262.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-5-860x489.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-5-768x437.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-5-1536x874.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-5-750x427.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-5-1140x648.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1950px) 100vw, 1950px"/></p>
<p>Source: <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BTCUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">BTCUSD on TradingView.com</a></p>
<p>The next key resistance is near the $27,000 level. A clear move above the $27,000 resistance might call for a move toward the $27,400 resistance. Any more gains above the $27,400 resistance zone might send the price toward the $28,500 resistance zone.</p>
<h2>More Losses in BTC?</h2>
<p>If Bitcoin’s price fails to clear the $26,600 resistance, it could continue to move down. another decline. Immediate support on the downside is near the $26,200 level.</p>
<p>The next major support is near the $25,840 level, below which the price might gain bearish momentum. In the stated case, the price could drop toward the $25,400 support.</p>
<p>Technical indicators:</p>
<p>Hourly MACD – The MACD is now gaining pace in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>Hourly RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BTC/USD is below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Levels – $26,200, followed by $25,840.</p>
<p>Major Resistance Levels – $26,600, $27,000, and $27,400.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/shutterstock_1182580207-460x259.jpg" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance Coin (BNB) At Risk: $200 Million Liquidation Looms</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/bnb/binance-coin-bnb-at-risk-200-million-liquidation-looms/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 02:00:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BNB]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance Coin (BNB)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bnbusdt]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=536946</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Binance Coin (BNB) has been one of the top-performing cryptocurrencies in recent years, with its value rising significantly since its launch in 2017. However, the coin has experienced a sharp decline in value following the recent Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) complaint against Binance.US and increased regulatory oversight by the US watchdog. Currently, BNB is trading at $260, down by over 7% and 14% in 24 hours and the last seven days, respectively. This drop has been attributed to the recent regulatory scrutiny, as well as broader market trends. Related Reading: Bitcoin 24-Hour Volatility Soars, Why Bulls Could Win Fight In Short-Term BNB Price Drop Spells Trouble The BNB bridge suffered an exploit that has put Binance Coin in a precarious position, with a potential liquidation of $200 million on Venus Decentralized Autonomous Organization (DAO) looming if the price drops by 14% to $220.  Venus DAO is a community-driven organization that governs the Venus Protocol, which is a decentralized lending and borrowing platform built on the Binance Smart Chain. The Venus Protocol allows users to borrow and lend cryptocurrencies, and earn interest on their holdings. According to the researcher DeFi Ignas, the exploit occurred on October 7th, 2022, when an attacker minted 2 million BNB ($593 million)) and deposited 900,000 BNB as collateral to Venus. They then borrowed other assets on Venus to launder as much money as possible. This is the single largest potential liquidation in all of Decentralized Finance (DeFi) and cannot be closed. Following the exploit, BNB Chain was halted to upgrade the network, and the Binance Bridge hack now ranks as the third-largest overall hack. All three of the top hacks have been cross-chain bridge exploits, highlighting the vulnerabilities of the DeFi ecosystem. According to Ignas, to prevent any cascading liquidations, the BNB Chain will liquidate the position itself. However, the good news is that Venus DAO has voted to whitelist BNB Chain as the sole liquidator of the BNB exploiter address. This move should help to prevent any further market disruptions and provide some stability to the market. Binance.US Netflow Plummets Blockchain and data research firm Nansen has reported that the net outflows from major cryptocurrency exchanges Binance and Coinbase have decreased in the 24 hours following the news of the SEC&#8217;s lawsuit against Coinbase. The outflows retraced to $491.9M and $105.3M, respectively. This is in contrast to the situation 24 hours after the SEC sued Binance when Binance&#8217;s netflow was $78M positive. However, after the SEC filed to seek a temporary restraining order to freeze Binance&#8217;s US assets, Binance&#8217;s netflow turned negative, dropping to -$123.6M. Related Reading: Late Evidence In Criminal Trial Irks SBF, FTX Explores Options For AI Stock Sale The decrease in net outflows from Binance and Coinbase suggests that investors are becoming more cautious in light of the SEC&#8217;s legal actions against major cryptocurrency exchanges. The SEC&#8217;s lawsuit against Coinbase, in particular, has raised concerns about the regulatory scrutiny faced by the crypto industry as a whole. Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com  &#160;]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Binance Coin (BNB) has been one of the top-performing cryptocurrencies in recent years, with its value rising significantly since its launch in 2017. However, the coin has experienced a sharp decline in value following the recent Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) complaint against Binance.US and increased regulatory oversight by the US watchdog.</p>
<p>Currently, BNB is trading at $260, down by over 7% and 14% in 24 hours and the last seven days, respectively. This drop has been attributed to the recent regulatory scrutiny, as well as broader market trends.</p>

<h2>BNB Price Drop Spells Trouble</h2>
<p>The BNB bridge suffered an exploit that has put Binance Coin in a precarious position, with a potential liquidation of $200 million on Venus Decentralized Autonomous Organization (DAO) looming if the price drops by 14% to $220. </p>
<p>Venus DAO is a community-driven organization that governs the Venus Protocol, which is a decentralized lending and borrowing platform built on the Binance Smart Chain. The Venus Protocol allows users to borrow and lend cryptocurrencies, and earn interest on their holdings.</p>
<p><a href="https://twitter.com/cuntycakes123/status/1666460036946698242?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">According </a>to the researcher DeFi Ignas, the exploit occurred on October 7th, 2022, when an attacker minted 2 million BNB ($593 million)) and deposited 900,000 BNB as collateral to Venus. They then borrowed other assets on Venus to launder as much money as possible. This is the single largest potential liquidation in all of Decentralized Finance (DeFi) and cannot be closed.</p>
<p>Following the exploit, BNB Chain was halted to upgrade the network, and the Binance Bridge hack now ranks as the third-largest overall hack. All three of the top hacks have been cross-chain bridge exploits, highlighting the vulnerabilities of the DeFi ecosystem.</p>
<p>According to Ignas, to prevent any cascading liquidations, the BNB Chain will liquidate the position itself. However, the good news is that Venus DAO has voted to whitelist BNB Chain as the sole liquidator of the BNB exploiter address. This move should help to prevent any further market disruptions and provide some stability to the market.</p>
Binance.US Netflow Plummets
<p>Blockchain and data research firm Nansen has <a href="https://twitter.com/nansen_ai/status/1666445566341947392?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">reported </a>that the net outflows from major cryptocurrency exchanges Binance and Coinbase have decreased in the 24 hours following the news of the SEC&#8217;s lawsuit against Coinbase. The outflows retraced to $491.9M and $105.3M, respectively.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large wp-image-536948" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/FyBnaCxWYAEiWwd-860x459.jpg" alt="BNB" width="860" height="459" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/FyBnaCxWYAEiWwd-860x459.jpg 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/FyBnaCxWYAEiWwd-460x245.jpg 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/FyBnaCxWYAEiWwd-768x410.jpg 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/FyBnaCxWYAEiWwd-1536x819.jpg 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/FyBnaCxWYAEiWwd-2048x1093.jpg 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/FyBnaCxWYAEiWwd-750x400.jpg 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/FyBnaCxWYAEiWwd-1140x608.jpg 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/>
<p>This is in contrast to the situation 24 hours after the SEC sued Binance when Binance&#8217;s netflow was $78M positive. However, after the SEC filed to seek a temporary restraining order to freeze Binance&#8217;s US assets, Binance&#8217;s netflow turned negative, dropping to -$123.6M.</p>

<p>The decrease in net outflows from Binance and Coinbase suggests that investors are becoming more cautious in light of the SEC&#8217;s legal actions against major cryptocurrency exchanges. The SEC&#8217;s lawsuit against Coinbase, in particular, has raised concerns about the regulatory scrutiny faced by the crypto industry as a whole.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/H8aqGYgN/" alt="BNB" width="1814" height="858"/>
<p>Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com </p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/bernd-dittrich-DT71hAJoIJM-unsplash-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Shiba Inu Breaks Below This Formation: Signals Potential Further Losses</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/shiba-inu-breaks-below-this-formation-signals-potential-further-losses/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[anushsamal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 01:00:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Shiba Inu]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIB]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIBUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIBUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=536882</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Shiba Inu (SHIB) has been experiencing a sustained downtrend, coinciding with the broader weakening of the market in recent times. In the past 24 hours, the meme-coin has seen a decline of nearly 4% on its chart. Looking at the weekly chart, SHIB has depreciated by 6%. The technical analysis of SHIB reflects a prevailing bearish sentiment, with a decrease in demand and accumulation observed on the chart. As Bitcoin has demonstrated high volatility, SHIB has struggled to surpass its immediate resistance level. Related Reading: Chainlink Bulls Must Uphold This Critical Support Line For Potential 8% Rally However, if Bitcoin manages to maintain its recovery following a significant price plunge, there is a possibility of SHIB making a price comeback. This would require a decline in selling pressure over the subsequent trading sessions. To further confirm the negative price action, SHIB has broken below a formation that indicates bearish strength in the market. The market capitalization of SHIB has declined, indicating low buying strength on the one-day chart. Shiba Inu Price Analysis: One-Day Chart At the time of writing, SHIB was trading at $0.0000080. However, the bulls encountered resistance at $0.0000083, leading to a continuation of the coin&#8217;s downtrend. The immediate overhead resistance for SHIB is located at $0.0000083, followed by another resistance level at $0.0000087. If the price manages to surpass the $0.0000087 mark, it could potentially approach the $0.0000090 resistance level. Conversely, if the price falls from its current level, it may drop below $0.0000079, and a further decline could bring SHIB to $0.0000074. Notably, SHIB had formed a symmetrical triangle pattern, and the recent price movement saw it breaking below the triangle, indicating a continuation of the bearish sentiment on the chart. Additionally, the trading volume of SHIB in the last session was low, suggesting a lack of buying strength in the market. Technical Analysis Throughout the month of May and the beginning of June, SHIB faced a decline in buyers&#8217; confidence, resulting in a decrease in demand for the altcoin. The Relative Strength Index (RSI) remained below the half-line, indicating that sellers held the upper hand in the market. Furthermore, SHIB moved below the 20-Simple Moving Average, which confirmed the downward price action and suggested that sellers were driving the price momentum in the market. In line with the technical indicators, SHIB displayed sell signals on the chart. The Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD), which indicates price momentum and shifts, formed red histograms associated with the sell signal for the coin. This suggested a bearish outlook for SHIB. Additionally, the Bollinger Bands, which indicate price volatility and the likelihood of price fluctuations, had previously narrowed down. Related Reading: Aave Extends Losses But Here Are The Short Selling Targets However, at the time of the press, the bands began to diverge, indicating a potential increase in price volatility in the upcoming trading sessions. Featured Image From UnSplash, Charts From TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Shiba Inu (SHIB) has been experiencing a sustained downtrend, coinciding with the broader weakening of the market in recent times. In the past 24 hours, the meme-coin has seen a decline of nearly 4% on its chart. Looking at the weekly chart, SHIB has depreciated by 6%.</p>
<p>The technical analysis of SHIB reflects a prevailing bearish sentiment, with a decrease in demand and accumulation observed on the chart. As Bitcoin has demonstrated high volatility, SHIB has struggled to surpass its immediate resistance level.</p>

<p>However, if Bitcoin manages to maintain its recovery following a significant price plunge, there is a possibility of SHIB making a price comeback. This would require a decline in selling pressure over the subsequent trading sessions.</p>
<p>To further confirm the negative price action, SHIB has broken below a formation that indicates bearish strength in the market. The market capitalization of SHIB has declined, indicating low buying strength on the one-day chart.</p>
<h2>Shiba Inu Price Analysis: One-Day Chart</h2>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-536940 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/SHIBUSD_2023-06-07_18-47-35.png" alt="Shiba Inu" width="1817" height="830" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/SHIBUSD_2023-06-07_18-47-35.png 1817w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/SHIBUSD_2023-06-07_18-47-35-460x210.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/SHIBUSD_2023-06-07_18-47-35-860x393.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/SHIBUSD_2023-06-07_18-47-35-768x351.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/SHIBUSD_2023-06-07_18-47-35-1536x702.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/SHIBUSD_2023-06-07_18-47-35-750x343.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/SHIBUSD_2023-06-07_18-47-35-1140x521.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1817px) 100vw, 1817px"/>
<p>At the time of writing, SHIB was trading at $0.0000080. However, the bulls encountered resistance at $0.0000083, leading to a continuation of the coin&#8217;s downtrend. The immediate overhead resistance for SHIB is located at $0.0000083, followed by another resistance level at $0.0000087.</p>
<p>If the price manages to surpass the $0.0000087 mark, it could potentially approach the $0.0000090 resistance level. Conversely, if the price falls from its current level, it may drop below $0.0000079, and a further decline could bring SHIB to $0.0000074.</p>
<p>Notably, SHIB had formed a symmetrical triangle pattern, and the recent price movement saw it breaking below the triangle, indicating a continuation of the bearish sentiment on the chart. Additionally, the trading volume of SHIB in the last session was low, suggesting a lack of buying strength in the market.</p>
<h2>Technical Analysis</h2>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-536941 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/SHIBUSD_2023-06-07_18-48-08.png" alt="Shiba Inu" width="1817" height="743" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/SHIBUSD_2023-06-07_18-48-08.png 1817w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/SHIBUSD_2023-06-07_18-48-08-460x188.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/SHIBUSD_2023-06-07_18-48-08-860x352.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/SHIBUSD_2023-06-07_18-48-08-768x314.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/SHIBUSD_2023-06-07_18-48-08-1536x628.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/SHIBUSD_2023-06-07_18-48-08-750x307.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/SHIBUSD_2023-06-07_18-48-08-1140x466.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1817px) 100vw, 1817px"/>
<p>Throughout the month of May and the beginning of June, SHIB faced a decline in buyers&#8217; confidence, resulting in a decrease in demand for the altcoin.</p>
<p>The Relative Strength Index (RSI) remained below the half-line, indicating that sellers held the upper hand in the market.</p>
<p>Furthermore, SHIB moved below the 20-Simple Moving Average, which confirmed the downward price action and suggested that sellers were driving the price momentum in the market.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-536942 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/SHIBUSD_2023-06-07_18-48-45.png" alt="Shiba Inu" width="1817" height="743" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/SHIBUSD_2023-06-07_18-48-45.png 1817w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/SHIBUSD_2023-06-07_18-48-45-460x188.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/SHIBUSD_2023-06-07_18-48-45-860x352.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/SHIBUSD_2023-06-07_18-48-45-768x314.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/SHIBUSD_2023-06-07_18-48-45-1536x628.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/SHIBUSD_2023-06-07_18-48-45-750x307.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/SHIBUSD_2023-06-07_18-48-45-1140x466.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1817px) 100vw, 1817px"/>










<p>In line with the technical indicators, SHIB displayed sell signals on the chart. The Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD), which indicates price momentum and shifts, formed red histograms associated with the sell signal for the coin.</p>
<p>This suggested a bearish outlook for SHIB. Additionally, the Bollinger Bands, which indicate price volatility and the likelihood of price fluctuations, had previously narrowed down.</p>

<p>However, at the time of the press, the bands began to diverge, indicating a potential increase in price volatility in the upcoming trading sessions.</p>











]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/traxer-YcN2FTnpEec-unsplash-1-460x306.jpg" width="460" height="306" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Retests Moving Average That Marked All Major Market Bottoms</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-retests-moving-average-that-marked-all-major-market-bottoms/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tony "The Bull"]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 00:03:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xbt]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=536914</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin price is falling, crypto is crumbling, and the United States SEC appears to be out for blood. But before a bloodbath occurs across the digital asset market, the top cryptocurrency by market cap is making a stand at a key level. In fact, BTCUSD is retesting an important moving average that in the past marked ever single major bear market bottom. Take a look below. Bitcoin retests the 200-week moving average &#124; BTCUSD on TradingView.com SEC Onslaught Brings Bitcoin Down Against The 200-Week Moving Average The cryptocurrency market is on the ropes, quite literally. On weekly timeframes, BTCUSD has touched back down on the 200-week moving average. The pullback comes in the wake of a string of SEC-made charges against top crypto exchanges this week. Both Binance and Coinbase have been caught in the crosshairs. Related Reading: Bitcoin Weekly Momentum Crosses Bearish For First Time In 2023 Although the onslaught mostly focused on altcoins which are now deemed securities, the sell pressure has been able to cut Bitcoin down a few notches. But it is holding on for dear life. The 200-week moving average makes for an ideal location for a bounce, as this is where Bitcoin has put in a bear market bottom in the past. The line must hold for Bitcoin bulls &#124; BTCUSD on TradingView.com Why It&#8217;s Critical For BTCUSD To Hold For Renewed Confidence In Crypto Upon zooming out, we can see that a major bottom was put in when BTCUSD touched the line several times in 2015. It served as the bottom bounce yet again in 2018, and one more time in 2020 after the COVID crash. Considering its track record of success, it was especially shocking to see the moving average lost in 2022 following the LUNA collapse. Bitcoin then spent a cumulative 36 weeks below the long-term span. When the US banking sector began to fall apart in March 2022, BTCUSD rocketed above the line for the first time since losing it. Related Reading: Rare Crypto Signal Emerges That Could Spark Another 2017-Style Boom Now, it finds itself back there, even piercing the ever-critical line. Support is holding at the moment and the weekly is currently forming a hammer – a potential bullish reversal candlestick pattern. It is far too early to tell, however, considering there are still several days left before the weekly candle closes. If Bitcoin can hold above the 200-week moving average, it could tell the market that the bottom is in and finally lead to some renewed confidence in the crypto market. Losing the line again would be unprecedented, but then again, few thought it would be lost in 2022. Tony is the author of the CoinChartist (VIP) newsletter. Follow @TonyTheBullBTC &#38; @coinchartist_io on Twitter. Or join the TonyTradesBTC Telegram for daily market insights and technical analysis education. Please note: Content is educational and should not be considered investment advice. Featured image from iStockPhoto, Charts from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin price is falling, crypto is crumbling, and the United States SEC <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/polygon-matic-large-transactions-explode-742-amid-latest-sec-attack/">appears to be out for blood</a>. But before a bloodbath occurs across the digital asset market, the top cryptocurrency by market cap is making a stand at a key level.</p>
<p>In fact, BTCUSD is retesting an important moving average that in the past marked ever single major bear market bottom. Take a look below.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large wp-image-536919 aligncenter" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSD_2023-06-07_12-04-05-860x470.png" alt="BTCUSD_2023-06-07_12-04-05" width="860" height="470" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSD_2023-06-07_12-04-05-860x470.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSD_2023-06-07_12-04-05-460x251.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSD_2023-06-07_12-04-05-768x419.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSD_2023-06-07_12-04-05-1536x839.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSD_2023-06-07_12-04-05-2048x1118.png 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSD_2023-06-07_12-04-05-750x409.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSD_2023-06-07_12-04-05-1140x622.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/></p>

<h2>SEC Onslaught Brings Bitcoin Down Against The 200-Week Moving Average</h2>
<p>The cryptocurrency market is on the ropes, quite literally. On weekly timeframes, BTCUSD has touched back down on the 200-week moving average. The pullback comes in the wake of a string of SEC-made charges against top crypto exchanges this week. Both Binance and Coinbase have been caught in the crosshairs.</p>

<p>Although the onslaught mostly focused on altcoins which are now deemed securities, the sell pressure has been able to cut Bitcoin down a few notches. But it is holding on for dear life.</p>
<p>The 200-week moving average makes for an ideal location for a bounce, as this is where Bitcoin has put in a bear market bottom in the past.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large wp-image-536918 aligncenter" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSD_2023-06-07_12-03-44-860x493.png" alt="BTCUSD_2023-06-07_12-03-44" width="860" height="493" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSD_2023-06-07_12-03-44-860x493.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSD_2023-06-07_12-03-44-460x264.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSD_2023-06-07_12-03-44-768x441.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSD_2023-06-07_12-03-44-1536x881.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSD_2023-06-07_12-03-44-2048x1175.png 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSD_2023-06-07_12-03-44-750x430.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSD_2023-06-07_12-03-44-1140x654.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/></p>

<h2>Why It&#8217;s Critical For BTCUSD To Hold For Renewed Confidence In Crypto</h2>
<p>Upon zooming out, we can see that a major bottom was put in when BTCUSD touched the line several times in 2015. It served as the bottom bounce yet again in 2018, and one more time in 2020 after the COVID crash.</p>
<p>Considering its track record of success, it was especially shocking to see the moving average lost in 2022 following the LUNA collapse. Bitcoin then spent a cumulative 36 weeks below the long-term span. When the US banking sector began to fall apart in March 2022, BTCUSD rocketed above the line for the first time since losing it.</p>

<p>Now, it finds itself back there, even piercing the ever-critical line. Support is holding at the moment and the weekly is currently forming a hammer – a potential bullish reversal candlestick pattern. It is far too early to tell, however, considering there are still several days left before the weekly candle closes.</p>
<p>If Bitcoin can hold above the 200-week moving average, it could tell the market that the bottom is in and finally lead to some renewed confidence in the crypto market. Losing the line again would be unprecedented, but then again, few thought it would be lost in 2022.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/iStock-1308820789-460x250.jpg" width="460" height="250" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cardano (ADA) Declines As Market Recovers Amid Security Charges</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/cardano/cardano-ada-declines-as-market-recovers-amid-security-charges/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Best Owie]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 23:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cardano]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADA price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[adausd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADAUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano Foundation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=536840</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Cardano (ADA) has emerged as one of the worst performers over the last day despite the rest of the market seeing some upside. This can be attributed to the security charges from the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), a classification that has loomed heavy over staking tokens in the last year. Cardano Foundation Deny Security Claims In the SEC lawsuits that have circulated against crypto exchanges such as Binance and Coinbase this week, the SEC has pointed to some cryptocurrencies as being securities in a bid to nail the exchanges for unregistered securities trading. Related Reading: Not Immune To FUD? Binance Sees $1.5 Billion In Outflows In 24 Hours One of the cryptocurrencies that were named is Cardano, a network that uses a proof of stake mechanism where users stake their native token, ADA, to help secure the network, and earn rewards for it. ADA was named among a list of other tokens including MATIC, BUSD, BNB, FIL, SOL, SAND, ATOM, MANA, COTI, AXS, and ALGO. And despite this already long list, the SEC seems to believe more tokens qualify as securities given the wording of “including but not limited to.” In light of this recent classification by the SEC, the Cardano Foundation has come forward to contest the regulator’s claims. In a tweet on its official page, the foundation expressed its disagreement with this classification and said it looked forward to working with regulators. “The Cardano Foundation disagrees with the recent qualification of ADA as a security under US law. We look forward to the continued engagement with regulators and policymakers to achieve legal clarity and certainty on these matters,” the Foundation said. ADA price falls to $0.33 &#124; Source: ADAUSD on TradingView.com ADA Continues To Struggle Despite the Cardano Foundation taking to Twitter to debunk the SEC’s claims of ADA being a security, the coin has not fared well in the market. While the general market is on a recovery trend with Bitcoin moving back above $26,000, ADA has remained stagnant. Out of the top 10 largest cryptocurrencies by market cap, ADA is currently the worst performer of the bunch. Where Bitcoin and Ethereum are seeing an upside of around 3% at this time, Cardano’s token is nursing 3.6% losses. Its performance is even worse on the weekly chart with 9% losses in seven days. Related Reading: Galaxy Digital CEO Mike Novogratz Says This Will Kickstart The Bitcoin Bull Market ADA’s performance is not out of the ordinary as such a classification has put selling pressure on the digital asset. Investors are understandably moving to remove some of their holdings for fear of further legal action from the SEC. However, there has been no indication of what the regulator plans to do against the digital assets it classified as securities. At the time of writing, ADA is changing hands at a price of $0.3406, bringing its total market cap to $11.89 billion. Follow Best Owie on Twitter for market insights, updates, and the occasional funny tweet… Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="p2">Cardano (ADA) has emerged as one of the worst performers over the last day despite the rest of the market seeing some upside. This can be attributed to the security charges from the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), a classification that has loomed heavy over staking tokens in the last year.</p>
<h2 class="p2">Cardano Foundation Deny Security Claims</h2>
<p class="p2">In the SEC <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/sec-sues-binance-and-ceo-for-securities-fraud/" rel="nofollow">lawsuits</a> that have circulated against crypto exchanges such as Binance and Coinbase this week, the SEC has pointed to some cryptocurrencies as being securities in a bid to nail the exchanges for unregistered securities trading.</p>

<p class="p2">One of the cryptocurrencies that were named is Cardano, a network that uses a proof of stake mechanism where users stake their native token, ADA, to help secure the network, and earn rewards for it. ADA was named among a list of other tokens including MATIC, BUSD, BNB, FIL, SOL, SAND, ATOM, MANA, COTI, AXS, and ALGO. And despite this already long list, the SEC seems to believe more tokens qualify as securities given the wording of “including but not limited to.”</p>
<p class="p2">In light of this recent classification by the SEC, the Cardano Foundation has come forward to contest the regulator’s claims. In a <a href="https://twitter.com/Cardano_CF/status/1666128229952897024?s=20" rel="nofollow">tweet</a> on its official page, the foundation expressed its disagreement with this classification and said it looked forward to working with regulators.</p>
<p class="p2">“The Cardano Foundation disagrees with the recent qualification of ADA as a security under US law. We look forward to the continued engagement with regulators and policymakers to achieve legal clarity and certainty on these matters,” the Foundation said.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/LkiBYuhs/" alt="Cardano (ADA) price chart from TradingView.com" width="2882" height="1724"/></p>

<h2 class="p2">ADA Continues To Struggle</h2>
<p class="p2">Despite the Cardano Foundation taking to Twitter to debunk the SEC’s claims of ADA being a security, the coin has not fared well in the market. While the general market is on a recovery trend with Bitcoin moving back above $26,000, ADA has remained stagnant.</p>
<p class="p2">Out of the top 10 largest cryptocurrencies by market cap, ADA is currently the worst performer of the bunch. Where Bitcoin and Ethereum are seeing an upside of around 3% at this time, Cardano’s token is nursing 3.6% losses. Its performance is even worse on the weekly chart with 9% losses in seven days.</p>

<p class="p2">ADA’s performance is not out of the ordinary as such a classification has put selling pressure on the digital asset. Investors are understandably moving to remove some of their holdings for fear of further legal action from the SEC. However, there has been no indication of what the regulator plans to do against the digital assets it classified as securities.</p>
<p class="p2">At the time of writing, ADA is changing hands at a price of $0.3406, bringing its total market cap to $11.89 billion.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/iStock-1336958377-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Coinbase CEO Takes On SEC, Igniting Crypto Community&#8217;s Passion for Clarity</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/coinbase/coinbase-ceo-takes-on-sec-igniting-crypto-communitys-passion-for-clarity/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 22:00:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brian armstrong]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC Lawsuit]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=536934</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[In a fiery showdown, Coinbase CEO Brian Armstrong confronts the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) lawsuit, igniting a passionate response from the crypto community. His unwavering defense not only stirs enthusiasm among supporters but also intensifies demands for clear regulations in the industry. Armstrong has welcomed the SEC lawsuit against his exchange, stating that a court battle will help establish much-needed clarity around crypto rules and regulations.  “Regarding the SEC complaint against us today, we’re proud to represent the industry in court to finally get some clarity around crypto rules. We’ll get the job done. In the meantime, let’s all keep moving forward and building as an industry. America will get this right in the end,” the CEO said. Taking The SEC Head On Armstrong expressed unwavering confidence in Coinbase&#8217;s legal team and the facts surrounding cryptocurrencies and the law. In a tweet, he stated that representing the industry in court against the SEC was essential to obtain the long-awaited clarity in the crypto space.  Related Reading: Bitcoin Realized Loss Remains Low Despite Volatility, What Does This Mean? He further emphasized that Coinbase underwent a rigorous review process by the SEC when it became a public company in 2021 and highlighted the regulatory inconsistencies between the SEC and the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC). Coinbase CEO&#8217;s Defense Spurs Enthusiasm And Demands For Regulatory Clarity Armstrong’s unflinching confidence reverberates through the crypto space as he takes a stand against the SEC. The SEC&#8217;s lawsuit against Coinbase alleges a violation of securities laws, claiming that the exchange offered unregistered securities and operated as an unregistered security broker. The inclusion of prominent tokens like Polygon (MATIC), Cardano (ADA), and Solana (SOL) in the lawsuit further amplifies the anger within the community.  COIN recovers to $52 after Tuesday crash &#124; Source: Coinbase Global, Inc on TradingView.com However, crypto enthusiasts feel the weight of the SEC&#8217;s regulatory overreach, demanding fair treatment and a clear delineation between securities and commodities.  Coinbase&#8217;s relationship with the SEC has been marred by contention and frustration. The exchange has long called for transparent rules and guidelines from the SEC, seeking clarity on which digital assets should be classified as securities.  In response to the SEC&#8217;s lack of action, Coinbase previously filed a lawsuit, highlighting the need for regulatory guidance. Now, the battle intensifies as the SEC counters Coinbase&#8217;s plea for clarity with legal action, fueling the community&#8217;s determination to fight for a just and equitable regulatory framework. Related Reading: Late Evidence In Criminal Trial Irks SBF, FTX Explores Options For AI Stock Sale Coinbase’s stock COIN has suffered following the lawsuit, falling from $66 to $45 in one day before recovering above $52 where it is currently trading at the time of this writing. It is left to see where the lawsuit leads but the crypto market seems to have moved forward as prices have begun to recover with Bitcoin rising over 3% in the last 24 hours. Featured image from The Cryptocurrency Post, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In a fiery showdown, Coinbase CEO Brian Armstrong confronts the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) lawsuit, igniting a passionate response from the crypto community. His unwavering defense not only stirs enthusiasm among supporters but also intensifies demands for clear regulations in the industry.</p>
<p>Armstrong has welcomed the SEC lawsuit against his exchange, stating that a court battle will help establish much-needed clarity around crypto rules and regulations. </p>
<p>“Regarding the SEC complaint against us today, we’re proud to represent the industry in court to finally get some clarity around crypto rules. We’ll get the job done. In the meantime, let’s all keep moving forward and building as an industry. America will get this right in the end,” the CEO said.</p>
<h2>Taking The SEC Head On</h2>
<p>Armstrong expressed unwavering confidence in Coinbase&#8217;s legal team and the facts surrounding cryptocurrencies and the law. In a <a href="https://twitter.com/brian_armstrong/status/1666129111025324035?s=20" rel="nofollow">tweet</a>, he stated that representing the industry in court against the SEC was essential to obtain the long-awaited clarity in the crypto space. </p>

<p>He further emphasized that Coinbase underwent a rigorous review process by the SEC when it became a public company in 2021 and highlighted the regulatory inconsistencies between the SEC and the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC).</p>
<h2>Coinbase CEO&#8217;s Defense Spurs Enthusiasm And Demands For Regulatory Clarity</h2>
<p>Armstrong’s unflinching confidence reverberates through the crypto space as he takes a stand against the SEC. The SEC&#8217;s lawsuit against Coinbase alleges a violation of securities laws, claiming that the exchange offered unregistered securities and operated as an unregistered security broker. The inclusion of prominent tokens like Polygon (MATIC), Cardano (ADA), and Solana (SOL) in the lawsuit further amplifies the anger within the community. </p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/Cm8bXoRF/" alt="Coinbase (COIN) price chart from TradingView.com" width="2882" height="1724"/></p>

<p>However, crypto enthusiasts feel the weight of the SEC&#8217;s regulatory overreach, demanding fair treatment and a clear delineation between securities and commodities. </p>
<p>Coinbase&#8217;s relationship with the SEC has been marred by contention and frustration. The exchange has long called for transparent rules and guidelines from the SEC, seeking clarity on which digital assets should be classified as securities. </p>
<p>In response to the SEC&#8217;s lack of action, Coinbase previously filed a lawsuit, highlighting the need for regulatory guidance. Now, the battle intensifies as the SEC counters Coinbase&#8217;s plea for clarity with legal action, fueling the community&#8217;s determination to fight for a just and equitable regulatory framework.</p>

<p>Coinbase’s stock COIN has suffered following the lawsuit, falling from $66 to $45 in one day before recovering above $52 where it is currently trading at the time of this writing.</p>
<p>It is left to see where the lawsuit leads but the crypto market seems to have moved forward as prices have begun to recover with Bitcoin rising over 3% in the last 24 hours.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Coinbase-CEO-Brian-Armstrong-460x239.jpeg" width="460" height="239" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Bears Brace For The 50-Month MA Retest, Is A Rug Pull Imminent?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-bears-brace-for-the-50-month-ma-retest-is-a-rug-pull-imminent/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 21:00:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=536921</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Over the last 24 hours, Bitcoin (BTC), the largest cryptocurrency in the market by capitalization, has again failed to consolidate above the $27,000 level. This key resistance was lost at the beginning of the downtrend on May 8th and has not been breached. Additionally, the upper resistance level placed at $27,500 has also proven to be a challenge for BTC, as it has been unable to surpass it. According to the crypto analysis firm Material Indicators, the crypto market continues to be stimulated by the fear, uncertainty, and doubt (FUD) surrounding the industry. With thin bid liquidity, Bitcoin has been retesting the 200-Week Moving Average (MA).  Related Reading: LDO Leads Top Coins, Registers 6% Gains In One Day Bitcoin Faces Critical Test, Will The 200-Week MA Hold? According to Material Indicators, If the 200-Week MA does not hold, another retest of the 50-Month MA might be. Material Indicators suggest that if this happens, the liquidity and sentiment at the 50-Month MA will be stronger, potentially leading to a bullish market reversal. However, it is important to note that a &#8220;rug pull&#8221; at $25,000 &#8211; a sudden and significant drop in BTC&#8217;s price &#8211; could lead to a bearish market and further retest of the lower levels of $24,000 and $23,000. For the bulls, it is crucial to maintain control of the $27,000 level and push BTC&#8217;s price above the next significant resistance at $27,500. Doing so would allow the cryptocurrency to make another attempt at reaching the key psychological level of $30,000, which it has not achieved since April 19th. On the same note, according to Baro Virtual, a Crypto Quant author, the leverage ratio is overheating, potentially leading to a dip in BTC&#8217;s price to $24,000. The leverage ratio refers to the borrowed funds traders use to invest in BTC. When the leverage ratio increases, traders take on more debt to invest in the cryptocurrency. This can lead to a higher level of risk in the market, as a sudden drop in BTC&#8217;s price could trigger a significant amount of selling, resulting in a dip in price. BTC&#8217;s Bullish Engulfing Pattern Signals Buying Opportunities According to CJ, a cryptocurrency trader, there are several points that he is leaning into which could potentially provide opportunities for buying BTC. CJ notes that BTC has experienced a range of low deviation and reclaim and a daily bullish engulfing pattern. These indicators suggest that any dips into the FVG (fair value gap) are buying opportunities, with a target of $29,000-$30,000 liquidity. However, a close below $26,100 would be bearish for the cryptocurrency.  Bitcoin&#8217;s recent price movements have left traders and investors unsure of what to expect in the near term. While the cryptocurrency initially showed a bullish reaction to the fair value gap, with a bullish 4-hour candle, it is now retracing. It remains to be seen whether BTC can bounce back once again from its 200-week Moving Average or if a sudden and significant drop in price will push BTC into a new price regime and visit the lower levels.  Despite the uncertainty in the market, BTC is currently trading above key levels, and it needs to close above $26,000 to expect a further continuation of the uptrend. BTC&#8217;s gains in the past 24 hours have narrowed to only 0.8% after a recovery of 8% in the last few days. Related Reading: Bitcoin Realized Loss Remains Low Despite Volatility, What Does This Mean? Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Over the last 24 hours, Bitcoin (BTC), the largest cryptocurrency in the market by capitalization, has again failed to consolidate above the $27,000 level. This key resistance was lost at the beginning of the downtrend on May 8th and has not been breached. Additionally, the upper resistance level placed at $27,500 has also proven to be a challenge for BTC, as it has been unable to surpass it.</p>
<p><a href="https://twitter.com/MI_Algos/status/1666460487280738312?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">According </a>to the crypto analysis firm Material Indicators, the crypto market continues to be stimulated by the fear, uncertainty, and doubt (FUD) surrounding the industry. With thin bid liquidity, Bitcoin has been retesting the 200-Week Moving Average (MA). </p>

<h2>Bitcoin Faces Critical Test, Will The 200-Week MA Hold?</h2>
<p>According to Material Indicators, If the 200-Week MA does not hold, another retest of the 50-Month MA might be. Material Indicators suggest that if this happens, the liquidity and sentiment at the 50-Month MA will be stronger, potentially leading to a bullish market reversal.</p>
<p>However, it is important to note that a &#8220;rug pull&#8221; at $25,000 &#8211; a sudden and significant drop in BTC&#8217;s price &#8211; could lead to a bearish market and further retest of the lower levels of $24,000 and $23,000.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/HsfprxfA/" alt="Bitcoin " width="1813" height="858"/>
<p>For the bulls, it is crucial to maintain control of the $27,000 level and push BTC&#8217;s price above the next significant resistance at $27,500. Doing so would allow the cryptocurrency to make another attempt at reaching the key psychological level of $30,000, which it has not achieved since April 19th.</p>
<p>On the same note, <a href="https://twitter.com/BaroVirtual/status/1666399189205434370?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">according </a>to Baro Virtual, a Crypto Quant author, the leverage ratio is overheating, potentially leading to a dip in BTC&#8217;s price to $24,000.</p>
<p>The leverage ratio refers to the borrowed funds traders use to invest in BTC. When the leverage ratio increases, traders take on more debt to invest in the cryptocurrency. This can lead to a higher level of risk in the market, as a sudden drop in BTC&#8217;s price could trigger a significant amount of selling, resulting in a dip in price.</p>
BTC&#8217;s Bullish Engulfing Pattern Signals Buying Opportunities
<p><a href="https://twitter.com/irncrypt/status/1666458458843934722?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">According </a>to CJ, a cryptocurrency trader, there are several points that he is leaning into which could potentially provide opportunities for buying BTC.</p>
<p>CJ notes that BTC has experienced a range of low deviation and reclaim and a daily bullish engulfing pattern. These indicators suggest that any dips into the FVG (fair value gap) are buying opportunities, with a target of $29,000-$30,000 liquidity. However, a close below $26,100 would be bearish for the cryptocurrency. </p>
<p>Bitcoin&#8217;s recent price movements have left traders and investors unsure of what to expect in the near term. While the cryptocurrency initially showed a bullish reaction to the fair value gap, with a bullish 4-hour candle, it is now retracing.</p>
<p>It remains to be seen whether BTC can bounce back once again from its 200-week Moving Average or if a sudden and significant drop in price will push BTC into a new price regime and visit the lower levels. </p>
<p>Despite the uncertainty in the market, BTC is currently trading above key levels, and it needs to close above $26,000 to expect a further continuation of the uptrend. BTC&#8217;s gains in the past 24 hours have narrowed to only 0.8% after a recovery of 8% in the last few days.</p>

<p>Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/iStock-1316129074-460x251.jpg" width="460" height="251" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Shiba Inu (SHIB) Price Could Soar To Major Highs Soon, Here’s Why</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/shiba-inu-shib-price-could-soar-to-major-highs-soon-heres-why/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Edyme]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 20:00:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Shiba Inu]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[memecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIB]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shiba Inu (SHIB)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIBUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=536892</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Shiba Inu (SHIB) appears to be refueling its engines following a recent downturn. As the crypto community collectively holds its breath, the dog-inspired cryptocurrency could skyrocket to major highs sooner than expected. The latest catalyst propelling SHIB&#8217;s resurgence is a leap into the Metaverse. On June 6, the Shiba Inu Metaverse division unveiled its impending release of the long-awaited Rocket Pond trailer. As an integral part of Shiba&#8217;s virtual cosmos, the reveal of this trailer is set to enchant audiences with a peek into the Metaverse odyssey. The Dawn Of The SHIB Metaverse: Rocket Pond Since the unveiling of Rocket Pond&#8217;s initial sketch in September 2022, the SHIB community has been buzzing with anticipation. The release of the colored design offered users a preview of the Metaverse&#8217;s visual prowess, setting the stage for a reveal. Related Reading: Shiba Inu (SHIB) Poised For Significant Breakout: Here’s What To Watch Out For The SHIB Metaverse development squad amplified the excitement, taking to Twitter to tease their forthcoming release: We&#8217;re thrilled to announce that the trailer for Rocket Pond will be released tomorrow! We are so excited about the impressive progress the project has made, and this is just the beginning. Get ready to be amazed Rocket Pond is described as a secluded mountain retreat, infusing elements of quintessential camping experiences akin to YMCA or KOA, with modern attractions.  Rocket Pond To Soar SHIB&#8217;s Value The anticipated trailer showcases the narrative and design of Rocket Pond. This Metaverse hub is designed to provide users with an immersive experience. The charm of Rocket Pond draws its inspiration from picturesque locations such as Cape Canaveral, the Monument to the Conquerors of Space, Lake Tahoe, Glenwood Caverns Adventure Park, and Heavenly Village. The SHIB Metaverse merges nature with modern luxuries; particularly, Rocket Pond presents a unique offering. Notably, as this facet of the SHIB Metaverse continues to charm the community, it carries the potential to bolster the value and recognition of SHIB. The successful launch and adoption of Rocket Pond could fuel renewed interest and investment in Shiba Inu. This influx of attention could invariably lead to increased demand for SHIB, thereby providing upward pressure on its price. Related Reading: Shiba Inu Whale Accumulates 261 Billion Shib Tokens In Just Three Days With the confluence of factors, including the resurgence of SHIB and the rising popularity of Metaverses, Rocket Pond&#8217;s impact could send Shiba Inu (SHIB) soaring to new highs. Meanwhile, SHIB has been in the red over the past 7 days, down by 5.5%. Interestingly, despite the unveiling of the Rocket Pond trailer, the dog-inspired memecoin has recorded a continuous downtrend in the past 24 hours, down by 1.9% with a market price of $0.00000792. Featured image from Shutterstock, Chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w" dir="ltr">Shiba Inu (SHIB) appears to be refueling its engines following a recent downturn. As the crypto community collectively holds its breath, the dog-inspired cryptocurrency could skyrocket to major highs sooner than expected.</p>
<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w" dir="ltr">The latest catalyst propelling SHIB&#8217;s resurgence is a leap into the Metaverse. On June 6, the Shiba Inu Metaverse division <a href="https://twitter.com/mvshib/status/1666183768262967299?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">unveiled</a> its impending release of the long-awaited Rocket Pond trailer. </p>
<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w" dir="ltr">As an integral part of Shiba&#8217;s virtual cosmos, the reveal of this trailer is set to enchant audiences with a peek into the Metaverse odyssey.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">The Dawn Of The SHIB Metaverse: Rocket Pond</h2>
<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w" dir="ltr">Since the unveiling of Rocket Pond&#8217;s initial sketch in September 2022, the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/shiba-inu-investors-go-all-in/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">SHIB community</a> has been buzzing with anticipation. The release of the colored design offered users a preview of the Metaverse&#8217;s visual prowess, setting the stage for a reveal.</p>

<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w" dir="ltr">The SHIB Metaverse development squad amplified the excitement, taking to Twitter to tease their forthcoming release: </p>
<blockquote>
<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w" dir="ltr">We&#8217;re thrilled to announce that the trailer for Rocket Pond will be released tomorrow! We are so excited about the impressive progress the project has made, and this is just the beginning. Get ready to be amazed</p>
</blockquote>
<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w" dir="ltr">Rocket Pond is described as a secluded mountain retreat, infusing elements of quintessential camping experiences akin to YMCA or KOA, with modern attractions. </p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Rocket Pond To Soar SHIB&#8217;s Value</h2>
<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w" dir="ltr">The anticipated trailer showcases the narrative and design of Rocket Pond. This Metaverse hub is designed to provide users with an immersive experience.</p>
<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w" dir="ltr">The charm of Rocket Pond draws its inspiration from picturesque locations such as Cape Canaveral, the Monument to the Conquerors of Space, Lake Tahoe, Glenwood Caverns Adventure Park, and Heavenly Village. The SHIB Metaverse <a href="https://map.shib.io/#/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">merges</a> nature with modern luxuries; particularly, Rocket Pond presents a unique offering.</p>
<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w" dir="ltr">Notably, as this facet of the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/shiba-inu-burn-rate-surges-price-continues-in-red/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">SHIB</a> Metaverse continues to charm the community, it carries the potential to bolster the value and recognition of SHIB. The successful launch and adoption of Rocket Pond could fuel renewed interest and <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/shiba-inu-whale-accumulates-261-billion-shib-tokens-in-just-three-days/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">investment in Shiba Inu</a>. </p>
<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w" dir="ltr">This influx of attention could invariably lead to increased demand for SHIB, thereby providing upward pressure on its price.</p>

<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w" dir="ltr">With the confluence of factors, including the resurgence of SHIB and the rising popularity of Metaverses, Rocket Pond&#8217;s impact could send <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/shiba-inu-network-records-2538-new-addresses-in-a-day/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Shiba Inu (SHIB)</a> soaring to new highs. Meanwhile, SHIB has been in the red over the past 7 days, down by 5.5%.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/36fIebSg/" alt="Shiba Inu (SHIB) price chart on TradingView" width="2768" height="1556"/>
<p dir="ltr">Interestingly, despite the unveiling of the Rocket Pond trailer, the dog-inspired memecoin has recorded a continuous downtrend in the past 24 hours, down by 1.9% with a market price of $0.00000792.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Featured image from Shutterstock, Chart from TradingView</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/SHIB-Shibarium.jpg" width="350" height="250" />	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
