<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"

	xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
	xmlns:geo="http://www.w3.org/2003/01/geo/wgs84_pos#"
	>

<channel>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.newsbtc.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<description>Bitcoin &#38; Cryptocurrency News Today</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 03:54:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-cropped-favicon.png?fit=32%2C32</url>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
<site xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">221170450</site>	<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Price Key Indicators Suggest A Strong Case For More Losses</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-losses-29000/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 03:54:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xbtusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=547427</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin price moving lower below the $29,500 zone. BTC remains at risk of more downsides below the $29,000 support zone. Bitcoin is still trading well below the $29,650 resistance zone. The price is trading below $29,300 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average. There is a connecting bearish trend line forming with resistance near $29,250 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Kraken). The pair could continue to move down and break the $29,000 support zone. Bitcoin Price Turns Red Bitcoin price failed to start a recovery wave above the $29,500 resistance zone. BTC started another decline from the $29,450 swing high. There was a clear move below the $29,250 level. The price retested the $29,100 support zone. A low is formed near $29,075 and the price is now consolidating losses. It is trading above the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the recent decline from the $29,450 swing high to the $29,075 low. Bitcoin is now trading below $29,300 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average. There is also a connecting bearish trend line forming with resistance near $29,250 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair. Immediate resistance is near the $29,250 level and the trend line. It is close to the 50% Fib retracement level of the recent decline from the $29,450 swing high to the $29,075 low. The next major resistance is near $29,360 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average. Source: BTCUSD on TradingView.com The first major resistance is now forming near the $29,500 level. The main resistance is still near $29,650. A close above the $29,650 resistance could start a decent increase toward the $30,000 resistance zone. Any more gains might set the pace for a larger increase toward $30,500. More Losses In BTC? If Bitcoin fails to clear the $29,360 resistance, it could continue to move down. Immediate support on the downside is near the $29,100 zone. The next major support is near the $29,000 level. A downside break below the $29,000 level might start another steady decline. In the stated case, the price could drop toward $28,400. Technical indicators: Hourly MACD – The MACD is now gaining pace in the bearish zone. Hourly RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BTC/USD is now below the 50 level. Major Support Levels – $29,100, followed by $29,000. Major Resistance Levels – $29,250, $29,360, and $29,500.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>Bitcoin price moving lower below the $29,500 zone. BTC remains at risk of more downsides below the $29,000 support zone.</em></p>
<ul>
<li>Bitcoin is still trading well below the $29,650 resistance zone.</li>
<li>The price is trading below $29,300 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average.</li>
<li>There is a connecting bearish trend line forming with resistance near $29,250 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could continue to move down and break the $29,000 support zone.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Bitcoin Price Turns Red</h2>
<p>Bitcoin price failed to start a recovery wave above the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-muted-29650/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">$29,500 resistance zone</a>. BTC started another decline from the $29,450 swing high. There was a clear move below the $29,250 level.</p>
<p>The price retested the $29,100 support zone. A low is formed near $29,075 and the price is now consolidating losses. It is trading above the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the recent decline from the $29,450 swing high to the $29,075 low.</p>
<p>Bitcoin is now trading below $29,300 and the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-grinds-lower-29k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">100 hourly Simple moving average</a>. There is also a connecting bearish trend line forming with resistance near $29,250 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair.</p>
<p>Immediate resistance is near the $29,250 level and the trend line. It is close to the 50% Fib retracement level of the recent decline from the $29,450 swing high to the $29,075 low. The next major resistance is near $29,360 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" fetchpriority="high" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-547428" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-8.png?resize=1024%2C468" alt="Bitcoin Price" width="1024" height="468" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-8.png?resize=1024%2C468?w=1835 1835w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-8.png?resize=1024%2C468?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-8.png?resize=1024%2C468?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-8.png?resize=1024%2C468?w=860 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-8.png?resize=1024%2C468?w=1536 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-8.png?resize=1024%2C468?w=750 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-8.png?resize=1024%2C468?w=1140 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" loading="lazy" data-recalc-dims="1"/></p>
<p>Source: <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BTCUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">BTCUSD on TradingView.com</a></p>
<p>The first major resistance is now forming near the $29,500 level. The main resistance is still near $29,650. A close above the $29,650 resistance could start a decent increase toward the $30,000 resistance zone. Any more gains might set the pace for a larger increase toward $30,500.</p>
<h2>More Losses In BTC?</h2>
<p>If Bitcoin fails to clear the $29,360 resistance, it could continue to move down. Immediate support on the downside is near the $29,100 zone.</p>
<p>The next major support is near the $29,000 level. A downside break below the $29,000 level might start another steady decline. In the stated case, the price could drop toward $28,400.</p>
<p>Technical indicators:</p>
<p>Hourly MACD – The MACD is now gaining pace in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>Hourly RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BTC/USD is now below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Levels – $29,100, followed by $29,000.</p>
<p>Major Resistance Levels – $29,250, $29,360, and $29,500.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/04/shutterstock_649342378.jpg?fit=460%2C307" width="460" height="307" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">547427</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>This Dreaded Candlestick Formation Just Printed: Bitcoin To $18k?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/this-dreaded-candlestick-formation-just-printed-bitcoin-to-18k/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dalmas Ngetich]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 00:00:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin bulls]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[halving]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Head-and-Shoulder formation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[inflation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=547410</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin, the most valuable crypto asset, is at a critical juncture at spot rates if candlestick formation in the weekly chart is anything to go by. One analyst on X, formerly Twitter and NewsBTC Editorial Director Tony Spilotro, is sounding the alarm after picking out the bearish head-and-shoulder pattern in the weekly chart.  Will Bitcoin Crack? Although the pattern is technically in the last phase of formation, if realized, it could have dire implications for Bitcoin bulls as it may push prices below a multi-month critical support line toward $18,000 or lower in the weeks ahead. Even so, the volatile nature of crypto and BTC prices means traders should adopt a wait-and-see approach until it prints out. Related Reading: The Subtle Signs A Bullish Bitcoin Trend Is Brewing As of August 15, Bitcoin is stable and within a broader uptrend from a top-down perspective. Notably, the coin is confined within the trading range established between June and July 2023, as visible in the daily chart. Despite the general optimism of a price recovery above July 2023 highs, BTC was moving sideways and held above the $28,000 support level but below the $31,800 printed in the last days of H1 2023. Any breakout above $32,000 with expanding volumes might induce demand, forming an anchor for price gains toward $35,000 or better. While the inability of sellers to drive prices lower is bullish, at least from where buyers sit, the potential formation of the head and shoulder pattern in the weekly chart casts a shadow of doubt over bullish prospects. Subsequently, traders remain cautiously optimistic since the candlestick arrangement, particularly in the weekly timeframe, suggests a vulnerability that could affect market sentiment and hopes for sustained growth. Rate Hikes And Halving: Which Will Be A Stronger Influence? Several fundamental factors further complicate the outlook for Bitcoin&#8217;s price in the coming days. Inflation is relatively high in the United States (versus the benchmark rate of 2%), which may prompt the Federal Reserve to resume interest rate hikes in the third and fourth quarters of the year.  Despite relatively stable labor conditions and somewhat subdued inflation, the Fed&#8217;s recent rate hikes, now at the 5.25%-5.50% range, underscore the central bank&#8217;s commitment to curbing inflation and maintaining economic stability. Related Reading: This Event Causes Bitcoin Traders’ Sentiment To Rise, Will BTC Surpass $30,000? The potential impact of the Federal Reserve&#8217;s tightening policy on crypto is reminiscent of the events in 2022 when Bitcoin cracked, falling from 2021 peaks to below $16,000 in late 2022. While Bitcoin&#8217;s potential to serve as a store of value, akin to gold, during times of crisis can be a possibility in 2023 and the future, analysts still view it as a &#8220;risky&#8221; asset. From a bullish lens, Bitcoin will halve its miner rewards from 6.25 BTC in 2024. This reduction may cause a supply shock, making BTC scarcer, and may support prices in the second half of next year.  Feature image from Canva, chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin, the most valuable crypto asset, is at a critical juncture at spot rates if candlestick formation in the weekly chart is anything to go by. One analyst on X, formerly Twitter and NewsBTC Editorial Director Tony Spilotro, is <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://twitter.com/tonythebullBTC/status/1691428467185696768" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">sounding the alarm</a> after picking out the bearish head-and-shoulder pattern in the weekly chart. </p>
<h2>Will Bitcoin Crack?</h2>
<p>Although the pattern is technically in the last phase of formation, if realized, it could have dire implications for Bitcoin bulls as it may push prices below a multi-month critical support line toward $18,000 or lower in the weeks ahead. Even so, the volatile nature of crypto and BTC prices means traders should adopt a wait-and-see approach until it prints out.</p>
<img decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-547423" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-Head-and-Shoulder-Formation-in-Weekly-Chart.jpeg?resize=1024%2C637" alt="Bitcoin Head and Shoulder Formation in Weekly Chart| TradingView" width="1024" height="637" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-Head-and-Shoulder-Formation-in-Weekly-Chart.jpeg?resize=1024%2C637?w=2048 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-Head-and-Shoulder-Formation-in-Weekly-Chart.jpeg?resize=1024%2C637?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-Head-and-Shoulder-Formation-in-Weekly-Chart.jpeg?resize=1024%2C637?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-Head-and-Shoulder-Formation-in-Weekly-Chart.jpeg?resize=1024%2C637?w=860 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-Head-and-Shoulder-Formation-in-Weekly-Chart.jpeg?resize=1024%2C637?w=1536 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-Head-and-Shoulder-Formation-in-Weekly-Chart.jpeg?resize=1024%2C637?w=750 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-Head-and-Shoulder-Formation-in-Weekly-Chart.jpeg?resize=1024%2C637?w=1140 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" loading="lazy" data-recalc-dims="1"/>

<p>As of August 15, Bitcoin is stable and within a broader uptrend from a top-down perspective. Notably, the coin is confined within the trading range established between June and July 2023, as visible in the daily chart. </p>
<p>Despite the general optimism of a price recovery above July 2023 highs, BTC was moving sideways and held above the $28,000 support level but below the $31,800 printed in the last days of H1 2023. Any breakout above $32,000 with expanding volumes might induce demand, forming an anchor for price gains toward $35,000 or better.</p>
<a href="https://www.tradingview.com/x/j9dAvCtd/" rel="nofollow"><img decoding="async" class="size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/j9dAvCtd/" alt="Bitcoin price on August 15| Source: BTCUSDT on Binance, TradingView" width="1226" height="595" loading="lazy"/></a>
<p>While the inability of sellers to drive prices lower is bullish, at least from where buyers sit, the potential formation of the head and shoulder pattern in the weekly chart casts a shadow of doubt over bullish prospects. Subsequently, traders remain cautiously optimistic since the candlestick arrangement, particularly in the weekly timeframe, suggests a vulnerability that could affect market sentiment and hopes for sustained growth.</p>
<h2>Rate Hikes And Halving: Which Will Be A Stronger Influence?</h2>
<p>Several fundamental factors further complicate the outlook for Bitcoin&#8217;s price in the coming days. Inflation is relatively high in the United States (versus the benchmark rate of 2%), which may prompt the Federal Reserve to resume interest rate hikes in the third and fourth quarters of the year. </p>
<p>Despite relatively stable labor conditions and somewhat subdued inflation, the Fed&#8217;s <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/fed-poised-hike-rates-markets-anticipate-inflation-endgame-2023-07-26/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">recent</a> rate hikes, now at the 5.25%-5.50% range, underscore the central bank&#8217;s commitment to curbing inflation and maintaining economic stability.</p>

<p>The potential impact of the Federal Reserve&#8217;s tightening policy on crypto is reminiscent of the events in 2022 when Bitcoin cracked, falling from 2021 peaks to below $16,000 in late 2022. While Bitcoin&#8217;s potential to serve as a store of value, akin to gold, during times of crisis can be a possibility in 2023 and the future, analysts still view it as a &#8220;risky&#8221; asset.</p>
<p>From a bullish lens, Bitcoin will halve its miner rewards from 6.25 BTC in 2024. This reduction may cause a supply shock, making BTC scarcer, and may support prices in the second half of next year. </p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-Head-and-Shoulder-Formation.jpg?fit=460%2C260" width="460" height="260" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">547410</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Will Bitcoin Price Crash Similarly To 2019 And 2020?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/will-bitcoin-price-crash-similarly-to-2019-and-2020/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Best Owie]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 23:00:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=547375</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin price has mostly maintained the $29,000 level for the better part of the week. This points to low activity and momentum in the market, as well as a reluctance to engage in the digital asset at this point. One reason for this reluctance is the expectation that the Bitcoin price will see another crash before the bull market resumes. However, this crypto analyst explains why expectations may be dashed this time around. Bitcoin Price May Not See A Repeat Of 2019-2020 Before the 2020-2021 bull market kicked in, the Bitcoin price had seen a rollercoaster year. Mostly, the bear market had ravaged the digital asset causing it to fall more than 80% below its all-time high price at the time, and the crashes would continue well into 2020. Related Reading: Base TVL Surges 900% In 2 Weeks, What’s Driving The Growth? Given the tendency of the Bitcoin price to follow previous trends, investors are understandably expecting a repeat of this trend. But pseudonymous crypto analyst “Tony The Bull” took to X (formerly Twitter) to use the ‘recency bias’ to explain why this may not happen. In the post, the crypto analyst used an analogy of a town that had not had a flood before, suddenly experiencing a flash storm rainstorm. Given that it had not happened before, businesses were caught unaware without flood insurance. However, going forward, the businesses begin to expect another flood and as such, they get flood insurance. The analyst explained that even though measures would be put in place to decrease the chances of such as flood happening again, people continued to operate with the knowledge of the impact of the flood. “It is the brain’s way to going with the most easily accessible information, which is the one that has most recently impacted you in a significant way,” the analyst said. “This is what’s called recency bias.” BTC movement over the last five years &#124; Source: BTCUSD on Tradingview.com This recency bias, when applied to Bitcoin, shows investors are expecting a repeat of 2019-2020 because it is the most recent bear market. Hence, investors are operating with the knowledge of the most recent impactful event. “But much like the flood never happened before, we had a once in a lifetime pandemic. The probability is rather low we’ll see the same price action as 2019 and 2020,” Tony The Bull explains. BTC Price Sticking To Previous Trends? The analyst’s position is backed up by the fact that the Bitcoin price has continuously deviated from historical trends during this cycle. One example is that while the digital asset’s price did fall to around 70% below its $69,000 all-time high, it recovered to almost 50% below its ATH. Related Reading: Regulatory Pressure Mounts On Worldcoin, Can WLD Price Recover? However, a similar trend was recorded in 2019 when BTC’s price recovered above $11,000 toward the middle of the year. But by the end of the year, had lost about half of those gains. With the rest of the gains being wiped out in early 2020. If BTC does end up following the previously established trend though, then the digital asset’s price could fall as low as $12,000 before the next bull run begins. However, it is now a waiting game to see what ends up happening. Follow Best Owie on Twitter for market insights, updates, and the occasional funny tweet… Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="p2">Bitcoin price has mostly maintained the $29,000 level for the better part of the week. This points to low activity and momentum in the market, as well as a reluctance to engage in the digital asset at this point. One reason for this reluctance is the expectation that the Bitcoin price will see another crash before the bull market resumes. However, this crypto analyst explains why expectations may be dashed this time around.</p>
<h2 class="p2">Bitcoin Price May Not See A Repeat Of 2019-2020</h2>
<p class="p2">Before the 2020-2021 bull market kicked in, the Bitcoin price had seen a rollercoaster year. Mostly, <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-prediction-crypto-analyst-forecasts-new-ath-by-2024-can-it-happen/">the bear market had ravaged the digital asset</a> causing it to fall more than 80% below its all-time high price at the time, and the crashes would continue well into 2020.</p>

<p class="p2">Given the tendency of the Bitcoin price to follow previous trends, investors are understandably expecting a repeat of this trend. But pseudonymous crypto analyst “<a href="https://twitter.com/tonythebullBTC/status/1691070332017258499?s=20" rel="nofollow">Tony The Bull</a>” took to X (formerly Twitter) to use the ‘recency bias’ to explain why this may not happen.</p>
<p class="p2">In the post, the crypto analyst used an analogy of a town that had not had a flood before, suddenly experiencing a flash storm rainstorm. Given that it had not happened before, businesses were caught unaware without flood insurance. However, going forward, the businesses begin to expect another flood and as such, they get flood insurance.</p>
<p class="p2">The analyst explained that even though measures would be put in place to decrease the chances of such as flood happening again, people continued to operate with the knowledge of the impact of the flood. “It is the brain’s way to going with the most easily accessible information, which is the one that has most recently impacted you in a significant way,” the analyst said. “This is what’s called recency bias.”</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/mWKsLTJj/" alt="Bitcoin (BTC) price chart from Tradingview.com " width="2884" height="1746"/></p>

<p class="p2">This recency bias, when applied to Bitcoin, shows investors are expecting a repeat of 2019-2020 because it is the most recent bear market. Hence, investors are operating with the knowledge of the most recent impactful event.</p>
<p class="p2">“But much like the flood never happened before, we had a once in a lifetime pandemic. The <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/former-sec-lawyer-spot-bitcoin-etf/">probability</a> is rather low we’ll see the same price action as 2019 and 2020,” Tony The Bull explains.</p>
<h2 class="p2">BTC Price Sticking To Previous Trends?</h2>
<p class="p2">The analyst’s position is backed up by the fact that the Bitcoin price has continuously deviated from historical trends during this cycle. One example is that while the digital asset’s price did fall to around 70% below its $69,000 all-time high, it recovered to almost <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-trapped-longs-to-more-downside/">50% below its ATH</a>.</p>

<p class="p2">However, a similar trend was recorded in 2019 when BTC’s price recovered above $11,000 toward the middle of the year. But by the end of the year, had lost about half of those gains. With the rest of the gains being wiped out in early 2020.</p>
<p class="p2">If BTC does end up following the previously established trend though, then the digital asset’s price could fall as low as $12,000 before the next bull run begins. However, it is now a waiting game to see what ends up happening.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/iStock-1182811569.jpg?fit=460%2C210" width="460" height="210" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">547375</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>THORSwap (THOR) 300% Surge In A Week: What&#8217;s The Secret Behind Its Thunderous Rise?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/thorchain/thor-300-surge-in-a-week-whats-the-secret-behind-its-thunderous-rise/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 21:00:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[THORChain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thorchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thorchain (RUNE)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[THORswap]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[THORUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=547414</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[In recent weeks, the native token of THORSwap, THOR, has experienced a surge, with its value increasing by nearly 300%. This surge has attracted attention within the crypto community, prompting an exploration of the factors contributing to THOR&#8217;s rapid growth.  THORSwap, a cross-chain decentralized exchange (DEX) aggregator built on the THORChain network, has been pivotal in driving this surge.  THORSwap Emerges As A Leading DEX? According to a report by crypto analytics Messari, THORSwap stands out among other automated market maker (AMM) protocols by offering a range of distinctive features.  As a DEX aggregator, it leverages the underlying THORChain network to facilitate seamless cross-chain transactions, eliminating the need for bridging or wrapped assets.  The report claims that THORSwap&#8217;s cross-chain DEX aggregation feature sets it apart by tapping into multiple liquidity sources and supporting a wide range of digital assets.  Related Reading: This Event Causes Bitcoin Traders’ Sentiment To Rise, Will BTC Surpass $30,000? By integrating with 1inch and assessing liquidity from over 50 sources on Ethereum, Polygon, and the Binance Smart Chain, THORSwap becomes an “unparalleled aggregator of aggregators,” offering users an extensive selection of native assets to swap, according to Messari. Moreover, the THOR token functions as the native utility token for THORSwap, offering traders numerous incentives. THOR holders can benefit from yields, revenue fee sharing, and trading discounts.  Moreover, THORSwap adopts continuous liquidity pools (CLPs), an innovation pioneered by protocols like Bancor. According to the report, CLPs create trustless pools of liquidity that eliminate the need for matching buyers and sellers, promoting a “well-functioning” decentralized market with limited volatility and price manipulation.  Additionally, THORSwap offers Impermanent Loss Protection (IPL) to safeguard liquidity providers from potential losses, ensuring they are better off providing liquidity than holding the underlying assets. THORChain recently introduced Synthetic Assets (&#8220;Synths&#8221;) to address the challenges of interacting with multiple blockchains.  These fully collateralized representations of assets, backed by THORChain&#8217;s liquidity pools, enable cost-effective and instant settlement without the risk of impermanent loss or liquidation.  The introduction of Synths has increased demand for THOR tokens while simultaneously boosting the network&#8217;s Total Locked Value (TVL). THORChain&#8217;s Performance Reflects Growing Interest? THORChain has reached significant milestones, solidifying its position in the industry. The report noted that the Total Value Locked metric stands impressively at $218.80 million, showcasing the trust and confidence users place in THORSwap and THORChain&#8217;s cross-chain liquidity provision capabilities.  Furthermore, the Total Volume of $11.60 billion represents the cumulative value of trades executed on the THORSwap platform. This figure reflects the increasing trading activity and demand for cross-chain swaps facilitated by THORChain&#8217;s protocol. These statistics highlight the influence and adoption of THORChain within the DeFi space. As the demand for cross-chain liquidity continues to surge, THORChain&#8217;s protocol and THORSwap&#8217;s user-friendly interface can potentially position them as industry leaders. Related Reading: Renowned Finance Author Says Bitcoin Price Will Reach $1 Million If This Happens As the THORChain ecosystem continues to evolve and demonstrate its value, the growth of the THOR token highlights the platform&#8217;s increasing adoption and recognition in the market.  Investors and crypto enthusiasts seem to recognize THORChain as a critical player in the DeFi space, leveraging its protocol to harness the benefits of cross-chain liquidity provision. As of the current market data, THOR is trading at $0.339695. Although it has experienced an 11.6% decrease in the past 24 hours, it has maintained substantial gains over the past seven and fourteen days, with impressive increases of 307% and 330%, respectively. Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In recent weeks, the native token of THORSwap, THOR, has experienced a surge, with its value increasing by nearly 300%. This surge has attracted attention within the crypto community, prompting an exploration of the factors contributing to THOR&#8217;s rapid growth. </p>
<p>THORSwap, a cross-chain decentralized exchange (DEX) aggregator built on the THORChain network, has been pivotal in driving this surge. </p>
<h2>THORSwap Emerges As A Leading DEX?</h2>
<p>According to a <a href="https://messari.io/report/thorswap-solving-cross-chain-s-centralization-problem" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">report </a>by crypto analytics Messari, THORSwap stands out among other automated market maker (AMM) protocols by offering a range of distinctive features. </p>
<p>As a DEX aggregator, it leverages the underlying THORChain network to facilitate seamless cross-chain transactions, eliminating the need for bridging or wrapped assets. </p>
<p>The report claims that THORSwap&#8217;s cross-chain DEX aggregation feature sets it apart by tapping into multiple liquidity sources and supporting a wide range of digital assets. </p>

<p>By integrating with 1inch and assessing liquidity from over 50 sources on Ethereum, Polygon, and the Binance Smart Chain, THORSwap becomes an “unparalleled aggregator of aggregators,” offering users an extensive selection of native assets to swap, according to Messari.</p>
<p>Moreover, the THOR token functions as the native utility token for THORSwap, offering traders numerous incentives. THOR holders can benefit from yields, revenue fee sharing, and trading discounts. </p>
<p>Moreover, THORSwap adopts continuous liquidity pools (CLPs), an innovation pioneered by protocols like Bancor. According to the report, CLPs create trustless pools of liquidity that eliminate the need for matching buyers and sellers, promoting a “well-functioning” decentralized market with limited volatility and price manipulation. </p>
<p>Additionally, THORSwap offers Impermanent Loss Protection (IPL) to safeguard liquidity providers from potential losses, ensuring they are better off providing liquidity than holding the underlying assets.</p>
<p>THORChain recently introduced Synthetic Assets (&#8220;Synths&#8221;) to address the challenges of interacting with multiple blockchains. </p>
<p>These fully collateralized representations of assets, backed by THORChain&#8217;s liquidity pools, enable cost-effective and instant settlement without the risk of impermanent loss or liquidation. </p>
<p>The introduction of Synths has increased demand for THOR tokens while simultaneously boosting the network&#8217;s Total Locked Value (TVL).</p>
<h2>THORChain&#8217;s Performance Reflects Growing Interest?</h2>
<p>THORChain has reached significant <a href="https://app.thorswap.finance/dashboard" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">milestones</a>, solidifying its position in the industry. The report noted that the Total Value Locked metric stands impressively at $218.80 million, showcasing the trust and confidence users place in THORSwap and THORChain&#8217;s cross-chain liquidity provision capabilities. </p>
<p>Furthermore, the Total Volume of $11.60 billion represents the cumulative value of trades executed on the THORSwap platform. This figure reflects the increasing trading activity and demand for cross-chain swaps facilitated by THORChain&#8217;s protocol.</p>
<p>These statistics highlight the influence and adoption of THORChain within the DeFi space. As the demand for cross-chain liquidity continues to surge, THORChain&#8217;s protocol and THORSwap&#8217;s user-friendly interface can potentially position them as industry leaders.</p>

<p>As the THORChain ecosystem continues to evolve and demonstrate its value, the growth of the THOR token highlights the platform&#8217;s increasing adoption and recognition in the market. </p>
<p>Investors and crypto enthusiasts seem to recognize THORChain as a critical player in the DeFi space, leveraging its protocol to harness the benefits of cross-chain liquidity provision.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/fM6oRENr/" alt="THORswap" width="1815" height="858"/>
<p>As of the current market data, THOR is trading at $0.339695. Although it has experienced an 11.6% decrease in the past 24 hours, it has maintained substantial gains over the past seven and fourteen days, with impressive increases of 307% and 330%, respectively.</p>
<p>Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Downloader.la-64dbd107ecfd9.jpg?fit=460%2C307" width="460" height="307" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">547414</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Institutional XRP Holdings Rise Rapidly Following Ripple&#8217;s Win Over SEC</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/institutional-xrp-holdings-rise/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 20:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Institutional Investors]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrp]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP investors]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrpusdt]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=547385</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Now that Ripple has prevailed over the SEC in court, major players are eager to get their hands on XRP. According to recent data, institutions have been getting their hands on the cryptocurrency at a steady rate, as reflected in the digital asset fund flows report.  Institutional XRP Holdings Rise Rapidly In the days following Ripple’s partial victory in the SEC lawsuit, XRP volumes and prices rose dramatically as crypto traders rushed to the cryptocurrency in anticipation of a continued bull run. However, price metrics from Coinmarketcap show that the euphoria has subsided, with XRP now down 13.39% in a monthly time frame. On-chain data has also shown whales dumping the token to take profits, increasing the selling pressure on the token. Related Reading: Here’s Why This Former SEC Lawyer Thinks A Spot Bitcoin ETF Isn’t Coming On the other hand, the tide is turning for the once embattled crypto among institutional investors as inflows into XRP digital asset funds are increasing steadily. According to the weekly report on the digital asset fund flows by CoinShares, XRP saw $0.5 million in inflows last week.  Over the past 16 weeks, XRP has seen consistent inflows into crypto investment funds, making up 12% of all digital assets under management. In total, XRP’s assets under management have risen 127% since the beginning of the year, outpacing the growth of other popular altcoins like Polygon and Cardano. XRP price returns to $0.6256 &#124; Source: XRPUSD on Tradingview.com Investor Attitude Toward Crypto Funds Is Growing Crypto funds, in general, have seen a shift to positive sentiment from investors. In the first week of the month, digital asset investment products saw outflows, with investors taking profits in recent weeks. Bitcoin alone saw outflows totaling $111 million, its highest since March. XRP, however, did witness inflows of $0.5 million during this period.  The latest report would see digital asset investment products receive inflows of $29 million throughout the week. Bitcoin would also return as the primary focus, seeing $27 million of inflows after three prior weeks of $144 million outflows. Related Reading: Winds Of Change: Bitcoin Miner Riot Sees Substantial Increase In BTC Holdings With the recent inflows, institutional investors are signaling their faith in XRP’s future by increasing their asset holdings. In July, many digital asset funds saw a 57% increase in their XRP Exchange Traded Products (ETPs). Fineqia, for instance, saw its XRP AUM increase from $49 million to $76.8 million.  The price of the token appears to have weakened in momentum in recent weeks, much like the rest of the crypto market. At the time of writing, XRP is down by 0.60% in the last 24 hours and is trading at 0.625. Even so, the mood around XRP feels decidedly more optimistic as investors expect a final decision in the Ripple-SEC lawsuit.  Featured image from iStock, chart from Tradingview.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Now that Ripple has prevailed over the SEC in court, major players are eager to get their hands on XRP. According to recent data, institutions have been getting their hands on the cryptocurrency at a steady rate, as reflected in the digital asset fund flows report. </p>
<h2>Institutional XRP Holdings Rise Rapidly</h2>
<p>In the days following Ripple’s partial victory in the SEC lawsuit, XRP volumes and prices rose dramatically as crypto traders rushed to the cryptocurrency in anticipation of a continued bull run. However, price metrics from Coinmarketcap <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/xrp/" rel="nofollow">show </a>that the euphoria has subsided, with XRP now down 13.39% in a monthly time frame. On-chain data has also shown whales dumping the token to take profits, increasing the selling pressure on the token.</p>

<p>On the other hand, the tide is turning for the once embattled crypto among institutional investors as inflows into XRP digital asset funds are increasing steadily. According to the weekly report on the digital <a href="https://blog.coinshares.com/volume-144-digital-asset-fund-flows-weekly-report-7d29c8c04df5" rel="nofollow">asset fund flows</a> by CoinShares, XRP saw $0.5 million in inflows last week. </p>
<p>Over the past 16 weeks, XRP has seen consistent inflows into crypto investment funds, making up 12% of all digital assets under management. In total, XRP’s assets under management have risen 127% since the beginning of the year, outpacing the growth of other popular altcoins like Polygon and Cardano.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/qlWEwL70/" alt="Ripple (XRP) price chart from Tradingview.com" width="2884" height="1746"/></p>

<h2>Investor Attitude Toward Crypto Funds Is Growing</h2>
<p>Crypto funds, in general, have seen a shift to positive sentiment from investors. In the <a href="https://blog.coinshares.com/volume-143-digital-asset-fund-flows-weekly-report-6d46f78754c" rel="nofollow">first week</a> of the month, digital asset investment products saw outflows, with investors taking profits in recent weeks. Bitcoin alone saw outflows totaling $111 million, its highest since March. XRP, however, did witness inflows of $0.5 million during this period. </p>
<p>The latest report would see digital asset investment products receive inflows of $29 million throughout the week. Bitcoin would also return as the primary focus, seeing $27 million of inflows after three prior weeks of $144 million outflows.</p>

<p>With the recent inflows, institutional investors are signaling their faith in XRP’s future by increasing their asset holdings. In July, many digital asset funds saw a 57% increase in their XRP Exchange Traded Products (ETPs). Fineqia, <a href="https://twitter.com/sentosumosaba/status/1689203209519427584?s=20" rel="nofollow">for instance</a>, saw its XRP AUM increase from $49 million to $76.8 million. </p>
<p>The price of the token appears to have weakened in momentum in recent weeks, much like the rest of the crypto market. At the time of writing, XRP is down by 0.60% in the last 24 hours and is trading at 0.625. Even so, the mood around XRP feels decidedly more optimistic as investors expect a final decision in the Ripple-SEC lawsuit. </p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/iStock-1363462648.jpg?fit=460%2C307" width="460" height="307" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">547385</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Renowned Finance Author Says Bitcoin Price Will Reach $1 Million If This Happens</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-price-will-reach-1-million/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 19:00:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin prediction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=547382</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin&#8217;s creator, Satoshi Nakamoto, created Bitcoin in response to the 2008 financial crisis as an alternative to government-controlled money. Since then, Bitcoin has gone to spearhead the crypto industry, with many investors calling it digital gold. Now, renowned finance author Robert Kiyosaki has argued that Bitcoin price could reach $100,000 soon and go as high as $1 million. Bold Prediction On Bitcoin Robert Kiyosaki, best known for his bestselling book ‘Rich Dad Poor Dad,’ is known to make very bullish predictions on the price of Bitcoin. In a recent post on social media platform X, formerly known as Twitter, Kiyosaki tweeted of Bitcoin reaching 100,000 soon, calling it the &#8220;people&#8217;s gold.&#8221; However, a stock and bond market crash could see Bitcoin reach $1 million. Related Reading: US Prosecutors Accuse FTX’s Sam Bankman-Fried Of Using $100M To Curry Political Favors Kiyosaki also shared his predictions on gold and silver, calling them &#8220;GOD’S money.&#8221; According to the finance educator, gold and silver can reach $75,000 and $60,000 respectively if the world economy crashes.  BITCOIN to $100k. Saying for years gold&#38;silver GOD’S money. BITCOIN peoples $. Bad news IF stock &#38; bond market crash gold&#38;silver skyrocket. WORSE NEWS IF world economy crashes BC $1 million Gold $ 75K silver to $60k. SAVERS of FAKE US $ F’d. DEBT too high. Mom, Pop &#38; kids in… — Robert Kiyosaki (@theRealKiyosaki) August 14, 2023 He explained that if the economy collapsed, the value of government-issued currencies would drop drastically. As people lose faith in fiat money, many would turn to Bitcoin and precious metals as an alternative store of value. The increased demand, coupled with the limited supply of Bitcoin, would cause the price to skyrocket. Earlier this year, Kiyosaki made a similar claim regarding Bitcoin, touting a price of $500,000 for each Bitcoin by 2025. Michael Saylor, another big name in the finance sector, predicted a similar price of $1 million for BTC in the next few years. What Is The Basis For The $1 Million Bitcoin Price Prediction? Kiyosaki&#8217;s recent predictions about the US dollar, in particular, have come on the heels of the BRICS alliance, which is now gaining traction. BRICS, which is an alliance between the emerging economies of Brazil, Russia, India, China, and South Africa, has gained ground in its campaign to support the reduction of transactions in the US dollar and the promotion of trading and settlement in local currencies.  As a result, many names in finance have seen this as a plan to de-dollarize trades in the BRICS countries, with reports of Saudi Arabia and possibly Mexico and Japan joining them. Reports are also that the BRICS alliance is working on creating a new currency backed by gold to settle global trades.  Related Reading: BALD Deployer Moves Proceeds Of The Rug From Base To Ethereum According to Kiyosaki, the only saving grace for everyday investors is to get into real gold, silver, and Bitcoin as stores of value. “SAVERS of FAKE US $ F’d,” Kiyosaki tweeted. Giant crash coming. Fake money-aka fist currency to die. BRUCS meeting in S. Africa August 22 to put nail in coffin of fiat…fake money. Get into real gold, silver &#38; Bitcoin asap. Take care. End of fiat (fake) money near. — Robert Kiyosaki (@theRealKiyosaki) July 13, 2023 BTC price continues to hold $29,000 support &#124; Source: BTCUSD on Tradingview.com  Featured image from iStock, chart from Tradingview.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin&#8217;s creator, Satoshi Nakamoto, created Bitcoin in response to the 2008 financial crisis as an alternative to government-controlled money. Since then, Bitcoin has gone to spearhead the crypto industry, with many investors calling it digital gold. Now, renowned finance author Robert Kiyosaki has argued that Bitcoin price could reach $100,000 soon and go as high as $1 million.</p>
<h2>Bold Prediction On Bitcoin</h2>
<p>Robert Kiyosaki, best known for his bestselling book ‘Rich Dad Poor Dad,’ is known to make very bullish predictions on the price of Bitcoin. In a recent post on social media platform X, formerly known as Twitter, Kiyosaki tweeted of Bitcoin reaching 100,000 soon, calling it the &#8220;people&#8217;s gold.&#8221; However, a stock and bond market crash could see Bitcoin reach $1 million.</p>

<p>Kiyosaki also shared his predictions on gold and silver, calling them &#8220;GOD’S money.&#8221; According to the finance educator, gold and silver can reach $75,000 and $60,000 respectively if the world economy crashes. </p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">BITCOIN to $100k. Saying for years gold&amp;silver GOD’S money. BITCOIN peoples $. Bad news IF stock &amp; bond market crash gold&amp;silver skyrocket. WORSE NEWS IF world economy crashes BC $1 million Gold $ 75K silver to $60k. SAVERS of FAKE US $ F’d. DEBT too high. Mom, Pop &amp; kids in…</p>
<p>— Robert Kiyosaki (@theRealKiyosaki) <a href="https://twitter.com/theRealKiyosaki/status/1691174700234477570?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">August 14, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p>He explained that if the economy collapsed, the value of government-issued currencies would drop drastically. As people lose faith in fiat money, many would turn to Bitcoin and precious metals as an alternative store of value. The increased demand, coupled with the limited supply of Bitcoin, would cause the price to skyrocket.</p>
<p>Earlier this year, Kiyosaki made a <a href="https://twitter.com/theRealKiyosaki/status/1678652054951317504?s=20" rel="nofollow">similar claim</a> regarding Bitcoin, touting a price of $500,000 for each Bitcoin by 2025. <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/michael-saylor-says-bitcoin-is-the-oxygen-mask-that-will-save-investors/">Michael Saylor</a>, another big name in the finance sector, predicted a <a href="https://twitter.com/CryptoNewsYes/status/1680672701755555842?s=20" rel="nofollow">similar price</a> of $1 million for BTC in the next few years.</p>
<h2>What Is The Basis For The $1 Million Bitcoin Price Prediction?</h2>
<p>Kiyosaki&#8217;s recent predictions about the US dollar, in particular, have come on the heels of the BRICS alliance, which is now gaining traction. BRICS, which is an alliance between the emerging economies of Brazil, Russia, India, China, and South Africa, has gained ground in its campaign to support the reduction of transactions in the US dollar and the promotion of trading and settlement in local currencies. </p>
<p>As a result, many names in finance have seen this as a plan to de-dollarize trades in the BRICS countries, with reports of Saudi Arabia and possibly Mexico and Japan joining them. Reports are also that the BRICS alliance is working on creating a new currency backed by gold to settle global trades. </p>

<p>According to Kiyosaki, the only saving grace for everyday investors is to get into real gold, silver, and Bitcoin as stores of value. “SAVERS of FAKE US $ F’d,” Kiyosaki tweeted.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Giant crash coming. Fake money-aka fist currency to die. BRUCS meeting in S. Africa August 22 to put nail in coffin of fiat…fake money. Get into real gold, silver &amp; Bitcoin asap. Take care. End of fiat (fake) money near.</p>
<p>— Robert Kiyosaki (@theRealKiyosaki) <a href="https://twitter.com/theRealKiyosaki/status/1679322816565645312?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">July 13, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/YnXUjq8H/" alt="Bitcoin price chart from Tradingview.com " width="2884" height="1746"/></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/iStock-1356848899-1.jpg?fit=460%2C307" width="460" height="307" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">547382</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>This Event Causes Bitcoin Traders&#8217; Sentiment To Rise, Will BTC Surpass $30,000?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/this-event-causes-bitcoin-traders-sentiment-to-rise-will-btc-surpass-30000/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reynaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 18:00:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=547367</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Bitcoin price continues to compress around its current levels, but during today’s trading session, there was an uptick in volatility. The rise in this metric could hint at a shift in the narratives influencing BTC’s price action. Related Reading: Bitcoin Prediction: Crypto Analyst Forecasts New ATH by 2024 – Can It Happen? As of this writing, Bitcoin trades at $29,300 with sideways movement in the last 24 hours. In the previous seven days, the cryptocurrency saw similar action pushing other assets in a similar direction or no direction as the sector flatlines in the short term. Bitcoin ETF Becomes Dominant Narrative In Crypto Market? In a recent market update, crypto analysis firm Blofin pointed to an uptick in market sentiment. Coupled with a rise in volatility, market participants are reacting to the potential announcement from the US Securities Exchange Commission (SEC) around a spot Bitcoin ETF. The Commission is set to rule on asset manager Grayscale’s petition to transform their Grayscale Bitcoin Trust (GBTC) into an ETF. The decision was supposed to come out today, Blofin stated, but it could drag on until this Friday, August 18th. If the SEC postpones the decision for any reason, as it did with Ark’s petition, the market will likely keep moving sideways. In that sense, development around the ETF decision is gaining strength over macroeconomic dynamics. This change in dynamics is more evident in the derivatives sector, with options traders becoming more bullish for the coming months. Blofin noted the following on this dynamic: (…) The news above (on the Bitcoin ETF approval) has promoted the rapid rise of short-term bullish sentiment and uncertainty in the market (…). It appears that investors are waiting for good news related to the spot Bitcoin ETF. And “smart” traders are positioning accordingly. The report notes that the open interest for options contracts is skewed to the call (buy) side. Related Reading: XRP Price at Potentially Significant Turning Point, Key Support Nearby As data from the derivatives platform Deribit shows, traders are betting that the price of Bitcoin will rise above $30,000 by the end of August or September. As seen on the chart below, 57,000 contracts will expire by the end of this month and 90,700 next month. Coupled with the rise in Open Interest skewed to the call side, the chart above shows that traders are betting on a Bitcoin rally above $30,000 to $40,000. The spot BTC ETF decision will move the market, particularly at the end of August and September. Cover image from Unsplash, chart from Tradingview]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>The Bitcoin price continues to compress around its current levels, but during today’s trading session, there was an uptick in volatility. The rise in this metric could hint at a shift in the narratives influencing BTC’s price action. </strong></p>

<p>As of this writing, Bitcoin trades at $29,300 with sideways movement in the last 24 hours. In the previous seven days, the cryptocurrency saw similar action pushing other assets in a similar direction or no direction as the sector flatlines in the short term.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-547380 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-price-BTC-BTCUSDT-1.png?w=860&#038;resize=860%2C410" alt="Bitcoin price BTC BTCUSDT" width="860" height="410" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-price-BTC-BTCUSDT-1.png?w=1758 1758w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-price-BTC-BTCUSDT-1.png?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-price-BTC-BTCUSDT-1.png?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-price-BTC-BTCUSDT-1.png?w=860&#038;resize=860%2C410 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-price-BTC-BTCUSDT-1.png?w=1536 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-price-BTC-BTCUSDT-1.png?w=750 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-price-BTC-BTCUSDT-1.png?w=1140 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" data-recalc-dims="1"/>
<h2>Bitcoin ETF Becomes Dominant Narrative In Crypto Market?</h2>
<p>In a recent market update, crypto analysis firm Blofin pointed to an uptick in market sentiment. Coupled with a rise in volatility, market participants are reacting to the potential announcement from the US Securities Exchange Commission (SEC) around a spot Bitcoin ETF.</p>
<p>The Commission is set to rule on asset manager Grayscale’s petition to transform their Grayscale Bitcoin Trust (GBTC) into an ETF. The decision was supposed to come out today, Blofin stated, but it could drag on until this Friday, August 18th.</p>
<p>If the SEC postpones the decision for any reason, as it did with Ark’s petition, the market will likely keep moving sideways. In that sense, development around the ETF decision is gaining strength over macroeconomic dynamics.</p>
<p>This change in dynamics is more evident in the derivatives sector, with options traders becoming more bullish for the coming months. Blofin noted the following on this dynamic:</p>
<blockquote><p>(…) The news above (on the Bitcoin ETF approval) has promoted the rapid rise of short-term bullish sentiment and uncertainty in the market (…). It appears that investors are waiting for good news related to the spot Bitcoin ETF.</p></blockquote>
<p>And “smart” traders are positioning accordingly. The report notes that the open interest for options contracts is skewed to the call (buy) side.</p>

<p>As data from the derivatives platform Deribit shows, traders are betting that the price of Bitcoin will rise above $30,000 by the end of August or September. As seen on the chart below, 57,000 contracts will expire by the end of this month and 90,700 next month.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-547379 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-price-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-OI.jpg?w=860&#038;resize=860%2C227" alt="Bitcoin price BTC BTCUSDT Chart OI" width="860" height="227" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-price-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-OI.jpg?w=1534 1534w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-price-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-OI.jpg?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-price-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-OI.jpg?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-price-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-OI.jpg?w=860&#038;resize=860%2C227 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-price-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-OI.jpg?w=750 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-price-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-OI.jpg?w=1140 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" data-recalc-dims="1"/>
<p>Coupled with the rise in Open Interest skewed to the call side, the chart above shows that traders are betting on a Bitcoin rally above $30,000 to $40,000. The spot BTC ETF decision will move the market, particularly at the end of August and September.</p>
<p>Cover image from Unsplash, chart from Tradingview</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-Price-BTC-BTCUSDT-4.jpg?fit=460%2C307" width="460" height="307" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">547367</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Subtle Signs A Bullish Bitcoin Trend Is Brewing</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/the-subtle-signs-a-bullish-bitcoin-trend-is-brewing/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tony "The Bull"]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 17:05:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xbt]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xbtusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=547389</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin price remains stagnant for going on months now, with no clear trend developing and volatility in a downward spiral. However, some subtle signs are popping up that could suggest that a bullish Bitcoin trend is beginning to take shape. Make Friends With Strong Trends “The trend is your friend” is one of the most famous trading quotes, highlighting how capturing as much of the prevailing trend as possible can lead to the most profitable results. For this reason, in technical analysis, trend-following tools are among the most successful. But what is an investor or trader to do when there is a clear absence of any discernible trend? The answer is “to wait for the trend to appear” but that’s easier said than done. This is why specific tools have been created to tell when assets like Bitcoin or even stocks are trending or not. One such tool is starting to rise after several weeks of sideways price action, and it suggest that the underlying trend is strengthening. The Average Directional Index &#124; BTCUSD on TradingView.com Bullish Bitcoin Is Building Muscle The Average Directional Index (ADX) is a trend strength measuring tool, created by the father of technical indicators, J. Welles, Wilder, Jr. Other tools Wilder built include the Parabolic SAR, Average True Range, and the Relative Strength Index. A reading above 20 on the ADX means a trend is developing. The more it turns up, the stronger the trend. After weeks of sideways, the trend is starting to strengthen again. The tool also includes two Directional Movement indicators, the DI+ and DI-. The DI+ is currently above the DI-, showing that bulls in control of the underlying price action. All that’s left is for the ADX to strengthen further and Bitcoin could finally break out of this range and begin trending. What Bitcoin bulls ultimately want to see next is for the ADX to grow even steeper, similar to what we can see in late 2020 and into early 2022. The lack of another strong trend at the second 2021 peak was a warning that something was off. Will the bullish trend continue to strengthen, or will bears regain control? #Bitcoin 1W Average Directional Index is turning back up above 20 — this is the signature of a strengthening trend DI+ is above DI- which shows bulls are in control Trend-following tools may soon prove more useful with a trend growing pic.twitter.com/9nAUEVIcL3 &#8212; Tony &#34;The Bull&#34; (@tonythebullBTC) August 14, 2023 Tony is the author of the CoinChartist (VIP) newsletter. Sign up for free. Follow @TonyTheBullBTC &#38; @coinchartist_io on Twitter. Or join the TonyTradesBTC Telegram for daily market insights and technical analysis education. Please note: Content is educational and should not be considered investment advice. Featured image from iStockPhoto, Charts from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin price remains stagnant for going on months now, with no clear trend developing and volatility in a downward spiral. However, some subtle signs are popping up that could suggest that a bullish Bitcoin trend is beginning to take shape.</p>
<h2>Make Friends With Strong Trends</h2>
<p>“The trend is your friend” is one of the most famous trading quotes, highlighting how capturing as much of the prevailing trend as possible can lead to the most profitable results.</p>
<p>For this reason, in technical analysis, trend-following tools are among the most successful. But what is an investor or trader to do when there is a clear absence of any discernible trend?</p>
<p>The answer is “to wait for the trend to appear” but that’s easier said than done. This is why specific tools have been created to tell when assets like Bitcoin or even stocks are trending or not. One such tool is starting to rise after several weeks of sideways price action, and it suggest that the underlying trend is strengthening.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large wp-image-547390 aligncenter" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F3gWev9X0AYtIfg.jpeg?w=860&#038;resize=860%2C535" alt="bitcoin adx" width="860" height="535" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F3gWev9X0AYtIfg.jpeg?w=2048 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F3gWev9X0AYtIfg.jpeg?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F3gWev9X0AYtIfg.jpeg?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F3gWev9X0AYtIfg.jpeg?w=860&#038;resize=860%2C535 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F3gWev9X0AYtIfg.jpeg?w=1536 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F3gWev9X0AYtIfg.jpeg?w=750 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F3gWev9X0AYtIfg.jpeg?w=1140 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" data-recalc-dims="1"/></p>

<h2>Bullish Bitcoin Is Building Muscle</h2>
<p>The Average Directional Index (ADX) is a trend strength measuring tool, created by the father of technical indicators, J. Welles, Wilder, Jr. Other tools Wilder built include the Parabolic SAR, Average True Range, and the Relative Strength Index.</p>
<p>A reading above 20 on the ADX means a trend is developing. The more it turns up, the stronger the trend. After weeks of sideways, the trend is starting to strengthen again.</p>
<p>The tool also includes two Directional Movement indicators, the DI+ and DI-. The DI+ is currently above the DI-, showing that bulls in control of the underlying price action. All that’s left is for the ADX to strengthen further and Bitcoin could finally break out of this range and begin trending.</p>
<p>What Bitcoin bulls ultimately want to see next is for the ADX to grow even steeper, similar to what we can see in late 2020 and into early 2022. The lack of another strong trend at the second 2021 peak was a warning that something was off. Will the bullish trend continue to strengthen, or will bears regain control?</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr"><a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Bitcoin?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#Bitcoin</a> 1W Average Directional Index is turning back up above 20 — this is the signature of a strengthening trend</p>
<p>DI+ is above DI- which shows bulls are in control</p>
<p>Trend-following tools may soon prove more useful with a trend growing <a href="https://t.co/9nAUEVIcL3" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/9nAUEVIcL3</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Tony &quot;The Bull&quot; (@tonythebullBTC) <a href="https://twitter.com/tonythebullBTC/status/1691126381005135872?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">August 14, 2023</a></p></blockquote>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/istock-teagkhdgkd.jpeg?fit=460%2C230" width="460" height="230" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">547389</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Chiliz (CHZ) Empowers Smart Contracts With Upgrades &#8211; Positive Impact On Price?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/chiliz-chz-empowers-smart-contracts-with-upgrades-positive-impact-on-price/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 17:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[chiliZ]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CHZ Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price action]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=547328</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Chiliz, the pioneering sports blockchain platform, is set to make waves once again as it teases forthcoming upgrades to its smart contracts. In a recent tweet, Chiliz unveiled its plans to enhance the functionality of its smart contracts, showcasing the company&#8217;s ongoing commitment to providing a seamless and efficient experience for its users.  Chiliz has been a trailblazer in the sports and entertainment industry, utilizing blockchain technology to bridge the gap between sports fans and their favorite teams. Related Reading: Dogecoin Vs. Bitcoin: Co-Founder Labels BTC Maximalists As ‘Insecure Losers’ The platform&#8217;s innovative approach allows fans to engage with their chosen teams through fan tokens, gaining access to exclusive content, rewards, and even influencing certain team decisions through token-based voting systems.  🗳️ Upcoming Proposals: Upgrading the Smart contracts Upgrade 1: Upgrading the contracts to allow factory contracts to deploy without being whitelisted as deployers. The factory contract will still need to be deployed by a whitelisted deployer.#ChilizGovernance ⚡ $CHZ pic.twitter.com/zyBTqzAhTJ — Chiliz ($CHZ) &#8211; Powering Socios.com ⚡ (@Chiliz) August 14, 2023 As the platform gears up for these improvements, the question on everyone&#8217;s mind is whether these upgrades will play a role in boosting the price of CHZ, Chiliz&#8217;s native cryptocurrency. Chiliz Upgrades On The Horizon The first of the upcoming upgrades focuses on streamlining the deployment of factory contracts. In a bid to improve efficiency, Chiliz plans to enable such contracts to be deployed without the need for whitelisting as deployers.  This move is expected to simplify the process while maintaining a level of security by ensuring that the factory contract is still initiated by a whitelisted deployer. By reducing friction in the contract deployment process, Chiliz aims to enhance user experience and attract a wider range of participants. The second upgrade revolves around staking pool contract enhancements. Chiliz aims to address issues related to the accuracy of voting power displayed for validators and the calculation of delegated amounts.  Chiliz is currently trading at $0.0748. Chart by TradingView.com To rectify this, the Chiliz team has indicated that a temporary downtime for the delegated and undelegated features will be necessary during the upgrade. While this may temporarily inconvenience users, the improvements are anticipated to provide a more accurate and transparent staking experience. Impact On CHZ Price As Chiliz enthusiasts eagerly await these upgrades, the impact on the price of CHZ remains a topic of interest. At the time of writing, CHZ is in the red in all timeframes, and priced at $0.074903 according to CoinGecko. The past 24 hours have seen a decline of 1.2% in its value, while the past seven days have witnessed a decline of 1.5%. These fluctuations underscore the inherent volatility of the cryptocurrency market. CHZ price action today. Source: Coingecko Related Reading: FDIC Warns Of Crypto’s Legal And Fraud Risks For US Banks – Here’s Why While the direct correlation between upgrades and price movements can be complex and multifaceted, the anticipated improvements in Chiliz&#8217;s smart contracts could bolster investor confidence in the platform&#8217;s future prospects.  (This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk). Featured image from Dr Trouble Hot Sauce]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Chiliz, the pioneering sports blockchain platform, is set to make waves once again as it teases forthcoming upgrades to its smart contracts. </p>
<p>In a recent tweet, Chiliz unveiled its plans to enhance the functionality of its smart contracts, showcasing the company&#8217;s ongoing commitment to providing a seamless and efficient experience for its users. </p>
<p>Chiliz has been a trailblazer in the sports and entertainment industry, utilizing blockchain technology to bridge the gap between sports fans and their favorite teams. </p>

<p>The platform&#8217;s innovative approach allows fans to engage with their chosen teams through fan tokens, gaining access to exclusive content, rewards, and even influencing certain team decisions through token-based voting systems. </p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en"><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f5f3.png" alt="🗳" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> Upcoming Proposals: Upgrading the Smart contracts</p>
<p>Upgrade 1: Upgrading the contracts to allow factory contracts to deploy without being whitelisted as deployers. The factory contract will still need to be deployed by a whitelisted deployer.<a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/ChilizGovernance?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#ChilizGovernance</a> <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/26a1.png" alt="⚡" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24CHZ&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$CHZ</a> <a href="https://t.co/zyBTqzAhTJ" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/zyBTqzAhTJ</a></p>
<p>— Chiliz ($CHZ) &#8211; Powering Socios.com <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/26a1.png" alt="⚡" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> (@Chiliz) <a href="https://twitter.com/Chiliz/status/1691037068963590146?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">August 14, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p>As the platform gears up for these improvements, the question on everyone&#8217;s mind is whether these upgrades will play a role in boosting <a href="https://u.today/chiliz-chz-unveils-game-changing-upgrades-for-smart-contracts" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">the price of CHZ</a>, Chiliz&#8217;s native cryptocurrency.</p>
<h2><strong>Chiliz Upgrades On The Horizon</strong></h2>
<p>The first of the <a href="https://twitter.com/Chiliz/status/1691037068963590146" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">upcoming upgrades</a> focuses on streamlining the deployment of factory contracts. In a bid to improve efficiency, Chiliz plans to enable such contracts to be deployed without the need for whitelisting as deployers. </p>
<p>This move is expected to simplify the process while maintaining a level of security by ensuring that the factory contract is still initiated by a whitelisted deployer. By reducing friction in the contract deployment process, Chiliz aims to enhance user experience and attract a wider range of participants.</p>
<p>The second upgrade revolves around staking pool contract enhancements. Chiliz aims to address issues related to the accuracy of voting power displayed for validators and the calculation of delegated amounts. </p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/IPJnrKlj/" width="1835" height="893"/></p>

<p>To rectify this, the Chiliz team has indicated that a temporary downtime for the delegated and undelegated features will be necessary during the upgrade. While this may temporarily inconvenience users, the improvements are anticipated to provide a more accurate and transparent staking experience.</p>
<h2><strong>Impact On CHZ Price</strong></h2>
<p>As Chiliz enthusiasts eagerly await these upgrades, the impact on the price of CHZ remains a topic of interest. At the time of writing, CHZ is in the red in all timeframes, and priced at $0.074903 according to <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/chiliz" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">CoinGecko</a>. </p>
<p>The past 24 hours have seen a decline of 1.2% in its value, while the past seven days have witnessed a decline of 1.5%. These fluctuations underscore the inherent volatility of the cryptocurrency market.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-547363" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-85.png?resize=1024%2C53" alt="" width="1024" height="53" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-85.png?resize=1024%2C53?w=1137 1137w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-85.png?resize=1024%2C53?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-85.png?resize=1024%2C53?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-85.png?resize=1024%2C53?w=860 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-85.png?resize=1024%2C53?w=750 750w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" data-recalc-dims="1"/></p>


<p>While the direct correlation between upgrades and price movements can be complex and multifaceted, the anticipated improvements in Chiliz&#8217;s smart contracts could bolster investor confidence in the platform&#8217;s future prospects. </p>
<p><em>(This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk).</em></p>
<p><em>Featured image from Dr Trouble Hot Sauce</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-84.png?fit=460%2C310" width="460" height="310" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">547328</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>DeFiance Capital Gains Upper Hand In Jurisdiction Battle Against 3AC: Singapore Courts To Preside</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/crypto/defiance-capital-gains-upper-hand-jurisdiction-against-3ac/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samuel Edyme]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 16:00:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3AC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DeFiance Capital]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[law]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[singapore]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=547334</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The crypto finance world has witnessed numerous disputes, but few have been similar to that of the ongoing feud between DeFiance Capital and Three Arrows Capital Limited (3AC). Particularly, this dispute underscores the intricate interplay between traditional financial frameworks and the evolving dynamics of digital assets. In a tweet posted earlier today, DeFiance Capital CEO shed new light on their ongoing legal tussle with 3AC, suggesting a turn in the tide. Statement and Update on Dispute with Three Arrows Capital Limited (3AC) We are very pleased to share a positive development on our end with the public. It is well-known that for the past year, we have been locked in a dispute with the 3AC estate who are claiming that the assets… — Arthur (@Arthur_0x) August 15, 2023 DeFiance Capital: A Year-long Struggle Almost a year ago, the disagreement between DeFiance Capital and the 3AC estate took center stage when the estate contended that the assets held by DeFiance Capital should be used to square off the debts of 3AC. Related Reading: 3AC NFTs Sale To Commence Soon Due to Liquidation Countering this claim, DeFiance maintained that they had complete authority and rightful ownership of their assets. This stance, they assert, aligns with common industry perceptions and is supported by available evidence. The debate took a geographical turn when the liquidators insisted on settling the dispute in the British Virgin Islands (BVI). DeFiance Capital, which was managed from Singapore alongside 3AC, found this choice of jurisdiction puzzling. They argued that the primary evidence and witnesses were based in Singapore, making it a more apt location for the hearing. Their persistence bore fruit last week when the High Court of Singapore agreed to their jurisdiction preference, subtly undermining the liquidators&#8217; earlier narrative that DeFiance&#8217;s stance held no ground. The Road Ahead: Seeking Effective Resolutions Despite these disagreements, DeFiance has shown a willingness to collaborate. They have extended assistance to 3AC&#8217;s liquidators in understanding the position of DeFiance and even offered help in identifying 3AC&#8217;s assets. The intention, as expressed by the CEO &#38; CIO of DeFiance, was to minimize the resources spent on deciding the hearing location and instead concentrate on the core issues at hand. However, the journey hasn&#8217;t been without its hitches. The liquidators faced setbacks in the US while trying to hold Three Arrows Capital Co-Founder  Kyle Davies accountable in a US court. This effort was thwarted when it came to light that Davies was no longer a US citizen, an information oversight that resulted in unnecessary legal expenses. Blossom Hing, representing DeFiance, highlighted the significance of the recent jurisdiction decision. Emphasizing that the Singapore International Commercial Court could address issues pertaining to BVI law, she expressed optimism about an efficient resolution that benefits all parties. Related Reading: Crypto Hedge Fund 3 Arrows Capital (3AC) Files For Bankruptcy Hing noted: We welcome the decision by the Singapore Court as it will ensure that important evidence located in Singapore would be available for the purposes of resolving the dispute in a just and efficient manner. Coupled with the fact that the Singapore International Commercial Court can hear arguments on and decide on BVI law issues, we believe that having the dispute heard in Singapore will result in considerable savings of costs and time for all parties. Featured image from Unsplash, Chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The crypto finance world has witnessed numerous disputes, but few have been similar to that of the ongoing feud between DeFiance Capital and <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/crypto-hedge-fund-3-arrows-capital-3ac-files-for-bankruptcy/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Three Arrows Capital Limited (3AC)</a>. Particularly, this dispute underscores the intricate interplay between traditional financial frameworks and the evolving dynamics of digital assets.</p>
<p>In a tweet posted earlier today, DeFiance Capital CEO shed new light on their ongoing legal tussle with 3AC, suggesting a turn in the tide.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Statement and Update on Dispute with Three Arrows Capital Limited (3AC)</p>
<p>We are very pleased to share a positive development on our end with the public.</p>
<p>It is well-known that for the past year, we have been locked in a dispute with the 3AC estate who are claiming that the assets…</p>
<p>— Arthur (@Arthur_0x) <a href="https://twitter.com/Arthur_0x/status/1691400992645087232?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">August 15, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<h2>DeFiance Capital: A Year-long Struggle</h2>
<p>Almost a year ago, the disagreement between DeFiance Capital and the 3AC estate took center stage when the estate contended that the assets held by DeFiance Capital should be used to square off the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/nft/3ac-nfts-sale-to-commence-soon-due-to-liquidation/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">debts of 3AC</a>.</p>

<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w g0rxnol2" dir="ltr">Countering this claim, DeFiance maintained that they had complete authority and rightful ownership of their assets. This stance, they assert, aligns with common industry perceptions and is supported by available evidence.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The debate took a geographical turn when the liquidators insisted on settling the dispute in the British Virgin Islands (BVI). DeFiance Capital, which was managed from Singapore alongside 3AC, found this choice of jurisdiction puzzling. </p>
<p dir="ltr">They argued that the primary evidence and witnesses were <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/crypto/singapore-red-cross-to-accept-crypto/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">based in Singapore</a>, making it a more apt location for the hearing. Their persistence bore fruit last week when the High Court of Singapore agreed to their jurisdiction preference, subtly undermining the liquidators&#8217; earlier narrative that DeFiance&#8217;s stance held no ground.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">The Road Ahead: Seeking Effective Resolutions</h2>
<p>Despite these disagreements, DeFiance has shown a willingness to collaborate. They have extended assistance to 3AC&#8217;s liquidators in understanding the position of DeFiance and even offered help in identifying 3AC&#8217;s assets.</p>
<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w g0rxnol2" dir="ltr">The intention, as expressed by the CEO &amp; CIO of DeFiance, was to minimize the resources spent on deciding the hearing location and instead concentrate on the core issues at hand.</p>
<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w g0rxnol2" dir="ltr">However, the journey hasn&#8217;t been without its hitches. The liquidators faced setbacks in the US while trying to hold Three Arrows Capital Co-Founder  Kyle Davies accountable in a US court. This effort was thwarted when it came to light that Davies was no longer a US citizen, an <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/crypto/judge-declares-crypto-is-personal-property/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">information oversight</a> that resulted in unnecessary legal expenses.</p>
<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w g0rxnol2" dir="ltr">Blossom Hing, representing DeFiance, highlighted the significance of the recent jurisdiction decision. Emphasizing that the Singapore International Commercial Court could address issues pertaining to BVI law, she expressed optimism about an efficient resolution that benefits all parties.</p>

<p dir="ltr">Hing noted:</p>
<blockquote>
<p dir="ltr">We welcome the decision by the Singapore Court as it will ensure that important evidence located in Singapore would be available for the purposes of resolving the dispute in a just and efficient manner. Coupled with the fact that the Singapore International Commercial Court can hear arguments on and decide on BVI law issues, we believe that having the dispute heard in Singapore will result in considerable savings of costs and time for all parties.</p>
</blockquote>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/ufLoPCNB/" alt="The global crypto market cap value on TradingView" width="2770" height="1408"/>
<p dir="ltr">Featured image from Unsplash, Chart from TradingView</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/DeFiance-Capital-Gains-Upper-Hand-In-Jurisdiction-Battle-Against-3AC.jpg?fit=460%2C307" width="460" height="307" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">547334</post-id>	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
