<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
>

<channel>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.newsbtc.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<description>Bitcoin &#38; Cryptocurrency News Today</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 14:01:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>MATIC Gains 10% In One Day, Is A Price Rally Coming?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/matic/matic-gains-10-in-one-day-is-a-price-rally-coming/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Semilore Faleti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 14:00:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[MATIC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[July]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Polygon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[price rally]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Santiment]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=542147</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[MATIC, the native token of the Polygon network, has witnessed a significant price gain in the last day, drawing much attention from investors. According to data by CoinMarketCap, MATIC gained by 10.44% over the last 24 hours, representing a better market performance than most top assets, including Bitcoin (BTC), Ethereum (ETH), Solana (SOL), etc. MATIC&#8217;s Price Overview In July  Since the beginning of the month, the MATIC market has experienced a series of gains and losses, which, so far, have been in line with the general crypto market. Related Reading: BNB Price at Make-or-Break Levels As The Bulls Aim Big Above This Resistance MATIC began the month trading around $0.66 before witnessing a steady price rise to hit the $0.71 resistance zone on July 4. However, after failing to break past this barrier, the ERC-20 token saw its price fall by 7%, returning to the $0.66 price mark the following day. On July 6, MATIC attempted another bullish run but was followed by a sharp price decline. But since then, the token has seen a steady price increase since then, leading up to its recent price boost.  In the early hours of today, MATIC‘s price shot up by 10%, breaking past the $0.71 resistance level to attain a peak price of $0.74, and has since remained in that zone. This price increase moves MATIC&#8217;s total gain in July to 12.12% as of this writing. In addition, blockchain analytics firm Santiment also reported the Polygon utility token to have recently witnessed “some positive on-chain signs.&#8221; These included an increase in new daily addresses, declining exchange supply, and low-profit taking. According to data by CoinMarketCap, MATIC is currently exchanging hands at $0.74, with a 0.86% gain in the last hour. The token’s trading volume is up by 93.17% and is now sitting at $543.19 million. With a market cap of $6.9 billion, MATIC ranks as the 12th-largest cryptocurrency. Is A Bullish Run On For MATIC? Following MATIC’s price hike today, there is likely much speculation on the token’s next movement. Looking at its 4-hour chart, the Relative Strength Index (RSI) has just dipped below the overbought zone indicating a bearish trend on the horizon.  However, its Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD) is well-placed above the signal line, so the bullish run may still be on. According to MATIC’s price movement, the token appears to be in an ascending channel recording higher highs and lows in the last month. If MATIC manages to break out of its current consolidation zone, it is expected to only trade as high as $0.77, which represents its next resistance level. Related Reading: MATIC Price Prediction: Polygon Bulls Aim For $0.80 On the other hand, if the bears do assume control of the market,  they could push the price of MATIC as low as $0.69, which marks the token’s next support level.  In other news, the general crypto market has witnessed an upturn from its form yesterday, with the total crypto market cap having increased by 1.4% in the last 24 hours.  MATIC Trading At $0.7385 On The 4-Hour Chart &#124; Source: MATICUSD Chart On Tradingview.com Featured Image From Investeek, Chart From Tradingview]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MATIC, the native token of the Polygon network, has witnessed a significant price gain in the last day, drawing much attention from investors. According to <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/polygon/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">data by CoinMarketCap,</a> MATIC gained by 10.44% over the last 24 hours, representing a better market performance than most top assets, including Bitcoin (BTC), Ethereum (ETH), Solana (SOL), etc.</p>
<h2>MATIC&#8217;s Price Overview In July </h2>
<p>Since the beginning of the month, the MATIC market has experienced a series of gains and losses, which, so far, have been in line with the general crypto market.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/bnb/bnb-price-resistance-255/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">BNB Price at Make-or-Break Levels As The Bulls Aim Big Above This Resistance</a></p>
<p>MATIC began the month trading around $0.66 before witnessing a steady price rise to hit the $0.71 resistance zone on July 4. However, after failing to break past this barrier, the ERC-20 token saw its price fall by 7%, returning to the $0.66 price mark the following day.</p>
<p>On July 6, MATIC attempted another bullish run but was followed by a sharp price decline. But since then, the token has seen a steady price increase since then, leading up to its recent price boost. </p>
<p>In the early hours of today, MATIC‘s price shot up by 10%, breaking past the $0.71 resistance level to attain a peak price of $0.74, and has since remained in that zone. This price increase moves MATIC&#8217;s total gain in July to 12.12% as of this writing.</p>
<p>In addition, blockchain analytics firm Santiment also<a href="https://twitter.com/santimentfeed/status/1678449031952089088?s=46&amp;t=JAUmthpFclo8jS4VJkm3DQ" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow"> reported</a> the Polygon utility token to have recently witnessed “some positive on-chain signs.&#8221; These included an increase in new daily addresses, declining exchange supply, and low-profit taking.</p>
<p>According to data by CoinMarketCap, MATIC is currently exchanging hands at $0.74, with a 0.86% gain in the last hour. The token’s trading volume is up by 93.17% and is now sitting at $543.19 million. With a market cap of $6.9 billion, MATIC ranks as the 12th-largest cryptocurrency.</p>
<h2>Is A Bullish Run On For MATIC?</h2>
<p>Following MATIC’s price hike today, there is likely much speculation on the token’s next movement. Looking at its 4-hour chart, the Relative Strength Index (RSI) has just dipped below the overbought zone indicating a bearish trend on the horizon.  However, its Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD) is well-placed above the signal line, so the bullish run may still be on.</p>
<p>According to MATIC’s price movement, the token appears to be in an ascending channel recording higher highs and lows in the last month. If MATIC manages to break out of its current consolidation zone, it is expected to only trade as high as $0.77, which represents its next resistance level.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/matic-analysis/matic-price-prediction-polygon-aim-0-80/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">MATIC Price Prediction: Polygon Bulls Aim For $0.80</a></p>
<p>On the other hand, if the bears do assume control of the market,  they could push the price of MATIC as low as $0.69, which marks the token’s next support level. </p>
<p>In other news, the general crypto market has witnessed an upturn from its form yesterday, with the total crypto market cap having increased by 1.4% in the last 24 hours. </p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/zQtellPV/" alt="MATIC" width="1480" height="913"/></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/bb204098c64b9c700d51f38e6e7fbb7d-460x259.jpeg" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Update: Top 3 Altcoins To Watch This Week</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/crypto-update-top-3-altcoins-watch-this-week/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jake Simmons]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 12:55:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrencies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MATIC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIB]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shiba Inu]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sol]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Solana]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=542115</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[While the Bitcoin price is currently stuck in a sideways trend, a few altcoins on the crypto market are currently showing a strong momentum. These three altcoins are currently attracting the attention of investors and traders alike: Shiba Inu (SHIB), Solana (SOL), and Polygon (MATIC). Let&#8217;s dive into the technical chart analysis of these altcoins and examine the potential price moves that could unfold this week. Shiba Inu (SHIB) &#8211; A Make-or-Break Moment SHIB finds itself at a critical juncture, where the next move could determine its trajectory for the rest of the year. After experiencing a remarkable rally earlier this year, SHIB entered a descending trend channel at the beginning of February, dragging its price below the yearly opening level. However, a breakthrough from this channel occurred over the weekend, signaling a potential reversal. Related Reading: Arkham’s New Crypto Intel Trading Platform: A Game Changer For Traders? As the SHIB bulls attempt to validate this breakout, their success could propel the price upwards by 30%, as NewsBTC reported yesterday. This would bring SHIB towards the resistance area between $0.00000969 (200-day EMA) and $0.00000977 (38.2% Fibonacci), with a significant psychological milestone of $0.00001 within reach. Nonetheless, a confirmation of the breakout is still pending. While the Shiba Inu price managed to stay above the trend channel yesterday, the bulls are still hesitant to make an impulsive move higher towards the 23.6% Fibonacci level at $0.00000834. A breakout above this can be seen as confirmation of a trend change. Solana (SOL) &#8211; Rising Against The Crypto Odds Solana (SOL) made a splash in the crypto market last week, recording an impressive 39% price increase over the last 12 days. This surge propelled SOL to the critical resistance level represented by the 200-day exponential moving average (EMA). Breaking through this level has been a persistent challenge for SOL since April 2022, but recent developments offer hope for a potential breakthrough. At press time, the SOL price overcame the 200-EMA at $21.98, trading at 22.07. A daily close above this price level would be massively bullish. SOL&#8217;s rally is particularly noteworthy, considering the setbacks it faced due to the FTX drama and the SEC&#8217;s classification of it as a security. Should the 200-day EMA be breached, the 50% Fibonacci retracement level and the yearly high at $27.00 could serve as the next targets for an extended rally, which could give investors another 22% profit, as detailed in our last analysis. Related Reading: Hackers Have Stolen $30 Billion In Crypto Since 2012, SlowMist Report Finds Polygon (MATIC) &#8211; New Momentum Recent developments have sparked interest and potential opportunities for investors. The announcement of former Chief Legal Officer Marc Boiron as the new CEO has generated positive sentiment within the community. On-chain data indicates a significant spike in social volume following the news, suggesting increased attention and potential bullish sentiment for MATIC&#8217;s price.  From a technical standpoint, MATIC has seen a 40% increase since its local bottom in June. The price currently sits below the 23.6% Fibonacci retracement level, and a breakout above this level could potentially drive MATIC towards the 200-day EMA and the 38.2% Fibonacci retracement level, offering a 22% rally. However, breaking the resistance at the first Fibonacci level at $0.756 is a crucial step to watch for potential upward momentum. Please note: The analysis and observations in this article should not be considered financial advice. Cryptocurrency investments carry inherent risks, and readers are urged to conduct thorough research before making any investment decisions. Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>While the Bitcoin price is currently stuck in a sideways trend, a few altcoins on the crypto market are currently showing a strong momentum. These three altcoins are currently attracting the attention of investors and traders alike: Shiba Inu (SHIB), Solana (SOL), and Polygon (MATIC). Let&#8217;s dive into the technical chart analysis of these altcoins and examine the potential price moves that could unfold this week.</p>
<h2>Shiba Inu (SHIB) &#8211; A Make-or-Break Moment</h2>
<p>SHIB finds itself at a critical juncture, where the next move could determine its trajectory for the rest of the year. After experiencing a remarkable rally earlier this year, SHIB entered a descending trend channel at the beginning of February, dragging its price below the yearly opening level. However, a breakthrough from this channel occurred over the weekend, signaling a potential reversal.</p>

<p>As the SHIB bulls attempt to validate this breakout, their success could propel the price upwards by 30%, as NewsBTC <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/shiba-inu-shib-breakout-alert-potential-30-rally/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">reported</a> yesterday. This would bring SHIB towards the resistance area between $0.00000969 (200-day EMA) and $0.00000977 (38.2% Fibonacci), with a significant psychological milestone of $0.00001 within reach.</p>
<p>Nonetheless, a confirmation of the breakout is still pending. While the Shiba Inu price managed to stay above the trend channel yesterday, the bulls are still hesitant to make an impulsive move higher towards the 23.6% Fibonacci level at $0.00000834. A breakout above this can be seen as confirmation of a trend change.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-542123 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/SHIBUSD_2023-07-11_10-31-12.png" alt="Shiba Inu price" width="3628" height="1672" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/SHIBUSD_2023-07-11_10-31-12.png 3628w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/SHIBUSD_2023-07-11_10-31-12-460x212.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/SHIBUSD_2023-07-11_10-31-12-860x396.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/SHIBUSD_2023-07-11_10-31-12-768x354.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/SHIBUSD_2023-07-11_10-31-12-1536x708.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/SHIBUSD_2023-07-11_10-31-12-2048x944.png 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/SHIBUSD_2023-07-11_10-31-12-750x346.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/SHIBUSD_2023-07-11_10-31-12-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 3628px) 100vw, 3628px"/>
<h2>Solana (SOL) &#8211; Rising Against The Crypto Odds</h2>
<p>Solana (SOL) made a splash in the crypto market last week, recording an impressive 39% price increase over the last 12 days. This surge propelled SOL to the critical resistance level represented by the 200-day exponential moving average (EMA).</p>
<p>Breaking through this level has been a persistent challenge for SOL since April 2022, but recent developments offer hope for a potential breakthrough. At press time, the SOL price overcame the 200-EMA at $21.98, trading at 22.07. A daily close above this price level would be massively bullish.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-542122 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/SOLUSD_2023-07-11_10-28-31.png" alt="Solana crypto SOL price" width="3628" height="1672" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/SOLUSD_2023-07-11_10-28-31.png 3628w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/SOLUSD_2023-07-11_10-28-31-460x212.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/SOLUSD_2023-07-11_10-28-31-860x396.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/SOLUSD_2023-07-11_10-28-31-768x354.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/SOLUSD_2023-07-11_10-28-31-1536x708.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/SOLUSD_2023-07-11_10-28-31-2048x944.png 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/SOLUSD_2023-07-11_10-28-31-750x346.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/SOLUSD_2023-07-11_10-28-31-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 3628px) 100vw, 3628px"/>
<p>SOL&#8217;s rally is particularly noteworthy, considering the setbacks it faced due to the FTX drama and the SEC&#8217;s classification of it as a security. Should the 200-day EMA be breached, the 50% Fibonacci retracement level and the yearly high at $27.00 could serve as the next targets for an extended rally, which could give investors another 22% profit, as <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/solana/solana-sol-prediction-price-hits-key-resistance-whats-next/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">detailed </a>in our last analysis.</p>

<h2>Polygon (MATIC) &#8211; New Momentum</h2>
<p>Recent developments have sparked interest and potential opportunities for investors. The <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/matic-analysis/polygon-labs-ceo-steps-down-chief-legal-officer-takes-the-helm/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">announcement</a> of former Chief Legal Officer Marc Boiron as the new CEO has generated positive sentiment within the community. On-chain data indicates a significant spike in social volume following the news, suggesting increased attention and potential bullish sentiment for MATIC&#8217;s price. </p>
<p>From a technical standpoint, MATIC has seen a 40% increase since its local bottom in June. The price currently sits below the 23.6% Fibonacci retracement level, and a breakout above this level could potentially drive MATIC towards the 200-day EMA and the 38.2% Fibonacci retracement level, offering a 22% rally. However, breaking the resistance at the first Fibonacci level at $0.756 is a crucial step to watch for potential upward momentum.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-542125 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/MATICUSD_2023-07-11_10-33-59.png" alt="Polygon MATIC price" width="3628" height="1672" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/MATICUSD_2023-07-11_10-33-59.png 3628w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/MATICUSD_2023-07-11_10-33-59-460x212.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/MATICUSD_2023-07-11_10-33-59-860x396.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/MATICUSD_2023-07-11_10-33-59-768x354.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/MATICUSD_2023-07-11_10-33-59-1536x708.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/MATICUSD_2023-07-11_10-33-59-2048x944.png 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/MATICUSD_2023-07-11_10-33-59-750x346.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/MATICUSD_2023-07-11_10-33-59-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 3628px) 100vw, 3628px"/>
<p><em>Please note: The analysis and observations in this article should not be considered financial advice. Cryptocurrency investments carry inherent risks, and readers are urged to conduct thorough research before making any investment decisions.</em></p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/iStock-1357255026-460x259.jpg" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ex Paxful CEO Warns Users to &#8216;Stop Trading&#8217;, Are Their Funds At Risk?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/ex-paxful-ceo-warns-users-to-stop-trading-are-their-funds-at-risk/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ebo Victor]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 12:00:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[paxful]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=542110</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Paxful, founded in 2015, has established itself as one of the world&#8217;s prominent peer-to-peer Bitcoin marketplaces, with a strong mission to enable financial access for individuals globally. Boasting an extensive user base of 9 million and offering over 350 payment options, the platform has garnered substantial popularity. However, on July 7, Ray Youssef, the former CEO of Paxful, conveyed a message to the platform&#8217;s users, urging them to cease trading activities. Financial Instability And Comparisons To FTX Collapse Youssef expressed concerns about the current state of Paxful, claiming that the company is now solely focused on paying legal bills and cautioned that no African or non-American should trust any IS corporation. These warnings from Youssef were prompted by reports that Paxful had removed the reserve funds amount from the platform&#8217;s status page. Related Reading: Paxful CEO Says He Has ‘Lost’ 5 Bank Accounts Reserve funds are often savings accounts or highly liquid assets placed aside to cover unforeseen financial responsibilities, and Youssef believes that Paxful&#8217;s lack of reserves puts the company at risk of financial instability. Without these funds, Paxful may struggle to manage cash flow fluctuations, fulfill immediate financial obligations, or respond effectively to emergencies. Consequently, this situation has the potential to jeopardize Paxful&#8217;s survival. Youssef also concurred with a Twitter user who compared Paxful and the collapse of FTX. The user highlighted that FTX, despite being one of the world&#8217;s largest cryptocurrency exchanges at the time, had filed for bankruptcy. This collapse was triggered by Changpeng Zhao, the CEO of Binance, announcing that his exchange would be dumping its FTT Token holdings, amounting to around $2 billion. The bank run that followed this announcement opened up a web of lies and mismanagement that led to the eventual collapse of the exchange. The announcement caused a sharp decline in the price of FTT and generated concern among investors. As a result, traders hurriedly withdrew their funds from FTX, leading the company to confront a substantial $8 billion shortfall. To prevent a similar case like FTX bankruptcy, Youssef advised Paxful users to withdraw their funds until further investigation is conducted to uncover the truth behind the situation. By taking control of their own cryptocurrency assets, users can mitigate potential risks and ensure the security of their investments Related Reading: FTX Puts Sale Of $500 Million Stake In AI Firm Anthropic On Hold Youssef&#8217;s Concerns And Allegations Post-Departure From Paxful Trading on various P2P marketplaces, including Paxful, was temporarily suspended in early April due to regulatory reasons. When Paxful announced the resumption of services, Ray Youssef, who had already left the organization, expressed his uncertainty regarding the current state of affairs and emphasized his inability to vouch for anything happening within Paxful. Since he departed from the exchange, Youssef has been actively promoting Civkit, the platform he founded. While many of his followers have praised his efforts, accusations have labeled him an attention seeker. Additionally, some individuals have accused him of leveraging his influence to undermine competitors and rivals in the industry. Featured image from Shutterstock, charts from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Paxful, founded in 2015, has established itself as one of the world&#8217;s prominent peer-to-peer Bitcoin marketplaces, with a strong mission to enable financial access for individuals globally. Boasting an extensive user base of 9 million and offering over 350 payment options, the platform has garnered substantial popularity.</p>
<p>However, on July 7, Ray Youssef, the former CEO of Paxful, conveyed a message to the platform&#8217;s users, urging them to cease trading activities.</p>
<h2>Financial Instability And Comparisons To FTX Collapse</h2>
<p><a href="https://twitter.com/raycivkit/status/1677424162015461377?t=AodsJaBDJWzQgjHkEAnIoQ&amp;s=19" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Youssef expressed concerns</a> about the current state of Paxful, claiming that the company is now solely focused on paying legal bills and cautioned that no African or non-American should trust any IS corporation. These warnings from Youssef were prompted by reports that Paxful had removed the reserve funds amount from the platform&#8217;s status page.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/paxful-ceo-says-he-has-lost-5-bank-accounts/?swcfpc=1">Paxful CEO Says He Has ‘Lost’ 5 Bank Accounts</a></p>
<p>Reserve funds are often savings accounts or highly liquid assets placed aside to cover unforeseen financial responsibilities, and Youssef believes that Paxful&#8217;s lack of reserves puts the company at risk of financial instability. Without these funds, Paxful may struggle to manage cash flow fluctuations, fulfill immediate financial obligations, or respond effectively to emergencies. Consequently, this situation has the potential to jeopardize Paxful&#8217;s survival.</p>
<p>Youssef also concurred with a <a href="https://twitter.com/raycivkit/status/1677424162015461377?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Twitter user</a> who compared Paxful and the collapse of FTX. The user highlighted that FTX, despite being one of the world&#8217;s largest cryptocurrency exchanges at the time, had filed for bankruptcy. This collapse was triggered by Changpeng Zhao, the CEO of Binance, announcing that his exchange would be dumping its FTT Token holdings, amounting to around $2 billion. The bank run that followed this announcement opened up a web of lies and mismanagement that led to the eventual collapse of the exchange.</p>
<p>The announcement caused a sharp decline in the price of <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/ftx/ftt-flies-45-on-rumors-of-ftx-planned-relaunch/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">FTT</a> and generated concern among investors. As a result, traders hurriedly withdrew their funds from FTX, leading the company to confront a substantial $8 billion shortfall.</p>
<p>To prevent a similar case like FTX bankruptcy, Youssef advised Paxful users to withdraw their funds until further investigation is conducted to uncover the truth behind the situation.</p>
<blockquote><p>By taking control of their own cryptocurrency assets, users can mitigate potential risks and ensure the security of their investments</p></blockquote>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/ftx/ftx-puts-sale-of-500-million-stake-in-ai-firm-anthropic-on-hold/?swcfpc=1">FTX Puts Sale Of $500 Million Stake In AI Firm Anthropic On Hold</a></p>
<h2>Youssef&#8217;s Concerns And Allegations Post-Departure From Paxful</h2>
<p>Trading on various P2P marketplaces, including Paxful, was temporarily suspended in early April due to regulatory reasons. When Paxful announced the resumption of services, Ray Youssef, who had already left the organization, <a href="https://twitter.com/raycivkit/status/1677432977184137217?t=Of8jGSEroNdmKzJdfgjNog&amp;s=19" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">expressed his uncertainty</a> regarding the current state of affairs and emphasized his inability to vouch for anything happening within Paxful.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/6Z3RrQKA/" alt="Paxful " width="1515" height="638"/>
<p>Since he departed from the exchange, Youssef has been actively promoting <a href="https://civkit.org/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Civkit</a>, the platform he founded. While many of his followers have praised his efforts, accusations have labeled him an attention seeker. Additionally, some individuals have accused him of leveraging his influence to undermine competitors and rivals in the industry.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/paxful-460x242.jpg" width="460" height="242" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Standard Chartered Raises Bitcoin Forecast To $120,000, Citing Miners&#8217; Reduced Selling</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/standard-chartered-raises-bitcoin-forecast/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samuel Edyme]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 11:00:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[prediction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Standered Chartered]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=542074</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Standard Chartered, one of the world&#8217;s leading banks, has raised its long-term Bitcoin price forecast, predicting that the value of the flagship cryptocurrency could reach $120,000 by the end of 2024. This upward revision comes as the bank acknowledges the potential for miners to hold a larger share of the newly minted Bitcoin supply. With the recent surge in Bitcoin&#8217;s price, Standard Chartered sees an opportunity for miners to reduce their selling activities, which could have implications for the cryptocurrency&#8217;s scarcity and future value. Miners&#8217; Role In Bitcoin Value Proposition Miners hold a significant position within the crypto ecosystem, as they are responsible for the creation and upkeep of the network. And Standard Chartered&#8217;s forecast of Bitcoin reaching $120,000 by the end of 2024 is rooted in the notion that miners may adapt their selling practices to cover operational expenses, particularly the costs of electricity required for mining activities. Related Reading: Standard Chartered Predicts Bitcoin Could Reach $100,000 By End of 2024 By reducing the portion of newly generated Bitcoins they sell, miners can balance their cash inflows while simultaneously decreasing the overall supply of Bitcoin available in the market. This adjustment in selling behavior has the potential to impact the supply-demand dynamics of Bitcoin and potentially contribute to a surge in its value. The rationale behind Standard Chartered&#8217;s prediction lies in the assumption that miners, who currently produce approximately 900 new BTC daily on a global scale, will opt to hold onto a larger portion of their newly minted coins. By doing so, they can cover their operational costs more efficiently. If this adjustment occurs and the proportion of BTC sold by miners decreases, it could lead to a reduction in the net supply of Bitcoin by roughly 250,000  BTC per year. Such a decrease in supply has the potential to exert upward pressure on the value of Bitcoin as demand potentially outpaces the available coins in circulation. Factors Driving Standard Chartered&#8217;s Optimism Standard Chartered&#8217;s revised forecast is underpinned by the expectation that increased profitability for miners per Bitcoin mined will encourage them to hold onto a larger portion of their newly minted supply. Geoff Kendrick, a top FX analyst at the bank, suggests that as Bitcoin&#8217;s price approaches the $50,000 threshold, miners may reduce the proportion of BTC they sell from 100% to approximately 20-30%. This reduction in daily supply, from 900 BTC to a range of 180-270, would equate to a significant reduction in net BTC supply of roughly 250,000 BTC per year. Furthermore, Kendrick points to an upcoming event that will halve the number of BTC that can be mined each day, which is an intrinsic feature of Bitcoin&#8217;s design. This mechanism, known as the &#8220;halving,&#8221; gradually limits the supply of new BTC to maintain scarcity and mitigate inflation. Related Reading: Dormant Bitcoin Supply Peaks As Institutional Investors Show Increased Involvement By combining the potential reduction in miner selling with the forthcoming halving, Standard Chartered anticipates an environment conducive to a sustained increase in Bitcoin&#8217;s price over the long term. Meanwhile, over the past day, Bitcoin has traded below the $31,000 level particularly, with a market price of $30,441, at the time of writing.  Nevertheless, the asset is seeing 1% gains in the last 24 hours with a 24-hour trading volume of $10.6 billion. Featured image from Unsplash, Chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Standard Chartered, one of the world&#8217;s leading banks, has <a href="https://www.reuters.com/technology/standard-chartered-bumps-up-bitcoin-forecast-120000-2023-07-10/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">raised</a> its long-term Bitcoin price forecast, predicting that the value of the flagship cryptocurrency could reach $120,000 by the end of 2024. This <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/standard-chartered-predicts-bitcoin-could-reach-100000/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">upward revision</a> comes as the bank acknowledges the potential for miners to hold a larger share of the newly minted Bitcoin supply. </p>
<p>With the recent surge in Bitcoin&#8217;s price, Standard Chartered sees an opportunity for miners to reduce their selling activities, which could have implications for the cryptocurrency&#8217;s scarcity and future value.</p>
<h2>Miners&#8217; Role In Bitcoin Value Proposition</h2>
<p>Miners hold a significant position within the crypto ecosystem, as they are responsible for the creation and upkeep of the network. And Standard Chartered&#8217;s forecast of Bitcoin reaching $120,000 by the end of 2024 is rooted in the notion that miners may adapt their <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/surging-demand-for-bitcoin-ordinals-propels-to-210m/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">selling practices</a> to cover operational expenses, particularly the costs of electricity required for mining activities.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/standard-chartered-predicts-bitcoin-could-reach-100000/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Standard Chartered Predicts Bitcoin Could Reach $100,000 By End of 2024</a></p>
<p>By reducing the portion of newly generated Bitcoins they sell, miners can balance their cash inflows while simultaneously decreasing the overall supply of Bitcoin available in the market. This adjustment in selling behavior has the potential to impact the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/dormant-bitcoin-supply-peaks-as-institutional-investors/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">supply-demand dynamics o</a>f Bitcoin and potentially contribute to a surge in its value.</p>
<p>The rationale behind Standard Chartered&#8217;s prediction lies in the assumption that miners, who currently produce approximately 900 new BTC daily on a global scale, will opt to hold onto a larger portion of their newly minted coins. By doing so, they can cover their operational costs more efficiently. </p>
<p>If this adjustment occurs and the proportion of BTC sold by miners decreases, it could lead to a reduction in the net supply of Bitcoin by roughly 250,000  BTC per year. Such a decrease in supply has the potential to exert upward pressure on the value of Bitcoin as demand potentially outpaces the available coins in circulation.</p>
<h2>Factors Driving Standard Chartered&#8217;s Optimism</h2>
<p>Standard Chartered&#8217;s revised forecast is underpinned by the expectation that increased profitability for miners per Bitcoin mined will encourage them to hold onto a larger portion of their newly minted supply. </p>
<p>Geoff Kendrick, a top FX analyst at the bank, suggests that as Bitcoin&#8217;s price approaches the $50,000 threshold, miners may reduce the proportion of BTC they sell from 100% to approximately 20-30%. This reduction in daily supply, from 900 BTC to a range of 180-270, would equate to a significant reduction in net BTC supply of roughly 250,000 BTC per year.</p>
<p>Furthermore, Kendrick points to an upcoming event that will halve the number of BTC that can be mined each day, which is an intrinsic feature of <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-could-soar-in-next-bull-cycle-predicts-crypto/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Bitcoin&#8217;s design</a>. This mechanism, known as the &#8220;halving,&#8221; gradually limits the supply of new BTC to maintain scarcity and mitigate inflation.</p>

<p>By combining the potential reduction in miner selling with the forthcoming halving, Standard Chartered anticipates an environment conducive to a sustained increase in Bitcoin&#8217;s price over the long term.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/fGtrB6m0/" alt="Bitcoin price chart on TradingView" width="2770" height="1556"/>
<p>Meanwhile, over the past day,<a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/analysts-forecast-bitcoin-btc-to-hit-310000-if-this-happens/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener "> Bitcoin has traded below the $31,000</a> level particularly, with a market price of $30,441, at the time of writing.  Nevertheless, the asset is seeing 1% gains in the last 24 hours with a 24-hour trading volume of $10.6 billion.</p>
<p>Featured image from Unsplash, Chart from TradingView</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-1.jpg" width="350" height="250" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Microstrategy Stock Surges 7% As Berenberg Highlights Bitcoin Halving&#8217;s Impact</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/microstrategy-stock-surges-as-berenberg-highlights-bitcoin-halvings/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samuel Edyme]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 10:00:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Microstrategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MSTR]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=542094</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Hamburg-based Berenberg Capital Markets recently highlighted the upcoming Bitcoin halving event as a potential trigger for the bullish case of Microstrategy, a United States-based software firm, in a recent research note. The research note emphasized that Microstrategy, with a bullish price target of $430, primarily derives its value from its substantial holdings of over 150,000 BTC. And Berenberg expects the historical trend of Bitcoin rallying after each halving to repeat. Halving Events And Bitcoin&#8217;s Market Impact Halving events are significant occurrences in the Bitcoin network that happen approximately every four years. During these events, the rate of new coin issuance is reduced by 50%, resulting in a slower influx of new Bitcoins into the market. The upcoming fourth Bitcoin halving, scheduled for April 26, 2024, is expected to follow this pattern. Related Reading: Michael Saylor Doubles Down On Bitcoin, Adds 12,333 BTC To MicroStrategy’s Holdings Berenberg&#8217;s recent research note highlighted the historical trend observed in the previous three halvings and suggested that a pre-halving rally could potentially commence in about four months. If this rally follows a similar trajectory to previous halvings. It could persist until approximately October 2025, according to the research note. Berenberg noted: If the historical pattern established by the first three Bitcoin halvings continues to play out with the fourth halving, then the pre-halving rally would begin about four months from now. If a rally were to occur after the fourth halving, and if it were as long-lived as the rallies that occurred after the past couple of halvings, then it would continue until around October 2025. Correlation Between Bitcoin And Microstrategy&#8217;s Stock According to the research note, there is a strong correlation between Microstrategy&#8217;s stock price and the price of Bitcoin, estimated to be around 0.90. If the fourth bitcoin halving triggers a significant rally in the price of the cryptocurrency, it is likely that Microstrategy&#8217;s stock will follow suit. This forecast is due to the positive outlook for Bitcoin&#8217;s post-halving performance contributing to the anticipation of a potential rally in Microstrategy&#8217;s stock price. Following the release of Berenberg&#8217;s research note, Microstrategy&#8217;s stock, with the ticker symbol MSTR, has already witnessed a notable surge of 7% in the past day. The stock, which was trading below its current price range in the previous month, is now valued at $407. The market&#8217;s positive response reflects the optimism surrounding the potential impact of the upcoming Bitcoin halving event on Microstrategy&#8217;s performance. Furthermore, it is worth noting that the concept of halving has since been associated with significant market movements in the past. And investors closely monitor these events for potential opportunities. Related Reading: MicroStrategy Bought Bitcoin To Avoid Liquidation, Peter Schiff Reveals The reduction in new coin issuance, combined with market demand, has historically contributed to price appreciation in Bitcoin. As such, the anticipation of the upcoming halving has sparked interest and speculation among market participants. Berenberg&#8217;s analysis adds to the narrative that the halving event could have a bullish impact on the price of Bitcoin. And, consequently, on companies like Microstrategy, which holds a substantial amount of Bitcoin on its balance sheet. Featured image from Blockchain Reporter, Chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Hamburg-based Berenberg Capital Markets recently highlighted the upcoming Bitcoin halving event as a potential trigger for the bullish case of Microstrategy, a United States-based software firm, in a recent research <a href="https://www.theblock.co/post/238784/bitcoin-halving-underpins-bull-case-for-microstrategy-berenberg-says" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">note</a>.</p>
<p>The research note emphasized that <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/michael-saylor-doubles-down-on-bitcoin-adds-12333-btc-to-microstrategys-holdings/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Microstrategy</a>, with a bullish price target of $430, primarily derives its value from its substantial holdings of over 150,000 BTC. And Berenberg expects the historical trend of <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/former-microstrategy-ceo-says-bitcoin-rally-just-getting-started/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Bitcoin rallying</a> after each halving to repeat.</p>
<h2>Halving Events And Bitcoin&#8217;s Market Impact</h2>
<p>Halving events are significant occurrences in the Bitcoin network that happen approximately every four years. During these events, the rate of new coin issuance is reduced by 50%, resulting in a slower influx of new <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/microstrategy-acquired-an-additional-1045-bitcoin/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Bitcoins into the market</a>. The upcoming fourth Bitcoin halving, scheduled for April 26, 2024, is expected to follow this pattern.</p>

<p>Berenberg&#8217;s recent research note highlighted the historical trend observed in the previous three halvings and suggested that a pre-halving rally could potentially commence in about four months. If this rally follows a similar trajectory to previous halvings. It could persist until approximately October 2025, according to the research note.</p>
<p>Berenberg noted:</p>
<blockquote><p>If the historical pattern established by the first three Bitcoin halvings continues to play out with the fourth halving, then the pre-halving rally would begin about four months from now. If a rally were to occur after the fourth halving, and if it were as long-lived as the rallies that occurred after the past couple of halvings, then it would continue until around October 2025.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Correlation Between Bitcoin And Microstrategy&#8217;s Stock</h2>
<p>According to the research note, there is a strong <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/microstrategy-bought-bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">correlation between Microstrategy&#8217;s</a> stock price and the price of Bitcoin, estimated to be around 0.90. If the fourth bitcoin halving triggers a significant rally in the price of the cryptocurrency, it is likely that Microstrategy&#8217;s stock will follow suit. </p>
<p>This forecast is due to the positive outlook for Bitcoin&#8217;s post-halving performance contributing to the anticipation of a potential rally in Microstrategy&#8217;s stock price.</p>
<p>Following the release of Berenberg&#8217;s research note, Microstrategy&#8217;s stock, with the ticker symbol MSTR, has already witnessed a notable surge of 7% in the past day. The stock, which was trading below its current price range in the previous month, is now valued at $407.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/WgxMHFWr/" alt="Microstrategy&#039;s (MSTR) Stock price chart on TradingView amid Berenberg Bitcoin halving impact forecast" width="2770" height="1556"/>
<p>The market&#8217;s positive response reflects the optimism surrounding the potential impact of the upcoming Bitcoin halving event on Microstrategy&#8217;s performance. Furthermore, it is worth noting that the concept of halving has since been associated with significant market movements in the past. And investors closely monitor these events for potential opportunities.</p>

<p>The reduction in new coin issuance, combined with market demand, has historically contributed to <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/rumors-of-microstrategy-selling-bitcoin-grow-with-teslas-disclosure/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">price appreciation in Bitcoin</a>. As such, the anticipation of the upcoming halving has sparked interest and speculation among market participants. </p>
<p>Berenberg&#8217;s analysis adds to the narrative that the halving event could have a bullish impact on the price of Bitcoin. And, consequently, on companies like Microstrategy, which holds a substantial amount of Bitcoin on its balance sheet.</p>
<p>Featured image from Blockchain Reporter, Chart from TradingView</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/microstrategy-bitcoin-750x536-1-460x329.jpeg" width="460" height="329" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dogecoin (DOGE) Price Downtrend Set To Persist &#8211; What To Expect</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/dogecoin-price-downtrend-set-to-persist/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 10:00:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Doge price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[meme coins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price action]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=542126</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Dogecoin (DOGE) experienced a substantial surge on the price chart towards the end of June. However, despite this notable increase, it failed to ward off the sellers who swiftly entered the market.  Can Dogecoin regain its momentum and rise again, or will it succumb to the mounting pressure from the bearish sentiment? Bitcoin (BTC) also experienced a downturn in the previous week, and this negative trend had a noticeable impact on the sentiment surrounding Dogecoin. Unfortunately, the figures did not provide a strong basis for a potential recovery in DOGE. Instead, it indicated a looming decline towards the price range of $0.053 and $0.048. DOGE Bearish Indicators Emerge The current DOGE price on CoinGecko stands at $0.0652, experiencing a modest 0.7% rally within the past 24 hours. However, it is important to note that a decline of 5.8% has been recorded over the course of the past seven days. Source: Coingecko This price movement has prompted a closer examination of the market conditions, revealing some bearish signals and underlying trends. Related Reading: Cardano Price Momentum Bid Fizzles Out Despite New Payment Feature Based on a DOGE price report, it appears that bears are preparing to exert downward pressure on prices once again. The Relative Strength Index (RSI) has slipped below the neutral 50 level, indicating a shift in momentum towards the bearish side, suggesting that selling pressure may increase in the near future. DOGE market cap back at $9 billion. Chart: TradingView.com Additionally, the On-Balance Volume (OBV) has been unable to surpass a resistance level since May, reflecting a lack of interest from buyers. This suggests that market participants may be hesitant to make significant purchases, contributing to the downward pressure on DOGE prices. Related Reading: PEPE Potential Rebound: Key Details You Shouldn’t Miss Although some buyers noticed the recent short-term rally and made purchases as prices slowly edged higher, it is worth noting that this rally pales in comparison to the significant surge the meme coin experienced in early April, when Dogecoin reached the $0.1 level. DOGE seven-day price action. Source: Coingecko. This discrepancy, referring to the difference between the current rally and previous ones, implies that the present market upswing may be lacking an equivalent degree of enthusiasm and support from buyers. This observation raises questions about the sustainability and strength of the crypto. Outlook For DOGE The bearish signals observed, such as the RSI dropping below the neutral 50 level and the lack of conviction from buyers indicated by the OBV, suggest a challenging road ahead for DOGE. These factors may contribute to increased selling pressure and further price declines. Considering the current market conditions, it is important to approach the outlook for DOGE with caution. The short-term rally, although relatively subdued compared to past performances, could still offer opportunities for traders looking for quick gains. However, it is vital to remain vigilant and closely monitor the market dynamics. (This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk). Featured image from iStock]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Dogecoin (DOGE) experienced a substantial surge on the price chart towards the end of June. However, despite this notable increase, it failed to ward off the sellers who swiftly entered the market. </p>
<p>Can Dogecoin regain its momentum and rise again, or will it succumb to the mounting pressure from the bearish sentiment?</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC) also experienced a downturn in the previous week, and this negative trend had a noticeable impact on the sentiment surrounding Dogecoin. </p>
<p>Unfortunately, the figures did not provide a strong basis for a potential recovery in DOGE. Instead, it indicated a looming decline towards the price range of $0.053 and $0.048.</p>
<h2><strong>DOGE Bearish Indicators Emerge</strong></h2>
<p>The current <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/dogecoin" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">DOGE price on CoinGecko</a> stands at $0.0652, experiencing a modest 0.7% rally within the past 24 hours. However, it is important to note that a decline of 5.8% has been recorded over the course of the past seven days.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-542130" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-63.png" alt="" width="1138" height="62" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-63.png 1138w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-63-460x25.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-63-860x47.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-63-768x42.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-63-750x41.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 1138px) 100vw, 1138px"/></p>

<p>This price movement has prompted a closer examination of the market conditions, revealing some bearish signals and underlying trends.</p>

<p>Based on a <a href="https://ambcrypto.com/why-dogecoin-is-set-to-continue-its-downtrend-after-the-late-june-rally/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">DOGE price report</a>, it appears that bears are preparing to exert downward pressure on prices once again. The Relative Strength Index (RSI) has slipped below the neutral 50 level, indicating a shift in momentum towards the bearish side, suggesting that selling pressure may increase in the near future.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/fZnU911e/" width="2475" height="1187"/></p>

<p>Additionally, the On-Balance Volume (OBV) has been unable to surpass a resistance level since May, reflecting a lack of interest from buyers. This suggests that market participants may be hesitant to make significant purchases, contributing to the downward pressure on DOGE prices.</p>

<p>Although some buyers noticed the recent short-term rally and made purchases as prices slowly edged higher, it is worth noting that this rally pales in comparison to the significant surge the meme coin experienced in early April, when Dogecoin reached the $0.1 level.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-542142" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-65.png" alt="" width="778" height="477" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-65.png 778w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-65-460x282.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-65-768x471.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-65-750x460.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 778px) 100vw, 778px"/></p>

<p>This discrepancy, referring to the difference between the current rally and previous ones, implies that the present market upswing may be lacking an equivalent degree of enthusiasm and support from buyers. This observation raises questions about the sustainability and strength of the crypto.</p>
<h2><strong>Outlook For DOGE</strong></h2>
<p>The bearish signals observed, such as the RSI dropping below the neutral 50 level and the lack of conviction from buyers indicated by the OBV, suggest a challenging road ahead for DOGE. These factors may contribute to increased selling pressure and further price declines.</p>
<p>Considering the current market conditions, it is important to approach the outlook for DOGE with caution. The short-term rally, although relatively subdued compared to past performances, could still offer opportunities for traders looking for quick gains. However, it is vital to remain vigilant and closely monitor the market dynamics.</p>
<p><em>(This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk).</em></p>
<p><em>Featured image from iStock</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-64-460x267.png" width="460" height="267" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin At Mid-Cycle Point: Historical Pattern Repeating Itself?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-mid-cycle-point-historical-pattern-repeating/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jake Simmons]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 08:50:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[glassnode]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[halving]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=542088</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin has reached a critical juncture in its current market cycle, according to a recent analysis conducted by on-chain analytics firm Glassnode. The data reveals striking similarities to historical patterns, raising questions about the potential emergence of a familiar phenomenon: the re-accumulation period. A Resilient Market: Bitcoin Holds Firm At Mid-Cycle The Glassnode analysis reveals that Bitcoin is consolidating around the $30,000 mark, which acts as a significant mid-point within the 2021-2023 cycle. The historical significance of this level is not to be overlooked, as it has been tested repeatedly in previous cycles. Remarkably, the mid-cycle phenomenon is not exclusive to the current cycle; similar mid-cycle points were observed in both 2013-2016 and 2018-2019, displaying analogous supply dynamics. As Bitcoin currently hovers around the $30,000 mid-point, approximately 75% of the total supply is currently held in a profitable state, while the remaining 25% remains in a loss position. This balance of supply held in profit versus loss is reminiscent of equilibrium points witnessed during previous cycles, indicating a potential re-accumulation period. Related Reading: Bitcoin Hash Rate Retakes All-Time High As Miners Continue To Expand Capacity As Glassnode explains, &#8220;This 75:25 balance of supply held in profit:loss is the equilibrium point for Bitcoin. 50% of all trading days have seen a higher Profit-to-Loss balance, and 50% a lower one.&#8221; Such equilibrium points have historically required time for the market to digest and re-consolidate around, often accompanied by a period of sideways trading and volatility. This has become known as the &#8220;re-accumulation period.&#8221; At the moment, The supply held &#8220;in-loss&#8221; has declined to just 4.79 million BTC, reaching similar levels seen in July 2021 ($30k), July 2020 ($9.2k), April 2016 ($6.5k), and March 2016 ($425). Robust Recovery And Historical Comparisons According to Glassnode, Bitcoin&#8217;s price performance in 2023 has demonstrated remarkable resilience, with a maximum drawdown of only -18% thus far, a shallow correction compared to previous cycles. This suggests a substantial underlying demand for the asset and indicates a potential strong degree of investor support. Related Reading: Bitcoin Google Search Interest Stands At Critical Level, What This Forecast For BTC Glassnode&#8217;s analysis further highlights the similarities between the current recovery rally and those observed in prior cycles. Historically, recovery rallies following a similar magnitude move off the cycle&#8217;s bottom often marked the genesis of a new cyclical uptrend. While exceptions exist, the parallels between the current recovery and those of the past offer an intriguing possibility for Bitcoin&#8217;s future trajectory. The report notes, &#8220;With the exception of 2019, all prior cycles which experienced a similar magnitude move off the bottom were, in fact, the genesis point of a new cyclical uptrend.&#8221; Remarkably, previous re-accumulation periods were characterized by a lack of macro market direction and tending to trade sideways. “With the market back at this equilibrium point, it remains to be seen if a similarly lengthy and choppy process is needed to overcome it,” concludes Glassnode. The Takeaway: Will History Repeat For BTC? Glassnode&#8217;s analysis unveils a fascinating narrative within Bitcoin&#8217;s ongoing market cycle. The emergence of the mid-cycle point and the familiar supply dynamics indicate that historical patterns are repeating themselves. While no crystal ball can predict the future with certainty, these insights offer intriguing possibilities for Bitcoin&#8217;s trajectory. At press time, the BTC price was at $30,626 and remained in the trading range of the last two weeks. Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin has reached a critical juncture in its current market cycle, according to a recent <a href="https://insights.glassnode.com/the-week-onchain-week-28-2023/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">analysis</a> conducted by on-chain analytics firm Glassnode. The data reveals striking similarities to historical patterns, raising questions about the potential emergence of a familiar phenomenon: the re-accumulation period.</p>
<h2>A Resilient Market: Bitcoin Holds Firm At Mid-Cycle</h2>
<p>The Glassnode analysis reveals that Bitcoin is consolidating around the $30,000 mark, which acts as a significant mid-point within the 2021-2023 cycle. The historical significance of this level is not to be overlooked, as it has been tested repeatedly in previous cycles.</p>
<p>Remarkably, the mid-cycle phenomenon is not exclusive to the current cycle; similar mid-cycle points were observed in both 2013-2016 and 2018-2019, displaying analogous supply dynamics.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-542102 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-8.png" alt="Bitcoin mid-cycle points" width="1495" height="861" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-8.png 1495w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-8-460x265.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-8-860x495.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-8-768x442.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-8-750x432.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-8-1140x657.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1495px) 100vw, 1495px"/>
<p>As Bitcoin currently hovers around the $30,000 mid-point, approximately 75% of the total supply is currently held in a profitable state, while the remaining 25% remains in a loss position. This balance of supply held in profit versus loss is reminiscent of equilibrium points witnessed during previous cycles, indicating a potential re-accumulation period.</p>

<p>As Glassnode explains, &#8220;This 75:25 balance of supply held in profit:loss is the equilibrium point for Bitcoin. 50% of all trading days have seen a higher Profit-to-Loss balance, and 50% a lower one.&#8221; Such equilibrium points have historically required time for the market to digest and re-consolidate around, often accompanied by a period of sideways trading and volatility. This has become known as the &#8220;re-accumulation period.&#8221;</p>
<p>At the moment, The supply held &#8220;in-loss&#8221; has declined to just 4.79 million BTC, reaching similar levels seen in July 2021 ($30k), July 2020 ($9.2k), April 2016 ($6.5k), and March 2016 ($425).</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-542096 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/13_supplyprofitloss.png" alt="Bitcoin supply in profit and loss" width="8358" height="4814" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/13_supplyprofitloss.png 8358w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/13_supplyprofitloss-460x265.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/13_supplyprofitloss-860x495.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/13_supplyprofitloss-768x442.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/13_supplyprofitloss-1536x885.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/13_supplyprofitloss-2048x1180.png 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/13_supplyprofitloss-750x432.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/13_supplyprofitloss-1140x657.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 8358px) 100vw, 8358px"/>
<h2>Robust Recovery And Historical Comparisons</h2>
<p>According to Glassnode, Bitcoin&#8217;s price performance in 2023 has demonstrated remarkable resilience, with a maximum drawdown of only -18% thus far, a shallow correction compared to previous cycles. This suggests a substantial underlying demand for the asset and indicates a potential strong degree of investor support.</p>

<p>Glassnode&#8217;s analysis further highlights the similarities between the current recovery rally and those observed in prior cycles. Historically, recovery rallies following a similar magnitude move off the cycle&#8217;s bottom often marked the genesis of a new cyclical uptrend.</p>
<p>While exceptions exist, the parallels between the current recovery and those of the past offer an intriguing possibility for Bitcoin&#8217;s future trajectory. The report notes, &#8220;With the exception of 2019, all prior cycles which experienced a similar magnitude move off the bottom were, in fact, the genesis point of a new cyclical uptrend.&#8221;</p>
<p>Remarkably, previous re-accumulation periods were characterized by a lack of macro market direction and tending to trade sideways. “With the market back at this equilibrium point, it remains to be seen if a similarly lengthy and choppy process is needed to overcome it,” concludes Glassnode.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-542097 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/14_relunrealizedloss-1.png" alt="Bitcoin Relative Unrealized Loss" width="2400" height="1382" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/14_relunrealizedloss-1.png 2400w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/14_relunrealizedloss-1-460x265.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/14_relunrealizedloss-1-860x495.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/14_relunrealizedloss-1-768x442.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/14_relunrealizedloss-1-1536x884.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/14_relunrealizedloss-1-2048x1179.png 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/14_relunrealizedloss-1-750x432.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/14_relunrealizedloss-1-1140x656.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 2400px) 100vw, 2400px"/>
<h2>The Takeaway: Will History Repeat For BTC?</h2>
<p>Glassnode&#8217;s analysis unveils a fascinating narrative within Bitcoin&#8217;s ongoing market cycle. The emergence of the mid-cycle point and the familiar supply dynamics indicate that historical patterns are repeating themselves. While no crystal ball can predict the future with certainty, these insights offer intriguing possibilities for Bitcoin&#8217;s trajectory.</p>
<p>At press time, the BTC price was at $30,626 and remained in the trading range of the last two weeks.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-542099 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD_2023-07-11_09-13-07.png" alt="Bitcoin price" width="3628" height="1672" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD_2023-07-11_09-13-07.png 3628w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD_2023-07-11_09-13-07-460x212.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD_2023-07-11_09-13-07-860x396.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD_2023-07-11_09-13-07-768x354.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD_2023-07-11_09-13-07-1536x708.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD_2023-07-11_09-13-07-2048x944.png 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD_2023-07-11_09-13-07-750x346.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD_2023-07-11_09-13-07-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 3628px) 100vw, 3628px"/>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/iStock-1198722186-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>PEPE Potential Rebound: Key Details You Shouldn&#8217;t Miss</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/pepe-potential-rebound-key-details-you-shouldnt-miss/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 07:55:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[meme coins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PEPE price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price action]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=542086</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[PEPE recently reached a new peak, driven by the significant hype surrounding Bitcoin Exchange-Traded Funds (ETFs). However, as the initial excitement surrounding ETFs subsided, Bitcoin (BTC) experienced a period of fluctuation.  Notably, during this time, PEPE has been gradually making lower highs. Amidst these fluctuations, it becomes essential to examine the underlying factors that have contributed to the declining trend in PEPE&#8217;s price perfomance. Are there external market forces at play, or is it indicative of a broader shift in the cryptocurrency landscape? Additionally, how will this development impact the future trajectory of PEPE and other cryptocurrencies? PEPE Price Performance: From Highs To Fluctuations PEPE recently reached a new high of $0.00000190. However, its current price on CoinGecko stands at $0.00000152, reflecting a modest 4.3% rally in the past 24 hours. Nevertheless, over the course of the last seven days, PEPE has experienced a significant decline of 13%. Source: Coingecko Technical indicators further emphasize the shift in PEPE&#8217;s price trajectory. A PEPE price report highlights that various indicators have flashed sell signals. Notably, the Relative Strength Index (RSI) has made lower highs, indicating a decline in buying pressure over the past few days. Total market cap of cryptocurrencies currently at $1.16 billion. Chart: TradingView.com Moreover, the On Balance Volume has eased, suggesting a decrease in demand, while the Average Directional Index (ADX) has dropped below 20, indicating a lack of a strong trend for PEPE.  These technical signals hint at the challenges PEPE has faced in the face of its recent fluctuations. Altcoins&#8217; Massive Pullbacks Amidst Bitcoin&#8217;s Extended Consolidation Meanwhile, Bitcoin (BTC) has entered a phase of extended consolidation, with its price fluctuating above the $30,000 mark for nearly two weeks. This prolonged period of stability, coupled with intermittent fluctuations, has had a cascading effect on the broader cryptocurrency market, leading to significant pullbacks in most altcoins, including PEPE. Related Reading: Litecoin (LTC) Price Weakens Below $100 As Bears Extend Their Grip BTC&#8217;s status as the leading cryptocurrency makes its price movements a crucial factor influencing the market sentiment and performance of other digital assets. When Bitcoin experiences extended consolidation, investors and traders often exercise caution and become more hesitant to make significant moves. PEPE seven-day price action. Source: Coingecko As a result, altcoins, which rely on BTC&#8217;s stability and positive market sentiment, tend to be more susceptible to pullbacks and corrections. The pullbacks in altcoins have been notable, with many experiencing substantial declines in value during this period of Bitcoin&#8217;s consolidation. The high correlation between Bitcoin and altcoins like PEPE exacerbates the impact of the crypto&#8217;s fluctuations on their prices. Related Reading: Cardano Price Momentum Bid Fizzles Out Despite New Payment Feature As the alpha coin&#8217;s consolidation continues, closely monitoring its price movements and assessing the subsequent impact on altcoins and meme coins like PEPE becomes paramount for market watchers. (This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk). Featured image from PBS]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>PEPE recently reached a new peak, driven by the significant hype surrounding Bitcoin Exchange-Traded Funds (ETFs). However, as the initial excitement surrounding ETFs subsided, Bitcoin (BTC) experienced a period of fluctuation. </p>
<p>Notably, during this time, PEPE has been gradually making lower highs. Amidst these fluctuations, it becomes essential to examine the underlying factors that have contributed to the declining trend in PEPE&#8217;s price perfomance.</p>
<p>Are there external market forces at play, or is it indicative of a broader shift in the cryptocurrency landscape? Additionally, how will this development impact the future trajectory of PEPE and other cryptocurrencies?</p>
<h2><strong>PEPE Price Performance: From Highs To Fluctuations</strong></h2>
<p>PEPE recently reached a new high of $0.00000190. However, its current price on <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/pepe" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">CoinGecko</a> stands at $0.00000152, reflecting a modest 4.3% rally in the past 24 hours. Nevertheless, over the course of the last seven days, PEPE has experienced a significant decline of 13%.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-542087" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-60.png" alt="" width="1138" height="63" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-60.png 1138w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-60-460x25.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-60-860x48.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-60-768x43.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-60-750x42.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 1138px) 100vw, 1138px"/></p>

<p>Technical indicators further emphasize the shift in PEPE&#8217;s price trajectory. A <a href="https://ambcrypto.com/is-a-rebound-likely-for-pepe-heres-what-you-need-to-know/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">PEPE price report</a> highlights that various indicators have flashed sell signals. Notably, the Relative Strength Index (RSI) has made lower highs, indicating a decline in buying pressure over the past few days.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/sWUfo5hL/" width="2475" height="1187"/></p>

<p>Moreover, the On Balance Volume has eased, suggesting a decrease in demand, while the Average Directional Index (ADX) has dropped below 20, indicating a lack of a strong trend for PEPE. </p>
<p>These technical signals hint at the challenges PEPE has faced in the face of its recent fluctuations.</p>
<h2><strong>Altcoins&#8217; Massive Pullbacks Amidst Bitcoin&#8217;s Extended Consolidation</strong></h2>
<p>Meanwhile, Bitcoin (BTC) has entered a phase of extended consolidation, with its price fluctuating above the $30,000 mark for nearly two weeks. This prolonged period of stability, coupled with intermittent fluctuations, has had a cascading effect on the broader cryptocurrency market, leading to significant pullbacks in most altcoins, including PEPE.</p>

<p>BTC&#8217;s status as the leading cryptocurrency makes its price movements a crucial factor influencing the market sentiment and performance of other digital assets. When Bitcoin experiences extended consolidation, investors and traders often exercise caution and become more hesitant to make significant moves.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-542111" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-61.png" alt="" width="769" height="491" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-61.png 769w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-61-460x294.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-61-750x479.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 769px) 100vw, 769px"/></p>

<p>As a result, altcoins, which rely on <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-07-10/standard-chartered-ups-bitcoin-forecast-to-120-000-by-end-2024" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">BTC&#8217;s stability and positive market sentiment</a>, tend to be more susceptible to pullbacks and corrections.</p>
<p>The pullbacks in altcoins have been notable, with many experiencing substantial declines in value during this period of Bitcoin&#8217;s consolidation. The high correlation between Bitcoin and altcoins like PEPE exacerbates the impact of the crypto&#8217;s fluctuations on their prices.</p>

<p>As the alpha coin&#8217;s consolidation continues, closely monitoring its price movements and assessing the subsequent impact on altcoins and meme coins like PEPE becomes paramount for market watchers.</p>
<p><em>(This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk).</em></p>
<p><em>Featured image from PBS</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-62-460x259.png" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>BNB Price at Make-or-Break Levels As The Bulls Aim Big Above This Resistance</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/bnb/bnb-price-resistance-255/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 04:43:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BNB]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance Coin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BNB Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BNBUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bnbusdt]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=542083</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[BNB price (Binance coin) is rising above $245 against the US Dollar. The price could start a strong increase if it clears the $250 and $255 resistance levels. Binance coin price is attempting a fresh increase from the $232 zone against the US Dollar. The price is now trading above $240 and the 100 simple moving average (4 hours). There is a major bearish trend line forming with resistance near $248 on the 4-hour chart of the BNB/USD pair (data source from Binance). The pair might gain bullish momentum above $248 and $250. Binance Coin Price Eyes Fresh Rally In the past few days, BNB price saw a couple of swing moves from $250. There was a move below the $240 support zone. However, the bulls were seen active near the $232 support zone. The price traded as low as $231 and is currently rising, similar to Bitcoin and Ethereum. There was a move above the $240 resistance. The price climbed above the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $255 swing high to the $231 low. BNB price is now trading above $240 and the 100 simple moving average (4 hours). On the upside, it is facing resistance near the $248 level. There is also a major bearish trend line forming with resistance near $248 on the 4-hour chart of the BNB/USD pair. It is close to the 76.4% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $255 swing high to the $231 low. The next major resistance is near $250. A close above the $250 resistance might increase the chances of a push above the $255 resistance. Source: BNBUSD on TradingView.com A clear move above the $252 resistance might start a steady increase. The next major resistance is near the $270 level, above which the price might rise toward the $285 resistance. Another Rejection in BNB? If BNB fails to clear the $250 resistance, it could start another decline. Initial support on the downside is near the $240 level and the 100 simple moving average (4 hours). The next major support is near the $232 level. If there is a downside break below the $232 support, the price could drop toward the $222 support. Any more losses could send the price toward the $210 support. Technical Indicators 4-Hours MACD – The MACD for BNB/USD is gaining pace in the bullish zone. 4-Hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BNB/USD is currently above the 50 level. Major Support Levels – $240, $232, and $225. Major Resistance Levels – $250, $255, and $270.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>BNB price (Binance coin) is rising above $245 against the US Dollar. The price could start a strong increase if it clears the $250 and $255 resistance levels.</em></p>
<ul>
<li>Binance coin price is attempting a fresh increase from the $232 zone against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>The price is now trading above $240 and the 100 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There is a major bearish trend line forming with resistance near $248 on the 4-hour chart of the BNB/USD pair (data source from Binance).</li>
<li>The pair might gain bullish momentum above $248 and $250.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Binance Coin Price Eyes Fresh Rally</h2>
<p>In the past few days, BNB price saw a couple of swing moves from $250. There was a move below the $240 support zone. However, the bulls were seen active near the $232 support zone.</p>
<p>The price traded as low as $231 and is currently rising, similar to <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-holds-ground-30k-2/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Bitcoin</a> and <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-turning-point-1900/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Ethereum</a>. There was a move above the $240 resistance. The price climbed above the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $255 swing high to the $231 low.</p>
<p>BNB price is now trading above $240 and the 100 simple moving average (4 hours). On the upside, it is facing resistance near the $248 level. There is also a major bearish trend line forming with resistance near $248 on the 4-hour chart of the BNB/USD pair.</p>
<p>It is close to the 76.4% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $255 swing high to the $231 low. The next major resistance is near $250. A close above the $250 resistance might increase the chances of a push above the $255 resistance.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-542084" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Binance-Coin-BNB-1.png" alt="BNB Price" width="1835" height="845" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Binance-Coin-BNB-1.png 1835w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Binance-Coin-BNB-1-460x212.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Binance-Coin-BNB-1-860x396.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Binance-Coin-BNB-1-768x354.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Binance-Coin-BNB-1-1536x707.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Binance-Coin-BNB-1-750x345.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Binance-Coin-BNB-1-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1835px) 100vw, 1835px"/></p>
<p>Source: <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BNBUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">BNBUSD on TradingView.com</a></p>
<p>A clear move above the $252 resistance might start a steady increase. The next major resistance is near the $270 level, above which the price might rise toward the $285 resistance.</p>
<h2>Another Rejection in BNB?</h2>
<p>If BNB fails to clear the $250 resistance, it could start another decline. Initial support on the downside is near the $240 level and the 100 simple moving average (4 hours).</p>
<p>The next major support is near the $232 level. If there is a downside break below the $232 support, the price could drop toward the $222 support. Any more losses could send the price toward the $210 support.</p>
<p>Technical Indicators</p>
<p>4-Hours MACD – The MACD for BNB/USD is gaining pace in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>4-Hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BNB/USD is currently above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Levels – $240, $232, and $225.</p>
<p>Major Resistance Levels – $250, $255, and $270.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/shutterstock_1509655121-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum Price Reaches Key Turning Point, $1,900 Is The Key</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-turning-point-1900/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 04:16:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=542080</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Ethereum price is attempting a fresh increase from $1,825 against the US Dollar. ETH could rally if there is a clear move above the $1,900 resistance. Ethereum is currently attempting a recovery wave above the $1,855 zone. The price is trading above $1,865 and the 100-hourly Simple Moving Average. There is a major bearish trend line forming with resistance near $1,900 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD (data feed via Kraken). The pair could start a decent increase if there is a close above $1,900. Ethereum Price Revisits Resistance Ethereum’s price remained stable above the $1,825 support zone. ETH started a slow recovery wave and was able to climb a few points higher above $1,850, similar to Bitcoin. The bulls were able to push the price above the 100-hourly Simple Moving Average. The price broke the 50% Fib retracement level of the key decline from the $1,955 swing high to the $1,825 low. However, the bears were seen active near the $1,900 resistance zone. There is also a major bearish trend line forming with resistance near $1,900 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD. Ether is now trading above $1,865 and the 100-hourly Simple Moving Average. Immediate resistance is near the $1,890 level. The first major resistance is near the $1,900 zone and the trend line. The trend line is close to the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the key decline from the $1,955 swing high to the $1,825 low. Source: ETHUSD on TradingView.com A close above the $1,900 resistance could start a decent increase toward $1,975. The next major resistance is near the $2,000 level. Any more gains could send Ether toward the $2,050 resistance or even $2,120. Another Rejection in ETH? If Ethereum fails to clear the $1,900 resistance, it could start another decline. Initial support on the downside is near the $1,865 level or the 100-hourly Simple Moving Average. The first major support is near the $1,825 level, below which there is a risk of a larger decline. The next major support is near the $1,740 level. Any more losses could send Ether toward the $1,720 support level in the near term. Technical Indicators Hourly MACD – The MACD for ETH/USD is losing momentum in the bullish zone. Hourly RSI &#8211; The RSI for ETH/USD is now above the 50 level. Major Support Level – $1,825 Major Resistance Level – $1,900]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>Ethereum price is attempting a fresh increase from $1,825 against the US Dollar. ETH could rally if there is a clear move above the $1,900 resistance.</em></p>
<ul>
<li>Ethereum is currently attempting a recovery wave above the $1,855 zone.</li>
<li>The price is trading above $1,865 and the 100-hourly Simple Moving Average.</li>
<li>There is a major bearish trend line forming with resistance near $1,900 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD (data feed via Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could start a decent increase if there is a close above $1,900.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Ethereum Price Revisits Resistance</h2>
<p>Ethereum’s price remained stable above the $1,825 support zone. ETH started a slow recovery wave and was able to climb a few points higher above $1,850, similar to <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-holds-ground-30k-2/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Bitcoin</a>.</p>
<p>The bulls were able to push the price above the 100-hourly Simple Moving Average. The price broke the 50% Fib retracement level of the key decline from the $1,955 swing high to the $1,825 low. However, the bears were seen active near the $1,900 resistance zone.</p>
<p>There is also a major <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-bearish-revisit-1800/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">bearish trend line forming with resistance near $1,900</a> on the hourly chart of ETH/USD. Ether is now trading above $1,865 and the 100-hourly Simple Moving Average.</p>
<p>Immediate resistance is near the $1,890 level. The first major resistance is near the $1,900 zone and the trend line. The trend line is close to the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the key decline from the $1,955 swing high to the $1,825 low.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-542081" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ethereum-6.png" alt="Ethereum Price" width="1835" height="845" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ethereum-6.png 1835w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ethereum-6-460x212.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ethereum-6-860x396.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ethereum-6-768x354.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ethereum-6-1536x707.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ethereum-6-750x345.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ethereum-6-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1835px) 100vw, 1835px"/></p>
<p>Source: <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/ETHUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">ETHUSD on TradingView.com</a></p>
<p>A close above the $1,900 resistance could start a decent increase toward $1,975. The next major resistance is near the $2,000 level. Any more gains could send Ether toward the $2,050 resistance or even $2,120.</p>
<h2>Another Rejection in ETH?</h2>
<p>If Ethereum fails to clear the $1,900 resistance, it could start another decline. Initial support on the downside is near the $1,865 level or the 100-hourly Simple Moving Average.</p>
<p>The first major support is near the $1,825 level, below which there is a risk of a larger decline. The next major support is near the $1,740 level. Any more losses could send Ether toward the $1,720 support level in the near term.</p>
<p>Technical Indicators</p>
<p>Hourly MACD<strong> – </strong>The MACD for ETH/USD is losing momentum in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>Hourly RSI<strong> &#8211; </strong>The RSI for ETH/USD is now above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Level – $1,825</p>
<p>Major Resistance Level – $1,900</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/shutterstock_547233985-460x301.jpg" width="460" height="301" />	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
