<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
>

<channel>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.newsbtc.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<description>Bitcoin &#38; cryptocurrency news today, price &#38; technical analysis</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 21:59:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>BRC-20 Token Standard A Hotspot For New Memecoins As PEPE Soars</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/brc-20-token-standard-a-hotspot-for-new-memecoins-as-pepe-soars/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mudiaga Iritare]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 23:00:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BRC-20]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[memecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PEPE]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[The Bitcoin Standard]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=530074</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The memecoin ecosystem has once again brought magic to crypto investors as PEPE the frog records massive gains and unbelievable numbers. The now popular PEPE meme token based on Ethereum was originally inspired by the Bitcoin BRC-20 PEPE which launched earlier in March, 2023. PEPE&#8217;s exponential price growth in its barely first month recorded close to 38,900% ROI for early investors. This has led to crypto enthusiasts and developers to explore the original BRC-20 token standard version with which the first PEPE was created on. The BRC-20 is a new and unique token standard that has recently gained massive popularity and exposure due to the successes of the Ethereum based PEPE. Related Reading: Pepe Shakes Off CZ’s Controversial Views On Meme Coins, Shoots Up 709% A Dive Into The BRC-20 Token Standard The BRC-20 token standard is an experimental mechanism to launch a token based on the Bitcoin blockchain network. This new token standard was created by a pseudonymous on-chain analyst called Domo. Domo created the BRC-20 token standard in March 2023 to facilitate transfers of fungible tokens across the Bitcoin network. This new experimental standard would also enable developers and programmers to create and send fungible tokens, including memecoins, via the Bitcoin ordinals protocol. While several token standards are present in the blockchain industry, the BRC-20 was modeled after the popular Ethereum ERC-20 standard, although there are some fundamental differences. The ERC-20 standard which requires using smart contracts to launch a token is quite different from the BRC-20. The latter simply requires a Bitcoin wallet to mint and create tokens without using smart contracts. Related Reading: SUI Gets A Bear Introduction On Day 2, Will Sell Pressure Continue? PEPE Sets A Precedence For Newer Memecoins Recently, there has been a frenzy of newer memecoins launching into the crypto market using the BRC-20 token standard due to its popularity. According to data reports from Coinmarketcap, 8,500 tokens, including memecoins, have been minted and launched using this standard. This has resulted in a massive surge in the BRC-20 token market capitalization and transaction volume which were reported to outperform Bitcoin by over 50% between April 29 and May 2, 2023. We can see that in the last 10 days number of BRC20 tx has largely surpassed that of ordinals. They might even soon overload the bitcoin network and cause issues. pic.twitter.com/FSGzkfeTJT &#8212; Crypto Koryo (@CryptoKoryo) May 2, 2023 The increasing transaction volumes and market capitalization of BRC-20, have drawn the interests of many investors who explore a variety of tokens created using this new token standard. However, it is important to note that the BRC-20 standard is still in its experimental phase, and as such, caution should be exerted when exploring tokens based on it. Bitcoin hovers near support at $29,200 on the daily chart timeframe &#124; Source: BTCUSD on TradinView.com Featured Image from Istock, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The memecoin ecosystem has once again brought magic to crypto investors as PEPE the frog records massive gains and unbelievable numbers. The now popular PEPE meme token based on Ethereum was originally inspired by the Bitcoin BRC-20 PEPE which <a href="https://twitter.com/Pepe_Brc20/status/1638100996781137920?t=u4Q6oJs3truDL2NEWJ0vJA&amp;s=19" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">launched</a> earlier in March, 2023.</p>
<p>PEPE&#8217;s exponential price growth in its barely first month recorded close to 38,900% ROI for early investors. This has led to crypto enthusiasts and developers to explore the original BRC-20 token standard version with which the first PEPE was created on.</p>
<p>The BRC-20 is a new and unique token standard that has recently gained massive popularity and exposure due to the successes of the Ethereum based PEPE.</p>

<h2>A Dive Into The BRC-20 Token Standard</h2>
<p>The BRC-20 token standard is an experimental mechanism to launch a token based on the Bitcoin blockchain network. This new token standard was created by a pseudonymous on-chain analyst called Domo.</p>
<p>Domo created the BRC-20 token <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://twitter.com/domodata/status/1634247606262964228?t=IwdP1zTvXbUjRuwbBIFFoA&amp;s=19" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">standard</a> in March 2023 to facilitate transfers of fungible tokens across the Bitcoin network.</p>
<p>This new experimental standard would also enable developers and programmers to create and send fungible tokens, including memecoins, via the Bitcoin ordinals protocol.</p>
<p>While several token standards are present in the blockchain industry, the BRC-20 was modeled after the popular Ethereum ERC-20 standard, although there are some fundamental differences.</p>
<p>The ERC-20 standard which requires using smart contracts to launch a token is quite different from the BRC-20. The latter simply requires a Bitcoin wallet to mint and create tokens without using smart contracts.</p>



<h2>PEPE Sets A Precedence For Newer Memecoins</h2>
<p>Recently, there has been a frenzy of newer memecoins launching into the crypto market using the BRC-20 token standard due to its popularity. According to data<a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://coinmarketcap.com/community/articles/6453f515fec63d16dc5922df" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow"> reports</a> from Coinmarketcap, 8,500 tokens, including memecoins, have been minted and launched using this standard.</p>
<p>This has resulted in a massive surge in the BRC-20 token market capitalization and transaction volume which were reported to outperform Bitcoin by over 50% between April 29 and May 2, 2023.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">We can see that in the last 10 days number of BRC20 tx has largely surpassed that of ordinals. They might even soon overload the bitcoin network and cause issues. <a href="https://t.co/FSGzkfeTJT" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/FSGzkfeTJT</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Crypto Koryo (@CryptoKoryo) <a href="https://twitter.com/CryptoKoryo/status/1653531706257731585?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">May 2, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p></p>
<p>The increasing transaction volumes and market capitalization of BRC-20, have drawn the interests of many investors who explore a variety of tokens created using this new token standard.</p>
<p>However, it is important to note that the BRC-20 standard is still in its experimental phase, and as such, caution should be exerted when exploring tokens based on it.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/9ZTgS07j/" alt="BRC-20" width="1280" height="538" /></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/iStock-1311128315-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Study: Shiba Inu (SHIB) Is More Of A Successful Memecoin Than PEPE and DOGE</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/shiba-inu-shib-is-successful-memecoin-than-pepe-and-doge/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Edyme]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 21:30:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Shiba Inu]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[doge]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PEPE]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIB]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[WOJAK]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=530176</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Regarding meme coins, there is no denying that Shiba Inu (SHIB) has been one of the most talked-about tokens in recent times. Its success is partly due to its captivating name and adorable mascot, which has been a hit with social media users.  However, beyond the hype, how does SHIB compare to other meme coins such as PEPE and DOGE? PEPE is the newly hyped memecoin in the crypto market. With the token doing over 20x since its creation, it has attracted many traders and investors. Dogecoin (DOGE), on the other hand, is known as Elon Musk’s favorite.  Related Reading: BREAKING: Binance Lists PEPE And FLOKI In Innovation Zone SHIB, PEPE, And DOGE: The Comparison On May 5, Coingecko released a study that analyzed the price returns of meme coins over a period, utilizing data from CoinGecko. The study considered the start of data availability as the hypothetical date of purchase, while the all-time high price, as of May 4, 2023, was taken as the selling point to achieve profits. According to the data from Coingecko, SHIB required an initial investment of just $12 to reach $1M in 2021, making it one of the most affordable meme coins in the market. In contrast, DOGE required an initial investment of $820 in 2013, which is significantly higher.  Other meme coins, such as PEPE and WOJAK, require an initial investment of $158,312 and $175,330, respectively, making them far less accessible to the average investor in 2023. Regarding price gains, SHIB was the most successful meme coin, with an incredible 8,424,202.3% increase at its peak compared to its starting price on August 1, 2020. This is a testament to the popularity of SHIB and its ability to attract investors worldwide. On the other hand, DOGE has been a successful meme coin over the long run, having been a pioneer in the category since 2013. DOGE&#8217;s price performance has been impressive and consistently in the top 10 cryptocurrencies by market capitalization.  Meanwhile, Shiba Inu has struggled to reach the top 10 while still ranking 16th in the global crypto market.  Related Reading: Is It Too Late To Buy Shiba Inu (SHIB)? Shiba Inu Downtrend Price Action Notably, SHIB has recently experienced significant price volatility, leading to downward price action. This has been attributed to several factors, including profit-taking, a broader market downturn, and investors moving to a more attractive memecoin currently PEPE. According to CoinGecko data, SHIB&#8217;s price was $0.00000001 on August 1, 2020, and it reached an all-time high of $0.00008616 on October 28, 2021. At the time of writing, SHIB trades at $0.00001000, representing an 88.43% decline from its all-time high. SHIB’s market capitalization has gradually plummeted in the past 7 days, moving from a high of $6.1 billion on April 29 to as low as $5.8 billion. Interestingly, its daily trading volume has since surged over the same period from $91.8 million to $144 million in the past 24 hours. Featured image from iStock, Chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Regarding meme coins, there is no denying that <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/mystery-wallet-burns-1-69-billion-shiba-inu-will-it-result-in-price-bump/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Shiba Inu (SHIB)</a> has been one of the most talked-about tokens in recent times. Its success is partly due to its captivating name and adorable mascot, which has been a hit with social media users. </p>
<p>However, beyond the hype, how does SHIB compare to other meme coins such as PEPE and DOGE? PEPE is the newly hyped memecoin in the crypto market. With the token<a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/pepe/from-27-to-4m-pepe-wallet-unable-to-sell-unstoppable-rally/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"> doing over 20x</a> since its creation, it has attracted many traders and investors. Dogecoin (DOGE), on the other hand, is known as Elon Musk’s favorite. </p>

<h2>SHIB, PEPE, And DOGE: The Comparison</h2>
<p>On May 5, Coingecko <a href="https://twitter.com/coingecko/status/1654364395890409475?s=61&amp;t=upH-TE3H_czpmCo_noqE6A" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">released</a> a <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/research/publications/meme-coin-millionaire?utm_campaign=Data%2BVisualization&amp;utm_medium=social" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">study</a> that analyzed the price returns of meme coins over a period, utilizing data from CoinGecko. The study considered the start of data availability as the hypothetical date of purchase, while the all-time high price, as of May 4, 2023, was taken as the selling point to achieve profits.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium wp-image-530177" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/twitter_3e0d855dc7818831421feb2f2a93b714-460x460.jpeg" alt="Initial investment needed to reach $1M with Memecoins. " width="460" height="460" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/twitter_3e0d855dc7818831421feb2f2a93b714-460x460.jpeg 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/twitter_3e0d855dc7818831421feb2f2a93b714-860x860.jpeg 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/twitter_3e0d855dc7818831421feb2f2a93b714-200x200.jpeg 200w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/twitter_3e0d855dc7818831421feb2f2a93b714-768x768.jpeg 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/twitter_3e0d855dc7818831421feb2f2a93b714-42x42.jpeg 42w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/twitter_3e0d855dc7818831421feb2f2a93b714-75x75.jpeg 75w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/twitter_3e0d855dc7818831421feb2f2a93b714-350x350.jpeg 350w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/twitter_3e0d855dc7818831421feb2f2a93b714-750x750.jpeg 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/twitter_3e0d855dc7818831421feb2f2a93b714-1140x1140.jpeg 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/twitter_3e0d855dc7818831421feb2f2a93b714.jpeg 1216w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px" />
<p>According to the data from Coingecko, SHIB required an initial investment of just $12 to reach $1M in 2021, making it one of the most affordable meme coins in the market. In contrast, DOGE required an initial investment of $820 in 2013, which is significantly higher. </p>
<p>Other meme coins, such as <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/altcoin/breaking-binance-lists-pepe-and-floki-in-innovation-zone/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">PEPE</a> and WOJAK, require an initial investment of $158,312 and $175,330, respectively, making them far less accessible to the average investor in 2023.</p>
<p>Regarding price gains, SHIB was the most successful meme coin, with an incredible 8,424,202.3% increase at its peak compared to its starting price on August 1, 2020. This is a testament to the popularity of SHIB and its ability to attract investors worldwide.</p>
<p>On the other hand, DOGE has been a successful meme coin over the long run, having been a pioneer in the category since 2013. DOGE&#8217;s price performance has been impressive and consistently in the top 10 cryptocurrencies by market capitalization. </p>
<p>Meanwhile, Shiba Inu has struggled to reach the top 10 while still ranking 16th in the global crypto market. </p>

<h2>Shiba Inu Downtrend Price Action</h2>
<p>Notably, SHIB has recently experienced significant price volatility, leading to downward price action. This has been attributed to several factors, including profit-taking, a broader market downturn, and investors moving to a more attractive memecoin currently PEPE.</p>
<p>According to CoinGecko data, <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/press-releases/is-it-too-late-to-buy-shiba-inu-shib/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SHIB&#8217;s price</a> was $0.00000001 on August 1, 2020, and it reached an all-time high of $0.00008616 on October 28, 2021. At the time of writing, SHIB trades at $0.00001000, representing an 88.43% decline from <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/shiba-inu-burn-rate-explodes-31000-will-price-heat-up-as-well/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">its all-time high</a>.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/NWHsq6Vt/" alt="Shiba Inu (SHIB)'s price chart on TradingView" width="2768" height="1556" />
<p>SHIB’s market capitalization has gradually plummeted in the past 7 days, moving from a high of $6.1 billion on April 29 to as low as $5.8 billion. Interestingly, its daily trading volume has since surged over the same period from $91.8 million to $144 million in the past 24 hours. </p>
<p class="p1">Featured image from iStock, Chart from TradingView</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Shiba-Inu-460x329.jpeg" width="460" height="329" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Breaks Out: Experts Predict $36,000 Target As Market Outlook Remains Positive</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-breaks-out-experts-predict-36000-target-as-market-outlook-remains-positive/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 20:30:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=530147</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC), the world&#8217;s largest cryptocurrency, could be set for a significant price surge in the coming weeks, according to experts at Matrixport, a leading provider of cryptocurrency financial services. The company has projected a target of $36,000 for Bitcoin, based on a technical breakout that signals a strong rally amidst a positive market outlook fueled by stock buybacks and meme coins. Related Reading: 4 Reasons To Be Bullish On Bitcoin In Short-And Mid-Term Bitcoin Set To Soar With Strong Technical Breakout And Meme Coin Frenzy Matrixport&#8217;s analysis shows that Bitcoin is currently trading within a narrowing triangle formation, which is about to break to the upside. This could potentially project a move higher by around 6,100 points, which would bring the price of Bitcoin to the projected target of $36,000. The positive market outlook for Bitcoin is driven in part by the popularity of meme coins, which have seen a surge in interest among retail investors. Additionally, stock buybacks by major corporations have provided a boost to the broader market, which has spilled over into the cryptocurrency space. Furthermore, according to Matrixport, Bitcoin could see a significant price increase of up to 20% from current levels. This would set a target of $35,000 to $36,000 for Bitcoin, driven by a potential breakout in the market. Matrixport&#8217;s analysis shows that a breakout could be imminent for Bitcoin, which could lead to significant gains for the cryptocurrency. Additionally, the recent 25 basis point interest rate hike by the Federal Reserve may be the last for this cycle, potentially setting up the market for another strong rally. Moreover, Despite a recent decline in trading volume, Matrixport notes that the path higher for Bitcoin sees only limited resistance, with transactions on the network reaching new all-time highs and the number of active addresses remaining strong. Another interesting trend highlighted by Matrixport is the increasing popularity of meme coins such as DinoLFG, Pepe, Wojak, ChadCoin, and IgnoreFud. While these meme coins may be small, their trading activity is worth noting as it signals a shift in market sentiment towards a more positive outlook. BTC’s MVRV Ratio Breaks Key Threshold, Signaling Bull Run Ahead According to a recent analysis by CryptoQuant’s researcher, “Onchained”, In January 2023, Bitcoin&#8217;s market-value-to-realized-value (MVRV) ratio broke the 1 level in an upward direction, indicating a substantial increase in its price due to significant accumulation in both the spot and derivatives markets. The MVRV ratio has revealed that the 1.5 level is of significant importance, serving as a crucial threshold for Bitcoin to enter its bull run. Currently, Bitcoin&#8217;s MVRV has been fluctuating between 1.55 and 1.45 this month, with large investors closely monitoring the indicator to capitalize on Bitcoin dips and accumulate discounted BTC to fill their bags. Furthermore, According to Onchained’s analysis, the MVRV ratio experiences a trend change when it breaks its 365-day simple moving average (365DSMA). If the ratio breaks this moving average in an upward trend, it signifies the start of a bull market, with the MVRV ratio changing direction to reach high levels typically between 2 to 3.75 or more.  Conversely, if the MVRV ratio breaks the 365DSMA in a downward trend, it signals the start of a bear market, with the ratio changing direction to reach low values of 1 or less. These patterns are visible in the chart. Onchained’s analysis has revealed that when the MVRV ratio breaks the 1.5 level, the 365DSMA becomes flattened before changing direction upward. Currently, it appears that BTC is experiencing this trend, as its MVRV ratio fluctuates in the range of 1.5 values. If Bitcoin breaks the $30,000 level, a rapid change in its MVRV ratio is expected, which is likely to shift to a range of values between 1.8 and 2. Related Reading: Mystery Wallet Burns 1.69 Billion Shiba Inu, Will It Result In Price Bump? Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin (BTC), the world&#8217;s largest cryptocurrency, could be set for a significant price surge in the coming weeks, <a href="https://twitter.com/realMatrixport/status/1654020799018446848?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">according </a>to experts at Matrixport, a leading provider of cryptocurrency financial services. The company has projected a target of $36,000 for Bitcoin, based on a technical breakout that signals a strong rally amidst a positive market outlook fueled by stock buybacks and meme coins.</p>

<h2><b>Bitcoin Set To Soar With Strong Technical Breakout And Meme Coin Frenzy</b></h2>
<p>Matrixport&#8217;s analysis shows that Bitcoin is currently trading within a narrowing triangle formation, which is about to break to the upside. This could potentially project a move higher by around 6,100 points, which would bring the price of Bitcoin to the projected target of $36,000.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large wp-image-530149" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/FvRCoUcagAEEXzH-860x499.jpg" alt="Bitcoin " width="860" height="499" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/FvRCoUcagAEEXzH-860x499.jpg 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/FvRCoUcagAEEXzH-460x267.jpg 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/FvRCoUcagAEEXzH-768x446.jpg 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/FvRCoUcagAEEXzH-750x436.jpg 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/FvRCoUcagAEEXzH-1140x662.jpg 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/FvRCoUcagAEEXzH.jpg 1512w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" />
<p>The positive market outlook for Bitcoin is driven in part by the popularity of meme coins, which have seen a surge in interest among retail investors. Additionally, stock buybacks by major corporations have provided a boost to the broader market, which has spilled over into the cryptocurrency space.</p>
<p>Furthermore, according to Matrixport, Bitcoin could see a significant price increase of up to 20% from current levels. This would set a target of $35,000 to $36,000 for Bitcoin, driven by a potential breakout in the market.</p>
<p>Matrixport&#8217;s analysis shows that a breakout could be imminent for Bitcoin, which could lead to significant gains for the cryptocurrency. Additionally, the recent 25 basis point interest rate hike by the Federal Reserve may be the last for this cycle, potentially setting up the market for another strong rally.</p>
<p>Moreover, Despite a recent decline in trading volume, Matrixport notes that the path higher for Bitcoin sees only limited resistance, with transactions on the network reaching new all-time highs and the number of active addresses remaining strong.</p>
<p>Another interesting trend highlighted by Matrixport is the increasing popularity of meme coins such as DinoLFG, Pepe, Wojak, ChadCoin, and IgnoreFud. While these meme coins may be small, their trading activity is worth noting as it signals a shift in market sentiment towards a more positive outlook.</p>
<b>BTC’s MVRV Ratio Breaks Key Threshold, Signaling Bull Run Ahead</b>
<p>According to a recent <a href="https://cryptoquant.com/insights/quicktake/6453d3c3bbe24f02e5edcd34-Analysis-of-Bitcoins-MVRV-Ratio-and-Moving-Averages-Insights-into-Bull-and-Bear-" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">analysis </a>by CryptoQuant’s researcher, “Onchained”, In January 2023, Bitcoin&#8217;s market-value-to-realized-value (MVRV) ratio broke the 1 level in an upward direction, indicating a substantial increase in its price due to significant accumulation in both the spot and derivatives markets.</p>
<p>The MVRV ratio has revealed that the 1.5 level is of significant importance, serving as a crucial threshold for Bitcoin to enter its bull run. Currently, Bitcoin&#8217;s MVRV has been fluctuating between 1.55 and 1.45 this month, with large investors closely monitoring the indicator to capitalize on Bitcoin dips and accumulate discounted BTC to fill their bags.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large wp-image-530150" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Screenshot_33-860x456.jpg" alt="Bitcoin " width="860" height="456" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Screenshot_33-860x456.jpg 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Screenshot_33-460x244.jpg 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Screenshot_33-768x407.jpg 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Screenshot_33-750x398.jpg 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Screenshot_33.jpg 883w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" />
<p>Furthermore, According to Onchained’s analysis, the MVRV ratio experiences a trend change when it breaks its 365-day simple moving average (365DSMA). If the ratio breaks this moving average in an upward trend, it signifies the start of a bull market, with the MVRV ratio changing direction to reach high levels typically between 2 to 3.75 or more. </p>
<p>Conversely, if the MVRV ratio breaks the 365DSMA in a downward trend, it signals the start of a bear market, with the ratio changing direction to reach low values of 1 or less. These patterns are visible in the chart.</p>
<p>Onchained’s analysis has revealed that when the MVRV ratio breaks the 1.5 level, the 365DSMA becomes flattened before changing direction upward. Currently, it appears that BTC is experiencing this trend, as its MVRV ratio fluctuates in the range of 1.5 values. If Bitcoin breaks the $30,000 level, a rapid change in its MVRV ratio is expected, which is likely to shift to a range of values between 1.8 and 2.</p>



<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/ETeFsoEP/" alt="Bitcoin " width="1813" height="858" />
<p>Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/iStock-1288562987-460x248.jpg" width="460" height="248" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Former DoJ Kennedy Jr, Laments on Global Financial Censorship, Shows Support For Bitcoin</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/former-doj-kennedy-jr-laments-on-global-financial-censorship-shows-support-for-bitcoin/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mike D.]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 19:30:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CBDCs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DoJ Kennedy Jr]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=530138</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The former US Department of Justice Attorney General Robert Francis Kennedy Jr, recently lamented the growing financial censorship worldwide and showed support for Bitcoin. The financial censorship of political enemies is something we’re used to seeing under authoritarian regimes. No one was surprised when Russia froze more than 100 bank accounts tied to opposition leader Alexei Navalny. But Canada did it too, locking more than 200 accounts of… &#8212; Robert F. Kennedy Jr (@RobertKennedyJr) May 5, 2023 According to Kennedy Jr, the major victims are political enemies of most governments that he classified as &#8220;authoritarian regimes.&#8221; Political Enemies Made To Suffer Financial Censorship In his Twitter post, Kennedy stated that the trend in this financial prohibition is evident in several countries globally. In 2019, Russian authorities froze over 100 bank accounts related to the opposition leader Alexei Navalny. Though the authorities stated that the action aligned with a money laundering investigation, many citizens believed it was politically inclined. Related Reading: Why Is Bitcoin And Crypto Up Today? Last year, Canada froze over 200 accounts of people and firms connected to the protests in Ottawa against Covid-19 mandates. According to the reports, Royal Canadian Mounted Police (RCMP) froze several financial products, which included bank and corporate accounts. Also, it froze a payment processing account with a valuation of about $3.8 million. After citing these instances, the environmental lawyer stated that financial censorship is gradually creeping into the United States. This means a person’s account could be frozen due to his comments on social media or political stance. Kennedy Jr cited the incidents in 2010 when PayPal, Mastercard, and Visa suspended an NGO and whistleblowing platform, WikiLeaks, that exposed big corporations and government institutions of unethical acts. Notably, the suspension was through the command of the US State Department.  DoJ Kennedy Jr On Bitcoin And CBDCs The central banks of countries manage Central Bank Digital Currencies (CBDCs). This means that the government will control the financial accounts of all residents in a country that runs CBDC.  Kenndy Jr believes CBDCs could magnify a government&#8217;s power to suppress meaningful political dissent. The authorities could decide to cut the financial access of some individuals just because of political statements and opinions.  Related Reading: Bitcoin On-Chain Transactions Reach New Heights, What’s Fueling the Surge? The lawyer noted that a meaningful dissent should include people&#8217;s ability to save and use their finances without political interference. It should be about maintaining the proper political protection from powerful personal interests regarding democracy.  But citizens&#8217; meaningful dissent is at risk with the adoption of CBDCs and their power to the government. As such, Kennedy Jr supported Bitcoin, stating that the crypto asset would allow anyone to operate financially without government interference. In his words, Bitcoin is a lifesaver that enables people’s free global movement and actions. Featured image from Pexels and chart from Traidngview.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The former US Department of Justice Attorney General Robert Francis Kennedy Jr, recently lamented the growing financial censorship worldwide and showed support for Bitcoin.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">The financial censorship of political enemies is something we’re used to seeing under authoritarian regimes. No one was surprised when Russia froze more than 100 bank accounts tied to opposition leader Alexei Navalny. But Canada did it too, locking more than 200 accounts of…</p>
<p>&mdash; Robert F. Kennedy Jr (@RobertKennedyJr) <a href="https://twitter.com/RobertKennedyJr/status/1654303142966706176?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">May 5, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p></p>
<p>According to Kennedy Jr, the major victims are political enemies of most governments that he classified as &#8220;authoritarian regimes.&#8221;</p>
<h2>Political Enemies Made To Suffer Financial Censorship</h2>
<p>In his Twitter post, Kennedy stated that the trend in this financial prohibition is evident in several countries globally. In 2019, <a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/uk-russia-politics-navalny-idUKKCN1UY1EZ" rel="nofollow">Russian authorities froze</a> over 100 bank accounts related to the opposition leader Alexei Navalny. Though the authorities stated that the action aligned with a money laundering investigation, many citizens believed it was politically inclined.</p>

<p>Last year, Canada froze over 200 accounts of people and firms connected to the protests in Ottawa against Covid-19 mandates. </p>
<p>According to the reports, Royal Canadian Mounted Police (RCMP) froze several financial products, which included bank and corporate accounts. Also, it froze a payment processing account with a valuation of about $3.8 million.</p>
<p>After citing these instances, the environmental lawyer stated that financial censorship is gradually creeping into the United States. This means a person’s account could be frozen due to his comments on social media or political stance.</p>
<p>Kennedy Jr cited the incidents in 2010 when PayPal, Mastercard, and Visa suspended an NGO and whistleblowing platform, WikiLeaks, that exposed big corporations and government institutions of unethical acts. Notably, the suspension was through the command of the US State Department. </p>
<h2>DoJ Kennedy Jr On Bitcoin And CBDCs</h2>
<p>The central banks of countries manage Central Bank Digital Currencies (CBDCs). This means that the government will control the financial accounts of all residents in a country that runs CBDC. </p>
<p>Kenndy Jr believes CBDCs could magnify a government&#8217;s power to suppress meaningful political dissent. The authorities could decide to cut the financial access of some individuals just because of political statements and opinions. </p>

<p>The lawyer noted that a meaningful dissent should include people&#8217;s ability to save and use their finances without political interference. It should be about maintaining the proper political protection from powerful personal interests regarding democracy. </p>
<p>But citizens&#8217; meaningful dissent is at risk with the adoption of CBDCs and their power to the government. As such, Kennedy Jr supported Bitcoin, stating that the crypto asset would allow anyone to operate financially without government interference.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-530140 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSDT_2023-05-05_19-18-00-860x499.png" alt="Former DoJ Kennedy Jr, Laments on Global Financial Censorship, Shows Support For Bitcoin" width="860" height="499" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSDT_2023-05-05_19-18-00-860x499.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSDT_2023-05-05_19-18-00-460x267.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSDT_2023-05-05_19-18-00-768x446.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSDT_2023-05-05_19-18-00-750x435.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSDT_2023-05-05_19-18-00.png 1116w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" />
<p>In his words, Bitcoin is a lifesaver that enables people’s free global movement and actions.</p>
<p>Featured image from Pexels and chart from Traidngview.com</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-Mean-Transaction-Size-460x260.jpg" width="460" height="260" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Pro-XRP Lawyer Castigates The SEC&#8217;s Argument Saying It&#8217;s Unfounded And Absurd</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/ripple/pro-xrp-lawyer-castigates-the-secs-argument-saying-its-unfounded-and-absurd/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mike D.]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 18:30:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[John Deaton]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrpusdt]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=530112</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Pro-XRP lawyer representing thousands of XRP holders as Amicus Curiae has slammed the US SEC&#8217;s position in the ongoing Ripple lawsuit. In a tweet, John Deaton claims the SEC undermined its once credible case by quoting an unrelated legal document. Deaton believes the document, dubbed ECF 640, supported his claim when the SEC stated that the XRP purchase was an investment in a &#8220;common enterprise.&#8221; “The quoted legal document supports [what I said] by stating that even if some country recognizes XRP as fiat currency in the future, it would still be considered a security.” If El Salvador 🇸🇻 recognized XRP as legal tender, like #BTC &#8211; the SEC claims it still a security. 🤦‍♂️ https://t.co/fI1Ofn23iN &#8212; John E Deaton (@JohnEDeaton1) May 5, 2023 According to Deaton, the SEC will still regard XRP as a security even if other countries recognize it as a legal tender. SEC’s XRP Theory Is Indefinable In Time And Space, Says Deaton Deaton argued that the SEC cannot boycott the Howey test by alleging that every XRP sale (before, now, and future) meets all the test’s prongs. He noted that no underlying asset in an investment contract was ever tagged security since the Howey test started 76 years ago. Related Reading: Bitcoin On-Chain Transactions Reach New Heights, What’s Fueling the Surge? The legal expert further explained that no investment contract exists without a legal relationship between the buyer and promoter. Deaton&#8217;s tweets suggest the SEC&#8217;s argument is absurd and lacks credibility.  Deaton cited his Amici motion to the federal judge presiding over the Ripple case, Judge Torres. He addressed the SEC&#8217;s argument as a shorthand and analytically lazy contention, slamming the agency for tagging every XRP sale, from its ICO to the present, financial security.  In the lawyer&#8217;s opinion, the scope of the SEC&#8217;s arguments is overstretched and indefinable in time and space. Community’s Responses to Deaton’s Argument Deaton&#8217;s tweets attracted other crypto proponents. While responding, a Twitter user @Kashta9 said he thinks the SEC’s position in the lawsuit is that all XRP sales, including those in the secondary market, are investment contracts. Other respondents said they don&#8217;t care about anybody&#8217;s opinion but the judge&#8217;s. Related Reading: Why Is Bitcoin And Crypto Up Today? Deaton ended his argument by expressing his confidence in Judge Torres&#8217; ability to recognize and act according to the massive public interest in the XRP lawsuit. The Ripple lawsuit is among the most viral topics in the crypto industry, with many anticipating a ruling in Q2 2023. A total of 75,000 XRP holders from the United States and 143 countries joined the Ripple lawsuit. However, no one can predict if it will become security until the judge pronounces judgment. Featured image from Pexels and chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Pro-XRP lawyer representing thousands of XRP holders as Amicus Curiae has slammed the US SEC&#8217;s position in the ongoing Ripple lawsuit.</p>
<p>In a tweet, John Deaton claims the SEC undermined its once credible case by quoting an unrelated legal document. Deaton believes the document, dubbed ECF 640, supported his claim when the SEC stated that the XRP purchase was an investment in a &#8220;common enterprise.&#8221;</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">“The quoted legal document supports [what I said] by stating that even if some country recognizes XRP as fiat currency in the future, it would still be considered a security.”</p>
<p>If El Salvador <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f1f8-1f1fb.png" alt="🇸🇻" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> recognized XRP as legal tender, like <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/BTC?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#BTC</a> &#8211; the SEC claims it still a security. <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f926-200d-2642-fe0f.png" alt="🤦‍♂️" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> <a href="https://t.co/fI1Ofn23iN" rel="nofollow">https://t.co/fI1Ofn23iN</a></p>
<p>&mdash; John E Deaton (@JohnEDeaton1) <a href="https://twitter.com/JohnEDeaton1/status/1654370806045048832?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">May 5, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p></p>
<p>According to Deaton, the SEC will still regard XRP as a security even if other countries recognize it as a legal tender.</p>
<h2>SEC’s XRP Theory Is Indefinable In Time And Space, Says Deaton</h2>
<p>Deaton <a href="https://twitter.com/JohnEDeaton1/status/1654280863339651072" rel="nofollow">argued</a> that the SEC cannot boycott the Howey test by alleging that every XRP sale (before, now, and future) meets all the test’s prongs. He noted that no underlying asset in an investment contract was ever tagged security since the Howey test started 76 years ago.</p>

<p>The legal expert further explained that no investment contract exists without a legal relationship between the buyer and promoter. Deaton&#8217;s tweets suggest the SEC&#8217;s argument is absurd and lacks credibility. </p>
<p>Deaton cited his Amici motion to the federal judge presiding over the Ripple case, Judge Torres. He addressed the SEC&#8217;s argument as a shorthand and analytically lazy contention, slamming the agency for tagging every XRP sale, from its ICO to the present, financial security. </p>
<p>In the lawyer&#8217;s opinion, the scope of the SEC&#8217;s arguments is overstretched and indefinable in time and space.</p>
<h2>Community’s Responses to Deaton’s Argument</h2>
<p>Deaton&#8217;s tweets attracted other crypto proponents. While responding, a Twitter user <a href="https://twitter.com/Kashta9/status/1654257260418457600" rel="nofollow">@Kashta9</a> said he thinks the SEC’s position in the lawsuit is that all XRP sales, including those in the secondary market, are investment contracts. Other respondents <a href="https://twitter.com/mreinvest/status/1654305809562492931" rel="nofollow">said</a> they don&#8217;t care about anybody&#8217;s opinion but the judge&#8217;s.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/why-is-bitcoin-and-crypto-up-today/">Why Is Bitcoin And Crypto Up Today?</a></p>
<p>Deaton ended his argument by <a href="https://twitter.com/JohnEDeaton1/status/1654445117342642176?cxt=HHwWgMCz-bHE4vUtAAAA" rel="nofollow">expressing</a> his confidence in Judge Torres&#8217; ability to recognize and act according to the massive public interest in the XRP lawsuit.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-530118 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSDT_2023-05-05_18-43-08-860x499.png" alt="Pro-XRP Lawyer Castigates The SEC's Argument Saying It's Unfounded And Absurd" width="860" height="499" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSDT_2023-05-05_18-43-08-860x499.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSDT_2023-05-05_18-43-08-460x267.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSDT_2023-05-05_18-43-08-768x446.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSDT_2023-05-05_18-43-08-750x435.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSDT_2023-05-05_18-43-08.png 1116w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" />
<p>The Ripple lawsuit is among the most viral topics in the crypto industry, with many anticipating a ruling in Q2 2023. A total of 75,000 XRP holders from the United States and 143 countries joined the Ripple lawsuit. However, no one can predict if it will become security until the judge pronounces judgment.</p>
<p>Featured image from Pexels and chart from TradingView</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/coin-g3c12cb5cb_1280-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Coinbase Q1 Report: Net Revenue Skyrockets 22% Quarter-Over-Quarter</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/coinbase-q1-report-net-revenue-skyrockets-22-quarter-over-quarter/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 17:40:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=530109</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Coinbase, one of the leading cryptocurrency exchanges, has reported impressive results for the first quarter of 2023. The company&#8217;s efforts toward building a more efficient and financially disciplined business have started to pay off. Despite a net loss of $79 million, Coinbase returned to positive Adjusted EBITDA, earnings before interests, taxes, and amortization, of $284 million, indicating a significant improvement in its financial metrics. According to Coinbase’s first quarter report, the company reduced costs and doubled down on operational excellence and risk management. These efforts resulted in a 22% Q/Q growth in net revenue and a 24% Q/Q decline in operating expenses. Coinbase Posts Strong Q1 Performance Coinbase announced a shift in focus in its latest quarterly report. The report showed that the company was no longer leading with messaging around SAAS, a cloud-based product that can be used directly by the users from their web browser via Coinbase One, as it did in the previous quarter. Related Reading: BREAKING: Binance Lists PEPE And FLOKI In Innovation Zone According to Ram Ahluwalia, the CEO of Lumida Wealth, the shift in focus is due to several factors. One of the main reasons is that Coinbase received feedback from customers indicating that they wanted the company to focus more on its core business of cryptocurrency trading and investing rather than expanding into other areas like SAAS. Additionally, the company recognized that there is a long road ahead for SAAS recurring revenue and that it may take some time to see significant results in this area. Despite this, Coinbase&#8217;s latest quarterly report showed that the company&#8217;s recurring revenue is still strong. However, a significant portion of this revenue comes from USDC interest income, which has been a primary driver of Coinbase&#8217;s success over the past year. Ahluwalia acknowledged that the company is aware of the risks associated with relying heavily on interest income and is actively working to diversify its revenue streams. According to Ahluwalia, the company&#8217;s interest income has grown rapidly in recent quarters, reaching $240 million in the first quarter of 2023. While loans grew by 20% quarter-over-quarter, indicating a strong appetite for loan products among Coinbase&#8217;s customers. Another interesting trend highlighted in the report is the fact that altcoins accounted for 45% of volume, indicating that Coinbase benefitted from a flight to safety as investors sought out more established cryptocurrencies. Also, assets on the platform grew by a massive 62% QoQ to $130 billion, a figure that is typically seen over a year rather than in a single quarter. Resilience In The Face Of Turmoil Coinbase revealed the rules governing the financial system are &#8220;outdated&#8221;, and the technology used to support it has been slow to catch up. This has resulted in a system that is “inefficient, costly, and often inaccessible” to large segments of the population. To address these issues, Coinbase is calling for a fundamental rethinking of the financial system. The company believes that blockchain technology and cryptocurrencies can play a key role in creating a more open, transparent, and efficient financial system that can serve the needs of everyone. &#160; Furthermore, Coinbase has been making strategic moves to position itself for growth and expansion in the cryptocurrency market. According to Ahluwalia, the company has over $5 billion in capital and liquidity, which is expected to strengthen the bid on Coinbase&#8217;s bond. Related Reading: 4 Reasons To Be Bullish On Bitcoin In Short-And Mid-Term In conclusion, Coinbase&#8217;s outlook for the future is optimistic, with the company benefiting from strong crypto asset prices and focused on achieving profitability and diversifying its revenue mix.  Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Coinbase, one of the leading cryptocurrency exchanges, has <a href="https://s27.q4cdn.com/397450999/files/doc_financials/2023/q1/Shareholder-Letter-Q1-2023.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">reported </a>impressive results for the first quarter of 2023. The company&#8217;s efforts toward building a more efficient and financially disciplined business have started to pay off. </p>
<p>Despite a net loss of $79 million, Coinbase returned to positive Adjusted EBITDA, earnings before interests, taxes, and amortization, of $284 million, indicating a significant improvement in its financial metrics.</p>
<p>According to Coinbase’s first quarter report, the company reduced costs and doubled down on operational excellence and risk management. These efforts resulted in a 22% Q/Q growth in net revenue and a 24% Q/Q decline in operating expenses.</p>
<h2><b>Coinbase Posts Strong Q1 Performance</b></h2>
<p>Coinbase announced a shift in focus in its latest quarterly report. The report showed that the company was no longer leading with messaging around SAAS, a cloud-based product that can be used directly by the users from their web browser via Coinbase One, as it did in the previous quarter.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/altcoin/breaking-binance-lists-pepe-and-floki-in-innovation-zone/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BREAKING: Binance Lists PEPE And FLOKI In Innovation Zone</a></p>
<p><a href="https://twitter.com/ramahluwalia/status/1654310641123880961?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">According </a>to Ram Ahluwalia, the CEO of Lumida Wealth, the shift in focus is due to several factors. One of the main reasons is that Coinbase received feedback from customers indicating that they wanted the company to focus more on its core business of cryptocurrency trading and investing rather than expanding into other areas like SAAS.</p>
<p> Additionally, the company recognized that there is a long road ahead for SAAS recurring revenue and that it may take some time to see significant results in this area.</p>
<p>Despite this, Coinbase&#8217;s latest quarterly report showed that the company&#8217;s recurring revenue is still strong. However, a significant portion of this revenue comes from USDC interest income, which has been a primary driver of Coinbase&#8217;s success over the past year. </p>
<p>Ahluwalia acknowledged that the company is aware of the risks associated with relying heavily on interest income and is actively working to diversify its revenue streams.</p>
<p>According to Ahluwalia, the company&#8217;s interest income has grown rapidly in recent quarters, reaching $240 million in the first quarter of 2023. While loans grew by 20% quarter-over-quarter, indicating a strong appetite for loan products among Coinbase&#8217;s customers.</p>
<p>Another interesting trend highlighted in the report is the fact that altcoins accounted for 45% of volume, indicating that Coinbase benefitted from a flight to safety as investors sought out more established cryptocurrencies. Also, assets on the platform grew by a massive 62% QoQ to $130 billion, a figure that is typically seen over a year rather than in a single quarter.</p>
<b>Resilience In The Face Of Turmoil</b>
<p>Coinbase revealed the rules governing the financial system are &#8220;outdated&#8221;, and the technology used to support it has been slow to catch up. This has resulted in a system that is “inefficient, costly, and often inaccessible” to large segments of the population.</p>
<p>To address these issues, Coinbase is calling for a fundamental rethinking of the financial system. The company believes that blockchain technology and cryptocurrencies can play a key role in creating a more open, transparent, and efficient financial system that can serve the needs of everyone.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large wp-image-530113" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/FvVDhxqWcAAuCT7-860x676.jpg" alt="Coinbase" width="860" height="676" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/FvVDhxqWcAAuCT7-860x676.jpg 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/FvVDhxqWcAAuCT7-460x362.jpg 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/FvVDhxqWcAAuCT7-768x604.jpg 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/FvVDhxqWcAAuCT7-750x589.jpg 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/FvVDhxqWcAAuCT7.jpg 1135w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" />
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Furthermore, Coinbase has been making strategic moves to position itself for growth and expansion in the cryptocurrency market. According to Ahluwalia, the company has over $5 billion in capital and liquidity, which is expected to strengthen the bid on Coinbase&#8217;s bond.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-reasons-bullish-in-short-and-mid-term/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">4 Reasons To Be Bullish On Bitcoin In Short-And Mid-Term</a></p>
<p>In conclusion, Coinbase&#8217;s outlook for the future is optimistic, with the company benefiting from strong crypto asset prices and focused on achieving profitability and diversifying its revenue mix. </p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/wosBzK0K/" alt="Coinbase" width="1814" height="858" />
<p>Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/spacex-p-KCm6xB9I-unsplash-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>PEPE Market Cap Crosses $1 Billion As Gemini Listing Rumors Spread</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/altcoin/pepe-market-cap-crosses-1-billion-as-gemini-listing-rumors-spread/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Best Owie]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 17:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[meme coin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[meme coins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PEPE]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PepeCoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=530053</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Crypto Twitter’s favorite new meme coin Pepecoin (PEPE) has hit another milestone. With an impressive rally over the last 24 hours, the coin crossed the $1 billion market cap mark and has now solidified its position as a top 100 cryptocurrency. But after rallying over 20,000x since its launch three weeks ago, what could be driving this fresh rally for the meme coin? Gemini Listing Rumors Spurs New Growth On Thursday, Tyler Winklevoss, one of the co-founders of the Gemini exchange, tweeted a frog emoji that spurred listing rumors in the PEPE community. The tweet which carried only the single emoji was followed up by another tweet with the emoji but this time with the words “sounds rare” added to it. Related Reading: Pro-XRP Attorney Shares Information That Could Be Bullish For Ripple Following the tweets, rumors quickly spread that the exchange may be planning to list the meme coin which has been pulling in significant volume since its launch. The rumors were further fueled by the PEPE team moving its treasury holdings to a multi-sig wallet. The reason for this is that larger exchanges oftentimes require team treasury funds to be secured before they are listed. So speculations rose quickly about a possible listing and the Winklevoss tweet has the community convinced that the Gemini listing is coming next. over the next hour you will see some transactions taking place from $PEPE pepecexwallet.eth. a multi-sig is being created and the cex-wallet tokens will be transferred to the safe. pic.twitter.com/anh6VGxjeN &#8212; Pepe (@pepecoineth) May 4, 2023 PEPE Rises 100% In One Day At this point, it is no longer a surprise when PEPE moves so quickly. But moving from a $500 million market cap to over $1 billion in one day in a bear market is a considerable feat. Nevertheless, that is what the meme coin did. Data from on-chain aggregator CoinGecko shows that PEPE’s price moved from a price of $0.00000114 which it opened the day with to a new all-time high of $0.00000310. This brought its market cap to a peak of $1.1 billion. PEPE reaches new all-time high before correcting downward &#124; Source: PEPEUSDT on TradingView.com If the Gemini listing rumors are true, then the meme coin could be gearing up for a run to $2 billion just off the listing alone. Its 24-hour trading volume of $800 million is also significantly higher than that of its largest competitors, including Dogecoin at $253 million and Shiba Inu at $94 million. The meme coin has already been listed by Binance in its Innovation Zone and more exchanges are expected to follow suit. Related Reading: This Meme Coin Created By GPT-4 Is Now Worth $40 Million, Here’s Why Interestingly, another 6x move from its current price would see the market cap of PEPE flip SHIB, something that would be a considerable feat, making it the second-largest meme coin by market cap. However, for now, PEPE is resting easily as the third-largest meme coin in the market. The community has also grown rapidly and as of the time of this writing, the PEPE official Twitter has over 233,000 followers. On-chain data also shows that there are now almost 92,000 holders of the less than one-month coin. Follow Best Owie on Twitter for market insights, updates, and the occasional funny tweet… Featured image from PYMNTS, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="p2">Crypto Twitter’s favorite new meme coin Pepecoin (PEPE) has hit another milestone. With an impressive rally over the last 24 hours, the coin crossed the $1 billion market cap mark and has now solidified its position as a top 100 cryptocurrency. But after rallying over 20,000x since its launch three weeks ago, what could be driving this fresh rally for the meme coin?</p>
<h2 class="p2">Gemini Listing Rumors Spurs New Growth</h2>
<p class="p2">On Thursday, Tyler Winklevoss, one of the co-founders of the Gemini exchange, <a href="https://twitter.com/tyler/status/1654208964991516673?s=20" rel="nofollow">tweeted</a> a frog emoji that spurred listing rumors in the PEPE community. The tweet which carried only the single emoji was followed up by another <a href="https://twitter.com/cameron/status/1654244409209155593?s=20" rel="nofollow">tweet</a> with the emoji but this time with the words “sounds rare” added to it.</p>

<p class="p2">Following the tweets, rumors quickly spread that the exchange may be planning to list the meme coin which has been pulling in significant volume since its launch. The rumors were further fueled by the PEPE team moving its treasury holdings to a multi-sig wallet.</p>
<p class="p2">The reason for this is that larger exchanges oftentimes require team treasury funds to be secured before they are listed. So speculations rose quickly about a possible listing and the Winklevoss tweet has the community convinced that the Gemini listing is coming next.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">over the next hour you will see some transactions taking place from <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24PEPE&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$PEPE</a> pepecexwallet.eth. </p>
<p>a multi-sig is being created and the cex-wallet tokens will be transferred to the safe. <a href="https://t.co/anh6VGxjeN" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/anh6VGxjeN</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Pepe (@pepecoineth) <a href="https://twitter.com/pepecoineth/status/1654228592363028481?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">May 4, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p></p>
<h2 class="p2">PEPE Rises 100% In One Day</h2>
<p class="p2">At this point, it is no longer a surprise when PEPE moves so quickly. But moving from a $500 million market cap to over $1 billion in one day in a bear market is a considerable feat. Nevertheless, that is what the meme coin did.</p>
<p class="p2">Data from on-chain aggregator CoinGecko shows that PEPE’s price moved from a price of $0.00000114 which it opened the day with to a new all-time high of $0.00000310. This brought its market cap to a peak of $1.1 billion.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/FTDmRkTo/" alt="Pepecoin (PEPE) price chart from TradingView.com" width="2854" height="1724" /></p>

<p class="p2">If the Gemini listing rumors are true, then the meme coin could be gearing up for a run to $2 billion just off the listing alone. Its <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/pepe" rel="nofollow">24-hour trading volume of $800 million</a> is also significantly higher than that of its largest competitors, including Dogecoin at $253 million and Shiba Inu at $94 million.</p>
<p>The meme coin has already been <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/altcoin/breaking-binance-lists-pepe-and-floki-in-innovation-zone/">listed</a> by Binance in its Innovation Zone and more exchanges are expected to follow suit.</p>

<p class="p2">Interestingly, another 6x move from its current price would see the market cap of PEPE flip SHIB, something that would be a considerable feat, making it the second-largest meme coin by market cap. However, for now, PEPE is resting easily as the third-largest meme coin in the market.</p>
<p class="p2">The community has also grown rapidly and as of the time of this writing, the PEPE official Twitter has over 233,000 followers. On-chain data also shows that there are now almost 92,000 holders of the less than one-month coin.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/PEPE-1-460x240.jpeg" width="460" height="240" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ripple Could Gain A New Ally Against The SEC, BitBoy</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/ripple-could-gain-a-new-ally-against-the-sec-bitboy/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mike D.]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 16:30:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BitBoy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stuart Alderoty]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrpusdt]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=530107</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Crypto influencer Ben Amstrong, alias Bitboy, has dropped a hint regarding the ongoing XRP lawsuit. The influencer asserted that Ripple and XRP could get a new ally in the ongoing SEC lawsuit. Following Bitboy’s assertion, the potential ally is the largest US-based crypto exchange, Coinbase, which recently filed a petition against the SEC. Bitboy’s revelation follows a meeting between the chief legal officers of Ripple and Coinbase, Stuart Alderoty and Paul Grewal. Recent Events Hint At Potential Coinbase And Ripple Alliance Coinbase has been at cross-chairs with the SEC over the regulator&#8217;s approach to crypto regulation. This issue led Coinbase to sue the SEC in response to a Wells notice from the regulator alleging securities law violation. Related Reading: Bitcoin On-Chain Transactions Reach New Heights, What’s Fueling the Surge? Stuart Aderoty&#8217;s remark in response to Coinbase’s fight against the SEC led many to believe the two firms might align against the regulator. The recent statement by Bitboy and the meeting of the two lawyers further confirm these speculations.  Although the specifics of the meetings remain unknown, both lawyers seemed excited about it. Grewal confirmed this by saying that they need to meet more often. More so, Stuart Alderoty expressed his gratitude, adding that Ripple’s legal team spent time discussing with Grewal. This statement suggests the meeting was professional and involved Ripple and Coinbase, not just a chance encounter. Why This Alliance May Be Imminent Due to the scarce information about the meeting, the XRP community began speculating on an alliance between the firms.  John Deaton, commenting on the meeting between the two attorneys, noted that survival in the US regulatory atmosphere could require a team-up with one&#8217;s enemy. Related Reading: Why Is Bitcoin And Crypto Up Today? The alliance speculations follow advice from prominent personalities like US congress candidate January Walker and attorney John Deaton. These two have urged the crypto community to team up and fight against the SEC’s regulatory war on cryptocurrencies. Coinbase’s recent lawsuit against the SEC asking the regulator for clear regulatory guidelines excited the XRP community and the broader crypto industry. Moreover, Alderoty’s remark, “the enemy of my enemy is my friend,” shortly after Coinbase confirmed the Wells notice hinted at a potential alliance between both firms. Featured image from Pexels and Chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Crypto influencer Ben Amstrong, alias Bitboy, has dropped a hint regarding the ongoing XRP lawsuit. The influencer <a href="https://twitter.com/Bitboy_Crypto/status/1654148682730688512" rel="nofollow">asserted</a> that Ripple and XRP could get a new ally in the ongoing SEC lawsuit.</p>
<p>Following Bitboy’s assertion, the potential ally is the largest US-based crypto exchange, Coinbase, which recently filed a petition against the SEC.</p>
<p>Bitboy’s revelation follows a meeting between the chief legal officers of Ripple and Coinbase, Stuart Alderoty and Paul Grewal.</p>
<h2>Recent Events Hint At Potential Coinbase And Ripple Alliance</h2>
<p>Coinbase has been at cross-chairs with the SEC over the regulator&#8217;s approach to crypto regulation. This issue led Coinbase to <a href="https://twitter.com/iampaulgrewal/status/1650655451720318976" rel="nofollow">sue</a> the SEC in response to a Wells notice from the regulator alleging securities law violation.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-on-chain-transactions-reach-new-heights-whats-fueling-the-surge/">Bitcoin On-Chain Transactions Reach New Heights, What’s Fueling the Surge?</a></p>
<p>Stuart Aderoty&#8217;s <a href="https://twitter.com/s_alderoty/status/1638708343417217024" rel="nofollow">remark</a> in response to Coinbase’s fight against the SEC led many to believe the two firms might align against the regulator. The recent statement by Bitboy and the meeting of the two lawyers further confirm these speculations. </p>
<p>Although the specifics of the meetings remain unknown, both lawyers seemed excited about it. Grewal confirmed this by saying that they need to meet more often.</p>
<p>More so, Stuart Alderoty <a href="https://twitter.com/s_alderoty/status/1653899296255901696?" rel="nofollow">expressed</a> his gratitude, adding that Ripple’s legal team spent time discussing with Grewal. This statement suggests the meeting was professional and involved Ripple and Coinbase, not just a chance encounter.</p>
<h2>Why This Alliance May Be Imminent</h2>
<p>Due to the scarce information about the meeting, the XRP community began speculating on an alliance between the firms. </p>
<p>John Deaton, <a href="https://twitter.com/JohnEDeaton1/status/1654184068735549440" rel="nofollow">commenting</a> on the meeting between the two attorneys, noted that survival in the US regulatory atmosphere could require a team-up with one&#8217;s enemy.</p>

<p>The alliance speculations follow advice from prominent personalities like US congress candidate <a href="https://twitter.com/UtahPolitician/status/1602671037044633600" rel="nofollow">January Walker</a> and attorney John Deaton. These two have urged the crypto community to team up and fight against the SEC’s regulatory war on cryptocurrencies.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-530110 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSDT_2023-05-05_18-34-13-860x499.png" alt="Ripple Could Gain A New Ally Against The SEC, BitBoy" width="860" height="499" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSDT_2023-05-05_18-34-13-860x499.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSDT_2023-05-05_18-34-13-460x267.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSDT_2023-05-05_18-34-13-768x446.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSDT_2023-05-05_18-34-13-750x435.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSDT_2023-05-05_18-34-13.png 1116w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" />
<p>Coinbase’s recent <a href="https://twitter.com/iampaulgrewal/status/1650655451720318976" rel="nofollow">lawsuit</a> against the SEC asking the regulator for clear regulatory guidelines excited the XRP community and the broader crypto industry. </p>
<p>Moreover, Alderoty’s <a href="https://twitter.com/s_alderoty/status/1638708343417217024" rel="nofollow">remark</a>, “the enemy of my enemy is my friend,” shortly after Coinbase confirmed the Wells notice hinted at a potential alliance between both firms.</p>
<p>Featured image from Pexels and Chart from TradingView.com</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/pexels-moose-photos-1036638-460x281.jpg" width="460" height="281" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Stacks (STX) Stumbles As Bulls Fail To Remain Intact</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/crypto/stacks-stx-stumbles-as-bulls-fail-to-remain-intact/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Eli Dambel]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 15:40:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bears]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bulls]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stacks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[STXUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=530089</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[On March 20, 2023, Stacks (STX) hit an all-time high of $1.30. But the price declined below the $1 mark on March 25 as the bears increased momentum. The asset has remained under the mark from March until May 5. The 4-hour time frame chart today indicates that the STX token is trading on a downtrend movement due to high selling pressure. The token is also in a long-term downtrend, with the bears increasing its selling pressure forming lower highs and higher lows. Will The Bulls Dethrone The Bears From The Market? The overall structure of the STX market is bearish, with the bears battling with the bulls to take full control. The 4-hour chart shows that the STACK token is trading at $0.7276, with a decrease of -6.47% within the last 24 hours. Related Reading: This Meme Coin Created By GPT-4 Is Now Worth $40 Million, Here’s Why STX&#8217;s 24-hour trading volume is down by 56.76%, with a total market cap of $1 billion. This also shows that STX is not experiencing many activities at the moment. Despite the increased selling momentum resulting from the investor&#8217;s sentiment, the bulls are attempting to regain control by taking advantage of the support level at $0.67. Stacks (STX) Price Analysis Currently, STX is trading within the range of the 200-day simple moving average and the 50-day simple moving average, suggesting a neutral market position or consolidation phase. Related Reading: Pro-XRP Attorney Shares Information That Could Be Bullish For Ripple Consequently, traders and investors may use the 50-day and 200-day SMAs as reliable support and resistance levels while trading.  Notably, a breach above the 50-day SMA may signal a potential short-term uptrend, presenting a buying opportunity for traders. The fact that STX lacks an obvious trend, either upward or downward, suggests that the price is stable. Currently, the RSI level of STX is 41, which shows that the STX market is heading towards the neutral zone, and there&#8217;s indecision. The Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD) line is below the signal line, which suggests a potential sell opportunity.  Moreover, the histogram, which measures the distance between the MACD line and the signal line, is below the zero line, indicating that the security is trading below its long-term trend.  Additionally, the histogram is increasing, implying that the bearish momentum is gaining strength. This situation suggests that STX is facing downward pressure, which could continue for some time, allowing traders to short the token. STX trades between the $0.6666 and $0.8275 primary support and resistance levels. Stack&#8217;s first important resistance level is $0.8275. If the price rises above this level, the next significant resistance levels are $1.0212 and 1.3103. Conversely, with high selling pressure, the price of STX may fall below its important support levels of $0.5220 &#38; $0.2684. Featured image from Pixabay and chart from Tradingview]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On March 20, 2023, Stacks (STX) hit an <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/chart/?symbol=BINANCE%3ASTXUSDT" rel="nofollow">all-time high</a> of $1.30. But the price declined below the $1 mark on March 25 as the bears increased momentum. The asset has remained under the mark from March until May 5.</p>
<p>The 4-hour time frame chart today indicates that the STX token is trading on a downtrend movement due to high selling pressure. The token is also in a long-term downtrend, with the bears increasing its selling pressure forming lower highs and higher lows.</p>
<h2>Will The Bulls Dethrone The Bears From The Market?</h2>
<p>The overall structure of the STX market is bearish, with the bears battling with the bulls to take full control. The 4-hour chart shows that the STACK token is trading at $0.7276, with a decrease of -6.47% within the last 24 hours.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/altcoin/this-meme-coin-created-by-gpt-4-is-now-worth-40-million-heres-why/?swcfpc=1">This Meme Coin Created By GPT-4 Is Now Worth $40 Million, Here’s Why</a></p>
<p>STX&#8217;s 24-hour <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/stacks/" rel="nofollow">trading volume</a> is down by 56.76%, with a total market cap of $1 billion. This also shows that STX is not experiencing many activities at the moment.</p>
<p>Despite the increased selling momentum resulting from the investor&#8217;s sentiment, the bulls are attempting to regain control by taking advantage of the support level at $0.67.</p>
<h2>Stacks (STX) Price Analysis</h2>
<p>Currently, STX is trading within the range of the 200-day simple moving average and the 50-day simple moving average, suggesting a neutral market position or consolidation phase.</p>

<p>Consequently, traders and investors may use the 50-day and 200-day SMAs as reliable support and resistance levels while trading. </p>
<p>Notably, a breach above the 50-day SMA may signal a potential short-term uptrend, presenting a buying opportunity for traders. The fact that STX lacks an obvious trend, either upward or downward, suggests that the price is stable.</p>
<p>Currently, the RSI level of STX is 41, which shows that the STX market is heading towards the neutral zone, and there&#8217;s indecision. The Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD) line is below the signal line, which suggests a potential sell opportunity. </p>
<p>Moreover, the histogram, which measures the distance between the MACD line and the signal line, is below the zero line, indicating that the security is trading below its long-term trend. </p>
<p>Additionally, the histogram is increasing, implying that the bearish momentum is gaining strength. This situation suggests that STX is facing downward pressure, which could continue for some time, allowing traders to short the token.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-530096 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/STXUSDT_2023-05-05_17-55-19-860x471.png" alt="Stacks (STX) Stumbles As Bulls Fail To Remain Intact, Another Bearish Trend For STX" width="860" height="471" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/STXUSDT_2023-05-05_17-55-19-860x471.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/STXUSDT_2023-05-05_17-55-19-460x252.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/STXUSDT_2023-05-05_17-55-19-768x420.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/STXUSDT_2023-05-05_17-55-19-750x411.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/STXUSDT_2023-05-05_17-55-19-1140x624.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/STXUSDT_2023-05-05_17-55-19.png 1529w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" />
<p>STX trades between the $0.6666 and $0.8275 primary support and resistance levels. Stack&#8217;s first important resistance level is $0.8275. If the price rises above this level, the next significant resistance levels are $1.0212 and 1.3103.</p>
<p>Conversely, with high selling pressure, the price of STX may fall below its important support levels of $0.5220 &amp; $0.2684.</p>
<p>Featured image from Pixabay and chart from Tradingview</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/polar-bear-g2523935d3_1280-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Mystery Wallet Burns 1.69 Billion Shiba Inu, Will It Result In Price Bump?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/mystery-wallet-burns-1-69-billion-shiba-inu-will-it-result-in-price-bump/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Eli Dambel]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 14:00:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Shiba Inu]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cultpunks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shib Burn]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=530081</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[An unidentified Shiba Inu wallet holder burnt about 1.69 billion SHIB in a single transaction. This burn event caused the overall SHIB burn rate to increase by 38,986.28%, exceeding yesterday&#8217;s burn rate of 1.34 million SHIB. SHIB burn events are critical to its price movement since they eliminate excess tokens in circulation and the 1.69 billion SHIB burn represents the third-largest burn event this week. However, the burn event did not significantly impact SHIB&#8217;s price, although it could improve its performance in the long term. SHIB Burn Rate Increasing This Week Shiba Inu experienced massive burn events this week from some of its top holders. CultPunks and a mysterious wallet are among the main contributors to these burns. A total of 2.25 billion SHIB token burns occurred on May 3-4. These transactions significantly increase the SHIB burns on the network in 2023. Related Reading: Pro-XRP Attorney Shares Information That Could Be Bullish For Ripple The new NFT collection on the Modulus Network, Cultpunks, burnt 246.74 million SHIB in a single transaction. Also, Blaze Token sent approximately 2 billion SHIB to the dead wallet in a single transaction. These burns contributed to the overall burn rate that increased progressively to date. Amid the ongoing burn transactions, some whales continue to accumulate SHIB tokens. Etherscan.io revealed that a prominent SHIB whale purchased 221.72 million SHIB worth $2.23 million in a single transaction.  The whale started its purchases on April 25, 2023, when it bought 730.61 million SHIB. Also, on April 27, the same whale acquired an additional 76.31 billion SHIB worth $770,036. Additionally, the SHIB whale bought 49.34 billion SHIB worth $495,868 on April 29.  Lastly, the same SHIB whale purchased 348.11 billion SHIB tokens worth $3.50 million last week in four transactions, bringing its current holdings to 21.6 trillion SHIB tokens ($218.19 million). Will The Burns And Whale Accumulation Boost Shiba Inu? Shiba Inu is fluctuating today despite the news of increasing token burns and accumulations. It has formed a Gravestone Doji candlestick indicating the possibility of further decline in its price. SHIB is trading below its 50-day and 200-day Simple Moving Averages (SMA), suggesting a bearish sentiment in the short and long term.  Also, its Relative Strength Index (RSI) value is 35.97, close to the oversold region of 30. However, the indicator is moving sideways, reflecting traders&#8217; uncertainty in the market today. Related Reading: This Meme Coin Created By GPT-4 Is Now Worth $40 Million, Here’s Why SHIB has dropped below the $0.0000102 support level turning it to resistance. Its closest support level is $0.00000963 and a decline below this level will push the asset into the oversold region. Also, its resistance levels are $0.0000102, $0.00001188, $0.000014, and $0.0000159. SHIB will likely decline to rest on the $0.00000963 support if the bears sustain their charge. Featured image from Pixabay and chart from Tradingview]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>An unidentified Shiba Inu wallet holder burnt <a href="https://www.shibburn.com/btx/0xdf9cc57cf0292d344a3103d490052610f8c6633b93d771482d676b39ea3344e3" rel="nofollow">about 1.69 billion</a> SHIB in a single transaction. This burn event caused the overall SHIB burn rate to increase by 38,986.28%, exceeding yesterday&#8217;s burn rate of 1.34 million SHIB.</p>
<p>SHIB <a href="https://twitter.com/shibburn/status/1653610356487385089" rel="nofollow">burn events</a> are critical to its price movement since they eliminate excess tokens in circulation and the 1.69 billion SHIB burn represents the third-largest burn event this week. However, the burn event did not significantly impact SHIB&#8217;s price, although it could improve its performance in the long term.</p>
<h2>SHIB Burn Rate Increasing This Week</h2>
<p>Shiba Inu experienced massive burn events this week from some of its <a href="https://twitter.com/cultpunksnfts/status/1643282399642484736?" rel="nofollow">top holders</a>. CultPunks and a mysterious wallet are among the main contributors to these burns. A total of 2.25 billion SHIB token burns occurred on May 3-4. These transactions significantly increase the SHIB burns on the network in 2023.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/pro-xrp-attorney-shares-information-that-could-be-bullish-for-ripple/?swcfpc=1">Pro-XRP Attorney Shares Information That Could Be Bullish For Ripple</a></p>
<p>The new NFT collection on the Modulus Network, Cultpunks, burnt 246.74 million SHIB in a single transaction. Also, <a href="https://twitter.com/blaze_token/status/1653532266252083200" rel="nofollow">Blaze Token</a> sent approximately 2 billion SHIB to the dead wallet in a single transaction. These burns contributed to the overall burn rate that increased progressively to date.</p>
<p>Amid the ongoing burn transactions, some whales continue to accumulate SHIB tokens. <a href="https://etherscan.io/token/0x95ad61b0a150d79219dcf64e1e6cc01f0b64c4ce" rel="nofollow">Etherscan.io</a> revealed <a href="https://twitter.com/army_shiba/status/1653679345708285952" rel="nofollow">that a prominent SHIB whale</a> purchased 221.72 million SHIB worth $2.23 million in a single transaction. </p>
<p>The whale started its purchases on April 25, 2023, when it bought 730.61 million SHIB. Also, on April 27, the same whale acquired an additional 76.31 billion SHIB worth $770,036. Additionally, the SHIB whale bought 49.34 billion SHIB worth $495,868 on April 29. </p>
<p>Lastly, the same SHIB whale purchased <a href="https://etherscan.io/token/0x95ad61b0a150d79219dcf64e1e6cc01f0b64c4ce" rel="nofollow">348.11 billion SHIB</a> tokens worth $3.50 million last week in four transactions, bringing its current holdings to 21.6 trillion SHIB tokens ($218.19 million).</p>
<h2>Will The Burns And Whale Accumulation Boost Shiba Inu?</h2>
<p>Shiba Inu is fluctuating today despite the news of increasing token burns and accumulations. It has formed a Gravestone Doji candlestick indicating the possibility of further decline in its price.</p>
<p>SHIB is trading below its 50-day and 200-day Simple Moving Averages (SMA), suggesting a bearish sentiment in the short and long term. </p>
<p>Also, its Relative Strength Index (RSI) value is 35.97, close to the oversold region of 30. However, the indicator is moving sideways, reflecting traders&#8217; uncertainty in the market today.</p>

<p>SHIB has dropped below the $0.0000102 support level turning it to resistance. Its closest support level is $0.00000963 and a decline below this level will push the asset into the oversold region.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-530085 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/SHIBUSDT_2023-05-05_17-41-31-860x470.png" alt="Mystery Wallet Burns 1.69 Billion Shiba Inu, Will It Result In Price Bump?" width="860" height="470" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/SHIBUSDT_2023-05-05_17-41-31-860x470.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/SHIBUSDT_2023-05-05_17-41-31-460x252.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/SHIBUSDT_2023-05-05_17-41-31-768x420.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/SHIBUSDT_2023-05-05_17-41-31-750x410.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/SHIBUSDT_2023-05-05_17-41-31-1140x624.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/SHIBUSDT_2023-05-05_17-41-31.png 1530w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" />
<p>Also, its resistance levels are $0.0000102, $0.00001188, $0.000014, and $0.0000159. SHIB will likely decline to rest on the $0.00000963 support if the bears sustain their charge.</p>
<p>Featured image from Pixabay and chart from Tradingview</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/shiba-inu-g674580f1a_1280-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
