<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
>

<channel>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.newsbtc.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<description>Bitcoin &#38; cryptocurrency news today, price &#38; technical analysis</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 03:12:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Ethereum Price Looks Set For Another Leg Over $2K</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-leg-over-2k/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 03:12:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=529013</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Ethereum price is trading in a positive zone above $1,850 support against the US Dollar. ETH could rally toward $2,000 if it stays above the $1,880 support. Ethereum is consolidating and facing resistance near the $1,925 level. The price is trading above $1,850 and the 100-hourly Simple Moving Average. There is a key contracting triangle forming with resistance near $1,920 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD (data feed via Kraken). The pair could rally again if it clears the $1,925 resistance. Ethereum Price Remains Supported Ethereum’s price started a fresh increase from the $1,800 support zone. ETH gained pace and was able to settle above the $1,850 resistance zone, similar to Bitcoin. The upward move was such that the price even cleared the $1,880 resistance. A high is formed near $1,940 and the price is now consolidating gains. It is trading near the 50% Fib retracement level of the recent increase from the $1,873 swing low to the $1,940 high. Ether price is also well above $1,850 and the 100-hourly Simple Moving Average. Besides, there is a key contracting triangle forming with resistance near $1,920 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD. Source: ETHUSD on TradingView.com Immediate resistance is near the $1,925 level and the triangle region. A close above the $1,925 level might start a fresh rally. In the stated case, the price could rise toward the $1,960 resistance. Any more gains could send Ether toward the $2,000 resistance. Finally, if the bulls remain in action, there could be a drift toward the $2,120 level where the bears might take a stand and protect more gains. Fresh Decline in ETH? If Ethereum fails to clear the $1,925 resistance, it could start another decline. Initial support on the downside is near the $1,890 level and triangle trend line. The next major support is near the $1,880 zone or the 100-hourly Simple Moving Average. It is close to the 76.4% Fib retracement level of the recent increase from the $1,873 swing low to the $1,940 high, below which ether price might revisit the $1,840 support zone. Any more losses may perhaps take the price toward $1,800 in the near term. Technical Indicators Hourly MACD – The MACD for ETH/USD is now losing momentum in the bullish zone. Hourly RSI &#8211; The RSI for ETH/USD is above the 50 level. Major Support Level – $1,880 Major Resistance Level – $1,925]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>Ethereum price is trading in a positive zone above $1,850 support against the US Dollar. ETH could rally toward $2,000 if it stays above the $1,880 support.</em></p>
<ul>
<li>Ethereum is consolidating and facing resistance near the $1,925 level.</li>
<li>The price is trading above $1,850 and the 100-hourly Simple Moving Average.</li>
<li>There is a key contracting triangle forming with resistance near $1,920 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD (data feed via Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could rally again if it clears the $1,925 resistance.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Ethereum Price Remains Supported</h2>
<p>Ethereum’s price started a fresh increase from the $1,800 support zone. ETH gained pace and was able to settle above the $1,850 resistance zone, similar to <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-bulls-keep-pushing-30k/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a>.</p>
<p>The upward move was such that the price even cleared the $1,880 resistance. A high is formed near $1,940 and the price is now consolidating gains. It is trading near the 50% Fib retracement level of the recent increase from the $1,873 swing low to the $1,940 high.</p>
<p>Ether price is also well above $1,850 and the 100-hourly Simple Moving Average. Besides, there is a key contracting triangle forming with resistance near $1,920 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Ethereum-18.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-529014" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Ethereum-18.png" alt="Ethereum Price" width="1834" height="845" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Ethereum-18.png 1834w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Ethereum-18-460x212.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Ethereum-18-860x396.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Ethereum-18-768x354.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Ethereum-18-1536x708.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Ethereum-18-750x346.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Ethereum-18-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1834px) 100vw, 1834px" /></a></p>
<p>Source: <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/ETHUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">ETHUSD on TradingView.com</a></p>
<p>Immediate resistance is near the $1,925 level and the triangle region. A close above the $1,925 level might start a fresh rally. In the stated case, the price could rise toward the $1,960 resistance. Any more gains could send Ether toward the $2,000 resistance. Finally, if the bulls remain in action, there could be a drift toward the $2,120 level where the bears might take a stand and protect more gains.</p>
<h2>Fresh Decline in ETH?</h2>
<p>If Ethereum fails to clear the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-rips-higher-2k/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener">$1,925 resistance</a>, it could start another decline. Initial support on the downside is near the $1,890 level and triangle trend line.</p>
<p>The next major support is near the $1,880 zone or the 100-hourly Simple Moving Average. It is close to the 76.4% Fib retracement level of the recent increase from the $1,873 swing low to the $1,940 high, below which ether price might revisit the $1,840 support zone. Any more losses may perhaps take the price toward $1,800 in the near term.</p>
<p>Technical Indicators</p>
<p>Hourly MACD<strong> – </strong>The MACD for ETH/USD is now losing momentum in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>Hourly RSI<strong> &#8211; </strong>The RSI for ETH/USD is above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Level – $1,880</p>
<p>Major Resistance Level – $1,925</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/shutterstock_584552989-1-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Bulls Keep Pushing, Why Rally Isn’t Over Yet</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-bulls-keep-pushing-30k/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 02:31:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xbtusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=529009</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin price started a fresh increase above the $29,000 resistance. BTC could rally if there is a clear move above the $30,000 resistance. Bitcoin is moving higher above the $28,800 and $29,000 resistance levels. The price is trading above $28,800 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average. There is a major contracting triangle forming with support near $29,250 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Kraken). The pair could continue to rise if it clears the $29,800 and $30,000 resistance levels. Bitcoin Price Extends Its Increase Bitcoin price remained strong above the $28,000 support zone. BTC bulls were active and were able to pump the price above the $28,500 resistance zone. There was a steady increase above the $28,800 and $29,000 resistance levels. The price traded close to the $30,000 resistance zone. A high is formed near $29,882 and the price is now consolidating gains. Bitcoin is trading above $28,800 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average. There is also a major contracting triangle forming with support near $29,250 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair. The triangle support is close to the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $27,258 swing low to the $29,882 high. Source: BTCUSD on TradingView.com Immediate resistance is near the $29,800 level and the triangle trend line. The next major resistance sits near the $30,000 zone. A close above the $30,000 resistance could send Bitcoin toward $30,500. Any more gains could open the doors for a test of the key barrier at $31,200. Fresh Decline in BTC? If Bitcoin’s price fails to clear the $29,800 resistance, it could again start a fresh decline. Immediate support on the downside is near the $29,250 level and the triangle region. A downside break below the triangle might send the price toward the 50% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $27,258 swing low to the $29,882 high. The next major support is near the $28,250 zone or the 100 hourly Simple moving average. Any more losses might take Bitcoin toward $27,800 in the near term. Technical indicators: Hourly MACD – The MACD is now gaining pace in the bullish zone. Hourly RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BTC/USD is now above the 50 level. Major Support Levels – $29,250, followed by $28,550. Major Resistance Levels – $29,800, $30,000, and $30,500.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>Bitcoin price started a fresh increase above the $29,000 resistance. BTC could rally if there is a clear move above the $30,000 resistance.</em></p>
<ul>
<li>Bitcoin is moving higher above the $28,800 and $29,000 resistance levels.</li>
<li>The price is trading above $28,800 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average.</li>
<li>There is a major contracting triangle forming with support near $29,250 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could continue to rise if it clears the $29,800 and $30,000 resistance levels.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Bitcoin Price Extends Its Increase</h2>
<p>Bitcoin price <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-volatility-30k/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener">remained strong above the $28,000 support zone</a>. BTC bulls were active and were able to pump the price above the $28,500 resistance zone.</p>
<p>There was a steady increase above the $28,800 and $29,000 resistance levels. The price traded close to the $30,000 resistance zone. A high is formed near $29,882 and the price is now consolidating gains. Bitcoin is trading above $28,800 and the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-signals-increase-29k/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener">100 hourly Simple moving average</a>.</p>
<p>There is also a major contracting triangle forming with support near $29,250 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair. The triangle support is close to the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $27,258 swing low to the $29,882 high.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Bitcoin-18.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-529010" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Bitcoin-18.png" alt="Bitcoin Price" width="1834" height="845" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Bitcoin-18.png 1834w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Bitcoin-18-460x212.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Bitcoin-18-860x396.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Bitcoin-18-768x354.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Bitcoin-18-1536x708.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Bitcoin-18-750x346.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Bitcoin-18-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1834px) 100vw, 1834px" /></a></p>
<p>Source: <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BTCUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">BTCUSD on TradingView.com</a></p>
<p>Immediate resistance is near the $29,800 level and the triangle trend line. The next major resistance sits near the $30,000 zone. A close above the $30,000 resistance could send Bitcoin toward $30,500. Any more gains could open the doors for a test of the key barrier at $31,200.</p>
<h2>Fresh Decline in BTC?</h2>
<p>If Bitcoin’s price fails to clear the $29,800 resistance, it could again start a fresh decline. Immediate support on the downside is near the $29,250 level and the triangle region.</p>
<p>A downside break below the triangle might send the price toward the 50% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $27,258 swing low to the $29,882 high. The next major support is near the $28,250 zone or the 100 hourly Simple moving average. Any more losses might take Bitcoin toward $27,800 in the near term.</p>
<p>Technical indicators:</p>
<p>Hourly MACD – The MACD is now gaining pace in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>Hourly RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BTC/USD is now above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Levels – $29,250, followed by $28,550.</p>
<p>Major Resistance Levels – $29,800, $30,000, and $30,500.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/shutterstock_793954189-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>XRP Dominates The Market: ADV On Centralized Exchanges Surged by 46% In Q1 2023, Report</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/xrp-dominates-the-market-adv-on-centralized-exchanges-surged-by-46-in-q1-2023-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 23:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ripple xrp]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrp]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrpusdt]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=528996</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[XRP, the sixth-largest cryptocurrency by market capitalization, has recorded significant gains in the first quarter of 2023. Despite a drop from its yearly high of $0.590, XRP dominated the crypto market with total sales in Q1 2023 of $361.06M, net of purchases, compared to $226.31M in the previous quarter. Related Reading: Avalanche Remains Under Pressure Despite Circle’s CCTP Effort XRP Shines In Q1, Records Impressive Growth And Performance According to the Q1 report by Ripple, XRP Ledger (XRPL) on-chain activity remained strong, with decentralized exchange volumes increasing by 34% to $115M in Q1 2023 versus Q4 2022. Furthermore, XRP Average Daily Volume (ADV) on centralized exchanges jumped 46% in Q1 to $1B from $698M, indicating high demand for the cryptocurrency. While financial turmoil dominated the markets in Q1 of 2023, the token recorded a 46% increase in volumes compared to the previous quarter, according to the report. This increase can be attributed to market recovery and large volatile events spike volumes. Furthermore, according to the data released by Ripple, the XRPL&#8217;s on-chain activity remained strong in Q1 2023. The total number of transactions increased to 116,341,516, up from 106,429,153 in the previous quarter. The average cost per transaction (in XRP) also increased slightly to 0.00121 from 0.00096 in Q4 2022, while the average cost per transaction was $0.000484. In addition, the XRPL burned 140,993 tokens for transaction fees in Q1 2023, reflecting an increase from the previous quarter. The average XRP closing price during the period was $0.40, slightly lower than the previous quarter&#8217;s $0.42. The XRPL&#8217;s decentralized exchange (DEX) volumes also increased in Q1 2023, with $114,567,441 traded on DEX, up from $85,772,947 in the previous quarter. The number of trust lines remained stable at 8,317,321, while the number of new wallets created was 140,558. Moreover, The XRP Ledger&#8217;s on-chain activity remains robust, with Ripple&#8217;s latest report revealing that transactions increased by 9% in Q1 2023 to 116 million, compared to 106 million in the previous quarter. NFTs have emerged as a key driver of activity, with over one million assets minted on the Ledger since XLS-20 went live on the mainnet. Rising Above The Rest The report also notes that due to the recent banking crisis, Ripple temporarily stopped purchasing XRP for several days due to the disruption. However, the company has since resumed purchases and plans to continue purchasing XRP as ODL (On-Demand Liquidity) adoption grows. In addition, during Q1 2023, three billion XRP were released out of escrow, with one billion released each month, in line with prior quarters and the official escrow arrangement. Of the three billion XRP, 2.1 billion were returned and subsequently put into new escrow contracts throughout the quarter, ensuring the stability and predictability of XRP&#8217;s supply. At the time of writing, XRP is trading at $0.4640, representing a decline of 2.5% over the past 24 hours. In the wider time frames, XRP is experiencing a downturn, with 5%, 8%, and 3% decreases in the seven-day, fourteen-day, and 30-day timeframes, respectively. Related Reading: Solana Can Rally Over 20% If It Breaches This Level Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>XRP, the sixth-largest cryptocurrency by market capitalization, has recorded significant gains in the first quarter of 2023. Despite a drop from its yearly high of $0.590, XRP dominated the crypto market with total sales in Q1 2023 of $361.06M, net of purchases, compared to $226.31M in the previous quarter.</p>

<h2><b>XRP Shines In Q1, Records Impressive Growth And Performance</b></h2>
<p><a href="https://ripple.com/insights/q1-2023-xrp-markets-report/?utm_campaign=" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">According </a>to the Q1 report by Ripple, XRP Ledger (XRPL) on-chain activity remained strong, with decentralized exchange volumes increasing by 34% to $115M in Q1 2023 versus Q4 2022. Furthermore, XRP Average Daily Volume (ADV) on centralized exchanges jumped 46% in Q1 to $1B from $698M, indicating high demand for the cryptocurrency.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-528997" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Screenshot_28.jpg" alt="XRP" width="848" height="528" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Screenshot_28.jpg 848w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Screenshot_28-460x286.jpg 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Screenshot_28-768x478.jpg 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Screenshot_28-750x467.jpg 750w" sizes="(max-width: 848px) 100vw, 848px" />
<p>While financial turmoil dominated the markets in Q1 of 2023, the token recorded a 46% increase in volumes compared to the previous quarter, according to the report. This increase can be attributed to market recovery and large volatile events spike volumes.</p>
<p>Furthermore, according to the data released by Ripple, the XRPL&#8217;s on-chain activity remained strong in Q1 2023. The total number of transactions increased to 116,341,516, up from 106,429,153 in the previous quarter. The average cost per transaction (in XRP) also increased slightly to 0.00121 from 0.00096 in Q4 2022, while the average cost per transaction was $0.000484.</p>
<p>In addition, the XRPL burned 140,993 tokens for transaction fees in Q1 2023, reflecting an increase from the previous quarter. The average XRP closing price during the period was $0.40, slightly lower than the previous quarter&#8217;s $0.42.</p>
<p>The XRPL&#8217;s decentralized exchange (DEX) volumes also increased in Q1 2023, with $114,567,441 traded on DEX, up from $85,772,947 in the previous quarter. The number of trust lines remained stable at 8,317,321, while the number of new wallets created was 140,558.</p>
<p>Moreover, The XRP Ledger&#8217;s on-chain activity remains robust, with Ripple&#8217;s latest report revealing that transactions increased by 9% in Q1 2023 to 116 million, compared to 106 million in the previous quarter. NFTs have emerged as a key driver of activity, with over one million assets minted on the Ledger since XLS-20 went live on the mainnet.</p>
<b>Rising Above The Rest</b>
<p>The report also notes that due to the recent banking crisis, Ripple temporarily stopped purchasing XRP for several days due to the disruption. However, the company has since resumed purchases and plans to continue purchasing XRP as ODL (On-Demand Liquidity) adoption grows.</p>
<p>In addition, during Q1 2023, three billion XRP were released out of escrow, with one billion released each month, in line with prior quarters and the official escrow arrangement. Of the three billion XRP, 2.1 billion were returned and subsequently put into new escrow contracts throughout the quarter, ensuring the stability and predictability of XRP&#8217;s supply.</p>
<p>At the time of writing, XRP is trading at $0.4640, representing a decline of 2.5% over the past 24 hours. In the wider time frames, XRP is experiencing a downturn, with 5%, 8%, and 3% decreases in the seven-day, fourteen-day, and 30-day timeframes, respectively.</p>

<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/ZFKJrLVl/" alt="XRP" width="1814" height="858" />
<p>Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/ivan-diaz-aMBhrrveocw-unsplash-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dogecoin Bears Unshaken Despite New Trading Pair Addition On Top Exchange</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/dogecoin/dogecoin-bears-unshaken-despite-new-trading-pair-addition-on-top-exchange/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mudiaga Iritare]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 22:00:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[alt coin trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[doge]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=528953</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Dogecoin bears dealt a blow on the Shiba Inu-inspired meme-coin yesterday after a sudden Bitcoin rally which saw the alpha coin reclaim the $30,000 price level and instantly crash to previous support levels. Several cryptocurrencies, including DOGE, recorded losses after what looked to be bullish sentiments returned to the market as Bitcoin rallied. However, today&#8217;s trade session looked positive for Dogecoin after a leading cryptocurrency exchange announced the addition of a new trading pair for DOGE. While trading pair additions can boost liquidity and positively impact the trading volume of a cryptocurrency, DOGE is yet to be impacted positively in price. Related Reading: EOS Foundation Launches Upgrade As Crypto Market Rallies Binance Exchange Pairs Up Dogecoin With TrueUSD (TUSD) On Thursday, April 27, 2023, the Binance exchange announced on their website and mobile trading application about the TrueUSD (TUSD) stablecoin addition as a DOGE trading pair. This addition is programmed to go live tomorrow, April 28, 2023, at 08:00 UTC. However, the Binance spot grid for DOGE/TUSD will be enabled within 48 hours of the trading start time. The TrueUSD(TUSD) team confirmed this development via their official Twitter handle. .@binance will add $DOGE/TUSD trading pair at Apr 28th 08:00 (UTC) Binance Spot Grid will be enabled for the trading pair within 48 hours of the trading start time. https://t.co/b1qqU3R7Qu &#8212; TrueUSD (@tusdio) April 27, 2023 Due to this positive announcement and development, Dogecoin has seen some gains and could continue to extend them in the coming days. Trading pair additions to a cryptocurrency can boost liquidity, price growth, and exchange trading volume. A potential hurdle for the bullish price action could come from Shibetoshi Nakamoto, who took to Twitter to say he does not represent DOGE. Shibetoshi, once again, established some distance between himself and the project, which could be detrimental to the long term due to the founder&#8217;s popularity and influence.  Related Reading: 37 Billion Dogecoin Holdings In Jeopardy: Price Level Investors Should Watch Doge Technical Analysis On The Daily Timeframe When writing, Dogecoin is trading at $0.079 and stands close to resistance levels on the daily chart timeframe. While Doge rallied and broke resistance yesterday due to Bitcoin&#8217;s sharp price movements from sub $27,000 to $30,000, the bullish price action was short-lived. Today&#8217;s trading session turned positive for Dogecoin, forming a bullish candle following the Binance announcement of a new stablecoin trading pair, TrueUSD. However, Dogecoin is yet to notably move in price as it trades below its immediate resistance level of $0.08. DOGE, which trades at $0.079 when writing, is on a negative 24-hour price change of -3% and looks to struggle with a price. Bitcoin&#8217;s unstable and sideways movements provide Dogecoin bears more room to impact. However, Dogecoin still has upside potential if Bitcoin picks up momentum. Doge seen trading at immediate resistance level on the daily chart timeframe &#124; Source: DOGEUSD on TradingView.com Featured Image from Istock, Chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Dogecoin bears dealt a blow on the Shiba Inu-inspired meme-coin yesterday after a sudden Bitcoin rally which saw the alpha coin reclaim the $30,000 price level and instantly crash to previous support levels. Several cryptocurrencies, including DOGE, recorded losses after what looked to be bullish sentiments returned to the market as Bitcoin rallied.</p>
<p>However, today&#8217;s trade session looked positive for Dogecoin after a leading cryptocurrency exchange announced the addition of a new trading pair for DOGE. While trading pair additions can boost liquidity and positively impact the trading volume of a cryptocurrency, DOGE is yet to be impacted positively in price.</p>

<h2>Binance Exchange Pairs Up Dogecoin With TrueUSD (TUSD)</h2>
<p>On Thursday, April 27, 2023, the Binance exchange <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.binance.com/en/feed/post/464941" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">announced</a> on their website and mobile trading application about the TrueUSD (TUSD) stablecoin addition as a DOGE trading pair.</p>
<p>This addition is programmed to go live tomorrow, April 28, 2023, at 08:00 UTC. However, the Binance spot grid for DOGE/TUSD will be enabled within 48 hours of the trading start time. The TrueUSD(TUSD) team confirmed this development via their official Twitter handle.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">.<a href="https://twitter.com/binance?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">@binance</a> will add <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24DOGE&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$DOGE</a>/TUSD trading pair at Apr 28th 08:00 (UTC)</p>
<p>Binance Spot Grid will be enabled for the trading pair within 48 hours of the trading start time. <a href="https://t.co/b1qqU3R7Qu" rel="nofollow">https://t.co/b1qqU3R7Qu</a></p>
<p>&mdash; TrueUSD (@tusdio) <a href="https://twitter.com/tusdio/status/1651524568744620032?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">April 27, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p></p>
<p>Due to this positive announcement and development, Dogecoin has seen some gains and could continue to extend them in the coming days. Trading pair additions to a cryptocurrency can boost liquidity, price growth, and exchange trading volume.</p>
<p>A potential hurdle for the bullish price action could come from Shibetoshi Nakamoto, who took to Twitter to <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://twitter.com/BillyM2k/status/1651033979678773248?t=e2CsczqmfhXZYEUl2oWWRg&amp;s=19" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">say</a> he does not represent DOGE. Shibetoshi, once again, established some distance between himself and the project, which could be detrimental to the long term due to the founder&#8217;s popularity and influence. </p>

<h2>Doge Technical Analysis On The Daily Timeframe</h2>
<p>When writing, Dogecoin is trading at $0.079 and stands close to resistance levels on the daily chart timeframe. While Doge rallied and broke resistance yesterday due to Bitcoin&#8217;s sharp price movements from sub $27,000 to $30,000, the bullish price action was short-lived.</p>
<p>Today&#8217;s trading session turned positive for Dogecoin, forming a bullish candle following the Binance announcement of a new stablecoin trading pair, TrueUSD.</p>
<p>However, Dogecoin is yet to notably move in price as it trades below its immediate resistance level of $0.08.
DOGE, which trades at $0.079 when writing, is on a negative 24-hour price change of -3% and looks to struggle with a price.</p>
<p>Bitcoin&#8217;s unstable and sideways movements provide Dogecoin bears more room to impact. However, Dogecoin still has upside potential if Bitcoin picks up momentum.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/bVK2dXwU/" alt="Dogecoin" width="1280" height="595" /></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/iStock-1371840452-1-460x248.jpg" width="460" height="248" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Bloodbath: Market Volatility Sparks Panic, Wipes Out $1 Billion In Open Interest</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-bloodbath-market-volatility-sparks-panic-wipes-out-1-billion-in-open-interest/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 21:00:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=528975</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[In the last 24 hours, Bitcoin (BTC) has experienced a sharp increase in volatility, with prices fluctuating between $29,000 and $27,000, given the lack of liquidity in the market. This sudden price action has had a significant impact on bulls and bears. However, as of this writing, Bitcoin has managed to recover the $29,000 level, and it remains to be seen if it can continue to recover and consolidate above its key psychological level of $30,000, supporting the continuation of its bull run or if it will be further slumps in the coming days or weeks. Related Reading: Shiba Inu Whales Unload Billions Amid SHIB Price Retreat False Rumors Cause Bitcoin Investors To Liquidate In Droves According to Satoshi Club, the rumors of the US government and Mt. Gox sales were initially believed to be true, leading to panic selling among Bitcoin traders. However, it was later confirmed that the data was misclassified, and no such sales were taking place. The impact of these rumors on the market was significant, as traders were already on edge due to the high levels of volatility in the market. The news of potential large-scale sales by the US government and Mt. Gox, a now-defunct Bitcoin exchange, only added to the uncertainty and fear among traders. The market panic led to liquidating $300 million worth of positions as of this writing and the wiping out of $1 billion in open interest within 24 hours. This was a significant blow to both long and short traders, as many were forced to exit their positions at a loss. Open interest can impact the price of Bitcoin because it reflects the level of market participation and sentiment. When open interest is high, it suggests greater interest and activity in the market, potentially leading to price movements. However, the market has since recovered, and Bitcoin&#8217;s value has risen again. The Funding Rate has returned to around 0.003, indicating that traders are no longer overleveraged, and the open interest has also decreased, indicating a lack of significant activity in the market. Will BTC Reclaim The $30,000 Mark? Material Indicators, a leading cryptocurrency analytics provider, has analyzed the Weekly BTC/USDT chart, which shows bid liquidity moving up and ask liquidity moving down. According to Material Indicators, when bid and ask liquidity becomes more concentrated around a price point, it dampens volatility, leading to a sideways chop until one side makes a move. Per Material’s analysis, this type of price action differs from what was observed yesterday, as bids and asks were initially moving up, indicating a clear path for a pump. However, as things started getting “toppy,” asks began dropping down, ultimately dumping into the liquidity void created on the way up. Furthermore, CryptoCon, a leading provider of cryptocurrency analysis, has highlighted the recent drop in Bitcoin&#8217;s value, which saw a 15% decline. This drop has allowed the Chaikin Money Flow (CMF) indicator to reset slightly, as it nears dangerously close to hitting the Mid-Top .35 line. The CMF indicator is a technical analysis tool that measures buying and selling pressure in the market. When the CMF is above zero, buying pressure is stronger than selling pressure, and vice versa when it is below zero. The Mid-Top line at .35 represents the halfway point in the cycle for Bitcoin&#8217;s true gains. According to CryptoCon, the mid-top cycle for Bitcoin is approaching soon, but it is only half of the &#8220;true gains&#8221; for Bitcoin in a cycle. This means there is still significant potential for Bitcoin to experience further gains in the market. Related Reading: Filecoin Price Struggles To Move, Will It Surpass The $6 Barrier? Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In the last 24 hours, Bitcoin (BTC) has experienced a sharp increase in volatility, with prices fluctuating between $29,000 and $27,000, given the lack of liquidity in the market. This sudden price action has had a significant impact on bulls and bears.</p>
<p>However, as of this writing, Bitcoin has managed to recover the $29,000 level, and it remains to be seen if it can continue to recover and consolidate above its key psychological level of $30,000, supporting the continuation of its bull run or if it will be further slumps in the coming days or weeks.</p>

<h2><b>False Rumors Cause Bitcoin Investors To Liquidate In Droves</b></h2>
<p><a href="https://twitter.com/esatoshiclub/status/1651496653910863872?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">According </a>to Satoshi Club, the rumors of the US government and Mt. Gox sales were initially believed to be true, leading to panic selling among Bitcoin traders. However, it was later confirmed that the data was misclassified, and no such sales were taking place.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large wp-image-528978" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/FutBrugWAAAsQ2e-860x314.jpg" alt="Bitcoin " width="860" height="314" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/FutBrugWAAAsQ2e-860x314.jpg 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/FutBrugWAAAsQ2e-460x168.jpg 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/FutBrugWAAAsQ2e-768x280.jpg 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/FutBrugWAAAsQ2e-750x274.jpg 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/FutBrugWAAAsQ2e-1140x416.jpg 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/FutBrugWAAAsQ2e.jpg 1370w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" />
<p>The impact of these rumors on the market was significant, as traders were already on edge due to the high levels of volatility in the market. The news of potential large-scale sales by the US government and Mt. Gox, a now-defunct Bitcoin exchange, only added to the uncertainty and fear among traders.</p>
<p>The market panic led to liquidating $300 million worth of positions as of this writing and the wiping out of $1 billion in open interest within 24 hours. This was a significant blow to both long and short traders, as many were forced to exit their positions at a loss.</p>
<p>Open interest can impact the price of Bitcoin because it reflects the level of market participation and sentiment. When open interest is high, it suggests greater interest and activity in the market, potentially leading to price movements.</p>
<p>However, the market has since recovered, and Bitcoin&#8217;s value has risen again. The Funding Rate has returned to around 0.003, indicating that traders are no longer overleveraged, and the open interest has also decreased, indicating a lack of significant activity in the market.</p>
<b>Will BTC Reclaim The $30,000 Mark?</b>
<p>Material Indicators, a leading cryptocurrency analytics provider, has <a href="https://twitter.com/MI_Algos/status/1651626914384158724?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">analyzed </a>the Weekly BTC/USDT chart, which shows bid liquidity moving up and ask liquidity moving down. According to Material Indicators, when bid and ask liquidity becomes more concentrated around a price point, it dampens volatility, leading to a sideways chop until one side makes a move.</p>
<p>Per Material’s analysis, this type of price action differs from what was observed yesterday, as bids and asks were initially moving up, indicating a clear path for a pump. However, as things started getting “toppy,” asks began dropping down, ultimately dumping into the liquidity void created on the way up.</p>
<p>Furthermore, CryptoCon, a leading provider of cryptocurrency analysis, has <a href="https://twitter.com/CryptoCon_/status/1651612259674718209?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">highlighted </a>the recent drop in Bitcoin&#8217;s value, which saw a 15% decline. This drop has allowed the Chaikin Money Flow (CMF) indicator to reset slightly, as it nears dangerously close to hitting the Mid-Top .35 line.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large wp-image-528980" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/FuuzU2iXwAUVs1G-860x544.jpg" alt="Bitcoin " width="860" height="544" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/FuuzU2iXwAUVs1G-860x544.jpg 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/FuuzU2iXwAUVs1G-460x291.jpg 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/FuuzU2iXwAUVs1G-768x485.jpg 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/FuuzU2iXwAUVs1G-750x474.jpg 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/FuuzU2iXwAUVs1G-1140x721.jpg 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/FuuzU2iXwAUVs1G.jpg 1397w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" />
<p>The CMF indicator is a technical analysis tool that measures buying and selling pressure in the market. When the CMF is above zero, buying pressure is stronger than selling pressure, and vice versa when it is below zero. The Mid-Top line at .35 represents the halfway point in the cycle for Bitcoin&#8217;s true gains.</p>
<p>According to CryptoCon, the mid-top cycle for Bitcoin is approaching soon, but it is only half of the &#8220;true gains&#8221; for Bitcoin in a cycle. This means there is still significant potential for Bitcoin to experience further gains in the market.</p>

<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/6rD1x6iI/" alt="Bitcoin " width="1813" height="858" />
<p>Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/victor-rodvang-tLy4yKj53NU-unsplash-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>PancakeSwap (CAKE) Plummets 24% Amidst Debate Over Reduced Staking Rewards</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/cake/pancakeswap-cake-plummets-amidst-debate/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Edyme]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 20:00:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[CAKE]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BSC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DeFi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DEX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PancakeSwap]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=528962</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[PancakeSwap (CAKE) token holders have been on a roller coaster ride as stakers brace for reduced rewards. The community is debating a change in the token&#8217;s economic model. Over the past week, governance token, CAKE, has suffered a continuous downward trend, dropping by 24%. Though the proposed change appears favorable to PancakeSwap, the heated debate has impacted the token&#8217;s value.  Community Debate Over Slashed Staking Rewards PancakeSwap is a decentralized exchange (DEX) built natively on the Binance Smart Chain (BSC). It allows users to trade cryptocurrencies, provide liquidity on trading pools, and earn rewards in the form of CAKE tokens. Though the DEX has gained popularity recently due to its low fees, fast transactions, and innovative features, the economic proposal has brought uncertainty to its investors. According to the proposal, the developers will reduce CAKE&#8217;s inflation rate from above 20% to 3-5%. Related Reading: PancakeSwap Voting To Make CAKE Deflationary, But Prices Are Free-falling This move is aimed at improving PancakeSwap&#8217;s “long-term health.” However, at the same time, it will lower the amount of tokens stakers can earn, leading to a decline in staking rewards. Voting for the proposal began on April 26 and is scheduled to conclude tomorrow, April 28th.  The community has already given a thumbs up to the &#8220;aggressive reduction&#8221; of staking rewards, which would reduce more than half the number of tokens emitted. Notably, Staking rewards are a vital component of any cryptocurrency. They incentivize token holders to keep their tokens in a platform or wallet rather than sell them on the market. Staking rewards are similar to interest earned on savings in a bank account. PancakeSwap&#8217;s staking rewards have been a significant selling point for the project, ranging from 50% to 200% per annum, depending on the trading pool. The proposed change has sparked a debate within the community, with some arguing that reduced staking rewards will drive investors away from the project, leading to a decline in demand. Although the proposed change aims to enhance tokenomics by reducing the dilution of CAKE&#8217;s supply, it has led to an exodus of stakers. As a result, the token&#8217;s price has dropped concurrently with the amount of CAKE unstaked, as seen in the chart below.  Meanwhile, the tokenomics change proposed by the team on April 19 has also significantly reduced staking activity. The amount of CAKE staked fell from 1.007 billion to 677.851 million CAKE as of April 27.  CAKE Plummets 24% In A Week The PancakeSwap (CAKE) token has experienced a sharp decline of over 24% in the past week following the proposed proposal to reduce the token&#8217;s inflation rate. CAKE has dropped by 24% in the past seven days, from a high of $3.43 on April 20 to a low of $27.57 on April 27.  The token&#8217;s market cap has also dropped from a high of $636 million to a low of $506 million over the same period. The sudden drop in CAKE&#8217;s price reflects the crypto community&#8217;s perception of the proposed change. If passed, the proposed change will significantly affect the project&#8217;s stakes earnings and likely reduce the token&#8217;s demand. Related Reading: CAKE Remains Under Pressure Despite PancakeSwap Dominating BSC The decline in staking activity has not only affected the token&#8217;s liquidity. But also resulted in a decrease in its trading volume, thereby leading to supporting the bearish trend.  Featured image from iStock, Chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/cake-not-looking-delectable-for-investors-despite-pancakeswaps-progress/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener">PancakeSwap (CAKE) token holders</a> have been on a roller coaster ride as stakers brace for reduced rewards. The community is debating a change in the token&#8217;s economic model.</p>
<p>Over the past week, governance token, CAKE, has <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/defi/pancakeswap-voting-to-make-cake-deflationary-but-prices-are-free-falling/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">suffered a continuous downward trend</a>, dropping by 24%. Though the proposed change appears favorable to PancakeSwap, the heated debate has impacted the token&#8217;s value. </p>
<h2>Community Debate Over Slashed Staking Rewards</h2>
<p>PancakeSwap is a decentralized exchange (DEX) built natively on the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/defi/cake-remains-under-pressure-despite-pancakeswap-dominating-bsc/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Binance Smart Chain (BSC)</a>. It allows users to trade cryptocurrencies, provide liquidity on trading pools, and earn rewards in the form of CAKE tokens.</p>
<p>Though the DEX has gained popularity recently due to its low fees, fast transactions, and innovative features, the economic proposal has brought uncertainty to its investors. According to the <a href="https://pancakeswap.finance/voting/proposal/0x707643dd2c2b941c7274f26a0362922198912e8549050ae9f2d1d9d71ada04bb" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">proposal</a>, the developers will reduce CAKE&#8217;s inflation rate from above 20% to 3-5%.</p>

<p>This move is aimed at improving PancakeSwap&#8217;s “long-term health.” However, at the same time, it will lower the amount of tokens stakers can earn, leading to a decline in staking rewards. Voting for the proposal began on April 26 and is scheduled to conclude tomorrow, April 28th. </p>
<p>The community has already given a thumbs up to the &#8220;aggressive reduction&#8221; of staking rewards, which would reduce more than half the number of tokens emitted.</p>
<p>Notably, Staking rewards are a vital component of any cryptocurrency. They incentivize token holders to keep their tokens in a platform or wallet rather than sell them on the market. Staking rewards are similar to interest earned on savings in a bank account.</p>
<p>PancakeSwap&#8217;s staking rewards have been a significant selling point for the project, <a href="https://pancakeswap.finance/pools" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">ranging from 50% to 200% per annum</a>, depending on the trading pool. The proposed change has sparked a debate within the community, with some arguing that reduced staking rewards will <a href="https://twitter.com/figolox/status/1648377837173325842?s=61&amp;t=EIoUYGIIpv0wbq8QOtOlyg" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">drive investors away</a> from the project, leading to a decline in demand.</p>
<p>Although the proposed change aims to enhance tokenomics by reducing the dilution of CAKE&#8217;s supply, it has led to an exodus of stakers. As a result, the token&#8217;s price has dropped concurrently with the amount of CAKE unstaked, as seen in the chart below. </p>
<p>Meanwhile, the tokenomics change proposed by the team on April 19 has also significantly reduced staking activity. The amount of CAKE staked fell from 1.007 billion to 677.851 million CAKE as of April 27. </p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-528965 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Screenshot-2023-04-27-at-17.24.12-860x313.png" alt="PancakeSwap staking." width="860" height="313" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Screenshot-2023-04-27-at-17.24.12-860x313.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Screenshot-2023-04-27-at-17.24.12-460x168.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Screenshot-2023-04-27-at-17.24.12-768x280.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Screenshot-2023-04-27-at-17.24.12-1536x560.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Screenshot-2023-04-27-at-17.24.12-2048x746.png 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Screenshot-2023-04-27-at-17.24.12-750x273.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Screenshot-2023-04-27-at-17.24.12-1140x415.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" />
<h2>CAKE Plummets 24% In A Week</h2>
<p>The PancakeSwap (CAKE) token has experienced a <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/pancakeswap-tvl-drops-12-did-this-exchange-received-a-lethal-blow/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener">sharp decline</a> of over 24% in the past week following the proposed proposal to reduce the token&#8217;s inflation rate. CAKE has dropped by 24% in the past seven days, from a high of $3.43 on April 20 to a low of $27.57 on April 27. </p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/wwc4VsgL/" alt="PancakeSwap (CAKE) price on TradingView" width="2768" height="1372" />
<p>The token&#8217;s market cap has also <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/pancakeswap-cake-slides-below-range-is-this-an-entry-point-for-buyers/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener">dropped from a high</a> of $636 million to a low of $506 million over the same period. The sudden drop in CAKE&#8217;s price reflects the crypto community&#8217;s perception of the proposed change. If passed, the proposed change will significantly affect the project&#8217;s stakes earnings and likely reduce the token&#8217;s demand.</p>



<p>Featured image from iStock, Chart from TradingView</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Optimism-460x259.jpeg" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Solana Can Rally Over 20% If It Breaches This Level</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/solana/solana-can-rally-over-20-if-it-breaches-this-level/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[anushsamal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 19:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Solana]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sol]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SOLUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SOLUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=528930</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Over the past few trading sessions, the Solana price has been lacking direction. It is currently showing a bearish trend. The daily chart indicates that SOL has lost almost 4% of its value. Over the past week, it has fallen by 5%, erasing most of its gains due to the recent decline in price. Additionally, the technical outlook for Solana is bearish. Demand has been falling as buyers have stayed away. SOL also depicted negative accumulation at the time of writing. Although SOL is currently heading in a bearish direction, there is still potential for a rally if it breaks through its overhead resistance level. Related Reading: Shiba Inu Whales Unload Billions Amid SHIB Price Retreat However, this will require a return of demand for the altcoin and consistent trading of Bitcoin above the $28,000 mark. Continued consolidation for SOL could lead to a loss of its current support and a subsequent drop in value over future trading sessions. The market capitalization of Solana has also decreased, indicating increased selling pressure on the daily chart. Solana Price Analysis: One-Day Chart At the time of writing, Solana was priced at $21.57. Its overhead resistance level was identified at $23.30, which also serves as crucial as it has previously acted as a sell zone for the coin. If SOL manages to surpass this resistance level, it could potentially reach $26. This will result in a price appreciation of almost 22%. Conversely, a decline from the current price level would push Solana down to $20 and eventually $18. The trading volume of Solana in the last session decreased, indicating a drop in demand for the altcoin at the time of writing. It is important to note that breaching the $23.30 resistance level would require a resurgence of demand for SOL. Technical Analysis Over the past week, demand for the altcoin has remained low, causing buyers to lose confidence, especially after its fall from the $23 level. At the time of writing, the Relative Strength Index indicated that selling strength had surpassed buying strength, as it was below the 50 mark. Additionally, SOL dropped below the 20-SMA line, signaling that sellers had taken control of the market. However, there is still a possibility for a bullish market if buyers make a slight push, allowing Solana to rise above the 50-SMA line. This move could attract more buyers and revive confidence in the altcoin. On the one-day chart, SOL showed sell signals that are consistent with other technical indicators. The Moving Average Convergence Divergence, which reflects price momentum, has formed red histograms that indicate sell signals for the altcoin. This signals a bearish price trend. Related Reading: Ethereum Price Dips and Then Rips Higher, Bulls Still Aim $2K Furthermore, the Directional Movement Index (DMI) is negative, with the -DI line (orange) positioned above the +DI line (blue). Additionally, the Average Directional Index (red) has fallen below 20, indicating a weakening direction in the current price. Featured Image From UnSplash, Charts From TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[









<p>Over the past few trading sessions, the Solana price has been lacking direction. It is currently showing a bearish trend. The daily chart indicates that SOL has lost almost 4% of its value. Over the past week, it has fallen by 5%, erasing most of its gains due to the recent decline in price.</p>
<p>Additionally, the technical outlook for Solana is bearish. Demand has been falling as buyers have stayed away. SOL also depicted negative accumulation at the time of writing. Although SOL is currently heading in a bearish direction, there is still potential for a rally if it breaks through its overhead resistance level.</p>

<p>However, this will require a return of demand for the altcoin and consistent trading of Bitcoin above the $28,000 mark. Continued consolidation for SOL could lead to a loss of its current support and a subsequent drop in value over future trading sessions. The market capitalization of Solana has also decreased, indicating increased selling pressure on the daily chart.</p>




<h2 class="text-gray-400 flex self-end lg:self-center justify-center mt-2 gap-2 md:gap-3 lg:gap-1 lg:absolute lg:top-0 lg:translate-x-full lg:right-0 lg:mt-0 lg:pl-2 visible">Solana Price Analysis: One-Day Chart</h2>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-528937 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/SOLUSD_2023-04-27_19-03-07.png" alt="Solana" width="1816" height="830" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/SOLUSD_2023-04-27_19-03-07.png 1816w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/SOLUSD_2023-04-27_19-03-07-460x210.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/SOLUSD_2023-04-27_19-03-07-860x393.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/SOLUSD_2023-04-27_19-03-07-768x351.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/SOLUSD_2023-04-27_19-03-07-1536x702.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/SOLUSD_2023-04-27_19-03-07-750x343.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/SOLUSD_2023-04-27_19-03-07-1140x521.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1816px) 100vw, 1816px" />












<p>At the time of writing, Solana was priced at $21.57. Its overhead resistance level was identified at $23.30, which also serves as crucial as it has previously acted as a sell zone for the coin.</p>
<p>If SOL manages to surpass this resistance level, it could potentially reach $26. This will result in a price appreciation of almost 22%. Conversely, a decline from the current price level would push Solana down to $20 and eventually $18.</p>
<p>The trading volume of Solana in the last session decreased, indicating a drop in demand for the altcoin at the time of writing. It is important to note that breaching the $23.30 resistance level would require a resurgence of demand for SOL.</p>
<h2>Technical Analysis</h2>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-528944 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/SOLUSD_2023-04-27_19-03-54.png" alt="Solana" width="1816" height="743" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/SOLUSD_2023-04-27_19-03-54.png 1816w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/SOLUSD_2023-04-27_19-03-54-460x188.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/SOLUSD_2023-04-27_19-03-54-860x352.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/SOLUSD_2023-04-27_19-03-54-768x314.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/SOLUSD_2023-04-27_19-03-54-1536x628.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/SOLUSD_2023-04-27_19-03-54-750x307.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/SOLUSD_2023-04-27_19-03-54-1140x466.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1816px) 100vw, 1816px" />











<p>Over the past week, demand for the altcoin has remained low, causing buyers to lose confidence, especially after its fall from the $23 level. At the time of writing, the Relative Strength Index indicated that selling strength had surpassed buying strength, as it was below the 50 mark.</p>
<p>Additionally, SOL dropped below the 20-SMA line, signaling that sellers had taken control of the market. However, there is still a possibility for a bullish market if buyers make a slight push, allowing Solana to rise above the 50-SMA line. This move could attract more buyers and revive confidence in the altcoin.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-528958 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/SOLUSD_2023-04-27_19-04-22.png" alt="Solana" width="1816" height="743" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/SOLUSD_2023-04-27_19-04-22.png 1816w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/SOLUSD_2023-04-27_19-04-22-460x188.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/SOLUSD_2023-04-27_19-04-22-860x352.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/SOLUSD_2023-04-27_19-04-22-768x314.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/SOLUSD_2023-04-27_19-04-22-1536x628.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/SOLUSD_2023-04-27_19-04-22-750x307.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/SOLUSD_2023-04-27_19-04-22-1140x466.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1816px) 100vw, 1816px" />










<p>On the one-day chart, SOL showed sell signals that are consistent with other technical indicators. The Moving Average Convergence Divergence, which reflects price momentum, has formed red histograms that indicate sell signals for the altcoin. This signals a bearish price trend.</p>

<p>Furthermore, the Directional Movement Index (DMI) is negative, with the -DI line (orange) positioned above the +DI line (blue). Additionally, the Average Directional Index (red) has fallen below 20, indicating a weakening direction in the current price.</p>




















]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/guerrillabuzz-5_asf_AsG-I-unsplash-1-460x259.jpg" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Avalanche Remains Under Pressure Despite Circle&#8217;s CCTP Effort</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/avalanche/avalanche-remains-under-pressure-despite-circles-cctp-effort/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dalmas Ngetich]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 18:00:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Avalanche]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AVAX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CCTP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[circle]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DeFi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USDC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=528949</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The native currency of Avalanche, AVAX, remains under pressure despite Circle&#8217;s effort to launch a facility that will enable the direct transfer of USDC between Ethereum and Avalanche blockchains.  Avalanche (AVAX) Is Down 18% From April 2023 Peaks Avalanche is a smart contracting platform with sub-second transaction finality and a rival of Ethereum. However, considering the first-mover advantage of Ethereum and the activity level on the pioneer smart contracting platform, Avalanche lags even though it offers high scalability translating to relatively low trading fees. Despite the launch of the Cross-Chain Transfer Protocol (CCTP) by Circle, the team behind USDC, a stablecoin; AVAX remains under trading range and has been unable to move higher, reversing recent losses. Related Reading: Avalanche Struggles Under $18 – More Losses Seem Likely When writing on April 27, AVAX is down 18% from April 2023 highs of around $20 and down roughly 10% in the last trading week, according to CoinMarketCap data. Although the market uptrend of April 26 temporarily forced AVAX higher, buyers on April 27 didn&#8217;t follow through. AVAX remains below the local resistance at $18 but above last week&#8217;s support at around $16.  However, from a broader perspective, AVAX is up 25% from March 2023 lows and has gained 65% from December 2022 lows. The impressive performance was a huge boost for AVAX, a coin that plunged 88% from November 2021 peaks when it was changing hands at around $145.  Based on the current AVAX formation, it is yet to be seen whether fundamental events will trigger demand and push the coin above $20, reversing this week&#8217;s losses.  Circle Launches Cross-Chain Transfer Protocol For USDC Transfer The decision by Circle to develop and launch a mainnet protocol for bidirectional cross-chain transfers between Ethereum and Avalanche will be convenient for users. It could also boost decentralized finance (DeFi) activities in Avalanche since users don&#8217;t have to use a third party, effectively eradicating the need for bridges and helping consolidate the web3 ecosystem. This would also have a significant effect on general liquidity on the Avalanche blockchain. Avalanche is suited for the development of decentralized finance (DeFi) dapps and as of April 27, the blockchain managed over $798 million as measured by the total value locked (TVL), according to DeFiLlama. Aave, a lending protocol available in, among other chains, Ethereum, is the largest DeFi dapp by TVL, managing $262 million. Besides liquidity, considering the mega hacks of 2022, for example, the Ronin and BNB Chain Bridge hacks, the Cross-Chain Transfer Protocol (CCTP) also boosts security for users and DeFi protocols. Related Reading: Will AVAX Price Get A Lift From Avalanche NFTs? Let’s Examine The Metrics Circle said several firms, including MetaMask, Celer, and Wormhole, have pledged to use the CCTP. Feature Image From Canva, Chart From TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The native currency of Avalanche, AVAX, remains under pressure despite Circle&#8217;s <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.circle.com/en/cross-chain-transfer-protocol" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">effort</a> to launch a facility that will enable the direct transfer of USDC between Ethereum and Avalanche blockchains. </p>
<h2><strong>Avalanche (AVAX) Is Down 18% From April 2023 Peaks</strong></h2>
<p>Avalanche is a smart contracting platform with sub-second transaction finality and a rival of Ethereum. However, considering the first-mover advantage of Ethereum and the activity level on the pioneer smart contracting platform, Avalanche lags even though it offers high scalability translating to relatively low trading fees.</p>
<p>Despite the launch of the Cross-Chain Transfer Protocol (CCTP) by Circle, the team behind USDC, a stablecoin; AVAX remains under trading range and has been unable to move higher, reversing recent losses.</p>

<p>When writing on April 27, AVAX is down 18% from April 2023 highs of around $20 and down roughly 10% in the last trading week, according to CoinMarketCap data. </p>
<p>Although the market uptrend of April 26 temporarily forced AVAX higher, buyers on April 27 didn&#8217;t follow through. AVAX remains below the local resistance at $18 but above last week&#8217;s support at around $16. </p>
<a href="https://www.tradingview.com/x/kCe6nHof/" rel="nofollow"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/kCe6nHof/" alt="Avalanche Price On April 27| Source: AVAXUSDT On Binance, TradingView" width="1147" height="851" /></a>
<p>However, from a broader perspective, AVAX is up 25% from March 2023 lows and has gained 65% from December 2022 lows. The impressive performance was a huge boost for AVAX, a coin that plunged 88% from November 2021 peaks when it was changing hands at around $145. </p>
<p>Based on the current AVAX formation, it is yet to be seen whether fundamental events will trigger demand and push the coin above $20, reversing this week&#8217;s losses. </p>
<h2><strong>Circle Launches Cross-Chain Transfer Protocol For USDC Transfer</strong></h2>
<p>The decision by Circle to develop and <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://youtu.be/WEH-E1bFuHs" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">launch</a> a mainnet protocol for bidirectional cross-chain transfers between Ethereum and Avalanche will be convenient for users. </p>
<p>It could also boost decentralized finance (DeFi) activities in Avalanche since users don&#8217;t have to use a third party, effectively eradicating the need for bridges and helping consolidate the web3 ecosystem. This would also have a significant effect on general liquidity on the Avalanche blockchain.</p>
<p>Avalanche is suited for the development of decentralized finance (DeFi) dapps and as of April 27, the blockchain <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://defillama.com/chain/Avalanche" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">managed</a> over $798 million as measured by the total value locked (TVL), according to DeFiLlama. Aave, a lending protocol available in, among other chains, Ethereum, is the largest DeFi dapp by TVL, managing $262 million.</p>
<p>Besides liquidity, considering the mega hacks of 2022, for example, the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/the-ronin-hack-aftermatch-axie-infinity-1m-bug-bounty/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ronin</a> and BNB Chain Bridge hacks, the Cross-Chain Transfer Protocol (CCTP) also boosts security for users and DeFi protocols.</p>

<p>Circle said several firms, including MetaMask, Celer, and Wormhole, have pledged to use the CCTP.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Avalanche-AVAX-Price-460x260.jpg" width="460" height="260" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Filecoin Price Struggles To Move, Will It Surpass The $6 Barrier?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/filecoin/filecoin-price-struggles-to-move-will-it-surpass-the-6-barrier/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Eli Dambel]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 17:00:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Filecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[filecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FILUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[RSI]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=528925</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The 30th largest cryptocurrency Filecoin (FIL) has recorded an increase in its 24-hour trading volume. This recent trend has attracted investors and traders closely monitoring its price movement. However, the coin struggles to break through the important $6 resistance. The question now is, will Filecoin be able to break the $6 barrier? What&#8217;s the future potential of Filecoin? Notably, FIL trading volume surged significantly in 24 hours. This volume indicates increased network activity which might later push FIL price if the crypto market breaks from the current downtrend.     Filecoin Recorded Price Dips, What&#8217;s The Current Sentiment? Filecoin is a peer-to-peer network created by Protocol Labs. Users pay storage miners to guarantee that their files are correctly and securely preserved over time. The Filecoin blockchain keeps track of transactions to verify file storage. The cryptocurrency market is known for its volatility. Sudden swings in the value of digital assets occur frequently. Being a player in this market, Filecoin has seen increased selling momentum and downward movement. Related Reading: MATIC Price Prediction: Polygon Recovery Faces Many Hurdles FIL has experienced some significant drop in price over the past few days, affecting its overall market sentiment and current price movement. But with the Fear &#38; Greed Index of 61 (Greed), the current sentiment is positive.  However, given that the price is in a zone where investors are likely to want to sell down, this suggests that there might be a potential price reversal. The trend reversed due to a shift in direction in the 50-day simple moving average (SMA) on 17 April 2023, and this may continue if bullish momentum remains weak. The SMA indicator is frequently used to spot trends, resistance and support levels, and probable buy/sell signals. By crossing below the 200-day SMA, the 50-day SMA has also formed a death cross, which might be a bearish signal and suggest a potential selling opportunity. The RSI is closely below the neutral zone, indicating the selling momentum is still high. However, the buyers are trying to build strength. Watch closely for a possible trend revisal. Filecoin Key Support And Resistance Zones On 23 April 2023, the Filecoin price dropped by 17.35%, making the coin fall to a support level of $5.117. The banking crisis&#8217;s impact on the financial market also affected the price movement of altcoins. Related Reading: Polygon Exchange Supply Spikes, More Downtrend Incoming? FIL could drop another 15%, reaching a month-long low of $4.79, if the panic persists and the altcoin breaches the crucial support level at $4.990. Filecoin trades between support and resistance levels of $5.46 and $5.8. The first significant resistance level for FIL is $6.388. If the price moves above the current point, the coin will reach the next resistance levels, at $8.34 and $9.24. Featured image from Pixabay and chart from Tradingview]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The 30th largest cryptocurrency Filecoin (FIL) has recorded an increase in its 24-hour trading volume. This recent trend has attracted investors and traders closely monitoring its price movement. However, the coin struggles to break through the important $6 resistance.</p>
<p>The question now is, will Filecoin be able to break the $6 barrier? What&#8217;s the future potential of Filecoin? Notably, FIL trading volume surged significantly in 24 hours. This volume indicates increased network activity which might later push FIL price if the crypto market breaks from the current downtrend.    </p>
<h2>Filecoin Recorded Price Dips, What&#8217;s The Current Sentiment?</h2>
<p>Filecoin is a peer-to-peer network created by Protocol Labs. Users pay storage miners to guarantee that their files are correctly and securely preserved over time. The Filecoin blockchain keeps track of transactions to verify file storage.</p>
<p>The cryptocurrency market is known for its volatility. Sudden swings in the value of digital assets occur frequently. Being a player in this market, Filecoin has seen increased selling momentum and downward movement.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/matic-analysis/matic-price-prediction-polygon-1-08/">MATIC Price Prediction: Polygon Recovery Faces Many Hurdles</a></p>
<p>FIL has experienced some significant drop in price over the past few days, affecting its overall market sentiment and current price movement. But with the Fear &amp; Greed Index of 61 (Greed), the current sentiment is positive. </p>
<p>However, given that the price is in a zone where investors are likely to want to sell down, this suggests that there might be a potential price reversal. </p>
<p>The trend reversed due to a shift in direction in the 50-day simple moving average (SMA) on 17 April 2023, and this may continue if bullish momentum remains weak. The SMA indicator is frequently used to spot trends, resistance and support levels, and probable buy/sell signals.</p>
<p>By crossing below the 200-day SMA, the 50-day SMA has also formed a death cross, which might be a bearish signal and suggest a potential selling opportunity. The <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/x/x2Ey0Kzs/" rel="nofollow">RSI</a> is closely below the neutral zone, indicating the selling momentum is still high. However, the buyers are trying to build strength. Watch closely for a possible trend revisal.</p>
<h2>Filecoin Key Support And Resistance Zones</h2>
<p>On 23 April 2023, the Filecoin price dropped by 17.35%, making the coin fall to a support level of $5.117. The banking crisis&#8217;s impact on the financial market also affected the price movement of altcoins.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/matic/polygon-exchange-supply-spikes-more-downtrend/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Polygon Exchange Supply Spikes, More Downtrend Incoming?</a></p>
<p>FIL could drop another 15%, reaching a month-long low of $4.79, if the panic persists and the altcoin breaches the crucial support level at $4.990.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-528926 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/FILUSDT_2023-04-27_18-12-59-860x501.png" alt="Filecoin Price Struggles To Surge, Will It Surpass The $6 Barrier?" width="860" height="501" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/FILUSDT_2023-04-27_18-12-59-860x501.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/FILUSDT_2023-04-27_18-12-59-460x268.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/FILUSDT_2023-04-27_18-12-59-768x447.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/FILUSDT_2023-04-27_18-12-59-750x437.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/FILUSDT_2023-04-27_18-12-59-1140x664.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/FILUSDT_2023-04-27_18-12-59.png 1437w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" />
<p>Filecoin trades between support and resistance levels of $5.46 and $5.8. The first significant resistance level for FIL is $6.388. If the price moves above the current point, the coin will reach the next resistance levels, at $8.34 and $9.24.</p>
<p>Featured image from Pixabay and chart from Tradingview</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/a6fe911ced0c47f7ad117488866c6fbf-460x259.png" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Chainlink Pushes Above $7, Will The Short-Term Recovery Hold?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/chainlink/chainlink-pushes-above-7-will-the-short-term-recovery-hold/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[anushsamal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 16:00:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Chainlink]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[chainlink]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Link]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LINKUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[linkusdt]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=528910</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The price of Chainlink had been in a period of consolidation over the past few sessions. However, the bulls were recently able to break above an important resistance level. Despite this recent bullish action, the daily chart showed a 6% depreciation and on the weekly chart, LINK had a 9% loss. The technical outlook looked bleak with fading demand and low accumulation. Nevertheless, if LINK can remain above the $7 mark, another rebound may be possible. As Bitcoin displayed mild bullish sentiment after reclaiming the $28,000 mark, most altcoins exhibited similar behaviors. Related Reading: Ethereum Exchange Inflows Trigger Drop Below $2,080: Will It Slide Lower This Week? If BTC retraces in the next trading sessions, LINK is expected to move closer to its immediate support level. Maintaining buying strength is crucial for the asset to stay above its local price floor. The market capitalization of LINK had fallen, indicating that sellers were more active. Chainlink Price Analysis: One-Day Chart At the time of writing, Chainlink was trading at $7.02, with its immediate resistance at $7.40. If the altcoin manages to surpass this resistance, it will encounter a tough price ceiling of $7.70, and reaching that level may revive the bulls. Conversely, failing to stay above the $7 mark will pull Chainlink down to $6.80. If this happens, LINK may decline by up to 15%, nearing the $5.80 mark. The last session saw a decrease in the amount of LINK traded, and indicators suggested that buying strength was weakening. Technical Analysis Chainlink had experienced a sharp drop in buyers&#8217; interest after encountering significant resistance at $7.70. However, demand for the altcoin could partially return if it moves above the $7.00 price mark. The Relative Strength Index was below the half-line, hovering around 40, indicating that sellers had taken control of the market. Additionally, LINK had fallen below the 20-Simple Moving Average line, signaling that sellers were driving the price momentum at press time. If demand picks up, LINK could rise above the 50-SMA line (yellow), providing some relief to the bulls. In line with the other technical indicators, LINK displayed sell signals, indicating a bearish turn in price. The Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD) demonstrates an asset&#8217;s price momentum and trend reversals as well. The MACD formed red histograms below the half-line, signaling a sell signal for the asset. The Parabolic SAR reads the price direction and changes in the same. The indicator formed dotted lines above the price candlesticks, suggesting a downtrend in the price. Related Reading: Render (RNDR): Biggest Gainer Among Top 100 Cryptos With A 22% Climb For LINK to maintain its price above the $7 mark, buying strength needs to resurface over the immediate trading sessions, and broader market strength has to remain consistent. Featured Image From UnSplash, Charts From TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The price of Chainlink had been in a period of consolidation over the past few sessions. However, the bulls were recently able to break above an important resistance level. Despite this recent bullish action, the daily chart showed a 6% depreciation and on the weekly chart, LINK had a 9% loss.</p>
<p>The technical outlook looked bleak with fading demand and low accumulation. Nevertheless, if LINK can remain above the $7 mark, another rebound may be possible. As Bitcoin displayed mild bullish sentiment after reclaiming the $28,000 mark, most altcoins exhibited similar behaviors.</p>

<p>If BTC retraces in the next trading sessions, LINK is expected to move closer to its immediate support level. Maintaining buying strength is crucial for the asset to stay above its local price floor. The market capitalization of LINK had fallen, indicating that sellers were more active.</p>
<h2>Chainlink Price Analysis: One-Day Chart</h2>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-528916 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/LINKUSD_2023-04-27_18-07-06.png" alt="Chainlink" width="1816" height="830" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/LINKUSD_2023-04-27_18-07-06.png 1816w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/LINKUSD_2023-04-27_18-07-06-460x210.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/LINKUSD_2023-04-27_18-07-06-860x393.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/LINKUSD_2023-04-27_18-07-06-768x351.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/LINKUSD_2023-04-27_18-07-06-1536x702.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/LINKUSD_2023-04-27_18-07-06-750x343.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/LINKUSD_2023-04-27_18-07-06-1140x521.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1816px) 100vw, 1816px" />
<p>At the time of writing, Chainlink was trading at $7.02, with its immediate resistance at $7.40. If the altcoin manages to surpass this resistance, it will encounter a tough price ceiling of $7.70, and reaching that level may revive the bulls.</p>
<p>Conversely, failing to stay above the $7 mark will pull Chainlink down to $6.80. If this happens, LINK may decline by up to 15%, nearing the $5.80 mark. The last session saw a decrease in the amount of LINK traded, and indicators suggested that buying strength was weakening.</p>
<h2>Technical Analysis</h2>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-528920 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/LINKUSD_2023-04-27_18-07-38.png" alt="Chainlink" width="1816" height="743" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/LINKUSD_2023-04-27_18-07-38.png 1816w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/LINKUSD_2023-04-27_18-07-38-460x188.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/LINKUSD_2023-04-27_18-07-38-860x352.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/LINKUSD_2023-04-27_18-07-38-768x314.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/LINKUSD_2023-04-27_18-07-38-1536x628.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/LINKUSD_2023-04-27_18-07-38-750x307.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/LINKUSD_2023-04-27_18-07-38-1140x466.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1816px) 100vw, 1816px" />
<p>Chainlink had experienced a sharp drop in buyers&#8217; interest after encountering significant resistance at $7.70. However, demand for the altcoin could partially return if it moves above the $7.00 price mark. The Relative Strength Index was below the half-line, hovering around 40, indicating that sellers had taken control of the market.</p>
<p>Additionally, LINK had fallen below the 20-Simple Moving Average line, signaling that sellers were driving the price momentum at press time. If demand picks up, LINK could rise above the 50-SMA line (yellow), providing some relief to the bulls.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-528922 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/LINKUSD_2023-04-27_18-08-01.png" alt="Chainlink" width="1816" height="743" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/LINKUSD_2023-04-27_18-08-01.png 1816w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/LINKUSD_2023-04-27_18-08-01-460x188.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/LINKUSD_2023-04-27_18-08-01-860x352.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/LINKUSD_2023-04-27_18-08-01-768x314.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/LINKUSD_2023-04-27_18-08-01-1536x628.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/LINKUSD_2023-04-27_18-08-01-750x307.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/LINKUSD_2023-04-27_18-08-01-1140x466.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1816px) 100vw, 1816px" />






<p>In line with the other technical indicators, LINK displayed sell signals, indicating a bearish turn in price. The Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD) demonstrates an asset&#8217;s price momentum and trend reversals as well. The MACD formed red histograms below the half-line, signaling a sell signal for the asset.</p>
<p>The Parabolic SAR reads the price direction and changes in the same. The indicator formed dotted lines above the price candlesticks, suggesting a downtrend in the price.</p>

<p>For LINK to maintain its price above the $7 mark, buying strength needs to resurface over the immediate trading sessions, and broader market strength has to remain consistent.</p>







]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/the-ian-x7C-hXn1250-unsplash-307x460.jpg" width="307" height="460" />	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
