<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	 xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" >

<channel>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://newsbtc.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://newsbtc.com</link>
	<description>Bitcoin &#38; cryptocurrency news today, price &#38; technical analysis</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 18:17:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<link>https://newsbtc.com</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Bearish Indicator: Bitcoin Volatility Hits All-Time Low</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-volatility-hits-all-time-low/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Best Owie]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 23:00:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin volatility]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[volatility]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=513734</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin volatility has been on a decline since the start of December. This has been a culmination of both low interest from investors, as well as the declining prices of digital assets in the market. It has not led bitcoin to record its lowest volatility level on record yet. Bitcoin At All-Time Low Volatility Will Clemente shared a chart on Sunday that showed that bitcoin volatility had fallen to an all-time low. The chart itself is interesting in the fact that it shows just how the bitcoin volatility had been moving over the last few months. Related Reading: FTX Token Jumps 65% As SBF Returns Home, Can FTT Hold The Gains? There were multiple spikes in volatility from the start to the middle of the year 2022. However, toward the end, volatility dives off a cliff and continues this downtrend at this time. Keep in mind that the volatility of an asset is basically how much the price in dollars moved up and down in a given period. The larger the movement in price, the higher the volatility of a coin. Given that the price of bitcoin has been more or less steady over the last few months, it tracks that the volatility would be lower. Then in December, the price of bitcoin had mainly revolved around the $16,000 level, causing volatility to decline. Bitcoin has barely moved price-wise in the last 7 days, up only 0.56% in this one-week period. It is the lowest that volatility has ever been, and while it would normally paint a bullish picture for the digital asset, it has invigorated the bears. BTC stalls at $16,800 &#124; Source: BTCUSD on TradingView.com Not A Good Time For BTC Now, more often than not, when volatility falls to such low levels, it has been right before a bull market where prices had recovered sharply. However, the timing of these have also mattered greatly because it is what determines whether low volatility is bearish or bullish.  One of the times when low volatility had been very bearish was back in 2018. Like now, the market had just come out of an explosive bull rally that saw bitcoin hit new all-time highs. But with such low momentum, it had caused the price to crash a further 50%. Related Reading: Ethereum Stalls At $1,200, Why Bears Still Have The Upper Hand Given the similarities of both situations, it is likely that this will go as it did in 2018 compared to when volatility hit a low in 2020. The bitcoin bottom is likely not in too, which lends credence to this bearish case, although the decline may not be as high as 50%. This chart posted by Twitter user @DrahoslavP puts in perspective just how volatility has affected the price of the digital asset. Every time volatility fell below value &#34;1&#34; it was followed by bullish rally with one exception &#8211; october 2018. pic.twitter.com/pzW1GCAr40 &#8212; Data Patron (@DrahoslavP) December 25, 2022 Nevertheless, it is not all bad news for bitcoin. In fact, looking over the long term, it is important for this to happen. Right after the low volatility and eventual decline in 2018, bitcoin marked the bottom of the bear market. This had given way to the recovery that would set the pace for the next bull market. In other words, if a decline follows the current volatility trend, then it may present the best opportunity for investors to get into the digital asset. For BTC bottom chasers, this could be the holy grail of bottom indicators. Featured image from CoinDesk, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="p2">Bitcoin volatility has been on a decline since the start of December. This has been a culmination of both low interest from investors, as well as the declining prices of digital assets in the market. It has not led bitcoin to record its lowest volatility level on record yet.</p>
<h2 class="p2">Bitcoin At All-Time Low Volatility</h2>
<p class="p2">Will Clemente shared a chart on Sunday that showed that bitcoin volatility had fallen to an all-time low. The chart itself is interesting in the fact that it shows just how the bitcoin volatility had been moving over the last few months.</p>

<p class="p2">There were multiple spikes in volatility from the start to the middle of the year 2022. However, toward the end, volatility dives off a cliff and continues this downtrend at this time. Keep in mind that the volatility of an asset is basically how much the price in dollars moved up and down in a given period. The larger the movement in price, the higher the volatility of a coin.</p>
<p class="p2">Given that the price of bitcoin has been more or less steady over the last few months, it tracks that the volatility would be lower. Then in December, the price of bitcoin had mainly revolved around the $16,000 level, causing volatility to decline.</p>
<p class="p2">Bitcoin has barely moved price-wise in the last 7 days, up only 0.56% in this one-week period. It is the lowest that volatility has ever been, and while it would normally paint a bullish picture for the digital asset, it has invigorated the bears.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/yck3ToaR/" alt="Bitcoin price chart from TradingView.com" width="3284" height="1760" /></p>

<h2 class="p2">Not A Good Time For BTC</h2>
<p class="p2">Now, more often than not, when volatility falls to such low levels, it has been right before a bull market where prices had recovered sharply. However, the timing of these have also mattered greatly because it is what determines whether low volatility is bearish or bullish. </p>
<p class="p2">One of the times when low volatility had been very bearish was back in 2018. Like now, the market had just come out of an explosive bull rally that saw bitcoin hit new all-time highs. But with such low momentum, it had caused the price to crash a further 50%.</p>

<p class="p2">Given the similarities of both situations, it is likely that this will go as it did in 2018 compared to when volatility hit a low in 2020. The bitcoin bottom is likely not in too, which lends credence to this bearish case, although the decline may not be as high as 50%. This chart posted by Twitter user @DrahoslavP puts in perspective just how volatility has affected the price of the digital asset.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Every time volatility fell below value &quot;1&quot; it was followed by bullish rally with one exception &#8211; october 2018. <a href="https://t.co/pzW1GCAr40" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/pzW1GCAr40</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Data Patron (@DrahoslavP) <a href="https://twitter.com/DrahoslavP/status/1607018404627746817?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">December 25, 2022</a></p></blockquote>
<p></p>
<p class="p2">Nevertheless, it is not all bad news for bitcoin. In fact, looking over the long term, it is important for this to happen. Right after the low volatility and eventual decline in 2018, bitcoin marked the bottom of the bear market. This had given way to the recovery that would set the pace for the next bull market.</p>
<p class="p2">In other words, if a decline follows the current volatility trend, then it may present the best opportunity for investors to get into the digital asset. For BTC bottom chasers, this could be the holy grail of bottom indicators.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/bitcoin-bear-460x253.jpeg" width="460" height="253" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Selling Pressure Becoming Exhausted? This Metric May Hint So</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-selling-pressure-exhausted-hint/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hououin Kyouma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 19:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Selling Pressure]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stablecoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stablecoins Redeemed Supply]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=513745</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The on-chain data for the stablecoin redemptions during the recent price plunge could suggest there aren&#8217;t many Bitcoin holders selling anymore. Stablecoin Redeem Count Has Remained Low Recently As pointed out by an analyst in a CryptoQuant post, large stablecoin redemptions have usually accompanied major declines in the Bitcoin price during this bear market. A stablecoin is said to be &#8220;redeemed&#8221; when an investor exchanges the token for fiat through the issuer of said coin. Investors usually use stablecoins when they want to escape the volatility associated with tokens like Bitcoin. Thus, redemptions of them can be a sign that investors are exiting the market currently. The &#8220;stablecoins redeemed supply&#8221; is an indicator that measures the total amount of such redemptions happening across the market of all types of stables. Another metric that keeps track of these withdrawals is the &#8220;stablecoins redeem event count,&#8221; which, as its name already implies, measures the total number of redemptions taking place in the market rather than the total sum of their value. Related Reading: Bitcoin Bullish Signal? Small Investors Show Rapid Accumulation Now, here is a chart that shows the trend in both these stablecoin redemptions indicators over the past year: Looks like only one of these metrics had its value elevated in recent days &#124; Source: CryptoQuant As the above graph displays, during the large declines in the price of Bitcoin in this bear market so far, the stablecoins redeemed supply has usually registered high values. This trend makes sense as investors would be converting to stables to sell off during the crash, and then redeeming them for fiat. Related Reading: Top 5 Cryptocurrencies To Keep An Eye On This Week – Post-Christmas Gainers The stablecoin redeem count also observed spikes during such dumping events, except for the most recent one. This implies that in the price plunges before the latest one, many investors always took part in stablecoin redemptions, showing that the market had a uniform and more natural selling appetite. In the most recent decline where Bitcoin went from above $18k to below $17k, however, the redeemed count has stayed low while the redeemed supply has still observed very high values. This means that only a few whales were involved in this dumping event, a possible sign that largescale selling pressure may be getting depleted in the market. BTC Price At the time of writing, Bitcoin&#8217;s price floats around $16,800, up 1% in the last seven days. Over the past month, the crypto has gained 2% in value. The price of the coin seems to have not shown any significant deviations in the last few days &#124; Source: BTCUSD on TradingView Featured image from Dmitry Demidko on Unsplash.com, charts from TradingView.com, CryptoQuant.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The on-chain data for the stablecoin redemptions during the recent price plunge could suggest there aren&#8217;t many Bitcoin holders selling anymore.</p>
<h2>Stablecoin Redeem Count Has Remained Low Recently</h2>
<p>As pointed out by an analyst in a CryptoQuant <a href="https://cryptoquant.com/quicktake/63a96633f307a42a00cc89c6-Movement-of-Redeemed-Stablecoin-by-Whales" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">post</a>, large stablecoin redemptions have usually accompanied major declines in the Bitcoin price during this bear market. A <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/stablecoins-fuel-christmas-bitcoin-rally/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">stablecoin</a> is said to be &#8220;redeemed&#8221; when an investor exchanges the token for fiat through the issuer of said coin.</p>
<p>Investors usually use stablecoins when they want to escape the volatility associated with tokens like Bitcoin. Thus, redemptions of them can be a sign that investors are exiting the market currently. The &#8220;stablecoins redeemed supply&#8221; is an indicator that measures the total amount of such redemptions happening across the market of all types of stables.</p>
<p>Another metric that keeps track of these withdrawals is the &#8220;stablecoins redeem event count,&#8221; which, as its name already implies, measures the total number of redemptions taking place in the market rather than the total sum of their value.</p>

<p>Now, here is a chart that shows the trend in both these stablecoin redemptions indicators over the past year:</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone aligncenter" src="https://img.cryptoquant.com/53005/quicktake/6o1eQ_6e8b7f63ad3aafa53ed3a901c8ff8bae6cd8251bd46ea726199cc6f296ab3f37.png" alt="Bitcoin vs Stablecoin Redemptions" width="1280" height="712" /></p>

<p>As the above graph displays, during the large declines in the price of Bitcoin in this bear market so far, the stablecoins redeemed supply has usually registered high values. This trend makes sense as investors would be converting to stables to sell off during the crash, and then redeeming them for fiat.</p>

<p>The stablecoin redeem count also observed spikes during such dumping events, except for the most recent one. This implies that in the price plunges before the latest one, many investors always took part in stablecoin redemptions, showing that the market had a uniform and more natural selling appetite.</p>
<p>In the most recent decline where Bitcoin went from above $18k to below $17k, however, the redeemed count has stayed low while the redeemed supply has still observed very high values. This means that only a few whales were involved in this dumping event, a possible sign that largescale <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-metric-selling-pressure-reaching-exhaustion/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">selling pressure</a> may be getting depleted in the market.</p>
<h2>BTC Price</h2>
<p>At the time of writing, <a href="https://newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-larger-recovery-17k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin&#8217;s price</a> floats around $16,800, up 1% in the last seven days. Over the past month, the crypto has gained 2% in value.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-513752 aligncenter" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/chart-30-460x259.png" alt="Bitcoin Price Chart" width="460" height="259" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/chart-30-460x259.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/chart-30-860x485.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/chart-30-768x433.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/chart-30-750x423.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/chart-30.png 974w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px" /></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/dmitry-demidko-OG3A-ilG8AY-unsplash-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Litecoin (LTC) Tops List Of Christmas Gainers, Is $100 Still Possible?</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/analysis/ltc/litecoin-tops-list-of-gainers/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Best Owie]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 17:00:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[LTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Litecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Litecoin performance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ltc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ltc price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ltc/usd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LTCUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=513733</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Litecoin (LTC) emerged as the top gainer over Christmas Day with an impressive performance. This put it ahead of market leaders such as bitcoin and ethereum in terms of performance, solidifying its position as the market leader through the first half of the holidays. Litecoin Tops List Of Gainers Over the last 24 hours, Litecoin has been on an upward rally that put its price firmly above $65, turning resistance into support for it. The digital asset saw upwards of a 6% increase in price over the last day. The rally stopped just below $70 before a slight downward correction took place. Related Reading: Ethereum Stalls At $1,200, Why Bears Still Have The Upper Hand Given that most of the crypto market remained muted through Christmas, this put Litecoin right at the top of the gainers&#8217; list. It also saw a significant jump in trading volume, rising more than 180% over the 24-hour period to be sitting at $437.7 million at the time of this writing. Its market cap crossed $4.9 and this saw it surpass Shiba Inu to reclaim its spot as the 14th largest cryptocurrency by market cap. Other cryptocurrencies that made the gainers list was GRT with more than a 4.20% increase in price over the one-day period. ICP was third on the list with 3.56% gains, while CSPR followed closely behind at 3.21%. Terra Classic (LUNC) featured as 5th on the list, rising about 3% on Christmas to be sitting at $0.0001486. Can LTC Reach $100? Litecoin’s recent bullish movement can be attributed to CNBC’s Jim Cramer saying during an interview that holders of the cryptocurrency are “idiots.” Following this, the digital asset had begun to trend on social media, resulting in an upward rally on Christmas Day. Bulls try to push LTC above $70 &#124; Source: BTCUSD on TradingView.com However, LTC hit a roadblock just before reaching $70. Even though this put it above its 50 and 100-day moving averages, there was still enough resistance from the bears to keep it from reclaiming this position in the short term. This means that successfully beating $70 will likely see a rapid rise to $80 for LTC. But $100 remains a long way off for LTC. Related Reading: FTX Token Jumps 65% As SBF Returns Home, Can FTT Hold The Gains? The recent rally does not carry enough momentum to see it through to $100. Add in the fact that the crypto winter is still in full swing and it becomes improbable that the digital asset would be able to reach this price level in the short term. If bitcoin were to fall further and hit $10,000, then LTC could reach a low of $30 before the next bull market begins. One important event to look towards that could mark a bullish trend for Litecoin, though, would be the next halving event happening in August 2023. When this happens, the block reward could drop another 50% to 6.25 LTC. This decrease in supply could end up pushing the price upwards, as long as demand remains high. Featured image from GoBankingRates, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="p2">Litecoin (LTC) emerged as the top gainer over Christmas Day with an impressive performance. This put it ahead of market leaders such as bitcoin and ethereum in terms of performance, solidifying its position as the market leader through the first half of the holidays.</p>
<h2 class="p2">Litecoin Tops List Of Gainers</h2>
<p class="p2">Over the last 24 hours, Litecoin has been on an upward rally that put its price firmly above $65, turning resistance into support for it. The digital asset saw upwards of a 6% increase in price over the last day. The rally stopped just below $70 before a slight downward correction took place.</p>

<p class="p2">Given that most of the crypto market remained muted through Christmas, this put Litecoin right at the <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/gainers-losers/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">top of the gainers&#8217; list</a>. It also saw a significant jump in trading volume, rising more than 180% over the 24-hour period to be sitting at $437.7 million at the time of this writing. Its market cap crossed $4.9 and this saw it surpass Shiba Inu to reclaim its spot as the 14th largest cryptocurrency by market cap.</p>
<p class="p2">Other cryptocurrencies that made the gainers list was GRT with more than a 4.20% increase in price over the one-day period. ICP was third on the list with 3.56% gains, while CSPR followed closely behind at 3.21%. Terra Classic (LUNC) featured as 5th on the list, rising about 3% on Christmas to be sitting at $0.0001486.</p>
<p class="p2">Can LTC Reach $100?</p>
<p class="p2">Litecoin’s recent bullish movement can be attributed to CNBC’s Jim Cramer saying during an interview that holders of the cryptocurrency are “idiots.” Following this, the digital asset had begun to trend on social media, resulting in an upward rally on Christmas Day.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/IS2oYHLr/" alt="Litecoin (LTC) price chart from TradingView.com" width="3284" height="1760" /></p>

<p class="p2">However, LTC hit a roadblock just before reaching $70. Even though this put it above its 50 and 100-day moving averages, there was still enough resistance from the bears to keep it from reclaiming this position in the short term. This means that successfully beating $70 will likely see a rapid rise to $80 for LTC. But $100 remains a long way off for LTC.</p>

<p class="p2">The recent rally does not carry enough momentum to see it through to $100. Add in the fact that the crypto winter is still in full swing and it becomes improbable that the digital asset would be able to reach this price level in the short term. If bitcoin were to fall further and hit $10,000, then LTC could reach a low of $30 before the next bull market begins.</p>
<p class="p2">One important event to look towards that could mark a bullish trend for Litecoin, though, would be the next <a href="https://www.litecoinhalving.com/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">halving event happening in August 2023</a>. When this happens, the block reward could drop another 50% to 6.25 LTC. This decrease in supply could end up pushing the price upwards, as long as demand remains high.</p>
<p>Featured image from GoBankingRates, chart from TradingView.com</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Litecoin-460x259.jpeg" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Bullish Signal? Small Investors Show Rapid Accumulation</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-bullish-small-rapid-accumulation/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hououin Kyouma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 15:00:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin accumulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Bullish Signal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=513730</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[On-chain data shows small Bitcoin holders have accumulated recently while whale holdings have decreased, a sign that may be bullish in the long term. Bitcoin Investors With 0-1,000 Coins Have Increased Their Holdings Recently As a Twitter user has pointed out using data from Santiment, holders with wallet amounts in the 0-1,000 coins range have aggressively accumulated at recent lows. The relevant indicator here is the &#8220;Bitcoin Supply Distribution,&#8221; which tells us which wallet groups are holding what percentage of the total supply right now. Wallets (or more simply, holders) are divided into wallet bands based on the number of coins they are holding at the moment. For example, the 1-10 coins cohort includes all addresses that are currently carrying at least 1 and at most 10 BTC. The Supply Distribution metric for this group measures the collective balance of all the wallets falling inside this range. Related Reading: What Makes Big Eyes Coin, Bitcoin Cash, And Solana Better Than Most Preceding Projects? Now, here is a chart that shows the trend in the Bitcoin Supply Distribution data for the 0-1,000 coins and 1,000-1,000,000 coins bands: Looks like the values of the metric for the two groups have moved oppositely to each other in recent days &#124; Source: ₿igMak on Twitter As you can see above, the Bitcoin Supply Distribution curve for the 1,000-1,000,000 coins band has observed a sharp decline recently. The holders belonging to this group are the whales, which means that the percentage of the supply held by these humongous holders has been going down, suggesting that they have been capitulating during this deep bear market. The supply share held by the 0-1,000 coins group, on the other hand, has rapidly increased recently, implying that retail investors have been accumulating large amounts during the recent lows in the price of the asset. From the chart, it&#8217;s apparent that such a pattern was also seen during the 2018/2019 bear market, albeit the scale of movement from both these groups was much smaller. Interestingly, this trend only formed in that bear after the cyclical low was already in for BTC. Related Reading: Bottom Signal: This Bitcoin Ratio Declines To Four-Year Low Thus, if history is anything to go by, this recent accumulation from the 0-1,000 coins group could help Bitcoin form the bottom for the current cycle (if it&#8217;s not already in), and therefore reverse the coin towards a bullish trend in the long term. BTC Price At the time of writing, Bitcoin&#8217;s price floats around $16,800, up 1% in the last seven days. Over the past month, the crypto has gained 2% in value. The value of the crypto seems to still be stuck in a sideways trend &#124; Source: BTCUSD on TradingView Featured image from André François McKenzie on Unsplash.com, charts from TradingView.com, Santiment.net]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On-chain data shows small Bitcoin holders have accumulated recently while whale holdings have decreased, a sign that may be bullish in the long term.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Investors With 0-1,000 Coins Have Increased Their Holdings Recently</h2>
<p>As a <a href="https://twitter.com/Mn2Big/status/1606787497647816706" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Twitter user</a> has pointed out using data from Santiment, holders with wallet amounts in the 0-1,000 coins range have aggressively accumulated at recent lows. The relevant indicator here is the &#8220;Bitcoin Supply Distribution,&#8221; which tells us which wallet groups are holding what percentage of the total supply right now.</p>
<p>Wallets (or more simply, holders) are divided into wallet bands based on the number of coins they are holding at the moment. For example, the 1-10 coins cohort includes all addresses that are currently carrying at least 1 and at most 10 BTC. The Supply Distribution metric for this group measures the collective balance of all the wallets falling inside this range.</p>

<p>Now, here is a chart that shows the trend in the Bitcoin Supply Distribution data for the 0-1,000 coins and 1,000-1,000,000 coins bands:</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone aligncenter" src="https://pbs.twimg.com/media/Fkx0tZLWAAArmAf?format=jpg&amp;name=large" alt="Bitcoin Supply Distribution" width="2048" height="693" /></p>

<p>As you can see above, the Bitcoin Supply Distribution curve for the 1,000-1,000,000 coins band has observed a sharp decline recently. The holders belonging to this group are the <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/ripple/xrp-accumulation-shark-whale-all-time-high/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">whales</a>, which means that the percentage of the supply held by these humongous holders has been going down, suggesting that they have been capitulating during this deep bear market.</p>
<p>The supply share held by the 0-1,000 coins group, on the other hand, has rapidly increased recently, implying that <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-retail-hold-17-of-supply/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">retail investors</a> have been accumulating large amounts during the recent lows in the price of the asset.</p>
<p>From the chart, it&#8217;s apparent that such a pattern was also seen during the 2018/2019 bear market, albeit the scale of movement from both these groups was much smaller. Interestingly, this trend only formed in that bear after the cyclical low was already in for BTC.</p>

<p>Thus, if history is anything to go by, this recent accumulation from the 0-1,000 coins group could help Bitcoin form the bottom for the current cycle (if it&#8217;s not already in), and therefore reverse the coin towards a bullish trend in the long term.</p>
<h2>BTC Price</h2>
<p>At the time of writing, <a href="https://newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-larger-recovery-17k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin&#8217;s price</a> floats around $16,800, up 1% in the last seven days. Over the past month, the crypto has gained 2% in value.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-513740 aligncenter" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/chart-29-460x259.png" alt="Bitcoin Price Chart" width="460" height="259" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/chart-29-460x259.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/chart-29-860x484.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/chart-29-768x432.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/chart-29-750x422.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/chart-29.png 972w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px" /></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/andre-francois-mckenzie-iGYiBhdNTpE-unsplash-1-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Top 5 Cryptocurrencies To Keep An Eye On This Week &#8211; Post-Christmas Gainers</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/top-5-cryptocurrencies-this-week/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 11:45:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MATIC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrp]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=513724</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[It has been a roller coaster ride for crypto investors this 2022. This month, total crypto market capitalization fell from around $2.2 trillion at the start of the year to approximately $850 billion. Several high-profile bankruptcies this year exacerbated the precipitous decline in valuation. The market for cryptocurrencies is still consolidating, with the majority of assets unable to make large gains. Despite the current crypto winter, cryptocurrencies remain by far the most profitable asset class for investment, with the ability to recover losses and hit record highs in the long run. Currently, investors anticipate that the cryptocurrency market will strive to end the large sell-offs in 2023. A lengthy crypto winter tends to test the patience of investors, but it is one of the finest opportunities to purchase good cryptocurrencies at a discount. Meanwhile, there is continued curiosity in how particular crypto assets will end 2022, as their price movement will provide insight into what to expect in the following year. Here are five cryptocurrencies to keep an eye on for the week of December 26. Bitcoin (BTC) The year has not been kind to the cryptocurrency with the largest market capitalization. Since the start of 2022, bitcoin has lost more than 60 percent of its value. Because of this, over 50% of BTC investors are currently losing money, causing the market to crash. Nevertheless, a number of evidence imply that bitcoin will make a strong comeback in 2023. As of this writing, bitcoin is trading at $16,864, up 0.7% in the last seven days, data from Coingecko shows. Benjamin Cowen, a well-known cryptocurrency specialist, predicted that once bitcoin bulls seize control of the market, a &#8220;long accumulation period&#8221; will commence. Related Reading: VeChain Jumps By 4% As VET Investors Look To Profit Before Christmas Image: Pixabay Ethereum (ETH) The current price of Ethereum is $1,221, an almost 3% increase over the past week. The 24-hour low is $1,203 and the 24-hour high is $1,222. The cryptocurrency is up 0.1% on the one-hour and 24-hour time frames. The Ethereum Exchange Reserve for All Exchanges measure reveals the ETH reserves on CEXs have decreased by more than a quarter, according to on-chain data. Thus, investors are acquiring Ethereum and are becoming more bullish. At the time of writing, the bulls must demonstrate a strong push and consolidation above the $1,230 zone before a countertrend strategy can be considered. The next bullish objective would be $1,300 and possibly $1,350. Cardano (ADA) Despite the turmoil of 2022, Cardano&#8217;s (ADA) onchain activity has continued to reach new benchmarks. Cardano smart contracts surpassed 4,400 this year, a 395 percent increase, and 57 million transactions were conducted, an increase of approximately 140 percent. At the time of writing, ADA was trading at $0.26, up 0.2% in the last 24 hours, after a nearly 3% weekly chart correction. Despite its poor performance, ADA remains among the top 10 largest cryptocurrencies by market capitalization, with around $9 billion valuation. Crypto total market cap at nearly $772 billion on the daily chart &#124; Chart: TradingView.com Polygon (MATIC) Several major cryptocurrencies are expected to drop below their most recent lows, but MATIC has outperformed as it attempts to establish a stable foundation well above its annual bottom. In its first few months of existence, the price of MATIC was very constant, fluctuating between $0.01 and $0.03. MATIC&#8217;s price, up 0.9% in the last 24 hours and trading at $8030, reached an all-time high of approximately $1.40 in late 2020, one year after its launch, as the entire cryptocurrency market began to recover. This signified a tremendous rise of more than 4,600% in comparison to its initial price. Related Reading: Optimism Sees Spike In USDC And USDT Transactions Eclipsing $1 Billion XRP Since the all-time high of $1.98 was achieved in April 2021, the XRP price has lost 80% of its market value. The XRP community awaits the judgement in the case between Ripple and the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). The ultimate verdict is likely to have an effect on the price of XRP, which has shown brief forays into the green zone despite an extended difficult market. Bulls are aiming for a post-Christmas breakout as the XRP price rallies to $0.35 at press time.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>It has been a roller coaster ride for crypto investors this 2022. This month, total crypto market capitalization fell from around $2.2 trillion at the start of the year to approximately $850 billion.</p>
<p>Several high-profile <a href="https://www.investopedia.com/what-went-wrong-with-ftx-6828447" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">bankruptcies</a> this year exacerbated the precipitous decline in valuation.</p>
<p>The market for cryptocurrencies is still consolidating, with the majority of assets unable to make large gains.</p>
<p>Despite the current crypto winter, cryptocurrencies remain by far the most profitable asset class for investment, with the ability to recover losses and hit record highs in the long run.</p>
<p>Currently, investors anticipate that the cryptocurrency market will strive to end the large sell-offs in 2023.</p>
<p>A lengthy crypto winter tends to test the patience of investors, but it is one of the finest opportunities to purchase good cryptocurrencies at a discount.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, there is continued curiosity in how particular crypto assets will end 2022, as their price movement will provide insight into what to expect in the following year.</p>
<p>Here are five cryptocurrencies to keep an eye on for the week of December 26.</p>
<h2><strong>Bitcoin (BTC)</strong></h2>
<p>The year has not been kind to the cryptocurrency with the largest market capitalization. Since the start of 2022, bitcoin has lost more than 60 percent of its value.</p>
<p>Because of this, over 50% of BTC investors are currently losing money, causing the market to crash. Nevertheless, a number of evidence imply that bitcoin will make a strong comeback in 2023.</p>
<p>As of this writing, <a href="https://www.business2community.com/crypto-news/bitcoin-price-prediction-can-btc-make-new-highs-in-2023-02593889" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">bitcoin </a>is trading at $16,864, up 0.7% in the last seven days,<a href="https://www.coingecko.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow"> data</a> from Coingecko shows.</p>
<p>Benjamin Cowen, a well-known cryptocurrency specialist, predicted that once bitcoin bulls seize control of the market, a &#8220;long accumulation period&#8221; will commence.</p>

<img loading="lazy" class="size-medium wp-image-490048" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/Crypto-Market-460x307.jpg" alt="Crypto Traders" width="460" height="307" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/Crypto-Market-460x307.jpg 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/Crypto-Market-860x573.jpg 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/Crypto-Market-768x512.jpg 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/Crypto-Market-1536x1024.jpg 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/Crypto-Market-750x500.jpg 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/Crypto-Market-1140x760.jpg 1140w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/Crypto-Market.jpg 1920w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px" />

<h2><strong>Ethereum (ETH)</strong></h2>
<p>The current price of Ethereum is $1,221, an almost 3% increase over the past week. The 24-hour low is $1,203 and the 24-hour high is $1,222. The cryptocurrency is up 0.1% on the one-hour and 24-hour time frames.</p>
<p>The Ethereum Exchange Reserve for All Exchanges measure reveals the ETH reserves on CEXs have decreased by more than a quarter, according to on-chain data. Thus, investors are acquiring Ethereum and are becoming more bullish.</p>
<p>At the time of writing, the bulls must demonstrate a strong push and consolidation above the $1,230 zone before a countertrend strategy can be considered. The next bullish objective would be $1,300 and possibly $1,350.</p>
<strong>Cardano (ADA)</strong>
<p>Despite the turmoil of 2022, Cardano&#8217;s (ADA) onchain activity has continued to reach new benchmarks.</p>
<p>Cardano smart contracts surpassed 4,400 this year, a 395 percent increase, and 57 million transactions were conducted, an increase of approximately 140 percent.</p>
<p>At the time of writing, <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">ADA</a> was trading at $0.26, up 0.2% in the last 24 hours, after a nearly 3% weekly chart correction.</p>
<p>Despite its poor performance, ADA remains among the top 10 largest cryptocurrencies by market capitalization, with around $9 billion valuation.</p>
<img loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/6AqCLbNJ/" width="2047" height="979" />

<strong>Polygon (MATIC)</strong>
<p>Several major cryptocurrencies are expected to drop below their most recent lows, but MATIC has outperformed as it attempts to establish a stable foundation well above its annual bottom.</p>
<p>In its first few months of existence, the price of <a href="https://www.cryptonewsz.com/forecast/matic-price-prediction/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">MATIC</a> was very constant, fluctuating between $0.01 and $0.03.</p>
<p>MATIC&#8217;s price, up 0.9% in the last 24 hours and trading at $8030, reached an all-time high of approximately $1.40 in late 2020, one year after its launch, as the entire cryptocurrency market began to recover.</p>
<p>This signified a tremendous rise of more than 4,600% in comparison to its initial price.</p>

<strong>XRP</strong>
<p>Since the all-time high of $1.98 was achieved in April 2021, the <a href="https://www.fxstreet.com/cryptocurrencies/news/sec-v-ripple-lawsuit-update-remittance-network-ripple-scores-another-small-win-in-court-case-202212220628" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">XRP</a> price has lost 80% of its market value.</p>
<p>The XRP community awaits the judgement in the case between Ripple and the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC).</p>
<p>The ultimate verdict is likely to have an effect on the price of XRP, which has shown brief forays into the green zone despite an extended difficult market.</p>
<p>Bulls are aiming for a post-Christmas breakout as the XRP price rallies to $0.35 at press time.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Crypto-460x329.png" width="460" height="329" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Litecoin Price Prediction: This Resistance Could Trigger New Rally</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/analysis/ltc/litecoin-price-prediction-80/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 06:37:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[LTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Litecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[litecoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ltc/usd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ltcusdc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LTCUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=513719</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Litecoin price remained well bid above the $60 support zone against the US Dollar. LTC is rising and might attempt a fresh rally above the $70 level. Litecoin started a fresh decline below $80 support against the US Dollar. The price is now trading below $70 and the 100 simple moving average (4-hours). There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $70.50 on the 4-hours chart of the LTC/USD pair (data feed from Kraken). The price could start a decent increase if there is a clear move above the $72 resistance. Litecoin Price Eyes Upside Break Earlier this month, litecoin price saw a steady decline from well above the $80 level against the US Dollar. LTC price declined below the $75 support zone to move into a bearish zone, similar to bitcoin and ethereum. The price gained pace below the $70 support and the 100 simple moving average (4-hours). A low was formed near $61.02 and the price is now attempting a recovery wave. There was a decent upside correction above the $63 and $65 levels. There was a move above the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the key decline from the $79.80 swing high to $61.02 low. The price is now trading near the $70 resistance and 100 simple moving average (4-hours). On the upside, an immediate resistance is near the $70.00 level. There is also a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $70.50 on the 4-hours chart of the LTC/USD pair. The trend line is near the 50% Fib retracement level of the key decline from the $79.80 swing high to $61.02 low. Source: LTCUSD on TradingView.com If there is a clear break above the $70.50 resistance, the price could start a strong increase. In the stated case, the price is likely to continue higher towards the $72 and $75 levels. Any more gains might send ltc price towards the $80 resistance zone. Fresh Decline in LTC? If Litecoin price fails to clear the $70.00 resistance level, there could be a fresh decline. An initial support on the downside is near the $65.50 level. The first major support is forming near the $64.00 level. Any further losses may perhaps send the price towards the $60.00 support in the coming sessions. Technical indicators: 4-hours MACD – The MACD is slowly gaining pace in the bullish zone. 4-hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for LTC/USD is above the 50 level. Major Support Levels – $65.50 followed by $60.00. Major Resistance Levels – $70.00 and $75.00.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>Litecoin price remained well bid above the $60 support zone against the US Dollar. LTC is rising and might attempt a fresh rally above the $70 level.</em></p>
<ul>
<li>Litecoin started a fresh decline below $80 support against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>The price is now trading below $70 and the 100 simple moving average (4-hours).</li>
<li>There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $70.50 on the 4-hours chart of the LTC/USD pair (data feed from Kraken).</li>
<li>The price could start a decent increase if there is a clear move above the $72 resistance.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Litecoin Price Eyes Upside Break</h2>
<p>Earlier this month, litecoin price saw a steady decline from well above the $80 level against the US Dollar. LTC price declined below the $75 support zone to move into a bearish zone, similar to <a href="https://newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-larger-recovery-17k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">bitcoin</a> and <a href="https://newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-muted-1230/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">ethereum</a>.</p>
<p>The price gained pace below the $70 support and the 100 simple moving average (4-hours). A low was formed near $61.02 and the price is now attempting a recovery wave. There was a decent upside correction above the $63 and $65 levels.</p>
<p>There was a move above the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the key decline from the $79.80 swing high to $61.02 low. The price is now trading near the $70 resistance and 100 simple moving average (4-hours).</p>
<p>On the upside, an immediate resistance is near the $70.00 level. There is also a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $70.50 on the 4-hours chart of the LTC/USD pair. The trend line is near the 50% Fib retracement level of the key decline from the $79.80 swing high to $61.02 low.</p>
<a href="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Litecoin-5.png"><img loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-513720" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Litecoin-5.png" alt="Litecoin Price" width="1950" height="1109" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Litecoin-5.png 1950w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Litecoin-5-460x262.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Litecoin-5-860x489.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Litecoin-5-768x437.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Litecoin-5-1536x874.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Litecoin-5-750x427.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Litecoin-5-1140x648.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1950px) 100vw, 1950px" /></a>
<p>Source: <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/LTCUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">LTCUSD on TradingView.com</a></p>
<p>If there is a clear break above the $70.50 resistance, the price could start a strong increase. In the stated case, the price is likely to continue higher towards the $72 and $75 levels. Any more gains might send ltc price towards the $80 resistance zone.</p>
<h2>Fresh Decline in LTC?</h2>
<p>If Litecoin price fails to clear the $70.00 resistance level, there could be a fresh decline. An initial support on the downside is near the $65.50 level.</p>
<p>The first major support is forming near the $64.00 level. Any further losses may perhaps send the price towards the $60.00 support in the coming sessions.</p>
<p>Technical indicators:</p>
<p>4-hours MACD – The MACD is slowly gaining pace in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>4-hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for LTC/USD is above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Levels – $65.50 followed by $60.00.</p>
<p>Major Resistance Levels – $70.00 and $75.00.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Depositphotos_78872860_s-2019-1-460x293.jpg" width="460" height="293" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Optimism Sees Spike In USDC And USDT Transactions Eclipsing $1 Billion</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/optimism-usdc-transactions-top-1b/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 04:19:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[OP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[OP Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[optimism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Optimism Network]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USDC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=513680</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Optimism blockchain network has recently noticed an enormous uptick in both USDC and USDT transactions which have eclipsed $1 billion. What seems to have caught people’s attention is the fact that the Optimism chain seems to be unrivaled and unmoved by the chaos happening in the crypto space. This is now tagged as an unusual trend because it goes against the current especially with the sudden spike in USDC and USDT. Here&#8217;s a quick glance at how the crypto and network are performing: OP price down by 1.83% Metamask provides support for L2 Solutions User retention rate grew to as much as 34% weekly Source: Santiment There seems to have been a convergence given the noticeable connection between the uptick in stablecoins with that of OP’s price performance. According to CoinMarketCap, OP price is currently up by 0.4% in the last 24 hours, or trading at $0.9348 as of press time. The USDC and USDT surge is observed to be following a market trend which would ultimately revert back to normal with the price of OP diminishing and with the USDC and USDT prices settling down. Related Reading: VeChain Jumps By 4% As VET Investors Look To Profit Before Christmas Potential Factors That Cause USDT, USDC Uptick With the increased activity, people are contemplating on what could have triggered the sudden uptick. One of the possible theories would be Optimism’s impressive Total Value Locked (TVL) as it grew immensely compared to other cryptocurrencies.   Another is the announcement of Metamask wallet providing support for Optimism and other Layer 2 solutions. It has definitely helped increase the awareness and adoption of Layer 2 which can attract more people to shift to the network. More so, the solution’s recent update on mobile accessibility is also one of the reasons why it has grown in popularity and also because users can easily and conveniently use Optimism via their mobile phones. Nevertheless, even before the mobile usability update, many users have already started flocking towards OP. Its user base has increased from 24,000 to 80,000 in just three months and the figures are predicted to rise especially with the recent Metamask update. Related Reading: SOL Recovery In 2023 – Will The Solana Mobile Updates Help? Crypto total market cap at nearly $772 billion on the daily chart &#124; Chart: TradingView.com Optimism Keeping Users Loyal In addition, the escalating number of transactions on the Optimism network is likely due to the uptick in stablecoin transactions. It has been observed that the network isn’t just good with the attraction game but can also keep their users loyal and satisfied. In fact, the retention rate of OP has grown to as much as 34% per week. A number of dApps are now on Optimism which also caused its TVL to increase to more than $500 million. Although there are occasions wherein the TVL declines, the spikes still outweigh the downtrend.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Optimism blockchain network has recently noticed an enormous uptick in both USDC and USDT transactions which have eclipsed $1 billion.</p>
<p>What seems to have caught people’s attention is the fact that the Optimism chain seems to be unrivaled and unmoved by the chaos happening in the crypto space. </p>
<p>This is now tagged as an unusual trend because it goes against the current especially with the sudden spike in USDC and USDT.</p>
<p>Here&#8217;s a quick glance at how the crypto and network are performing:</p>
<ul>
<li>OP price down by 1.83%</li>
<li>Metamask provides support for L2 Solutions</li>
<li>User retention rate grew to as much as 34% weekly</li>
</ul>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-513710 size-full" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/a-14.png" alt="" width="594" height="199" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/a-14.png 594w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/a-14-460x154.png 460w" sizes="(max-width: 594px) 100vw, 594px" /></p>

<p>There seems to have been a convergence given the noticeable connection between the uptick in stablecoins with that of OP’s price performance. </p>
<p>According to<a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/optimism-ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow"> CoinMarketCap</a>, OP price is currently up by 0.4% in the last 24 hours, or trading at $0.9348 as of press time.</p>
<p>The USDC and USDT surge is observed to be following a market trend which would ultimately revert back to normal with the price of OP diminishing and with the USDC and USDT prices settling down.</p>

<h2><b>Potential Factors That Cause USDT, USDC Uptick</b></h2>
<p>With the increased activity, people are contemplating on what could have triggered the sudden uptick. One of the possible theories would be Optimism’s impressive Total Value Locked (TVL) as it grew immensely compared to other cryptocurrencies.  </p>
<p>Another is the announcement of<a href="https://ambcrypto.com/metamask-gives-op-holders-a-few-reasons-to-be-optimistic-this-crypto-winter/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow"> Metamask</a> wallet providing support for Optimism and other Layer 2 solutions. It has definitely helped increase the awareness and adoption of Layer 2 which can attract more people to shift to the network.</p>
<p>More so, the solution’s recent update on mobile accessibility is also one of the reasons why it has grown in popularity and also because users can easily and conveniently use Optimism via their mobile phones.</p>
<p>Nevertheless, even before the mobile usability update, many users have already started flocking towards OP. Its user base has increased from 24,000 to 80,000 in just three months and the figures are predicted to rise especially with the recent Metamask update.</p>

<p><img loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/S4iVcbiK/" width="2047" height="979" /></p>

<h2><b>Optimism Keeping Users Loyal</b></h2>
<p>In addition, the escalating number of transactions on the Optimism network is likely due to the<a href="https://www.cryptoglobe.com/latest/2022/12/mysterious-transaction-volumes-on-optimism-op-blockchain-spark-speculation/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow"> uptick in stablecoin transactions</a>. It has been observed that the network isn’t just good with the attraction game but can also keep their users loyal and satisfied. In fact, the retention rate of OP has grown to as much as 34% per week.</p>
<p>A number of dApps are now on Optimism which also caused its TVL to increase to more than $500 million. Although there are occasions wherein the TVL declines, the spikes still outweigh the downtrend.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/optimism-460x314.jpg" width="460" height="314" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum Price Relatively Muted, Bulls Still Aim Key Upside Break</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-muted-1230/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 04:02:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=513706</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Ethereum is consolidating below the $1,230 resistance against the US Dollar. ETH could start a steady increase if it clears the $1,230 and $1,250 resistance levels. Ethereum is slowly moving higher from the $1,190 support zone. The price is now trading above $1,210 and the 100 hourly simple moving average. There was a break above a key bearish trend line with resistance near $1,215 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD (data feed via Kraken). The pair could gain bullish momentum if there is a clear move above $1,230 and $1,250. Ethereum Price Eyes Upside Break Ethereum price remained well bid above the $1,180 and $1,190 levels. ETH formed a base above the $1,190 level and started an upward move. There was a clear move above the $1,200 resistance zone and the 100 hourly simple moving average. Ether price climbed above the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $1,237 swing high to $1,193 swing low. Besides, there was a break above a key bearish trend line with resistance near $1,215 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD. The pair is now consolidating near the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $1,237 swing high to $1,193 swing low. An immediate resistance is near the $1,230 level. The next major resistance is near the $1,250 level. A clear upside break above the $1,250 resistance could start a steady increase. In the stated case, the price may perhaps rise towards the $1,300 resistance. Source: ETHUSD on TradingView.com The next major resistance could be $1,350. If there is an upside break above the $1,350 resistance, the price might rise towards $1,400. Any more gains might send the price towards the $1,500 resistance zone. ETH Still In a Range? If ethereum fails to climb above the $1,230 resistance, it could start another drop. An initial support on the downside is near the $1,215 level and the 100 hourly simple moving average. The next major support is near the $1,200 level. The first major support is near the $1,190 level. A downside break below $1,190 might spark a move towards the $1,150 support. Any more losses could lead the price towards the $1,100 zone. Technical Indicators Hourly MACD – The MACD for ETH/USD is now gaining momentum in the bullish zone. Hourly RSI &#8211; The RSI for ETH/USD is now above the 50 level. Major Support Level – $1,190 Major Resistance Level – $1,230]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>Ethereum is consolidating below the $1,230 resistance against the US Dollar. ETH could start a steady increase if it clears the $1,230 and $1,250 resistance levels.</em></p>
<ul>
<li>Ethereum is slowly moving higher from the $1,190 support zone.</li>
<li>The price is now trading above $1,210 and the 100 hourly simple moving average.</li>
<li>There was a break above a key bearish trend line with resistance near $1,215 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD (data feed via Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could gain bullish momentum if there is a clear move above $1,230 and $1,250.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Ethereum Price Eyes Upside Break</h2>
<p><a href="https://newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-key-trend-1250/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ethereum price remained well bid</a> above the $1,180 and $1,190 levels. ETH formed a base above the $1,190 level and started an upward move.</p>
<p>There was a clear move above the $1,200 resistance zone and the 100 hourly simple moving average. Ether price climbed above the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $1,237 swing high to $1,193 swing low.</p>
<p>Besides, there was a break above a key bearish trend line with resistance near $1,215 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD. The pair is now consolidating near the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $1,237 swing high to $1,193 swing low.</p>
<p>An immediate resistance is near the $1,230 level. The next <a href="https://newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-consolidates-1250/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">major resistance</a> is near the $1,250 level. A clear upside break above the $1,250 resistance could start a steady increase. In the stated case, the price may perhaps rise towards the $1,300 resistance.</p>
<p><a href="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Ethereum-18.png"><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-513707" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Ethereum-18.png" alt="Ethereum Price" width="1834" height="845" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Ethereum-18.png 1834w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Ethereum-18-460x212.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Ethereum-18-860x396.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Ethereum-18-768x354.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Ethereum-18-1536x708.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Ethereum-18-750x346.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Ethereum-18-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1834px) 100vw, 1834px" /></a></p>
<p>Source: <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/ETHUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">ETHUSD on TradingView.com</a></p>
<p>The next major resistance could be $1,350. If there is an upside break above the $1,350 resistance, the price might rise towards $1,400. Any more gains might send the price towards the $1,500 resistance zone.</p>
<h2>ETH Still In a Range?</h2>
<p>If ethereum fails to climb above the $1,230 resistance, it could start another drop. An initial support on the downside is near the $1,215 level and the 100 hourly simple moving average.</p>
<p>The next major support is near the $1,200 level. The first major support is near the $1,190 level. A downside break below $1,190 might spark a move towards the $1,150 support. Any more losses could lead the price towards the $1,100 zone.</p>
<p>Technical Indicators</p>
<p>Hourly MACD<strong> – </strong>The MACD for ETH/USD is now gaining momentum in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>Hourly RSI<strong> &#8211; </strong>The RSI for ETH/USD is now above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Level – $1,190</p>
<p>Major Resistance Level – $1,230</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/04/shutterstock_1029670141-460x276.jpg" width="460" height="276" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Price Close Above $17.5K Could Spark Larger Degree Recovery</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-larger-recovery-17k/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 03:19:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xbtusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=513702</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin price is attempting an upside break above $17,000. BTC could start a steady recovery if it clears the $17,000 and $17,200 resistance levels. Bitcoin is attempting an upside break above the $17,000 and $17,200 levels. The price is trading above $16,800 and the 100 hourly simple moving average. There was a break above a key bearish trend line with resistance near $16,820 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Kraken). The pair could attempt a fresh increase if there is a clear move above the $17,200 resistance zone. Bitcoin Price Eyes Upside Break Bitcoin price managed to stay above the $16,550 zone. A base was formed and the price started a fresh increase above the $16,700 resistance zone. BTC even climbed above the $16,800 resistance and the 100 hourly simple moving average. There was a clear move above the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $17,067 swing high to $16,565 low. Besides, there was a break above a key bearish trend line with resistance near $16,820 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair. Bitcoin price is now trading above $16,800 and the 100 hourly simple moving average. It is also trading above the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $17,067 swing high to $16,565 low. On the upside, an immediate resistance is near the $17,000 zone. The first major resistance is near the $17,200 zone. A clear move above the $17,200 resistance might start a steady recovery wave. Source: BTCUSD on TradingView.com The next major resistance is near $17,500, above which the price climb towards the $18,000 resistance zone. Any more gains might send the pair towards the $18,500 resistance zone. Fresh Drop in BTC? If bitcoin fails to clear the $17,200 resistance, there could be a fresh downward move. An immediate support on the downside is near the $16,800 level and the 100 hourly SMA The next major support is near the $16,680 level. A downside break below the $16,680 support might call for a move towards the $16,550 level. Any more losses might send the price towards $16,350. Technical indicators: Hourly MACD – The MACD is now gaining pace in the bullish zone. Hourly RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BTC/USD is now above the 50 level. Major Support Levels – $16,800, followed by $16,550. Major Resistance Levels – $17,000, $17,200 and $17,500.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>Bitcoin price is attempting an upside break above $17,000. BTC could start a steady recovery if it clears the $17,000 and $17,200 resistance levels.</em></p>
<ul>
<li>Bitcoin is attempting an upside break above the $17,000 and $17,200 levels.</li>
<li>The price is trading above $16,800 and the 100 hourly simple moving average.</li>
<li>There was a break above a key bearish trend line with resistance near $16,820 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could attempt a fresh increase if there is a clear move above the $17,200 resistance zone.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Bitcoin Price Eyes Upside Break</h2>
<p>Bitcoin price managed to stay above the $16,550 zone. A base was formed and the price started a fresh increase above the $16,700 resistance zone. BTC even climbed above the $16,800 resistance and the <a href="https://newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-recovery-fade-17-2k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">100 hourly simple moving average</a>.</p>
<p>There was a clear move above the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $17,067 swing high to $16,565 low. Besides, there was a break above a key bearish trend line with resistance near $16,820 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair.</p>
<p>Bitcoin price is now trading above $16,800 and the 100 hourly simple moving average. It is also trading above the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $17,067 swing high to $16,565 low.</p>
<p>On the upside, an immediate resistance is near the <a href="https://newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-shows-life-17k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">$17,000 zone</a>. The first major resistance is near the $17,200 zone. A clear move above the $17,200 resistance might start a steady recovery wave.</p>
<p><a href="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-22.png"><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-513703" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-22.png" alt="Bitcoin Price" width="1834" height="845" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-22.png 1834w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-22-460x212.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-22-860x396.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-22-768x354.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-22-1536x708.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-22-750x346.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-22-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1834px) 100vw, 1834px" /></a></p>
<p>Source: <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BTCUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">BTCUSD on TradingView.com</a></p>
<p>The next major resistance is near $17,500, above which the price climb towards the $18,000 resistance zone. Any more gains might send the pair towards the $18,500 resistance zone.</p>
<h2>Fresh Drop in BTC?</h2>
<p>If bitcoin fails to clear the $17,200 resistance, there could be a fresh downward move. An immediate support on the downside is near the $16,800 level and the 100 hourly SMA</p>
<p>The next major support is near the $16,680 level. A downside break below the $16,680 support might call for a move towards the $16,550 level. Any more losses might send the price towards $16,350.</p>
<p>Technical indicators:</p>
<p>Hourly MACD – The MACD is now gaining pace in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>Hourly RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BTC/USD is now above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Levels – $16,800, followed by $16,550.</p>
<p>Major Resistance Levels – $17,000, $17,200 and $17,500.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/04/shutterstock_456228007-460x306.jpg" width="460" height="306" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Crypto Holiday Special: Past, Present, And Future With Ex BNY Mellon David Schwed</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/interview/crypto-holiday-past-and-future-bny-mellon/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reynaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2022 18:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Interview]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BNY Mellon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Holiday]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=513590</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[2022 is coming to an end, and our staff at NewsBTC decided to launch this Crypto Holiday Special to provide some perspective on the crypto industry. We will talk with multiple guests to understand this year’s highs and lows for crypto. Related Reading: WAVES Gets Dragged Down By USDN, Despite Pumping Investor Distribution In the spirit of Charles Dicken&#8217;s classic, “A Christmas Carol,” we’ll look into crypto from different angles, look at its possible trajectory for 2023 and find common ground amongst these different views of an industry that might support the future of finances.  Yesterday, we spoke with investment firm Blofin on their perspective on the past, present, and future of crypto. Today, we continue the series with David Schwed, former Global Head of Digital Assets Technology at BNY Mellon, the world’s largest custodian and securities services provider, and current COO at Halborn. Schwed: &#8220;What changed was the reality that too good to be true yields are exactly that, too good to be true.  The money needs to come from somewhere, and it turns out that it was coming from risk loans and other business practices that relied on the steady increase of the price of crypto (&#8230;).&#8221; This major financial institution, along with some of the biggest banks in the U.S., Goldman Sachs, Morgan Stanley, J.P. Morgan, finally embraced cryptocurrencies in 2021 and 2022. Still, recent events in the industry might impact crypto and digital asset adoption for legacy financial institutions. Schwed: &#8220;I haven’t seen any slowdown from TradFi when it comes to entering/expanding into the crypto markets.&#8221; Traditional Finances (TradFi) and Crypto Finances, in their many forms (CeFi, DeFi, etc.), have been converging. Will the collapse of Three Arrows Capital (3AC) and FTX push these institutions away from crypto? What is the likeliest regulatory outlook for 2023? We asked this former BNY Mellon executive this and much more. This is what he told us: Q: What’s the most significant difference for the crypto market today compared to Christmas 2021? Beyond the price of Bitcoin, Ethereum, and others, what changed from that moment of euphoria to today’s perpetual fear? Has there been a decline in adoption and liquidity? Are fundamentals still valid? A: What changed was the reality that too good to be true yields are exactly that, too good to be true.  The money needs to come from somewhere, and it turns out that it was coming from risk loans and other business practices that relied on the steady increase of the price of crypto.  As the price fell and the loans were due, many faced liquidation of their collateral and margin calls.  That being said, we are seeing adoption in many other areas besides finance.  Many major retailers are also entering the ecosystem, such as Nike, Matterl, Samsung, and LVMH. Q: What are the dominant narratives driving this change in market conditions? And what should be the narrative today? What are most people overlooking? We saw a major crypto exchange blowing up, a hedge fund thought to be untouchable, and an ecosystem that promised a financial utopia. Is Crypto still the future of finance, or should the community pursue a new vision? A: The narrative today needs to be risk management and security.  Had 3AC/Voyager/Celsius and others had more institutional risk management practices, their demise may have been avoided.  The same thought goes into security.  There is a fundamental difference between crypto native security vs what we see in more mature financial institutions.  We need to improve both drastically in order to restore trust. Q: If you must choose one, what do you think was a significant moment for crypto in 2022? And will the industry feel its consequences across 2023? Where do you see the industry next Christmas? Will it survive this winter? Mainstream is once again declaring the death of the industry. Will they finally get it right? A: The most significant moment was the FTX crash.  The progression of SBF from the hero who will save us all to a criminal in a matter of weeks is evidence of the lack of transparency in the ecosystem.  We will certainly feel the impact as we head into 2023 . I don’t believe we’ve seen the full impact as it relates to other organizations who have some exposure to FTX or are generally over-leveraged.  I believe by the end of 2023 we will be back to where we were in the beginning of 2022 in part due to the institutional/enterprise markets.  I’ve heard “Crypto is dead” many times throughout the years and they’ve been wrong every time.  While the current situation is much different since the price decline is a result of many systemic failures, the same can be said for many crashes observed in TradFi Wall Street, the most similar being the 2008-2009 crisis and TradFi is still alive and kicking. Related Reading: Bitcoin Price Poised To Rally Big-Time On Today’s PCE Release Q: Traditional finances (Tradfi) and crypto are merging in many ways. Will the collapse of FTX affect this trend? And in this context, do you see regulations leaning toward adopting an approach that will halt the integration between legacy and crypto financial companies? A:  While the collapse of FTX and the resulting collateral damage has shown to have negatively impacted the crypto market, I haven’t seen any slowdown from TradFi when it comes to entering/expanding into the crypto markets.  In fact, many of the G-SIBs (Globally Systemically Important Banks) that I have spoken to have not changed or altered their roadmaps as it relates to crypto.  I haven’t seen any indication of regulations halting the integrations between traditional and crypto.  That being said, I believe we will see sweeping regulation in the crypto markets similar in size and scope of the Dodd-Frank Act. As of this writing, Bitcoin trades at $16,800 with sideways movement across the board. Image from Unsplash, chart from Tradingview.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>2022 is coming to an end, and our staff at NewsBTC decided to launch this Crypto Holiday Special to provide some perspective on the crypto industry. We will talk with multiple guests to understand this year’s highs and lows for crypto.</strong></p>

<p><strong>In the spirit of Charles Dicken&#8217;s classic, “A Christmas Carol,” we’ll look into crypto from different angles, look at its possible trajectory for 2023 and find common ground amongst these different views of an industry that might support the future of finances. </strong></p>
<p>Yesterday, we spoke with investment firm Blofin on their perspective on the past, present, and future of crypto. Today, we continue the series with David Schwed,<a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/davidschwed/details/experience/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow"> former Global Head of Digital Assets Technology at BNY Mellon</a>, the world’s largest custodian and securities services provider, and current COO at Halborn.</p>
<p style="text-align: center"><strong>Schwed: &#8220;What changed was the reality that too good to be true yields are exactly that, too good to be true.  The money needs to come from somewhere, and it turns out that it was coming from risk loans and other business practices that relied on the steady increase of the price of crypto (&#8230;).&#8221;</strong></p>
<p>This major financial institution, along with some of the biggest banks in the U.S., Goldman Sachs, Morgan Stanley, J.P. Morgan, finally embraced cryptocurrencies in 2021 and 2022. Still, recent events in the industry might impact crypto and digital asset adoption for legacy financial institutions.</p>
<p style="text-align: center"><strong>Schwed: &#8220;I haven’t seen any slowdown from TradFi when it comes to entering/expanding into the crypto markets.&#8221;</strong></p>
<p>Traditional Finances (TradFi) and Crypto Finances, in their many forms (CeFi, DeFi, etc.), have been converging. Will the collapse of Three Arrows Capital (3AC) and FTX push these institutions away from crypto? What is the likeliest regulatory outlook for 2023? We asked this former BNY Mellon executive this and much more. This is what he told us:</p>
<p><strong>Q: What’s the most significant difference for the crypto market today compared to Christmas 2021? Beyond the price of Bitcoin, Ethereum, and others, what changed from that moment of euphoria to today’s perpetual fear? Has there been a decline in adoption and liquidity? Are fundamentals still valid? </strong></p>
<p>A: What changed was the reality that too good to be true yields are exactly that, too good to be true.  The money needs to come from somewhere, and it turns out that it was coming from risk loans and other business practices that relied on the steady increase of the price of crypto.  As the price fell and the loans were due, many faced liquidation of their collateral and margin calls.  That being said, we are seeing adoption in many other areas besides finance.  Many major retailers are also entering the ecosystem, such as Nike, Matterl, Samsung, and LVMH.</p>
<p><strong>Q: What are the dominant narratives driving this change in market conditions? And what should be the narrative today? What are most people overlooking? We saw a major crypto exchange blowing up, a hedge fund thought to be untouchable, and an ecosystem that promised a financial utopia. Is Crypto still the future of finance, or should the community pursue a new vision?</strong></p>
<p>A: The narrative today needs to be risk management and security.  Had 3AC/Voyager/Celsius and others had more institutional risk management practices, their demise may have been avoided.  The same thought goes into security.  There is a fundamental difference between crypto native security vs what we see in more mature financial institutions.  We need to improve both drastically in order to restore trust.</p>
<p><strong>Q: If you must choose one, what do you think was a significant moment for crypto in 2022? And will the industry feel its consequences across 2023? Where do you see the industry next Christmas? Will it survive this winter? Mainstream is once again declaring the death of the industry. Will they finally get it right? </strong></p>
<p>A: The most significant moment was the FTX crash.  The progression of SBF from the hero who will save us all to a criminal in a matter of weeks is evidence of the lack of transparency in the ecosystem.  We will certainly feel the impact as we head into 2023 . I don’t believe we’ve seen the full impact as it relates to other organizations who have some exposure to FTX or are generally over-leveraged.  I believe by the end of 2023 we will be back to where we were in the beginning of 2022 in part due to the institutional/enterprise markets.  I’ve heard “Crypto is dead” many times throughout the years and they’ve been wrong every time.  While the current situation is much different since the price decline is a result of many systemic failures, the same can be said for many crashes observed in TradFi Wall Street, the most similar being the 2008-2009 crisis and TradFi is still alive and kicking.</p>

<p><strong>Q: Traditional finances (Tradfi) and crypto are merging in many ways. Will the collapse of FTX affect this trend? And in this context, do you see regulations leaning toward adopting an approach that will halt the integration between legacy and crypto financial companies?</strong></p>
<p>A:  While the collapse of FTX and the resulting collateral damage has shown to have negatively impacted the crypto market, I haven’t seen any slowdown from TradFi when it comes to entering/expanding into the crypto markets.  In fact, many of the G-SIBs (Globally Systemically Important Banks) that I have spoken to have not changed or altered their roadmaps as it relates to crypto.  I haven’t seen any indication of regulations halting the integrations between traditional and crypto.  That being said, I believe we will see sweeping regulation in the crypto markets similar in size and scope of the Dodd-Frank Act.</p>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-513600 size-large" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Crypto-Holiday-860x376.png" alt="Bitcoin BTC BTCUSDT Crypto Holiday" width="860" height="376" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Crypto-Holiday-860x376.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Crypto-Holiday-460x201.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Crypto-Holiday-768x336.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Crypto-Holiday-1536x671.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Crypto-Holiday-750x328.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Crypto-Holiday-1140x498.png 1140w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Crypto-Holiday.png 1814w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" />
<p>As of this writing, Bitcoin trades at $16,800 with sideways movement across the board. Image from Unsplash, chart from Tradingview.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Crypto-Holiday-Special-cover-image-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
