<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
>

<channel>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.newsbtc.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<description>Bitcoin &#38; cryptocurrency news today, price &#38; technical analysis</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 02:50:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Price Prints Bullish Technical Pattern, Why Close Above $28,500 Is Critical</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-bullish-28500-critical/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 02:50:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xbtusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=535406</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin price is up 4% and trading above $28,000. BTC must clear the $28,500 resistance zone to continue higher in the near term. Bitcoin is gaining pace above the $27,500 and $27,800 resistance levels. The price is trading above $28,000 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average. There is a key bullish trend line forming with support near $27,700 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Kraken). The pair could correct lower but the bulls might be active near $27,700 and $27,500. Bitcoin Price Recovers Over 4% Bitcoin price managed to stay above the $26,000 support zone. BTC formed a base and started a recovery wave above the $27,000 resistance. There was a steady increase once the price cleared the $27,500 resistance zone. It is up over 4% and there was a break above the $28,000 resistance. A high is formed near $28,450 and the price is now consolidating gains. It is trading near the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $27,143 swing low to the $28,450 high. Bitcoin price is now trading above $28,000 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average. There is also a key bullish trend line forming with support near $27,700 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair. Immediate resistance on the upside is near the $28,320 level. The next major resistance is near the $28,500 level. A close above the $28,500 resistance zone might send the price toward the $29,200 resistance zone. Source: BTCUSD on TradingView.com The next key resistance is near $29,500, above which the price might rise toward the $30,000 resistance. Any more gains might send the price toward the $31,200 resistance level. Are Dips Limited in BTC? If Bitcoin’s price fails to clear the $28,500 resistance, it could start a downside correction. Immediate support on the downside is near the $28,000 level. The next major support is near the $27,700 zone or the 50% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $27,143 swing low to the $28,450 high, below which the price might test the $27,500 support. Any more losses might take Bitcoin toward the $27,200 level in the near term. Technical indicators: Hourly MACD – The MACD is now losing pace in the bullish zone. Hourly RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BTC/USD is in the overbought zone. Major Support Levels – $28,000, followed by $27,700. Major Resistance Levels – $28,320, $28,500, and $29,200.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>Bitcoin price is up 4% and trading above $28,000. BTC must clear the $28,500 resistance zone to continue higher in the near term.</em></p>
<ul>
<li>Bitcoin is gaining pace above the $27,500 and $27,800 resistance levels.</li>
<li>The price is trading above $28,000 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average.</li>
<li>There is a key bullish trend line forming with support near $27,700 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could correct lower but the bulls might be active near $27,700 and $27,500.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Bitcoin Price Recovers Over 4%</h2>
<p>Bitcoin price managed to stay above the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-struggles-26650/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">$26,000 support zone</a>. BTC formed a base and started a recovery wave above the $27,000 resistance.</p>
<p>There was a steady increase once the price cleared the $27,500 resistance zone. It is up over 4% and there was a break above the $28,000 resistance. A high is formed near $28,450 and the price is now consolidating gains. It is trading near the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $27,143 swing low to the $28,450 high.</p>
<p>Bitcoin price is now trading above $28,000 and the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-bears-aim-25000/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">100 hourly Simple moving average</a>. There is also a key bullish trend line forming with support near $27,700 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair.</p>
<p>Immediate resistance on the upside is near the $28,320 level. The next major resistance is near the $28,500 level. A close above the $28,500 resistance zone might send the price toward the $29,200 resistance zone.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-535407" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-20.png" alt="Bitcoin Price" width="1834" height="845" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-20.png 1834w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-20-460x212.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-20-860x396.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-20-768x354.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-20-1536x708.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-20-750x346.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-20-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1834px) 100vw, 1834px"/></p>
<p>Source: <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BTCUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">BTCUSD on TradingView.com</a></p>
<p>The next key resistance is near $29,500, above which the price might rise toward the $30,000 resistance. Any more gains might send the price toward the $31,200 resistance level.</p>
<h2>Are Dips Limited in BTC?</h2>
<p>If Bitcoin’s price fails to clear the $28,500 resistance, it could start a downside correction. Immediate support on the downside is near the $28,000 level.</p>
<p>The next major support is near the $27,700 zone or the 50% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $27,143 swing low to the $28,450 high, below which the price might test the $27,500 support. Any more losses might take Bitcoin toward the $27,200 level in the near term.</p>
<p>Technical indicators:</p>
<p>Hourly MACD – The MACD is now losing pace in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>Hourly RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BTC/USD is in the overbought zone.</p>
<p>Major Support Levels – $28,000, followed by $27,700.</p>
<p>Major Resistance Levels – $28,320, $28,500, and $29,200.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/Depositphotos_180246254_s-2019-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Monaco, NFTs, And Formula 1: Reasons Polygon Is Bullish</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/nft/monaco-nfts-and-formula-1-reasons-polygon-is-bullish/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dalmas Ngetich]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 11:00:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[NFT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Formula 1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MATIC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[monaco]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NFTs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Platinium Group]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Polygon]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=535357</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Platinium Group, the premier ticket provider for Grand Prix events, has joined forces with an NFT marketplace, Elemint; and a web3 company, Bary, to release a new NFT ticketing system on Polygon that debuted this weekend at the Formula 1 event in Monaco. Tickets for the Monaco Grand Prix, which is ongoing and started on Friday, May 26, are being minted on Polygon, the Ethereum sidechain that enables fast processing speeds and high throughput. Polygon Labs&#8217; head of global business development, Urvit Goel, emphasized that the platform&#8217;s use of Ethereum&#8217;s robust security and NFTs&#8217; unfalsifiable uniqueness improves ticket authenticity, reduces the likelihood of counterfeiting, and gives fans a digital memento they can keep forever. The ticketing platform combines the robust security of Ethereum with the forge-proof uniqueness of NFTs to enhance ticket authenticity and prevent counterfeiting while providing fans with lasting digital mementos. Polygon Rally In response to this deal, MATIC prices rallied on May 26, soaring to as high as $0.97. Even though prices have since retracted, the upswing momentum remains and the token appears to be bottoming up. Related Reading: Shiba Inu Burn Rate Surges 1500% In 24 Hours, Yet Price Continues To Struggle In Red Whether this event will trigger more gains in the sessions ahead is yet to be seen. However, the spike that lifted MATIC above key resistance levels on May 26 may be the foundation for another rally going forward. Currently, MATIC is down 40% from February 2023 highs and remains under pressure, trailing other assets, including BTC. Besides price action, the release of the new ticketing platform on Polygon is when NFTs are finding new uses after a concerning contraction in 2022. Bertrand Labays, Platinum Group&#8217;s Chief Operating Officer, said the integration of blockchain in their operations is “imperative” and that NFTs would play a role in sports. NFT’s Rising Popularity Last year, NFTs trading volumes contracted, following the sharp retracement of asset prices. While MATIC recovered in Q1 2023, gains have not been strong in Q2 2023. However, the platform is positioning itself as a go-to portal for minting NFTs. Specifically, users are finding Polygon’s low-fees and high scalability an advantage. Besides, Polygon’s EVM compatibility means issuers can move their assets to Ethereum. Still, whether the recent announcement from Platinum will draw more interest remains to be seen. Related Reading: Sui (SUI) Continues Downward Trend As Bears Maintain Control Recently, Formula 1 also partnered with Tezos, a self-amending layer-1 blockchain, to launch a new NFT ticketing system. In this arrangement, Formula 1 fans would easily purchase tickets that exist as NFTs and stored permanently on the Polygon and Ethereum competitor. Beyond that, the NFL Players Association (NFLPA) joined hands with Chiliz to create a new NFT ticketing platform on Socios.com for NFL fans to purchase tickets. -Featured Image From Canva, Chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Platinium Group, the premier ticket provider for Grand Prix events, has joined forces with an NFT marketplace, Elemint; and a web3 company, Bary, to release a new NFT ticketing system on Polygon that debuted this weekend at the Formula 1 event in Monaco.</p>
<p>Tickets for the Monaco Grand Prix, which is ongoing and started on Friday, May 26, are being minted on Polygon, the Ethereum sidechain that enables fast processing speeds and high throughput.</p>
<p>Polygon Labs&#8217; head of global business development, Urvit Goel, <a href="https://twitter.com/0xPolygonLabs/status/1662114726866743296" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">emphasized</a> that the platform&#8217;s use of Ethereum&#8217;s robust security and NFTs&#8217; unfalsifiable uniqueness improves ticket authenticity, reduces the likelihood of counterfeiting, and gives fans a digital memento they can keep forever.</p>
<blockquote><p>The ticketing platform combines the robust security of Ethereum with the forge-proof uniqueness of NFTs to enhance ticket authenticity and prevent counterfeiting while providing fans with lasting digital mementos.</p></blockquote>
<h2><b>Polygon Rally</b></h2>
<p>In response to this deal, MATIC prices rallied on May 26, soaring to as high as $0.97. Even though prices have since retracted, the upswing momentum remains and the token appears to be bottoming up.</p>

<p>Whether this event will trigger more gains in the sessions ahead is yet to be seen. However, the spike that lifted MATIC above key resistance levels on May 26 may be the foundation for another rally going forward.</p>
<p>Currently, MATIC is down 40% from February 2023 highs and remains under pressure, trailing other assets, including BTC.</p>
<a href="https://www.tradingview.com/x/YQOrxVbC/" rel="nofollow"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/YQOrxVbC/" alt="MATIC Price On May 28| Source: MATICUSDT On Binance, TradingView" width="1225" height="595"/></a>
<p>Besides price action, the release of the new ticketing platform on Polygon is when NFTs are finding new uses after a concerning contraction in 2022.</p>
<p>Bertrand Labays, Platinum Group&#8217;s Chief Operating Officer, said the integration of blockchain in their operations is “imperative” and that NFTs would play a role in sports.</p>
<h2><b>NFT’s Rising Popularity</b></h2>
<p>Last year, NFTs trading volumes contracted, following the sharp retracement of asset prices. While MATIC recovered in Q1 2023, gains have not been strong in Q2 2023. However, the platform is positioning itself as a go-to portal for minting NFTs.</p>
<p>Specifically, users are finding Polygon’s low-fees and high scalability an advantage. Besides, Polygon’s EVM compatibility means issuers can move their assets to Ethereum.</p>
<p>Still, whether the recent announcement from Platinum will draw more interest remains to be seen.</p>

<p>Recently, Formula 1 also partnered with Tezos, a self-amending layer-1 blockchain, to launch a new NFT ticketing system. In this arrangement, Formula 1 fans would easily purchase tickets that exist as NFTs and stored permanently on the Polygon and Ethereum competitor.</p>
<p>Beyond that, the NFL Players Association (NFLPA) joined hands with Chiliz to create a new NFT ticketing platform on Socios.com for NFL fans to purchase tickets.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Polygon-MATIC-Price-460x260.jpg" width="460" height="260" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>European Commission To Present Regulatory Framework For Digital Euro In June</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/token/european-commission-to-present-regulatory-framework-for-digital-euro-in-june/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Olowoporoku Adeniyi]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 10:53:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Token]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CBDC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CBDCs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Digital Euro]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=535354</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Fabio Panetta, a member of the Executive Committee of the European Central Bank (ECB), recently announced that the European Commission would be presenting a legislative proposal for the digital euro in June. He further stated that the next steps would be decided in October. Digital Euro Regulatory Framework In Progress In an interview with the ECB&#8217;s official site, Panetta confirmed that the eurozone bank is in regular contact with the European Commission to establish a regulatory framework for the digital euro. The digital euro is set to become the official central bank digital currency (CBDC) for the 27 countries in the European Union. Panetta stated, &#8220;We are studying the design of the digital euro, its distribution, and its impact on the financial sector.&#8221; He also mentioned that the proposal expected to be presented in June would receive a response from the Governing Council of the ECB in October. Related Reading: Sui (SUI) Continues Downward Trend As Bears Maintain Control The Governing Council will then decide whether to initiate a preparation phase to develop and test the digital euro. According to Panetta, the European CBDC testing phase could last two to three years. If everything progresses smoothly and both the Governing Council of the ECB and the legislators of the European Parliament approve the proposal, the digital euro could be launched in approximately three to four years, estimated Panetta. Will The Digital Euro Receive Significant Adoption? During the interview, Panetta was asked about the benefits and potential risks of using the digital euro. In response, he emphasized the need to provide citizens with a risk-free digital means of payment that can be used freely throughout the euro area. Panetta highlighted that such a solution currently does not exist, pointing out that the card payment market is dominated by non-European companies, specifically referring to Visa and Mastercard. He stated that this situation would be unthinkable in the United States and expressed concern about companies selling users&#8217; personal data. Related Reading: Shiba Inu Burn Rate Surges 1500% In 24 Hours, Yet Price Continues To Struggle In Red Panetta also emphasized the importance of central bank money remaining at the financial system&#8217;s core. The increasing adoption of cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin (BTC) raises concerns for entities like the ECB. Addressing concerns about privacy, Panetta clarified that the ECB would not have access to personal data. Financial intermediaries will handle the distribution of the digital euro, and a balance must be found between ensuring confidentiality and combating money laundering and terrorist financing. Panetta noted that the responsibility of finding this balance lies with the legislators. CBDCs On The Rise  Central Bank Digital Currencies (CBDCs) are indeed on the rise as countries worldwide explore the potential of digital currencies issued and regulated by central banks. Countries like the Bahamas and Nigeria have already launched their digital currencies, while China and Japan are in advanced pilot stages. -Featured image from iStock.com, chart from Tradingview.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Fabio Panetta, a member of the Executive Committee of the European Central Bank (ECB), recently announced that the European Commission would be presenting a legislative proposal for the digital euro in June. He further stated that the next steps would be decided in October.</p>
<h2><strong>Digital Euro Regulatory Framework In Progress</strong></h2>
<p>In an <a href="https://www.ecb.europa.eu/press/inter/date/2023/html/ecb.in230524~c2d729b46a.en.html" rel="nofollow">interview</a> with the ECB&#8217;s official site, Panetta confirmed that the eurozone bank is in regular contact with the European Commission to establish a regulatory framework for the digital euro. The digital euro is set to become the official central bank digital currency (CBDC) for the 27 countries in the European Union.</p>
<p>Panetta stated, &#8220;We are studying the design of the digital euro, its distribution, and its impact on the financial sector.&#8221; He also mentioned that the proposal expected to be presented in June would receive a response from the Governing Council of the ECB in October.</p>
<p><b>Related Reading</b>: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/altcoin/sui-sui-continues-downward-trend-as-bears-maintain-control/?swcfpc=1">Sui (SUI) Continues Downward Trend As Bears Maintain Control</a></p>
<p>The Governing Council will then decide whether to initiate a preparation phase to develop and test the digital euro. According to Panetta, the European CBDC testing phase could last two to three years.</p>
<p>If everything progresses smoothly and both the Governing Council of the ECB and the legislators of the European Parliament approve the proposal, the digital euro could be launched in approximately three to four years, estimated Panetta.</p>
<h2><strong>Will The Digital Euro Receive Significant Adoption?</strong></h2>
<p>During the interview, Panetta was asked about the benefits and potential risks of using the digital euro. In response, he emphasized the need to provide citizens with a risk-free digital means of payment that can be used freely throughout the euro area.</p>
<p>Panetta highlighted that such a solution currently does not exist, pointing out that the card payment market is dominated by non-European companies, specifically referring to Visa and Mastercard. He stated that this situation would be unthinkable in the United States and expressed concern about companies selling users&#8217; personal data.</p>
<p><b>Related Reading</b>: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/shiba-inu-burn-rate-surges-price-continues-in-red/?swcfpc=1">Shiba Inu Burn Rate Surges 1500% In 24 Hours, Yet Price Continues To Struggle In Red</a></p>
<p>Panetta also emphasized the importance of central bank money remaining at the financial system&#8217;s core. The increasing adoption of cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin (BTC) raises concerns for entities like the ECB.</p>
<p>Addressing concerns about privacy, Panetta clarified that the ECB would not have access to personal data. Financial intermediaries will handle the distribution of the digital euro, and a balance must be found between ensuring confidentiality and combating money laundering and terrorist financing. Panetta noted that the responsibility of finding this balance lies with the legislators.</p>
<strong>CBDCs On The Rise </strong>
<p>Central Bank Digital Currencies (CBDCs) are indeed on the rise as countries worldwide explore the potential of digital currencies issued and regulated by central banks. Countries like the Bahamas and Nigeria have already launched their digital currencies, while China and Japan are in advanced pilot stages.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-535367 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSD_2023-05-28_11-39-11-860x432.png" alt="Bitcoin is trading at around $27,200: source @Tradingview" width="860" height="432" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSD_2023-05-28_11-39-11-860x432.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSD_2023-05-28_11-39-11-460x231.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSD_2023-05-28_11-39-11-768x386.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSD_2023-05-28_11-39-11-360x180.png 360w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSD_2023-05-28_11-39-11-750x377.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSD_2023-05-28_11-39-11-1140x573.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSD_2023-05-28_11-39-11.png 1478w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/>
<p><em>-Featured image from iStock.com, chart from Tradingview.com</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Digital-Euro-1-460x259.jpg" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sui (SUI) Continues Downward Trend As Bears Maintain Control</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/altcoin/sui-sui-continues-downward-trend-as-bears-maintain-control/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Olowoporoku Adeniyi]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 09:50:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SUI]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SUI price analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=535339</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The crypto market once again experienced a sell-off this week, leading to a plunge in the price of many crypto assets. The impact of this market downturn is not limited to Bitcoin alone, as it has affected various cryptocurrencies, including Sui (SUI), a Layer 1 smart contract platform. Sui has witnessed a significant decline of 15% in its value over the past seven days, reflecting the broader negative sentiment prevailing in the market. Sui Dips Below $1 Support Levels SUI experienced a significant setback this week, breaching its crucial support level at $1. This support had been maintained since early May, providing stability for the token during that period. However, after enduring two weeks of downward-sloping resistance from above, SUI finally succumbed to selling pressure. Related Reading: Shiba Inu Burn Rate Surges 1500% In 24 Hours, Yet Price Continues To Struggle In Red The token&#8217;s decline reached a low point of $0.95 on Wednesday, marking an all-time low for SUI since its launch at the beginning of the month. This sharp drop highlights the prevailing bearish sentiment surrounding the token and its challenges in the current market conditions. Technical Indicators Point To Potential Bearish Path Sui, a layer 1 smart contract platform, distinguishes itself with its unique programming language called &#8216;Move.&#8217; Developed by the lead executives of Meta&#8217;s now-defunct Diem stablecoin project, Sui aims to address common pain points of first-generation blockchains, such as scalability and programmability. Despite its innovative approach, Sui has struggled to generate substantial gains since its inception in the trading market. In the short term, the coin may continue to experience lower lows. According to technical analysis on TradingView, the current conditions indicate that asset selling might be prudent. Seven of the 11 daily technical indicators are signaling a &#8216;strong sell,&#8217; with no indicators displaying buy signals. Related Reading: Aptos Hackathon, Partnerships Set APT Bulls Up For A Strong Run Additionally, the relative strength index (RSI) for SUI is currently hovering slightly above 40. With the RSI above 40, it suggests that there is a moderate level of buying pressure, but the overall sentiment remains uncertain. To counteract this bearish trend, Sui would need to reclaim the $1.05 level as support, which could provide a foothold for potential recovery. However, if Bitcoin fails to maintain its support at $26,000, Sui will likely face further downward pressure, potentially sinking as low as $0.90. Given the current market conditions and technical indicators, investors and traders should exercise caution and closely monitor Sui&#8217;s performance. Evaluating factors such as market sentiment, trading volume, and overall market dynamics will be crucial in determining the future trajectory of Sui and whether it can reverse its bearish trend. At press time, SUI price was $0.987 $ with a 24-hour trading volume of $89,278,135 USD. -Featured image from iStock, charts from CoinMarket and TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The crypto market once again experienced a sell-off this week, leading to a plunge in the price of many crypto assets. The impact of this market downturn is not limited to Bitcoin alone, as it has affected various cryptocurrencies, including Sui (SUI), a Layer 1 smart contract platform. Sui has witnessed a significant decline of 15% in its value over the past seven days, reflecting the broader negative sentiment prevailing in the market.</p>
<h2><strong>Sui Dips Below $1 Support Levels</strong></h2>
<p>SUI experienced a significant setback this week, breaching its crucial support level at $1. This support had been maintained since early May, providing stability for the token during that period. However, after enduring two weeks of downward-sloping resistance from above, SUI finally succumbed to selling pressure.</p>
<p><strong>Related Reading</strong>: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/shiba-inu-burn-rate-surges-price-continues-in-red/?swcfpc=1">Shiba Inu Burn Rate Surges 1500% In 24 Hours, Yet Price Continues To Struggle In Red</a></p>
<p>The token&#8217;s decline reached a low point of $0.95 on Wednesday, marking an all-time low for SUI since its launch at the beginning of the month. This sharp drop highlights the prevailing bearish sentiment surrounding the token and its challenges in the current market conditions.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium wp-image-535340" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image1-3-460x278.png" alt="Sui experienced a slight correction this week: source @Coinmarketcap" width="460" height="278" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image1-3-460x278.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image1-3-768x464.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image1-3-750x453.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image1-3.png 850w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px"/>
<h2><strong>Technical Indicators Point To Potential Bearish Path</strong></h2>
<p>Sui, a layer 1 smart contract platform, distinguishes itself with its unique programming language called &#8216;Move.&#8217; Developed by the lead executives of Meta&#8217;s now-defunct Diem stablecoin project, Sui aims to address common pain points of first-generation blockchains, such as scalability and programmability.</p>
<p>Despite its innovative approach, Sui has struggled to generate substantial gains since its inception in the trading market. In the short term, the coin may continue to experience lower lows. According to technical <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/chart/rbyZ3E3v/" rel="nofollow">analysis on TradingView</a>, the current conditions indicate that asset selling might be prudent. Seven of the 11 daily technical indicators are signaling a &#8216;strong sell,&#8217; with no indicators displaying buy signals.</p>
<p><strong>Related Reading: </strong><a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/aptos-apt/aptos-hackathon-partnerships-set-apt-bulls-up-for-a-strong-run/">Aptos Hackathon, Partnerships Set APT Bulls Up For A Strong Run</a></p>
<p>Additionally, the relative strength index (RSI) for SUI is currently hovering slightly above 40. With the RSI above 40, it suggests that there is a moderate level of buying pressure, but the overall sentiment remains uncertain.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium wp-image-535341" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image2-3-460x254.png" alt="Sui is trading around the $1 mark amid bearish sentiments: source @tradingview" width="460" height="254" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image2-3-460x254.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image2-3-860x474.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image2-3-768x424.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image2-3-750x414.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image2-3.png 1079w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px"/>
<p>To counteract this bearish trend, Sui would need to reclaim the $1.05 level as support, which could provide a foothold for potential recovery. However, if Bitcoin fails to maintain its support at $26,000, Sui will likely face further downward pressure, potentially sinking as low as $0.90.</p>
<p>Given the current market conditions and technical indicators, investors and traders should exercise caution and closely monitor Sui&#8217;s performance. Evaluating factors such as market sentiment, trading volume, and overall market dynamics will be crucial in determining the future trajectory of Sui and whether it can reverse its bearish trend. At press time, SUI price was $0.987 $ with a 24-hour trading volume of $89,278,135 USD.</p>
<p><em>-Featured image from iStock, charts from CoinMarket and TradingView.com</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/iStock-1385861326-1-460x248.jpg" width="460" height="248" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Shiba Inu Burn Rate Surges 1500% In 24 Hours, Yet Price Continues To Struggle In Red</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/shiba-inu-burn-rate-surges-price-continues-in-red/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Edyme]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 07:50:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Shiba Inu]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[meme coin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIB]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Token]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=529545</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[While Shiba Inu (SHIB) token appears to be getting rivaled by another currently hyped meme coin called PEPE, the latest update shows SHIB still has a strong community devoted to its growth.  In the last 24 hours, the SHIB community continues to fulfill its burning commitment and surged SHIB’s burn rate by more than 1500%. However, despite the surge in burn rate, SHIB has continued to struggle in the red.  Interestingly, the burn rate surge was executed via a single wallet burning 246.7M SHIB tokens. Related Reading: Shiba Inu Community Destroys 3.26 Billion SHIB in April Amid Price Decline Shiba Inu Burn Rate Surges According to data from Etherscan.io, a wallet tagged &#8220;cultpunks.eth&#8221; has burned a staggering 246.74 million SHIB in a single transaction executed about four hours ago.  In the past day, the overall Shiba Inu burn rate has skyrocketed by 1549.47%, a result of the recent move made by &#8220;cultpunks.eth.&#8221; This marks the second time in the past 30 days that this wallet has burned a significant amount of SHIB. The first instance was on April 15th, when the wallet burned a staggering 230,799,740 (230.79M) SHIB in one transaction. The CultPunks team has committed to utilizing a portion of their raised funds upon sellout to burn SHIB tokens. In addition to this, they have also dedicated 1% of their funds to the ShytoshiKusama&#8217;s fund, which aims to empower women in blockchain, and 2% to the buyback and burn of CULT tokens. The CultPunks is a set of 10,000 exclusive and randomly produced NFTs that were launched through a partnership with Soupsea, an NFT marketplace on Modulus. These NFTs were created on April 15th, 2023, and have become increasingly popular among NFT enthusiasts. Despite the increase in the burn rate, the SHIB token price continues to struggle, and the cryptocurrency remains in the red. This is a significant contrast to the price rally the token experienced a few weeks ago. Related Reading: Here’s What PEPE And SHIB Have In Common, But Can It Catch Up To Shiba Inu? Price Action: Shiba Inu Downtrend The SHIB token price has been in a downtrend in the past few days. With the meme coin struggling to hold above key support levels. SHIB is currently trading at $0.00000996, down 12.8% over the past two weeks. The token has a market capitalization of $5.8 billion, making it the 16th largest cryptocurrency by market cap. The downtrend in the SHIB token price can be attributed to the overall bearish sentiment in the cryptocurrency market. Bitcoin, the leading cryptocurrency by market cap, has been in a downtrend, which has negatively impacted the prices of other cryptocurrencies, including SHIB.  Furthermore, the recent increase in the SHIB burn rate is yet to have a significant impact on the token price. However, with more significant tokens being burnt over time, SHIB’s price could get impacted hugely and record new highs in the long run. &#160; Featured image from Unsplash, Chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>While Shiba Inu (SHIB) token appears to be getting rivaled by another currently hyped meme coin called <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/crypto/heres-what-pepe-and-shiba-inu-have-in-common/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">PEPE</a>, the latest update shows SHIB still has a strong community devoted to its growth. </p>
<p>In the last 24 hours, the SHIB community <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/shiba-inu-community-destroys-3-26-billion-shib-in-april/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">continues to fulfill its burning commitment</a> and surged SHIB’s burn rate by more than 1500%. However, despite the surge in burn rate, SHIB has continued to struggle in the red. </p>
<p>Interestingly, the burn rate surge was executed via a single wallet burning 246.7M SHIB tokens.</p>

<h2>Shiba Inu Burn Rate Surges</h2>
<p>According to <a href="https://etherscan.io/tx/0x04f6e17b6f77fa150b1b2e8d643a9aa8a494c6ab274578cdea7d29285365c1e8" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">data</a> from Etherscan.io, a wallet tagged &#8220;cultpunks.eth&#8221; has burned a staggering 246.74 million SHIB in a single transaction executed about four hours ago. </p>
<p>In the past day, the overall Shiba Inu burn rate has <a href="https://www.shibburn.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">skyrocketed by 1549.47%</a>, a result of the recent move made by &#8220;cultpunks.eth.&#8221; This marks the second time in the past 30 days that this wallet has burned a significant amount of SHIB. The first instance was on April 15th, when the wallet burned a staggering 230,799,740 (230.79M) SHIB in one transaction.</p>
<p>The CultPunks team has committed to utilizing a portion of their raised funds upon sellout to burn SHIB tokens. In addition to this, they have also dedicated 1% of their funds to the ShytoshiKusama&#8217;s fund, which aims to empower women in blockchain, and 2% to the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/shiba-inu-whales-sell-billions/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">buyback</a> and burn of CULT tokens.</p>
<p>The CultPunks is a set of 10,000 exclusive and randomly produced NFTs that were launched through a partnership with Soupsea, an NFT marketplace on Modulus. These NFTs were created on April 15th, 2023, and have become increasingly popular among NFT enthusiasts.</p>
<p>Despite the increase in the burn rate, the SHIB token price continues to struggle, and the cryptocurrency remains in the red. This is a significant contrast to the price rally the token experienced a few weeks ago.</p>

<h2>Price Action: Shiba Inu Downtrend</h2>
<p>The SHIB token price has been in a downtrend in the past few days. With the meme coin struggling to hold above key support levels. SHIB is currently trading at $0.00000996, down 12.8% over the past two weeks. The token has a market capitalization of $5.8 billion, making it the 16th largest cryptocurrency by market cap.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/elKLrxbP/" alt="Shiba Inu (SHIB) price chart on TradingView" width="2768" height="1556"/>
<p>The downtrend in the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/shiba-inu-price-sluggish-is-it-a-good-time-to-invest-or-cut-losses/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">SHIB token price</a> can be attributed to the overall bearish sentiment in the cryptocurrency market. Bitcoin, the leading cryptocurrency by market cap, has been in a downtrend, which has negatively impacted the prices of other cryptocurrencies, including SHIB. </p>
<p>Furthermore, the recent increase in the SHIB burn rate is yet to have a significant impact on the token price. However, with more significant tokens being burnt over time, SHIB’s price could get impacted hugely and <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/shiba-inu-lead-dev-touts-go-mode-price-follow/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">record new highs</a> in the long run.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Featured image from Unsplash, Chart from TradingView</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Shiba-Inu-460x329.jpeg" width="460" height="329" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>NEO Token Surges 10% In The Past 24 Hours &#8211; Here’s Why</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/neo-price/neo-token-surges-10-in-the-past-24-hours-heres-why/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Olowoporoku Adeniyi]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 06:55:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[NEO]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[neo]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[neo analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[neo at resistance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=535348</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[NEO emerged as the largest gainer among the top 100 cryptocurrencies by market cap in the past 24 hours. At the time of writing, NEO has been trading at $10.75 while managing $106.2 million in volume, according to Coinmarketcap. The 59th largest crypto, with a market cap of $760.2 million, is also one of the top-performing coins in the past week, with more than 14% gains. NEO Experiences A Resurgence In 2023 Much like the rest of the crypto market, after the brutal 2022, NEO price surged in value in 2023 to nearly $15 towards the end of February, only to drop under $10 in the second week of March. Over the next month, the price of NEO went upwards before topping at just above $13.50. And last week, NEO went back to around $9 before it started gaining traction this week. While the exact reasons behind NEO&#8217;s current surge are not clear, it is worth considering the recent developments in the project. NEO has recently made a significant foray into the field of artificial intelligence (AI). As AI fever has gone mainstream and permeated the crypto industry, NEO&#8217;s integration of AI has sparked excitement and possibilities.  Related Reading: Kava (KAVA) Price Rallies 10% In 7 Days – Here’s Why This convergence of two rapidly evolving fields has the potential to introduce advancements in algorithmic trading, predictive models, forecasting tools, and enhanced security and fraud detection. However, it is worth noting that many crypto projects are leveraging the AI trend without substantial implementation or genuine value, which is a trend observed across various sectors due to the current hype surrounding AI technologies. In the case of NEO, the project recently announced the winners of its NeoChat ChatGPT launch competition. This investment in AI is likely one of the contributing factors to the recent spike in NEO&#8217;s price. While up 61% in 2023 so far, NEO is still down a whopping 95% from its all-time high (ATH) of almost $200 that was hit in Jan. 2018. NEO Price Analysis  The latest NEO price analysis shows the dominance of green candlesticks with slight resistance from the red ones. Yet, the latest chart shows bullish momentum, with the price approaching $10.88 for the second day today. The average of Bollinger bands is set at $10.07 at the time of writing. Related Reading: Shiba Inu Burn Rate Surges 1500% In 24 Hours, Yet Price Continues To Struggle In Red The short-term trend line and SMA 20 curve are upward, indicating a bullish uphold. The moving average indicator displays a value of $10.83, the highest value achieved in the past 24 hours. From the given NEO price analysis, the bulls are taking over the cryptocurrency with a steep rise in price. This rise may take the current price levels and reach a new high above the $10.90 resistance. The RSI score detected from the hourly chart is 71, which has crossed the overbought threshold set for the coin value. This affirms the upcoming rise in the price of the support level also continues to increase. The resistance level at $11.29 can be challenged if the buying momentum remains persistent. -Featured image from iStcok.com, charts from Coingecko and Tradingview]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NEO emerged as the largest gainer among the top 100 cryptocurrencies by market cap in the past 24 hours. At the time of writing, NEO has been trading at $10.75 while managing $106.2 million in volume, according to <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/neo/" rel="nofollow">Coinmarketcap</a>.</p>
<p>The 59th largest crypto, with a market cap of $760.2 million, is also one of the top-performing coins in the past week, with more than 14% gains.</p>
<h2><strong>NEO Experiences A Resurgence In 2023</strong></h2>
<p>Much like the rest of the crypto market, after the brutal 2022, NEO price surged in value in 2023 to nearly $15 towards the end of February, only to drop under $10 in the second week of March. Over the next month, the price of NEO went upwards before topping at just above $13.50. And last week, NEO went back to around $9 before it started gaining traction this week.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-535350 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Screenshot_133.png" alt="NEO has experienced a positive rise in the past 7 days: source @Coingecko" width="1041" height="122" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Screenshot_133.png 1041w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Screenshot_133-460x54.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Screenshot_133-860x101.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Screenshot_133-768x90.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Screenshot_133-750x88.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 1041px) 100vw, 1041px"/>
<p>While the exact reasons behind NEO&#8217;s current surge are not clear, it is worth considering the recent developments in the project. NEO has recently made a significant foray into the field of artificial intelligence (AI). As AI fever has gone mainstream and permeated the crypto industry, NEO&#8217;s integration of AI has sparked excitement and possibilities. </p>
<p><b>Related Reading</b>: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/altcoin/kava-kava-price-rallies-10-in-7-days-heres-why/">Kava (KAVA) Price Rallies 10% In 7 Days – Here’s Why</a></p>
<p>This convergence of two rapidly evolving fields has the potential to introduce advancements in algorithmic trading, predictive models, forecasting tools, and enhanced security and fraud detection. However, it is worth noting that many crypto projects are leveraging the AI trend without substantial implementation or genuine value, which is a trend observed across various sectors due to the current hype surrounding AI technologies.</p>
<p>In the case of NEO, the project recently announced the winners of its NeoChat ChatGPT launch competition. This investment in AI is likely one of the contributing factors to the recent spike in NEO&#8217;s price.</p>
<p>While up 61% in 2023 so far, NEO is still down a whopping 95% from its all-time high (ATH) of almost $200 that was hit in Jan. 2018.</p>
<h2><strong>NEO Price Analysis </strong></h2>
<p>The latest NEO price analysis shows the dominance of green candlesticks with slight resistance from the red ones. Yet, the latest chart shows bullish momentum, with the price approaching $10.88 for the second day today. The average of Bollinger bands is set at $10.07 at the time of writing.</p>
<p><b>Related Reading</b>: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/shiba-inu-burn-rate-surges-price-continues-in-red/?swcfpc=1">Shiba Inu Burn Rate Surges 1500% In 24 Hours, Yet Price Continues To Struggle In Red</a></p>
<p>The short-term trend line and SMA 20 curve are upward, indicating a bullish uphold. The moving average indicator displays a value of $10.83, the highest value achieved in the past 24 hours.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium wp-image-535349" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/NEOUSD_2023-05-28_10-51-34-460x231.png" alt="Neo charts point to a bullish trend: source @Tradingview" width="460" height="231" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/NEOUSD_2023-05-28_10-51-34-460x231.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/NEOUSD_2023-05-28_10-51-34-860x432.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/NEOUSD_2023-05-28_10-51-34-768x386.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/NEOUSD_2023-05-28_10-51-34-360x180.png 360w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/NEOUSD_2023-05-28_10-51-34-750x377.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/NEOUSD_2023-05-28_10-51-34-1140x573.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/NEOUSD_2023-05-28_10-51-34.png 1479w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px"/>
<p>From the given NEO price analysis, the bulls are taking over the cryptocurrency with a steep rise in price. This rise may take the current price levels and reach a new high above the $10.90 resistance. The RSI score detected from the hourly chart is 71, which has crossed the overbought threshold set for the coin value.</p>
<p>This affirms the upcoming rise in the price of the support level also continues to increase. The resistance level at $11.29 can be challenged if the buying momentum remains persistent.</p>
<p><em>-Featured image from iStcok.com, charts from Coingecko and Tradingview</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/a-147-460x263.png" width="460" height="263" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Aptos Hackathon, Partnerships Set APT Bulls Up For A Strong Run</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/aptos-apt/aptos-hackathon-partnerships-set-apt-bulls-up-for-a-strong-run/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 05:59:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Aptos (APT)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Aptos]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bull Market]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hack Holland]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[price analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=535312</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[At the time of writing, there are indications of a potential market recovery, at least the major coins like Bitcoin and Ethereum are posting decent gains. Aptos (APT) is one of the tokens that is expected to experience an increase in bullishness and price. Although APT’s gains are minuscule at 1.7% in the last 24 hours, the project&#8217;s partnerships and on-chain developments point to a somewhat rosy picture. APT price rose to $8.30 at the time of writing, contributing highly to this bullish momentum. Source: Coingecko Related Reading: Shiba Inu All Green Today – What’s The Energy Behind The Glow? Aptos Returns With Hack Holland  Crypto ecosystems use contests to support new projects that need funding. Aptos Hack returns with Hack Holland, an event to find the new wave of Web3 projects that will contribute to the industry’s growth. The Hack Holland hackathon, which takes place on June 5–7th, is set to engender the next wave of DeFi products and services on Aptos. The event will give away prizes in categories like NFTs, DeFi, public goods, and many more.  Ready to show off your skills and earn some serious rewards? 🏆💰 Aptos Hack Holland is your chance to hack game-changing Web3 ideas and win huge prizes. Step up to the challenge! Applications close May 29th ⤵️https://t.co/K6DGUNRUoi pic.twitter.com/BIpC7HDaP6 — Aptos (@Aptos_Network) May 27, 2023 More Projects In The Pipeline Along with the recent buzz Hack Holland produced is the upcoming second playtest of Metapixel’s Gran Saga: Unlimited. Metapixel is the Web3 arm of South Korean gaming company NPIXEL which entered the world of Web3 in November last year. If the playtest is successful, we may see more games built on the Aptos blockchain, further providing positivity in the long term.  Another exciting development is Quicknode’s announcement of its strategic partnership with Aptos in the realm of remote node infrastructure. This partnership is crucial for Aptos’ success as a robust blockchain infrastructure will ensure the dominance of the Aptos blockchain. Aptos joins the @QuickNode network to provide developers easy-to-use remote node infrastructure services &#8211; so devs can spend less time on node operations and more time on building and innovating. Learn more at https://t.co/fYorOhQFak. https://t.co/6gVy4dMaM5 — Aptos (@Aptos_Network) May 24, 2023 To onboard more developers on Aptos, Move launched a Developer Hub featuring tutorials and documents on how to get started building the Aptos blockchain using the Move developer language. This consolidation of resources should also have an effect on the amount of dApps the platform will have in the future.  APT total market currently at $1.6 billion on the weekend chart at TradingView.com Related Reading: Shiba Inu (SHIB) Price Slump Leaves Over 1 Million Wallets In The Red Zone At $8.30, Investors Have Room For Gains After reaching its all-time-high price back in January, APT has been in decline since then. However, this may change in the coming days or months. At the moment, the token is trading in a very tight range which contributes to the bullishness.  APT price performance. Source: Coingecko Meanwhile, investors and traders should defend the $7.5 support level if the market flips from bullish to bearish. Holding this support level will allow the bulls to target the $12 range in the medium to long term. If the momentum permits it, we might even see a return to $16 in the long run.  -Featured image from Asia Crypto Today]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>At the time of writing, there are indications of a potential market recovery, at least the major coins like Bitcoin and Ethereum are posting decent gains. Aptos (APT) is one of the tokens that is expected to experience an increase in bullishness and price.</p>
<p>Although APT’s gains are minuscule at 1.7% in the last 24 hours, the project&#8217;s partnerships and on-chain developments point to a somewhat rosy picture. <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/aptos" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">A</a>PT price rose to $8.30 at the time of writing, contributing highly to this bullish momentum.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-535317" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/a-144.png" alt="" width="1143" height="61" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/a-144.png 1143w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/a-144-460x25.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/a-144-860x46.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/a-144-768x41.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/a-144-1140x61.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/a-144-750x40.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 1143px) 100vw, 1143px"/></p>


<h2><strong>Aptos Returns With Hack Holland </strong></h2>
<p>Crypto ecosystems use contests to support new projects that need funding. Aptos Hack <a href="https://twitter.com/Aptos_Network/status/1662345390170214404?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">returns</a> with Hack Holland, an event to find the new wave of Web3 projects that will contribute to the industry’s growth. </p>
<p>The <a class="af mo" href="https://aptosfoundation.org/events/hack-holland-2023" target="_blank" rel="noopener ugc nofollow">Hack Holland hackathon</a>, which takes place on June 5–7th, is set to engender the next wave of DeFi products and services on Aptos. The event will give away prizes in categories like NFTs, DeFi, public goods, and many more. </p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Ready to show off your skills and earn some serious rewards? <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f3c6.png" alt="🏆" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f4b0.png" alt="💰" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /></p>
<p>Aptos Hack Holland is your chance to hack game-changing Web3 ideas and win huge prizes.</p>
<p>Step up to the challenge! Applications close May 29th <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2935.png" alt="⤵" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><a href="https://t.co/K6DGUNRUoi" rel="nofollow">https://t.co/K6DGUNRUoi</a> <a href="https://t.co/BIpC7HDaP6" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/BIpC7HDaP6</a></p>
<p>— Aptos (@Aptos_Network) <a href="https://twitter.com/Aptos_Network/status/1662345390170214404?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">May 27, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<h2><strong>More Projects In The Pipeline</strong></h2>
<p>Along with the recent buzz Hack Holland produced is the <a href="https://twitter.com/Aptos_Network/status/1662222059936837632?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">upcoming</a> second playtest of Metapixel’s Gran Saga: Unlimited. Metapixel is the Web3 arm of South Korean gaming company NPIXEL which <a href="https://metapixelblog.medium.com/metapixel-and-aptos-announce-strategic-partnership-9f287f23c180" rel="nofollow">entered</a> the world of Web3 in November last year. If the playtest is successful, we may see more games built on the Aptos blockchain, further providing positivity in the long term. </p>
<p>Another exciting development is Quicknode’s <a href="https://twitter.com/Aptos_Network/status/1661403652278587393?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">announcement</a> of its strategic partnership with Aptos in the realm of remote node infrastructure. This partnership is crucial for Aptos’ success as a robust blockchain infrastructure will ensure the dominance of the Aptos blockchain.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Aptos joins the <a href="https://twitter.com/QuickNode?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">@QuickNode</a> network to provide developers easy-to-use remote node infrastructure services &#8211; so devs can spend less time on node operations and more time on building and innovating.</p>
<p>Learn more at <a href="https://t.co/fYorOhQFak" rel="nofollow">https://t.co/fYorOhQFak</a>. <a href="https://t.co/6gVy4dMaM5" rel="nofollow">https://t.co/6gVy4dMaM5</a></p>
<p>— Aptos (@Aptos_Network) <a href="https://twitter.com/Aptos_Network/status/1661403652278587393?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">May 24, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p>To onboard more developers on Aptos, Move <a href="https://twitter.com/MoveBuilders/status/1662107430225051648?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">launched</a> a Developer Hub featuring tutorials and documents on how to get started building the Aptos blockchain using the Move developer language. This consolidation of resources should also have an effect on the amount of dApps the platform will have in the future. </p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/OLqZXvVV/" width="2047" height="979"/></p>


<strong>At $8.30, Investors Have Room For Gains</strong>
<p>After reaching its all-time-high price back in January, APT has been in decline since then. However, this may change in the coming days or months. At the moment, the token is trading in a very tight range which contributes to the bullishness. </p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-535318" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/a-145.png" alt="" width="746" height="88" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/a-145.png 746w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/a-145-460x54.png 460w" sizes="(max-width: 746px) 100vw, 746px"/></p>

<p>Meanwhile, investors and traders should defend the $7.5 support level if the market flips from bullish to bearish. Holding this support level will allow the bulls to target the $12 range in the medium to long term. If the momentum permits it, we might even see a return to $16 in the long run. </p>
<p><em>-Featured image from Asia Crypto Today</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/a-146-460x236.png" width="460" height="236" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Kava (KAVA) Price Rallies 10% In 7 Days &#8211; Here&#8217;s Why</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/altcoin/kava-kava-price-rallies-10-in-7-days-heres-why/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Olowoporoku Adeniyi]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 02:20:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Kava]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Kava analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[kava price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=535272</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[KAVA, the native token associated with the Kava platform, has experienced a whirlwind week regarding its price swing. The token, which began the week trading around $1.03, surged to $1.23 on May 23, driven by positive news within its ecosystem.  However, the bull momentum was short-lived, with the token recently experiencing a significant price correction. Nevertheless, at the time of writing, KAVA is up 10% and is one of the top gainers in the crypto market within this period.  What’s Behind The Recent Spike In Kava? However, it is important to analyze the factors behind this rally to assess its sustainability. Cryptocurrencies are known for their price volatility, and sudden reversals are not uncommon. In the case of KAVA, the token experienced a swift downturn following the initial surge, raising concerns about the solidity of the upward movement.  Related Reading: Bullish Case For Litecoin Grows Stronger As LTC Halving Draws Close This pattern is often observed when a rapid rise lacks strong fundamental support, leading to a correction as the market adjusts itself. In terms of recent developments, it was reported that the Digital Asset Exchange Association (DAXA) in South Korea removed investment warnings on KAVA and WAVES, the latter being another digital asset associated with the Waves platform.  The warnings had been issued due to concerns about stablecoins linked to these assets, which were found to be &#8220;not normally linked to 1 dollar”. However, after a thorough review, DAXA determined that the risks associated with KAVA and WAVES had been resolved, allowing South Korean exchanges to resume deposit services for these tokens. This news likely contributed to the positive sentiment surrounding KAVA and may have played a role in the recent price rally. In addition, the launch of the Kava 13 mainnet and the introduction of GameFi (Game Finance) and non-fungible tokens (NFTs) to the Kava ecosystem have also contributed to the positive momentum for the KAVA token. These developments have attracted attention and interest from users, investors, and traders, potentially driving the token&#8217;s price higher. What’s Next For KAVA? The price surge experienced by KAVA stands out as an outlier within the broader context of the cryptocurrency market. Considering the overall outlook, such gains may not be sustainable, and a subsequent correction could erase the entirety of the upward movement. Related Reading: Upcoming Interest Rate Hikes Could Be The Next Big Challenge For Bitcoin, Here’s Why If the current levels near $1.20 fail to provide sufficient support, KAVA/USD might retreat towards the support level at $1.10 or even lower. However, on the other hand, if there is an overall uptick in the market sentiment or if there is fresh, positive news specific to KAVA, it could potentially lead to renewed buying interest and push the price toward a retest of the recent highs. At press time, KAVA sells at $1.134 per token with a slight 0.9% 24-hour increase. -Featured image from Kava.io, charts from tradingview.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>KAVA, the native token associated with the Kava platform, has experienced a whirlwind week regarding its price swing. The token, which began the week trading around $1.03, surged to $1.23 on May 23, driven by positive news within its ecosystem. </p>
<p>However, the bull momentum was short-lived, with the token recently experiencing a significant price correction. Nevertheless, at the time of writing, KAVA is up 10% and is one of the top gainers in the crypto market within this period. </p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium wp-image-535274" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/KAVAUSDT_2023-05-27_15-40-21-460x254.png" alt="Kava has experienced a significant price correction this week; source @tradingview" width="460" height="254" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/KAVAUSDT_2023-05-27_15-40-21-460x254.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/KAVAUSDT_2023-05-27_15-40-21-860x474.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/KAVAUSDT_2023-05-27_15-40-21-768x424.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/KAVAUSDT_2023-05-27_15-40-21-750x414.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/KAVAUSDT_2023-05-27_15-40-21-1140x629.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/KAVAUSDT_2023-05-27_15-40-21.png 1479w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px"/>
<h2>What’s Behind The Recent Spike In Kava?</h2>
<p>However, it is important to analyze the factors behind this rally to assess its sustainability. Cryptocurrencies are known for their price volatility, and sudden reversals are not uncommon. In the case of KAVA, the token experienced a swift downturn following the initial surge, raising concerns about the solidity of the upward movement. </p>
<p><b>Related Reading:</b> <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/ltc/bullish-case-for-litecoin-grows-stronger-as-ltc-halving-draws-close/">Bullish Case For Litecoin Grows Stronger As LTC Halving Draws Close</a></p>
<p>This pattern is often observed when a rapid rise lacks strong fundamental support, leading to a correction as the market adjusts itself. In terms of recent developments, it was reported that the Digital Asset Exchange Association (DAXA) in South Korea removed investment warnings on KAVA and WAVES, the latter being another digital asset associated with the Waves platform. </p>
<p>The warnings had been issued due to concerns about stablecoins linked to these assets, which were found to be &#8220;not normally linked to 1 dollar”. However, after a thorough review, DAXA determined that the risks associated with KAVA and WAVES had been resolved, allowing South Korean exchanges to resume deposit services for these tokens. This news likely contributed to the positive sentiment surrounding KAVA and may have played a role in the recent price rally.</p>
<p>In addition, the launch of the Kava 13 mainnet and the introduction of GameFi (Game Finance) and non-fungible tokens (NFTs) to the Kava ecosystem have also contributed to the positive momentum for the KAVA token. These developments have attracted attention and interest from users, investors, and traders, potentially driving the token&#8217;s price higher.</p>
<h2>What’s Next For KAVA?</h2>
<p>The price surge experienced by KAVA stands out as an outlier within the broader context of the cryptocurrency market. Considering the overall outlook, such gains may not be sustainable, and a subsequent correction could erase the entirety of the upward movement.</p>
<p><b>Related Reading:</b> <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/upcoming-interest-rate-hikes-could-be-the-next-big-challenge-for-bitcoin-heres-why/">Upcoming Interest Rate Hikes Could Be The Next Big Challenge For Bitcoin, Here’s Why</a></p>
<p>If the current levels near $1.20 fail to provide sufficient support, KAVA/USD might retreat towards the support level at $1.10 or even lower.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-535275 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/KAVAUSDT_2023-05-27_15-52-29-860x432.png" alt="Kava currently trading below the $1.20 resistance mark: source @tradingview" width="860" height="432" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/KAVAUSDT_2023-05-27_15-52-29-860x432.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/KAVAUSDT_2023-05-27_15-52-29-460x231.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/KAVAUSDT_2023-05-27_15-52-29-768x386.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/KAVAUSDT_2023-05-27_15-52-29-360x180.png 360w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/KAVAUSDT_2023-05-27_15-52-29-750x377.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/KAVAUSDT_2023-05-27_15-52-29-1140x573.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/KAVAUSDT_2023-05-27_15-52-29.png 1479w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/>
<p>However, on the other hand, if there is an overall uptick in the market sentiment or if there is fresh, positive news specific to KAVA, it could potentially lead to renewed buying interest and push the price toward a retest of the recent highs. At press time, KAVA sells at $1.134 per token with a slight 0.9% 24-hour increase.</p>
<p><em>-Featured image from Kava.io, charts from tradingview.com</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/kava-1140x641-1-460x259.jpg" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>XRP Revisits $0.47 &#8211; What Can Be Expected For Short-Term Price Movement?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/xrp-revisits-0-47-what-can-be-expected-for-short-term-price-movement/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[anushsamal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 01:35:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrp]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrpusdt]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=535287</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[XRP has shown recent gains on its price chart, allowing the altcoin to surpass a significant resistance level. Although the 1% increase over the past 24 hours may not be substantial, it has helped maintain bullish momentum. However, on a weekly chart, XRP has experienced minimal movement. Despite this, the technical outlook for the coin indicates bullish strength in the market. Buying strength has risen, and both demand and accumulation have turned positive, contributing to this technical outlook. The performance of XRP on its chart may be influenced by the movement of Bitcoin. Related Reading: Bullish Case For Litecoin Grows Stronger As LTC Halving Draws Close If Bitcoin continues to appreciate and reaches the $27,000 range, XRP may attempt to break through its immediate resistance. With buying strength recovering and demand potentially supporting the bulls, their position in the market could strengthen. However, if the price remains stagnant at its current level, demand might start to decline, causing the bulls to lose momentum. The increase in the altcoin&#8217;s market capitalization over the past 24 hours suggests that buyers have gained control over sellers. XRP Price Analysis: One-Day Chart At the time of writing, XRP was trading at $0.47. In recent trading sessions, the altcoin successfully surpassed the resistance level of $0.45. Sustaining this positive momentum, the next resistance level for XRP is expected to be at $0.48. If this level is cleared, it could fuel a rally towards the $0.50 mark. However, if the price retreats from its current level, it may invite bearish pressure, potentially causing the price to settle around $0.43. Notably, the volume of XRP traded in the last session was relatively high, indicating a lower selling strength in the market. Technical Analysis During the recent trading sessions, the altcoin not only made progress in its price movement but also saw a notable recovery in buying strength. The Relative Strength Index (RSI) being above the half-line suggests that buyers have taken control of the price action in the market. Additionally, XRP moved above the 20-Simple Moving Average (SMA) line, indicating that buyers were driving the price momentum. This shift in momentum was supported by an increased demand for XRP in the market. In line with other technical indicators, the altcoin has started to exhibit buy signals on the chart. The Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD), a tool used to assess price momentum and potential reversals, displayed green histograms associated with buy signals. This suggests that there is a possibility of the altcoin attempting to break through its overhead resistance level. Related Reading: When Is A Token Coming For Coinbase’s Base L2? Here’s What The Roadmap Says Furthermore, the Bollinger Bands, which indicate price volatility and fluctuations, remained parallel and wide. This indicates that the XRP price action is not expected to be constricted or range-bound. The upper band of the Bollinger Bands intersected at $0.48, highlighting this level as an important resistance level or price ceiling for the altcoin to overcome. -Featured Image From iStock, Charts From TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>XRP has shown recent gains on its price chart, allowing the altcoin to surpass a significant resistance level. Although the 1% increase over the past 24 hours may not be substantial, it has helped maintain bullish momentum. However, on a weekly chart, XRP has experienced minimal movement.</p>
<p>Despite this, the technical outlook for the coin indicates bullish strength in the market. Buying strength has risen, and both demand and accumulation have turned positive, contributing to this technical outlook. The performance of XRP on its chart may be influenced by the movement of Bitcoin.</p>

<p>If Bitcoin continues to appreciate and reaches the $27,000 range, XRP may attempt to break through its immediate resistance. With buying strength recovering and demand potentially supporting the bulls, their position in the market could strengthen.</p>
<p>However, if the price remains stagnant at its current level, demand might start to decline, causing the bulls to lose momentum. The increase in the altcoin&#8217;s market capitalization over the past 24 hours suggests that buyers have gained control over sellers.</p>
<h2>XRP Price Analysis: One-Day Chart</h2>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-535291 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSD_2023-05-28_01-51-04.png" alt="XRP" width="1816" height="830" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSD_2023-05-28_01-51-04.png 1816w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSD_2023-05-28_01-51-04-460x210.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSD_2023-05-28_01-51-04-860x393.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSD_2023-05-28_01-51-04-768x351.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSD_2023-05-28_01-51-04-1536x702.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSD_2023-05-28_01-51-04-750x343.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSD_2023-05-28_01-51-04-1140x521.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1816px) 100vw, 1816px"/>






<p>At the time of writing, XRP was trading at $0.47. In recent trading sessions, the altcoin successfully surpassed the resistance level of $0.45. Sustaining this positive momentum, the next resistance level for XRP is expected to be at $0.48.</p>
<p>If this level is cleared, it could fuel a rally towards the $0.50 mark. However, if the price retreats from its current level, it may invite bearish pressure, potentially causing the price to settle around $0.43.</p>
<p>Notably, the volume of XRP traded in the last session was relatively high, indicating a lower selling strength in the market.</p>
<h2>Technical Analysis</h2>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-535292 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSD_2023-05-28_01-51-41.png" alt="" width="1816" height="743" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSD_2023-05-28_01-51-41.png 1816w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSD_2023-05-28_01-51-41-460x188.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSD_2023-05-28_01-51-41-860x352.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSD_2023-05-28_01-51-41-768x314.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSD_2023-05-28_01-51-41-1536x628.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSD_2023-05-28_01-51-41-750x307.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSD_2023-05-28_01-51-41-1140x466.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1816px) 100vw, 1816px"/>
<p>During the recent trading sessions, the altcoin not only made progress in its price movement but also saw a notable recovery in buying strength. The Relative Strength Index (RSI) being above the half-line suggests that buyers have taken control of the price action in the market.</p>
<p>Additionally, XRP moved above the 20-Simple Moving Average (SMA) line, indicating that buyers were driving the price momentum. This shift in momentum was supported by an increased demand for XRP in the market.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-535293 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSD_2023-05-28_01-52-05.png" alt="XRP" width="1817" height="743" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSD_2023-05-28_01-52-05.png 1817w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSD_2023-05-28_01-52-05-460x188.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSD_2023-05-28_01-52-05-860x352.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSD_2023-05-28_01-52-05-768x314.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSD_2023-05-28_01-52-05-1536x628.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSD_2023-05-28_01-52-05-750x307.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSD_2023-05-28_01-52-05-1140x466.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1817px) 100vw, 1817px"/>
<p>In line with other technical indicators, the altcoin has started to exhibit buy signals on the chart. The Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD), a tool used to assess price momentum and potential reversals, displayed green histograms associated with buy signals. This suggests that there is a possibility of the altcoin attempting to break through its overhead resistance level.</p>

<p>Furthermore, the Bollinger Bands, which indicate price volatility and fluctuations, remained parallel and wide. This indicates that the XRP price action is not expected to be constricted or range-bound.</p>
<p>The upper band of the Bollinger Bands intersected at $0.48, highlighting this level as an important resistance level or price ceiling for the altcoin to overcome.</p>







]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/istockphoto-1323355582-612x612-1-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Whales Flock To XRP, Accumulate 52 Million Tokens In Just 3 Weeks &#8211; Here&#8217;s Why</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/whales-flock-to-xrp-accumulating-52-million-tokens/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Edyme]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 01:18:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrp]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrpusdt]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=535286</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[In the world of crypto, the actions of large investors, known as whales, can often provide valuable insights into the market sentiment surrounding a particular digital asset. Recent data has revealed a common trend in the XRP market, as whales have been actively accumulating millions of tokens over a short period, particularly in the last three weeks. This surge in whale activity has sparked intrigue and speculation among crypto enthusiasts, suggesting a strong bullish sentiment toward Ripple&#8217;s remittance token. Whales Show Bullishness On XRP According to data shared by renowned crypto analyst Ali on Twitter, whales are making significant moves in the XRP market. Utilizing behavior analytics resource Santiment&#8217;s data, Ali highlighted the noteworthy accumulation of XRP by whales, which indicates their strong belief in the future prospects of the token. Related Reading: XRP Emerges As Top Performing Crypto With 55% Surge – Messari Report Over the past three weeks alone, these prominent investors have acquired 52 million XRP, representing an estimated value of over $22 million. Notably, the accumulation trend has been primarily observed among XRP whales, specifically addresses holding 10 million to 100 million XRP. This period of intense accumulation began on May 7, following a notable selloff pressure that occurred on April 12. During the selloff phase, Ripple&#8217;s token experienced a prolonged consolidation period, stemming from the temporary exhaustion of the rally before the latest move. However, the selloff eventually subsided, paving the way for the current accumulation trend witnessed among whales. What Drives The Accumulation  The sudden surge in XRP accumulation by whales has raised questions about what factors could be driving this bullish sentiment. While individual motivations may vary, several plausible explanations shed light on the underlying dynamics at play. One significant factor could be the anticipation of positive developments within the Ripple ecosystem, such as new partnerships or advancements in the adoption of Ripple&#8217;s token for cross-border transactions.  Last month, Ripple (XRP), Cardano (ADA), and several other cryptocurrencies received an adoption boost through a recently announced partnership between Binance Pay and CoinGate. This collaboration enables users of Binance Pay to make crypto payments to merchants powered by CoinGate. In turn, CoinGate merchants can facilitate Binance Pay payments during the checkout process. This new feature, which will be automatically activated, caters to various digital assets available on the Binance Pay platform, including Ripple (XRP), Cardano (ADA), and many others. Notably, such developments often drive demand for Ripple&#8217;s token, prompting investors to accumulate the token in anticipation of future price appreciation. Furthermore, the recent regulatory clarity surrounding Ripple&#8217;s legal battle with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) may have also contributed to the increased confidence among whales. Related Reading: XRP Bears Prevail As Asset Retreats From Recent Highs As Ripple continues to make progress in the legal proceedings, the resolution of the case could potentially remove a major overhang on XRP&#8217;s market sentiment, paving the way for renewed optimism and investment. Meanwhile, following the accumulation of whales, XRP has shown an upcoming uptick. Over the past 24 hours, Ripple&#8217;s token has seen a 1% gain. The asset currently trades at $0.47, at the time of writing. -Featured image from Unsplash, Chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In the world of crypto, the actions of large investors, known as whales, can often provide valuable insights into the market sentiment surrounding a particular digital asset. Recent <a href="https://twitter.com/ali_charts/status/1662215112659456000?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">data</a> has revealed a common trend in the XRP market, as whales have been actively accumulating millions of tokens over a short period, particularly in the last three weeks. </p>
<p>This surge in whale activity has sparked intrigue and speculation among crypto enthusiasts, suggesting a strong bullish sentiment toward <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/xrp-emerges-as-top-performing-crypto-with-55-surge-messari-report/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Ripple&#8217;s remittance token</a>.</p>
<h2>Whales Show Bullishness On XRP</h2>
<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w" dir="ltr">According to data shared by renowned crypto analyst Ali on Twitter, whales are making significant moves in the XRP market. Utilizing behavior analytics resource Santiment&#8217;s data, Ali highlighted the noteworthy accumulation of XRP by whales, which indicates their strong belief in the future prospects of the token.</p>

<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w" dir="ltr">Over the past three weeks alone, these prominent investors have acquired 52 million XRP, representing an estimated value of over $22 million.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Notably, the accumulation trend has been primarily observed among XRP whales, specifically addresses holding 10 million to 100 million XRP. This period of intense accumulation began on May 7, following a notable selloff pressure that occurred on April 12. </p>
<p dir="ltr">During the selloff phase, Ripple&#8217;s token experienced a prolonged consolidation period, stemming from the temporary exhaustion of the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/xrp-ledger-on-fire-daily-transactions-skyrocket-10-7-in-q1-2023/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">rally</a> before the latest move. However, the selloff eventually subsided, paving the way for the current accumulation trend witnessed among whales.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What Drives The Accumulation </h2>
<p>The sudden surge in XRP accumulation by whales has raised questions about what factors could be driving this bullish sentiment. While individual motivations may vary, several plausible explanations shed light on the underlying dynamics at play. </p>
<p>One significant factor could be the anticipation of positive <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/ripple/ripple-xrp-legal-defender-lauds-judge-torres-ruling-as-a-victory-for-the-people/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">developments</a> within the Ripple ecosystem, such as new partnerships or advancements in the adoption of Ripple&#8217;s token for cross-border transactions. </p>
<p>Last month, Ripple (XRP), Cardano (ADA), and several other cryptocurrencies received an adoption boost through a recently <a href="https://www.binance.com/en/blog/payment/binance-pay-is-even-more-versatile-thanks-to-our-coingate-partnership-3983097682377001190#:~:text=What%20Does%20the%20New%20Partnership,the%20service%20on%20and%20off." target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">announced</a> partnership between Binance Pay and CoinGate. This collaboration enables users of Binance Pay to make crypto payments to merchants powered by CoinGate. In turn, CoinGate merchants can facilitate Binance Pay payments during the checkout process.</p>
<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w" dir="ltr">This new feature, which will be automatically activated, caters to various digital assets available on the Binance Pay platform, including <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/xrp-bears-prevail-as-asset-retreats-from-recent-highs/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Ripple (XRP)</a>, Cardano (ADA), and many others.</p>
<p>Notably, such developments often drive demand for Ripple&#8217;s token, prompting investors to accumulate the token in anticipation of future price appreciation. Furthermore, the recent regulatory clarity surrounding Ripple&#8217;s legal battle with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) may have also contributed to the increased confidence among whales.</p>

<p>As Ripple continues to make progress in the legal proceedings, the resolution of the case could potentially remove a major overhang on XRP&#8217;s market sentiment, paving the way for renewed optimism and investment.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/DkZLSED7/" alt="XRP price chart on TradingView" width="2768" height="1556"/>
<p>Meanwhile, following the accumulation of whales, XRP has shown an upcoming uptick. Over the past 24 hours, Ripple&#8217;s token has seen a 1% gain. The asset currently <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/xrp-aims-for-0-50-hinges-on-breaking-through-this-price-level/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">trades at $0.47</a>, at the time of writing.</p>
<p><em>-Featured image from Unsplash, Chart from TradingView</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/XRP-2-460x329.jpeg" width="460" height="329" />	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
