<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
>

<channel>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.newsbtc.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<description>Bitcoin &#38; cryptocurrency news today, price &#38; technical analysis</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 05:07:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Dogecoin Price Prediction: Doge Hits Bearish Circuit and Could Drop To $0.07</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/dogecoin-price-prediction-doge-0-07-2/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 05:07:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Technical analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[doge]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DOGE/USDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dogeusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dogeusdt]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=530405</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Dogecoin started a fresh decline from $0.0820 against the US Dollar. DOGE is declining and might drop toward the $0.065 support zone. DOGE failed to clear $0.0820 and started a fresh decline against the US dollar. The price is trading below the $0.080 zone and the 100 simple moving average (4 hours). There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.078 on the 4-hours chart of the DOGE/USD pair (data source from Kraken). The pair could decline further if there is a move below $0.0720. Dogecoin Price Drops Further After a minor increase, Dogecoin’s price faced resistance near $0.0820. DOGE formed a high near $0.0815 and started a fresh decline, similar to Bitcoin and Ethereum. There was a clear move below the $0.0800 support and the 100 simple moving average (4 hours). The bears were able to push the price below the key support at $0.0775. A low is formed near $0.0734 and the price is now showing bearish signs. DOGE is trading below the $0.080 zone and the 100 simple moving average (4 hours). There is also a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.078 on the 4-hours chart of the DOGE/USD pair. On the upside, the price is facing resistance near the $0.0775 level. It is close to the 50% Fib retracement level of the recent decline from the $0.0815 swing high to the $0.0734 low. The next major resistance is near the $0.078 zone and the trend line. Source: DOGEUSD on TradingView.com The trend line is close to the 100 simple moving average (4 hours) and the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the recent decline from the $0.0815 swing high to the $0.0734 low. A close above the $0.078 resistance might send the price toward the $0.082 resistance. The next major resistance is near $0.0850. Any more gains might send the price toward the $0.090 level. More Losses in DOGE? If DOGE’s price fails to gain pace above the $0.078 level, it could continue to move down. Initial support on the downside is near the $0.0735 level. The next major support is near the $0.0720 level. If there is a downside break below the $0.072 support, the price could decline further. In the stated case, the price might decline toward the $0.070 level. Technical Indicators 4 Hours MACD – The MACD for DOGE/USD is now gaining momentum in the bearish zone. 4 Hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for DOGE/USD is now below the 50 level. Major Support Levels – $0.0735, $0.072, and $0.070. Major Resistance Levels – $0.0775, $0.0780, and $0.082.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>Dogecoin started a fresh decline from $0.0820 against the US Dollar. DOGE is declining and might drop toward the $0.065 support zone.</em></p>
<ul>
<li>DOGE failed to clear $0.0820 and started a fresh decline against the US dollar.</li>
<li>The price is trading below the $0.080 zone and the 100 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.078 on the 4-hours chart of the DOGE/USD pair (data source from Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could decline further if there is a move below $0.0720.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Dogecoin Price Drops Further</h2>
<p>After a minor increase, Dogecoin’s price faced resistance near $0.0820. DOGE formed a high near $0.0815 and started a fresh decline, similar to <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-rejection-30k/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a> and <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-vulnerable-1840/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ethereum</a>.</p>
<p>There was a clear move below the $0.0800 support and the 100 simple moving average (4 hours). The bears were able to push the price below the key support at $0.0775. A low is formed near $0.0734 and the price is now showing bearish signs.</p>
<p>DOGE is trading below the $0.080 zone and the 100 simple moving average (4 hours). There is also a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.078 on the 4-hours chart of the DOGE/USD pair.</p>
<p>On the upside, the price is facing resistance near the $0.0775 level. It is close to the 50% Fib retracement level of the recent decline from the $0.0815 swing high to the $0.0734 low. The next major resistance is near the $0.078 zone and the trend line.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Doegcoin-DOGE.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-530406" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Doegcoin-DOGE.png" alt="Dogecoin Price Prediction" width="1834" height="845" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Doegcoin-DOGE.png 1834w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Doegcoin-DOGE-460x212.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Doegcoin-DOGE-860x396.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Doegcoin-DOGE-768x354.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Doegcoin-DOGE-1536x708.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Doegcoin-DOGE-750x346.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Doegcoin-DOGE-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1834px) 100vw, 1834px" /></a></p>
<p>Source: <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/DOGEUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">DOGEUSD on TradingView.com</a></p>
<p>The trend line is close to the 100 simple moving average (4 hours) and the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the recent decline from the $0.0815 swing high to the $0.0734 low. A close above the $0.078 resistance might send the price toward the $0.082 resistance. The next major resistance is near $0.0850. Any more gains might send the price toward the $0.090 level.</p>
<h2>More Losses in DOGE?</h2>
<p>If DOGE’s price fails to gain pace above the $0.078 level, it could continue to move down. Initial support on the downside is near the $0.0735 level.</p>
<p>The next major support is near the $0.0720 level. If there is a downside break below the $0.072 support, the price could decline further. In the stated case, the price might decline toward the $0.070 level.</p>
<p>Technical Indicators</p>
<p>4 Hours MACD – The MACD for DOGE/USD is now gaining momentum in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>4 Hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for DOGE/USD is now below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Levels – $0.0735, $0.072, and $0.070.</p>
<p>Major Resistance Levels – $0.0775, $0.0780, and $0.082.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/iStock-1351825546-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum Price Just Signaled “Sell” And It’s Vulnerable to More Losses</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-vulnerable-1840/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 03:14:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=530401</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Ethereum price started a fresh decline below the $1,920 level against the US Dollar. ETH could extend losses if there is a clear move below the $1,840 support. Ethereum is moving lower from the $1,940 resistance zone. The price is trading below $1,900 and the 100-hourly Simple Moving Average. There is a major bearish trend line forming with resistance near $1,900 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD (data feed via Kraken). The pair could continue to move down if there is a clear move below $1,840. Ethereum Price Takes Hit Ethereum’s price struggled to clear the $2,000 resistance zone and started a fresh decline. ETH traded below the $1,920 and $1,900 support levels to enter a bearish zone, similar to Bitcoin. The price even traded close to $1,840. A low is formed near $1,843 and the price is now consolidating losses. It is trading below $1,900 and the 100-hourly Simple Moving Average. There is also a major bearish trend line forming with resistance near $1,900 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD. Immediate resistance is near the $1,890 level. It is close to the 50% Fib retracement level of the recent decline from the $1,936 high to the $1,843 low. The next major resistance seems to be forming near the trend line and $1,900. The main resistance is near $1,915 or the 76.4% Fib retracement level of the recent decline from the $1,936 high to the $1,843 low. A close above the $1,915 resistance zone could send Ethereum toward the $1,940 resistance. Source: ETHUSD on TradingView.com Any more gains might start a decent increase toward the $2,000 resistance. In the stated case, the price may even rise toward the $2,050 resistance. The next key resistance is near $2,120. More Losses in ETH? If Ethereum fails to clear the $1,900 resistance, it could continue to move down. Initial support on the downside is near the $1,840 level or the recent low. The next major support is near the $1,800 zone, below which ether price might drop toward the $1,740 support zone. Any more losses may perhaps take the price toward the $1,700 level in the near term. Technical Indicators Hourly MACD – The MACD for ETH/USD is now gaining momentum in the bearish zone. Hourly RSI &#8211; The RSI for ETH/USD is now below the 50 level. Major Support Level – $1,840 Major Resistance Level – $1,900]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>Ethereum price started a fresh decline below the $1,920 level against the US Dollar. ETH could extend losses if there is a clear move below the $1,840 support.</em></p>
<ul>
<li>Ethereum is moving lower from the $1,940 resistance zone.</li>
<li>The price is trading below $1,900 and the 100-hourly Simple Moving Average.</li>
<li>There is a major bearish trend line forming with resistance near $1,900 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD (data feed via Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could continue to move down if there is a clear move below $1,840.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Ethereum Price Takes Hit</h2>
<p>Ethereum’s price struggled to clear the $2,000 resistance zone and started a fresh decline. ETH traded below the $1,920 and $1,900 support levels to enter a bearish zone, similar to <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-rejection-30k/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a>.</p>
<p>The price even traded close to $1,840. A low is formed near $1,843 and the price is now consolidating losses. It is trading below $1,900 and the 100-hourly Simple Moving Average. There is also a major bearish trend line forming with resistance near $1,900 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD.</p>
<p>Immediate resistance is near the $1,890 level. It is close to the 50% Fib retracement level of the recent decline from the $1,936 high to the $1,843 low.</p>
<p>The next major resistance seems to be forming near the trend line and $1,900. The <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-fresh-rally-2k/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener">main resistance</a> is near $1,915 or the 76.4% Fib retracement level of the recent decline from the $1,936 high to the $1,843 low. A close above the $1,915 resistance zone could send Ethereum toward the $1,940 resistance.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ethereum-5.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-530402" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ethereum-5.png" alt="Ethereum Price" width="1834" height="845" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ethereum-5.png 1834w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ethereum-5-460x212.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ethereum-5-860x396.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ethereum-5-768x354.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ethereum-5-1536x708.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ethereum-5-750x346.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ethereum-5-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1834px) 100vw, 1834px" /></a></p>
<p>Source: <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/ETHUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">ETHUSD on TradingView.com</a></p>
<p>Any more gains might start a decent increase toward the $2,000 resistance. In the stated case, the price may even rise toward the $2,050 resistance. The next key resistance is near $2,120.</p>
<h2>More Losses in ETH?</h2>
<p>If Ethereum fails to clear the $1,900 resistance, it could continue to move down. Initial support on the downside is near the $1,840 level or the recent low.</p>
<p>The next major support is near the $1,800 zone, below which ether price might drop toward the $1,740 support zone. Any more losses may perhaps take the price toward the $1,700 level in the near term.</p>
<p>Technical Indicators</p>
<p>Hourly MACD<strong> – </strong>The MACD for ETH/USD is now gaining momentum in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>Hourly RSI<strong> &#8211; </strong>The RSI for ETH/USD is now below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Level – $1,840</p>
<p>Major Resistance Level – $1,900</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/iStock-1383710952-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>If Over 2,300 Banks In America Are Bankrupt, Will Bitcoin Break Above $40,000?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/if-over-2300-banks-in-america-are-bankrupt-will-bitcoin-break-above-40000/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dalmas Ngetich]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 02:41:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FDIC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[federal reserve]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[US Banks]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=530387</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The United States banking system is in trouble as over 2,300 financial institutions could have more liabilities than assets, recent analysis reveals. Subsequently, analysts say this could boost Bitcoin prices in the weeks and months ahead if the government doesn&#8217;t proceed carefully. US Banks Burning Through Capital Buffers The US Treasury and Federal Reserve say that the problems are peculiar to just individual banks, but experts are warning that the situation is much worse than the government admits. With the anti-inflationary measures in place, almost half of America&#8217;s 4,800 banks are burning through their capital buffers, and there is still more tightening to come from the Fed. Related Reading: Bitcoin Struggles To Break $30,000 Resistance Level: Here’s Why The full effect of monetary tightening by the Fed has yet to hit the economy, and only then would experts know whether the United States financial system will be able to safely deflate the excess leverage induced by extreme monetary stimulus during the pandemic between 2020 to 2021. The White House did not offer a blanket guarantee for all deposits because that would look like social welfare for the rich. Besides, the Federal Deposit Insurance Corporation (FDIC) reportedly has only $127 billion of assets and may require its own bailout. For that reason, financial institutions are now pressuring the United States Securities and Exchange Commission to crack down on short-selling strategies that profit when bank stocks slide. Lindsey Johnson, CEO of the Consumer Bankers Association, urged policymakers to take a serious look at the financial havoc wreaked by short-sellers. Bank Failures Could Drive Bitcoin Prices The turmoil in the banking industry is a concern for the Biden administration. If thousands of banks in the United States were to fail, it is possible that some investors could turn to Bitcoin as a way to protect their assets. With the Biden administration&#8217;s stance on cryptocurrencies, any action that places the banking system in jeopardy could drive Bitcoin prices higher, even above $40,000. The SEC is not currently contemplating any ban on short-selling bank stocks, according to a senior agency official. In 2008, the SEC called time-out on short-selling on nearly 1,000 financial stocks in a bid to restore faith in public markets.  However, the New York Fed later found that the ban did little to stem the financial stock market that was flaying out of control. Related Reading: Bitcoin Miners Reap Profits As Mining Difficulty Hits 3-Month Low Another study discovered that most of the stocks protected by the ban lost the citizens&#8217; confidence, suffering &#8220;a severe degradation&#8221; in market quality, price impact, and volatility. As financial institutions press the SEC to take action against short-sellers, and their role in the market, which is impacting Americans&#8217; confidence in the financial system. Yet, any careless moves to pull the pin could create more fissures, possibly buoying crypto and bitcoin prices. Feature Image From Canva, Chart From TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The United States banking system is in trouble as over 2,300 financial institutions could have more liabilities than assets, recent analysis <a href="https://www.gsb.stanford.edu/faculty-research/working-papers/monetary-tightening-us-bank-fragility-2023-mark-market-losses" rel="nofollow">reveals</a>. Subsequently, analysts say this could boost Bitcoin prices in the weeks and months ahead if the government doesn&#8217;t proceed carefully.</p>
<h2>US Banks Burning Through Capital Buffers</h2>
<p>The US Treasury and Federal Reserve say that the problems are peculiar to just individual banks, but experts are warning that the situation is much worse than the government admits.</p>
<p>With the anti-inflationary measures in place, almost half of America&#8217;s 4,800 banks are burning through their capital buffers, and there is still more <a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2023/03/17/business/federal-reserve-markets-mortgages-inflation-interest-rates.html" rel="nofollow">tightening</a> to come from the Fed.</p>

<p>The full effect of monetary tightening by the Fed has yet to hit the economy, and only then would experts know whether the United States financial system will be able to safely deflate the excess leverage induced by extreme monetary stimulus during the pandemic between 2020 to 2021.</p>
<p>The White House did not offer a blanket guarantee for all deposits because that would look like social welfare for the rich. Besides, the Federal Deposit Insurance Corporation (FDIC) reportedly has only $127 billion of assets and may require its own bailout.</p>
<p>For that reason, financial institutions are now <a href="https://www.aba.com/advocacy/policy-analysis/letter-to-the-sec-regarding-banking-industry" rel="nofollow">pressuring</a> the United States Securities and Exchange Commission to crack down on short-selling strategies that profit when bank stocks slide.</p>
<p>Lindsey Johnson, CEO of the Consumer Bankers Association, urged policymakers to take a serious look at the financial havoc wreaked by short-sellers.</p>
<h2>Bank Failures Could Drive Bitcoin Prices</h2>
<p>The turmoil in the banking industry is a concern for the Biden administration. If thousands of banks in the United States were to fail, it is possible that some investors could turn to Bitcoin as a way to <a href="https://www.marketplace.org/shows/marketplace-tech/what-the-bank-failures-mean-for-crypto/" rel="nofollow">protect</a> their assets.</p>
<p>With the Biden administration&#8217;s stance on cryptocurrencies, any action that places the banking system in jeopardy could drive Bitcoin prices higher, even above $40,000.</p>
<a href="https://www.tradingview.com/x/6FoSBMDS/" rel="nofollow"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/6FoSBMDS/" alt="Bitcoin Price On May 7| Source: BTCUSDT On Binance, TradingView" width="1280" height="595" /></a>
<p>The SEC is not currently <a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/usa-sec-idUSL1N3703UK" rel="nofollow">contemplating</a> any ban on short-selling bank stocks, according to a senior agency official.</p>
<p>In 2008, the SEC called time-out on short-selling on nearly 1,000 financial stocks in a bid to restore faith in public markets.  However, the New York Fed later found that the ban did little to stem the financial stock market that was flaying out of control.</p>

<p>Another study discovered that most of the stocks protected by the ban lost the citizens&#8217; confidence, suffering &#8220;a severe degradation&#8221; in market quality, price impact, and volatility.</p>
<p>As financial institutions press the SEC to take action against short-sellers, and their role in the market, which is impacting Americans&#8217; confidence in the financial system. Yet, any careless moves to pull the pin could create more fissures, possibly buoying crypto and bitcoin prices.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-Mean-Transaction-Size-460x260.jpg" width="460" height="260" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Price Faces Another Rejection, Risk of Renewed Downtrend Increases</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-rejection-30k/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 02:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xbtusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=530394</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin price failed to clear the $30,000 resistance. BTC is declining and remains at risk of a move toward the $27,200 support zone. Bitcoin is moving lower from the $29,750 resistance zone. The price is trading below $28,800 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average. There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $28,650 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Kraken). The pair could continue to move down if there is a move below the $28,000 support. Bitcoin Price Extends Losses Bitcoin price struggled to clear the $30,000 resistance zone. BTC faced a strong rejection near $29,750 and started a fresh decline. There was a clear move below the $29,200 and $29,000 levels. It traded close to the $28,000 support. A low is formed near $28,100 and the price is now consolidating losses. It is now trading below $28,800 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average. There is also a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $28,650 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair. Bitcoin is facing resistance near the $28,600 level. It is close to the 50% Fib retracement level of the recent decline from the $29,128 swing high to the $28,100 low. The next major resistance is near the trend line zone or the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the recent decline from the $29,128 swing high to the $28,100 low, above which the price might rise toward the $29,000 resistance zone or the 100 hourly Simple moving average. Source: BTCUSD on TradingView.com Any more gains could open the doors for a decent rally toward the $29,750 resistance. In the stated case, the price may perhaps rise toward the $30,000 level. More Losses in BTC? If Bitcoin’s price fails to clear the $28,650 resistance, it could continue to move down. Immediate support on the downside is near the $28,000 level and the recent low. The next major support is near the $27,650 zone, below which the price might drop toward the $27,200 support zone. Any more losses might take Bitcoin toward the $26,500 level in the near term. Technical indicators: Hourly MACD – The MACD is now gaining pace in the bearish zone. Hourly RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BTC/USD is now below the 50 level. Major Support Levels – $28,000, followed by $27,650. Major Resistance Levels – $28,650, $29,000, and $29,750.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>Bitcoin price failed to clear the $30,000 resistance. BTC is declining and remains at risk of a move toward the $27,200 support zone.</em></p>
<ul>
<li>Bitcoin is moving lower from the $29,750 resistance zone.</li>
<li>The price is trading below $28,800 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average.</li>
<li>There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $28,650 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could continue to move down if there is a move below the $28,000 support.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Bitcoin Price Extends Losses</h2>
<p>Bitcoin price struggled to clear the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-bullish-above-30k/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener">$30,000 resistance zone</a>. BTC faced a strong rejection near $29,750 and started a fresh decline. There was a clear move below the $29,200 and $29,000 levels.</p>
<p>It traded close to the $28,000 support. A low is formed near $28,100 and the price is now consolidating losses. It is now trading below $28,800 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average. There is also a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $28,650 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair.</p>
<p>Bitcoin is facing resistance near the $28,600 level. It is close to the 50% Fib retracement level of the recent decline from the $29,128 swing high to the $28,100 low.</p>
<p>The next major resistance is near the trend line zone or the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the recent decline from the $29,128 swing high to the $28,100 low, above which the price might rise toward the $29,000 resistance zone or the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-regains-strength-30k-2/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener">100 hourly Simple moving average</a>.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-5.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-530395" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-5.png" alt="Bitcoin Price" width="1834" height="845" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-5.png 1834w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-5-460x212.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-5-860x396.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-5-768x354.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-5-1536x708.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-5-750x346.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-5-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1834px) 100vw, 1834px" /></a></p>
<p>Source: <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BTCUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">BTCUSD on TradingView.com</a></p>
<p>Any more gains could open the doors for a decent rally toward the $29,750 resistance. In the stated case, the price may perhaps rise toward the $30,000 level.</p>
<h2>More Losses in BTC?</h2>
<p>If Bitcoin’s price fails to clear the $28,650 resistance, it could continue to move down. Immediate support on the downside is near the $28,000 level and the recent low.</p>
<p>The next major support is near the $27,650 zone, below which the price might drop toward the $27,200 support zone. Any more losses might take Bitcoin toward the $26,500 level in the near term.</p>
<p>Technical indicators:</p>
<p>Hourly MACD – The MACD is now gaining pace in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>Hourly RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BTC/USD is now below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Levels – $28,000, followed by $27,650.</p>
<p>Major Resistance Levels – $28,650, $29,000, and $29,750.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/04/shutterstock_1418423411-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>LUNC Continues Downward Trend Despite Testnet Upgrade</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/lunc-continues-downward-trend-despite-testnet-upgrade/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Opeyemi Sule]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 May 2023 15:51:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LUNC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Terra Classic]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=530345</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Recently, the Terra Classic ecosystem has been in the spotlight due to its developmental efforts, with the testnet upgrade to version 2.0.0 being the latest advancement. Contrary to general expectations, this recent improvement hasn&#8217;t translated into the price of the Terra Luna Classic token (LUNC). Since the start of February, the price of Terra Luna Classic has been on a downward trend. And it can be said that the project’s recent growth hasn&#8217;t done much to halt this decline. Related Reading: Terra Classic Recent Efforts Could Benefit LUNC’s Growth Potential LUNC Price Falls By 15% In Single Week Over the past seven days, the Terra Luna Classic market has experienced a drastic price decline, losing more than 15% of its value. This bearish period was preceded by a week in which the price of LUNC was relatively stable, moving in a horizontal direction. However, a broader look at the market shows that Terra Luna Classic has been on a downward trend in the past few months. Since the beginning of February, the token has recorded a price fall of nearly 53%.  According to data from CoinGecko, LUNC is currently valued at $0.00009549. In the past 24 hours, the value of this cryptocurrency has dropped by about 5%, falling beneath the crucial $0.0001 level in that time.  LUNCUSD on a downward trend &#124; Source: LUNCUSD chart on TradingView The last time Terra Luna Classic made it below this price point can be traced back to August 2022 &#8211; the aftermath of the Terra ecosystem collapse. With the $0.0001 level failing to hold, the token would hope to find rest at its next support level of $0.00009275, even though the current sentiment is strongly bearish. L1JTF Proposes Mainnet Upgrade To V2.0.0 In other news, the L1 Joint Task Force team just completed the upgrade of the rebel-2 testnet to v2.0.0, integrating various new features for better functionality and security. Notably, this serves as a preliminary step towards the Terra Classic mainnet upgrade. The testnet was upgraded to v.2.0.0 with Cosmos SDK v0.45 and will provide a secure and controlled environment for the L1 team to test upgrades on the mainnet. The testnet upgrade, completed on the 4th of May, was announced on Twitter by Till, a part-time developer for the L1 team. Following the successful testnet upgrade, the L1 team’s project manager submitted a proposal aimed at upgrading the Terra Classic mainnet to v2.0.0. According to the proposal document, the mainnet upgrade implementation is slated for May 17. This enhancement will implement a transition to Cosmos SDK v0.45.13 and Tendermint v34.24. It is important to mention that these upgrades are in accordance with Terra Classic’s revitalization plan. Having recorded considerable success in Q1 2023, the development team looks set to reach more milestones in Q2 2023. Related Reading: LUNC Proposal 11487 Gets Over 49% Of Voter Nod -Featured image from BTCC, chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Recently, the Terra Classic ecosystem has been in the spotlight due to its developmental efforts, with the testnet upgrade to version 2.0.0 being the latest advancement. Contrary to general expectations, this recent improvement hasn&#8217;t translated into the price of the Terra Luna Classic token (LUNC).</p>
<p>Since the start of February, the price of Terra Luna Classic has been on a downward trend. And it can be said that the project’s recent growth hasn&#8217;t done much to halt this decline.</p>

<h2>LUNC Price Falls By 15% In Single Week</h2>
<p>Over the past seven days, the Terra Luna Classic market has experienced a drastic price decline, losing more than 15% of its value. This bearish period was preceded by a week in which the price of LUNC was relatively stable, moving in a horizontal direction.</p>
<p>However, a broader look at the market shows that Terra Luna Classic has been on a downward trend in the past few months. Since the beginning of February, the token has recorded a price fall of nearly 53%. </p>
<p>According to<a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/terra-luna-classic" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow"> data from CoinGecko</a>, LUNC is currently valued at $0.00009549. In the past 24 hours, the value of this cryptocurrency has dropped by about 5%, falling beneath the crucial $0.0001 level in that time. </p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/dUq0dsJk/" alt="LUNC" width="1012" height="601" /></p>

<p>The last time Terra Luna Classic made it below this price point can be traced back to August 2022 &#8211; the aftermath of the Terra ecosystem collapse. With the $0.0001 level failing to hold, the token would hope to find rest at its next support level of $0.00009275, even though the current sentiment is strongly bearish.</p>
<h2>L1JTF Proposes Mainnet Upgrade To V2.0.0</h2>
<p>In other news, the L1 Joint Task Force team just <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/terra-classic-lunc-l1-team-completes-testnet-upgrade-to-v2-0-0/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">completed the upgrade of the rebel-2 testnet</a> to v2.0.0, integrating various new features for better functionality and security. Notably, this serves as a preliminary step towards the Terra Classic mainnet upgrade.</p>
<p>The testnet was upgraded to v.2.0.0 with Cosmos SDK v0.45 and will provide a secure and controlled environment for the L1 team to test upgrades on the mainnet. The testnet upgrade, completed on the 4th of May, was announced on Twitter by Till, a part-time developer for the L1 team.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Ok.</p>
<p>We upgraded the rebel-2 testnet to v2.0.0 with Cosmos SDK v0.45.</p>
<p>Purrs like a cat now. Thank you for participating in the upgrade test:<a href="https://twitter.com/StakeBin?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">@StakeBin</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/edk208?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">@edk208</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/Allnodes?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">@Allnodes</a><a href="https://twitter.com/Lunanauts_Lunc?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">@Lunanauts_Lunc</a><a href="https://twitter.com/StellarDrift__?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">@StellarDrift__</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/SolidVote?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">@SolidVote</a></p>
<p>&mdash; fragwuerdig (@frag_dude) <a href="https://twitter.com/frag_dude/status/1654141158648340507?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">May 4, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p></p>
<p>Following the successful testnet upgrade, the L1 team’s project manager submitted a proposal aimed at upgrading the Terra Classic mainnet to v2.0.0. According to the proposal document, the mainnet upgrade implementation is slated for May 17. This enhancement will implement a transition to Cosmos SDK v0.45.13 and Tendermint v34.24.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr"><a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/LUNCcommunity?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#LUNCcommunity</a> Please review and comment on the proposal to upgrade to v2.0.0 at the following location:<a href="https://t.co/6B60jBpo7r" rel="nofollow">https://t.co/6B60jBpo7r</a></p>
<p>&mdash; <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f525.png" alt="🔥" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />LuncBurnArmy<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f525.png" alt="🔥" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> (@luncburnarmy) <a href="https://twitter.com/luncburnarmy/status/1654326918856990720?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">May 5, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p></p>
<p>It is important to mention that these upgrades are in accordance with Terra Classic’s revitalization plan. Having recorded considerable success in Q1 2023, the development team looks set to reach more milestones in Q2 2023.</p>





]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Terra-Classic-LUNC-460x345.jpeg" width="460" height="345" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Lido DAO Records Biggest Network Transaction In 2 Years &#8211; Santiment</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/all/lido-dao-records-biggest-network-transaction-in-2-years-santiment/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Semilore Faleti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 May 2023 12:25:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[All]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DeFi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LDO]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Lido]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Lido DAO]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[OKX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Santiment]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=530346</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[DeFi staking protocol Lido DAO (LDO) has just experienced its largest network transaction in two years, according to a report by Santiment. The popular on-chain analytics firm states that on May 5, $135 million worth of LDO tokens were transferred from one self-custody wallet to another.   According to Santiment, 70 million LDO tokens were moved in this transaction, marking the network&#8217;s biggest coin transfer since June 2021 and its eighth-largest transfer of all time. Source: Santiment  Lido DAO is the most prominent liquid staking platform allowing users to effortlessly participate in staking on several PoS networks, including Ethereum (ETH), Polygon (MATIC), Polkadot (DOT), Solana (SOL), and Kusama (KSM). That said, the LDO whale transaction that occurred earlier today may have drawn much attention to the network; however, this is yet to elicit any positive price effect on the token. According to data by Coingecko, LDO is currently trading at $1.85, recording a 0.34% decline in the last 24 hours &#8211; and an 11.7% cumulative loss in the past week. Additionally, the token’s daily trading volume is down by 47.26% to a value of $31.95 million.  However, this current bearish form does not taint what has been a remarkable year for the Lido protocol. LDO trading at $1.863 &#124; Source: LDOUSD Chart on Tradingview.com  Related Reading: Bitcoin Struggles To Break $30,000 Resistance Level: Here’s Why Lido’s Impressive Year So Far Following the Merge of the Ethereum network last year, liquid staking protocols such as Lido became a focal point of investors’ interest. Moreover, this traction was further fueled by the anticipation of the Shanghai/Capella upgrade, which just occurred last month. Riding on the massive hype surrounding its network, Lido DAO recorded staggering gains in its Total Value Locked(TVL), displacing the MakerDAO &#8211; creator of the DAI stablecoin and first-ever successful DeFi project &#8211; as the biggest DeFi protocol in the crypto space.  Data from Defillama shows that the amount of staked ETH on Lido rose from 4.84 million ETH on January 2 2022, to its current figure of 6.33 million ETH, representing a total value of $12.15 billion.  In fact, total investment in Lido from all of its five supported blockchains has grown by over 108% since the beginning of the year, allowing the liquid-staking platform to gain a 28% market dominance in the DeFi space. That said, considering the latest partnership moves by its developer team, Lido could be set for more gains in the future. Related Reading: Cardano Whales Accumulating – Why Is ADA Bearish? OKX Wallet Integrates With Lido Earlier today, OKX announced the integration of Lido with its OKX wallet web extension allowing users to directly assess Lido’s staking service by visiting the platform’s official website via the “Discover” module on the wallet. This integration represents good news for Lido DAO with the prospect of many new users as OKX ranks as the second biggest crypto exchange with over 50 million customers worldwide. In addition to Lido, the OKX wallet offers access to 100+ DeFi protocols, including Aave, Curve, Sushiswap etc. That said, similar integrations with established centralized exchanges in the future could well result in Lido increasing its dominance in the DeFi space.  -Featured Image: The Market Periodical, chart from Tradingview]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>DeFi staking protocol Lido DAO (LDO) has just experienced its largest network transaction in two years, according to a<a href="https://twitter.com/santimentfeed/status/1654943486033149952?s=46&amp;t=JAUmthpFclo8jS4VJkm3DQ" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow"> report</a> by Santiment.</p>
<p>The popular on-chain analytics firm states that on May 5, $135 million worth of LDO tokens were transferred from one self-custody wallet to another.  </p>
<p>According to Santiment, 70 million LDO tokens were moved in this transaction, marking the network&#8217;s biggest coin transfer since June 2021 and its eighth-largest transfer of all time.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large wp-image-530349 aligncenter" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/FveIVqkaEAAVP6L-860x601.jpeg" alt="Lido" width="860" height="601" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/FveIVqkaEAAVP6L-860x601.jpeg 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/FveIVqkaEAAVP6L-460x321.jpeg 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/FveIVqkaEAAVP6L-768x537.jpeg 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/FveIVqkaEAAVP6L-1536x1073.jpeg 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/FveIVqkaEAAVP6L-2048x1431.jpeg 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/FveIVqkaEAAVP6L-750x524.jpeg 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/FveIVqkaEAAVP6L-1140x797.jpeg 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" /></p>

<p>Lido DAO is the most prominent liquid staking platform allowing users to effortlessly participate in staking on several PoS networks, including Ethereum (ETH), Polygon (MATIC), Polkadot (DOT), Solana (SOL), and Kusama (KSM).</p>
<p>That said, the LDO whale transaction that occurred earlier today may have drawn much attention to the network; however, this is yet to elicit any positive price effect on the token.</p>
<p>According to<a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/lido-dao" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow"> data by Coingecko</a>, LDO is currently trading at $1.85, recording a 0.34% decline in the last 24 hours &#8211; and an 11.7% cumulative loss in the past week. Additionally, the token’s daily trading volume is down by 47.26% to a value of $31.95 million. </p>
<p>However, this current bearish form does not taint what has been a remarkable year for the Lido protocol.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/lInAxREC/" alt="Lido" width="1479" height="913" /></p>


<h2>Lido’s Impressive Year So Far</h2>
<p>Following the Merge of the Ethereum network last year, liquid staking protocols such as Lido became a focal point of investors’ interest. Moreover, this traction was further fueled by the anticipation of the Shanghai/Capella upgrade, which just occurred last month.</p>
<p>Riding on the massive hype surrounding its network, Lido DAO<a href="https://decrypt.co/118270/lido-finance-up-8-after-overtaking-makerdaos-tvl?amp=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow"> recorded</a> staggering gains in its Total Value Locked(TVL), displacing the MakerDAO &#8211; creator of the DAI stablecoin and first-ever successful DeFi project &#8211; as the biggest DeFi protocol in the crypto space. </p>
<p><a href="https://defillama.com/protocol/lido?groupBy=monthly" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Data from Defillama</a> shows that the amount of staked ETH on Lido rose from 4.84 million ETH on January 2 2022, to its current figure of 6.33 million ETH, representing a total value of $12.15 billion. </p>
<p>In fact, total investment in Lido from all of its five supported blockchains has grown by over 108% since the beginning of the year, allowing the liquid-staking platform to gain a 28% market dominance in the DeFi space. </p>
<p>That said, considering the latest partnership moves by its developer team, Lido could be set for more gains in the future.</p>

<h2>OKX Wallet Integrates With Lido</h2>
<p>Earlier today, OKX <a href="https://www.globenewswire.com/news-release/2023/05/07/2662939/0/en/Flash-News-OKX-Wallet-Now-Integrated-with-Lido.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">announced</a> the integration of Lido with its OKX wallet web extension allowing users to directly assess Lido’s staking service by visiting the platform’s official website via the “Discover” module on the wallet.</p>
<p>This integration represents good news for Lido DAO with the prospect of many new users as OKX ranks as the second biggest crypto exchange with over 50 million customers worldwide. In addition to Lido, the OKX wallet offers access to 100+ DeFi protocols, including Aave, Curve, Sushiswap etc.</p>
<p>That said, similar integrations with established centralized exchanges in the future could well result in Lido increasing its dominance in the DeFi space. </p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/lido-dao-460x259.jpg" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Firms&#8217; Plans To Leave The US Speak Imminent Doom, Says Tim Draper</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/crypto/crypto-firms-plans-to-leave-the-us-speak-imminent-doom-says-tim-draper/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mike D.]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 May 2023 08:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[New York]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tim Drapar]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=530321</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The United States is gradually becoming too hot for crypto firms to operate due to unclear and stringent regulatory approaches. For instance, a recent development that sparked an outcry was the proposal to impose a 30% excise tax on crypto-mining facilities. US President Joe Biden&#8217;s budget proposal presented a phased-in tax on the electricity used by crypto mining firms. This tax and the Securities and Exchange Commission&#8217;s enforcement actions may push many top crypto firms and startups to consider offshore operations. As such, Tim Draper foresees a massive departure from the US that might crash its economy. US Unclear Regulatory Environment Is Leading To Massive Crypto Exodus In a Twitter post, the founder of DFJvc, Draper mentioned that Silicon Valley startups are relocating operations to Asia, Europe, and the Middle East. Related Reading: Bitcoin Miners Reap Profits As Mining Difficulty Hits 3-Month Low He further stated that Gemini and Coinbase are moving out of the US due to the regulatory pressure on their operations. Coinbase CEO Brian Armstrong hinted at the same outcome in an April conference organized by the Innovative Finance industry body.  While speaking, Armstrong stated that the Bahamas-based FTX exchange that crashed in 2022 shows the need for clear crypto regulations. As such, the industry needs clear regulations in the US and UK, or more firms will establish operations in &#8220;offshore havens.&#8221; New York Is Losing Blockchain Development Leadership Draper also pointed out that countries like Singapore, Dubai, and London gradually overtake New York in blockchain development. A report by Global Media Insight on March 29, 2023, pitched the UAE as the most digital-friendly country in the world. The report revealed that Dubai has many policies that support blockchain technology. As such, it is emerging as one of the best crypto trading markets worldwide.  In April, Binance also shared many reasons Dubai is crypto-friendly, mentioning tax-free zone, government support, high-tech infrastructure, etc. Related Reading: PEPE Market Cap Crosses $1 Billion As Gemini Listing Rumors Spread Apart from the UAE, London, and Singapore also has a more crypto-friendly environment than the US. According to Draper, these countries have positioned themselves to accommodate crypto firms, thereby attracting more investments gradually.  In conclusion, Draper believes that such an outflow of investment and development might leave the US economy in bad shape, increase homelessness and lead to a massive loss of jobs. -Featured image from CNBC and chart from Tradingview]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The United States is gradually becoming too hot for crypto firms to operate due to unclear and stringent regulatory approaches. For instance, a recent development that sparked an outcry was the proposal to impose a 30% excise tax on crypto-mining facilities.</p>
<p>US President Joe Biden&#8217;s <a href="https://home.treasury.gov/system/files/131/General-Explanations-FY2024.pdf" rel="nofollow">budget proposal</a> presented a phased-in tax on the electricity used by crypto mining firms. This tax and the Securities and Exchange Commission&#8217;s enforcement actions may push many top crypto firms and startups to consider offshore operations. As such, Tim Draper foresees a massive departure from the US that might crash its economy.</p>
<h2>US Unclear Regulatory Environment Is Leading To Massive Crypto Exodus</h2>
<p>In a Twitter <a href="https://twitter.com/TimDraper/status/1654640471174696960" rel="nofollow">post</a>, the founder of DFJvc, Draper mentioned that Silicon Valley startups are relocating operations to Asia, Europe, and the Middle East.</p>

<p>He further stated that Gemini and Coinbase are moving out of the US due to the regulatory pressure on their operations. Coinbase CEO Brian Armstrong h<a href="https://www.reuters.com/technology/coinbase-ceo-crypto-firms-will-develop-offshore-without-clear-regulations-2023-04-18/" rel="nofollow">inted</a> at the same outcome in an April conference organized by the Innovative Finance industry body. </p>
<p>While speaking, Armstrong stated that the Bahamas-based FTX exchange that crashed in 2022 shows the need for clear crypto regulations. As such, the industry needs clear regulations in the US and UK, or more firms will establish operations in &#8220;offshore havens.&#8221;</p>
<h2>New York Is Losing Blockchain Development Leadership</h2>
<p>Draper also pointed out that countries like Singapore, Dubai, and London gradually overtake New York in blockchain development. A <a href="https://www.globalmediainsight.com/blog/cryptocurrency-dubai/#:~:text=The%20UAE%20is%20the%20most,in%20Dubai%20and%20Abu%20Dhabi." rel="nofollow">report</a> by Global Media Insight on March 29, 2023, pitched the UAE as the most digital-friendly country in the world.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-530325 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/TOTAL_2023-05-07_09-38-34-860x499.png" alt="Crypto Firm’s Plans To Leave The US Speaks Imminent Doom, Says Tim Draper" width="860" height="499" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/TOTAL_2023-05-07_09-38-34-860x499.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/TOTAL_2023-05-07_09-38-34-460x267.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/TOTAL_2023-05-07_09-38-34-768x446.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/TOTAL_2023-05-07_09-38-34-750x435.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/TOTAL_2023-05-07_09-38-34.png 1116w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" />
<p>The report revealed that Dubai has many policies that support blockchain technology. As such, it is emerging as one of the best crypto trading markets worldwide. </p>
<p>In April, Binance also <a href="https://www.binance.com/en/feed/post/380179" rel="nofollow">shared</a> many reasons Dubai is crypto-friendly, mentioning tax-free zone, government support, high-tech infrastructure, etc.</p>

<p>Apart from the UAE, <a href="https://www.forbesindia.com/article/cryptocurrency/london-most-attractive-city-for-crypto-businesses-recap-research/83025/1#:~:text=Based%20on%20eight%20important%20factors,engage%20in%20the%20crypto%20world." rel="nofollow">London</a>, and <a href="https://www.exiger.com/perspectives/client-alert-navigating-crypto-regulations-in-singapore/#:~:text=As%20the%20world%20adopts%20varying,as%20a%20crypto%2Dfriendly%20environment." rel="nofollow">Singapore</a> also has a more crypto-friendly environment than the US. According to Draper, these countries have positioned themselves to accommodate crypto firms, thereby attracting more investments gradually. </p>
<p>In conclusion, Draper believes that such an outflow of investment and development might leave the US economy in bad shape, increase homelessness and lead to a massive loss of jobs.</p>
<p><em>-Featured image from CNBC and chart from Tradingview</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Screenshot-2023-05-07-093636-460x297.png" width="460" height="297" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Struggles To Break $30,000 Resistance Level: Here’s Why</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-struggles-to-break-30000-resistance-level-heres-why/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Olowoporoku Adeniyi]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 May 2023 07:00:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin price analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=530300</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The cryptocurrency market has been trading sideways in recent weeks, with the leading token, Bitcoin, following a similar pattern. Despite numerous attempts in April, Bitcoin has struggled to break the $31,000 mark. The price is blocked by its daily Kijun at around $29,100 and by its psychological resistance at $30,000. A correction to around $25,000 could be preferred to prepare for an extended bull run as long as this zone blocks prices. This would correspond to a retest of the same resistance level at the beginning of the year and can be confirmed as the support level.  In the event of a break through the $31,000 mark, then Bitcoin could continue to climb towards $33,500. This would provide the next resistance level ahead of a potential ascent to $40,000. However, if the bears persist below $25.000, Bitcoin risks breaking the price spread, which could cause the price to fall below the $18,000 mark. Related reading: Polygon Bears Gain Ground As MATIC Continues To Retreat Bullish Sentiment Based On External Factors Bitcoin is in good stead and could make a major bull run due to the following factors. First, the banking crisis is plaguing the United States and other parts of the world. Secondly, there is the decoupling between BTC and traditional markets. Finally, we can mention the brake on interest rates the US Federal Reserve promised.  The Silicon Valley Bank bankruptcy in early March is still wreaking havoc on the industry, with many Americans scared of placing their money in the Bank. Bitcoin&#8217;s recent price surge has coincided with this, showing its flexibility as digital gold.  Related reading: UMA Token Surges By 28% Despite General Bearish Trend There has been a surge among investors to diversify their assets into Bitcoin for good reasons. Bitcoin does not need intermediaries; anyone can store BTC in their wallets without trusting a centralized institution. Bitcoin is a unique asset due to its volatility. At times it shows a high correlation with stock indices. While sometimes, it diverges and forms its own course. The following graph shows the comparison with respect to gold, the S&#38;P500, and the NASDAQ. Pearson&#8217;s correlation shows how close BTC&#8217;s behavior is to that of certain traditional assets. If the shares of banking and fintech companies continue to fall, there’s likely to be a huge inflow of volume into the Bitcoin network leading to a price surge.  Finally, the Fed raised interest rates to 5.25% annually. This is the maximum level since 1997. But the increase came with an extra announcement: no new increases (or reductions) are foreseen for the remainder of 2023. Generally, a stalemate or reduction of interest rates is a catalyst for the increase in the price of risky assets, such as Bitcoin.  Bitcoin Price At the time of writing, Bitcoin is down 2% in the past 24 hours and trading for $28,826.  -Featured image iStock, charts from Tradingview]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The cryptocurrency market has been trading sideways in recent weeks, with the leading token, Bitcoin, following a similar pattern. Despite numerous attempts in April, Bitcoin has struggled to break the $31,000 mark. The price is blocked by its daily Kijun at around $29,100 and by its psychological resistance at $30,000. </p>
<p>A correction to around $25,000 could be preferred to prepare for an extended bull run as long as this zone blocks prices. This would correspond to a retest of the same resistance level at the beginning of the year and can be confirmed as the support level. </p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium wp-image-530302" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Screenshot_117-460x175.png" alt="Bitcoin struggling to surpass its resitance level: source@tradingview" width="460" height="175" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Screenshot_117-460x175.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Screenshot_117-860x327.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Screenshot_117-768x292.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Screenshot_117-750x285.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Screenshot_117.png 867w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px" />
<p>In the event of a break through the $31,000 mark, then Bitcoin could continue to climb towards $33,500. This would provide the next resistance level ahead of a potential ascent to $40,000. However, if the bears persist below $25.000, Bitcoin risks breaking the price spread, which could cause the price to fall below the $18,000 mark.</p>
<p><strong>Related reading: </strong><a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/matic/polygon-matic-bears-gain-ground/?swcfpc=1">Polygon Bears Gain Ground As MATIC Continues To Retreat</a></p>
<h2>Bullish Sentiment Based On External Factors</h2>
<p>Bitcoin is in good stead and could make a major bull run due to the following factors. First, the banking crisis is plaguing the United States and other parts of the world. Secondly, there is the decoupling between BTC and traditional markets. Finally, we can mention the brake on interest rates the US Federal Reserve promised. </p>
<p>The Silicon Valley Bank bankruptcy in early March is still wreaking havoc on the industry, with many Americans scared of placing their money in the Bank. Bitcoin&#8217;s recent price surge has coincided with this, showing its flexibility as digital gold. </p>
<p><strong>Related reading</strong>: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/defi/uma-token-surges-by-28-despite-general-bearish-trend/?swcfpc=1">UMA Token Surges By 28% Despite General Bearish Trend</a></p>
<p>There has been a surge among investors to diversify their assets into Bitcoin for good reasons. Bitcoin does not need intermediaries; anyone can store BTC in their wallets without trusting a centralized institution. Bitcoin is a unique asset due to its volatility. At times it shows a high correlation with stock indices. While sometimes, it diverges and forms its own course. The following graph shows the comparison with respect to gold, the S&amp;P500, and the NASDAQ.</p>
<p>Pearson&#8217;s correlation shows how close BTC&#8217;s behavior is to that of certain traditional assets. If the shares of banking and fintech companies continue to fall, there’s likely to be a huge inflow of volume into the Bitcoin network leading to a price surge. </p>
<p>Finally, the Fed raised interest rates to 5.25% annually. This is the maximum level since 1997. But the increase came with an extra announcement: no new increases (or reductions) are foreseen for the remainder of 2023. Generally, a stalemate or reduction of interest rates is a catalyst for the increase in the price of risky assets, such as Bitcoin. </p>
<h2>Bitcoin Price</h2>
<p>At the time of writing, Bitcoin is down 2% in the past 24 hours and trading for $28,826. </p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium wp-image-530304" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSD_2023-05-07_04-36-14-460x231.png" alt="Bitcoin is trading below $29,000: source@tradingview" width="460" height="231" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSD_2023-05-07_04-36-14-460x231.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSD_2023-05-07_04-36-14-860x432.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSD_2023-05-07_04-36-14-768x386.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSD_2023-05-07_04-36-14-360x180.png 360w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSD_2023-05-07_04-36-14-750x377.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSD_2023-05-07_04-36-14-1140x573.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSD_2023-05-07_04-36-14.png 1478w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px" />
<p><em>-Featured image iStock, charts from Tradingview</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/andre-francois-mckenzie-iGYiBhdNTpE-unsplash-1-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Coinbase Might Soon Offer Banking-Like Services, Claims Ripple Board Member</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/coinbase-might-soon-offer-banking-like-services-claims-ripple-board-member/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mike D.]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 May 2023 06:40:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[silicon valley]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=530316</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The second-largest crypto exchange, Coinbase, is still progressing despite the US Securities and Exchange Commission&#8217;s enforcement action against it.  As such, a Ripple board member and an angel investor at PartyDAO, Asheesh Birla, predict it might offer crypto-enabled banking services.  Coinbase Is Transitioning From Crypto Exchange In a Twitter thread, Birla recounted Coinbase&#8217;s mission, vision, and value proposition in the crypto industry, concluding that it might offer banking-like services backed by crypto. Related Reading: PEPE Market Cap Crosses $1 Billion As Gemini Listing Rumors Spread According to the angel investor, the second largest exchange aims at building the crypto economy. This financial system will be accessible, efficient, transparent, powered by crypto, and fair to all users.  Birla further revealed that Coinbase’s 2023 quarter-one report showed that more of the exchange’s revenues came from deposits through interest income, custodial fees, and blockchain rewards. These revenue streams were classified under subscription and services.   Based on the quarterly report, Birla pointed out USDC deposits interest at $199 million, representing 18% of all Coinbase revenue.  Also, the exchange&#8217;s revenue gradually moves from consumer transactions to institutional consumers with high margins. Institutional trading revenue spiked by 67% from its 2022 Q4 amount.  The Ripple board member also noted that Coinbase now benefits from banking-like revenues not entirely dependent on the crypto market.  Banking Crisis Might Push Alternative Services While concluding his post, Birla wondered if the time has come for consumers and institutions to turn to alternative services. Notably, the recent banking crisis that led to the crash of Silvergate, Silicon Valley, and Signature Bank has reduced people&#8217;s trust in the traditional financial system.  Birla cited a recent Bloomberg Opinion piece by Matt Levine titled; “Nobody Trusts Banks Now,&#8221; asking if the timing is right for everyone to move on to alternatives. In the piece, Levine described banking operations strategies in two ways. First, banks borrow short to lend long. Secondly, they borrow long to lend long. In the first strategy, banks use customers&#8217; deposits subject to fast withdrawals to buy bonds and fund loans. In the second strategy, banks use customers&#8217; deposits which could also be withdrawn in the short-term, although not always to buy bonds and fund loans. Related Reading: Bitcoin Miners Reap Profits As Mining Difficulty Hits 3-Month Low Considering these strategies purely dependent on customers&#8217; deposits, Levine concluded that the banking business is inherently risky.  The reason is that if all depositors wake up to withdraw their money simultaneously, the banks will crash. Also, the banks are in trouble if the interest on customers&#8217; deposits spikes.  That&#8217;s why research by Amit Seru disclosed that 200 more banks in the US face the same risks that crashed Silicon Valley Bank. As it stands now, only the future will tell if Birla&#8217;s musings will play out. -Featured image from Pexels and chart from Tradingview]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The second-largest crypto exchange, Coinbase, is still progressing despite the US Securities and Exchange Commission&#8217;s enforcement action against it. </p>
<p>As such, a Ripple board member and an angel investor at PartyDAO, Asheesh Birla, predict it might offer crypto-enabled banking services. </p>
<h2>Coinbase Is Transitioning From Crypto Exchange</h2>
<p>In a Twitter <a href="https://twitter.com/ashgoblue/status/1654570020222144514" rel="nofollow">thread</a>, Birla recounted Coinbase&#8217;s mission, vision, and value proposition in the crypto industry, concluding that it might offer banking-like services backed by crypto.</p>

<p>According to the angel investor, the second largest exchange aims at building the crypto economy. This financial system will be accessible, efficient, transparent, powered by crypto, and fair to all users. </p>
<p>Birla further revealed that Coinbase’s 2023 <a href="https://investor.coinbase.com/financials/quarterly-results/default.aspx" rel="nofollow">quarter-one report</a> showed that more of the exchange’s revenues came from deposits through interest income, custodial fees, and blockchain rewards. These revenue streams were classified under subscription and services.  </p>
<p>Based on the quarterly report, Birla pointed out USDC deposits interest at $199 million, representing 18% of all Coinbase revenue. </p>
<p>Also, the exchange&#8217;s revenue gradually moves from consumer transactions to institutional consumers with high margins. Institutional trading revenue spiked by 67% from its 2022 Q4 amount. </p>
<p>The Ripple board member also noted that Coinbase now benefits from banking-like revenues not entirely dependent on the crypto market. </p>
<h2>Banking Crisis Might Push Alternative Services</h2>
<p>While concluding his post, Birla wondered if the time has come for consumers and institutions to turn to alternative services.</p>
<p>Notably, the recent banking crisis that led to the crash of Silvergate, Silicon Valley, and Signature Bank has reduced people&#8217;s trust in the traditional financial system. </p>
<p>Birla cited a recent Bloomberg Opinion piece by Matt Levine titled; “Nobody Trusts Banks Now,&#8221; asking if the timing is right for everyone to move on to alternatives.</p>
<p>In the piece, Levine described banking operations strategies in two ways. First, banks borrow short to lend long. Secondly, they borrow long to lend long. In the first strategy, banks use customers&#8217; deposits subject to fast withdrawals to buy bonds and fund loans.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-530318 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/COIN_2023-05-07_09-21-08-860x499.png" alt="Coinbase Might Soon Offer Banking-Like Services, Claims Ripple Board Member" width="860" height="499" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/COIN_2023-05-07_09-21-08-860x499.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/COIN_2023-05-07_09-21-08-460x267.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/COIN_2023-05-07_09-21-08-768x446.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/COIN_2023-05-07_09-21-08-750x435.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/COIN_2023-05-07_09-21-08.png 1116w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" />
<p>In the second strategy, banks use customers&#8217; deposits which could also be withdrawn in the short-term, although not always to buy bonds and fund loans.</p>

<p>Considering these strategies purely dependent on customers&#8217; deposits, Levine concluded that the banking business is inherently risky. </p>
<p>The reason is that if all depositors wake up to withdraw their money simultaneously, the banks will crash. Also, the banks are in trouble if the interest on customers&#8217; deposits spikes. </p>
<p>That&#8217;s why <a href="https://siepr.stanford.edu/publications/monetary-tightening-and-us-bank-fragility-2023-mark-market-losses-and-uninsured" rel="nofollow">research</a> by Amit Seru disclosed that 200 more banks in the US face the same risks that crashed Silicon Valley Bank. As it stands now, only the future will tell if Birla&#8217;s musings will play out.</p>
<p><em>-Featured image from Pexels and chart from Tradingview</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/Coinbase-460x259.jpg" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cardano Whales Accumulating &#8211; Why Is ADA Bearish?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/cardano/cardano-whales-accumulating-why-is-ada-bearish/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dalmas Ngetich]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 May 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cardano]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano bears]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Djed]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hydra Head]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=530287</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Despite a massive Cardano whale accumulation, ADA, its native currency, remains bearish, prompting questions about the strength of the underlying fundamentals and whether the leg up of Q1 2023 is over. ADA&#8217;s volatility has been dropping in recent weeks despite a slew of positive developments, mainly from on-chain data.  Related Reading: Cardano TVL Climbs By 10% In A Day – Is ADA Set To Soar Once Again? As an illustration, the coin is down roughly 20% from April peaks and retesting a local support zone of around $0.38. Whales Doubling Down, Activity Rising In Cardano Still, even in these market conditions, there are signs that ADA whales are accumulating in the ecosystem. Although the reason for the swarm is unclear, according to IntoTheBlock, large transactions worth over $100,000 have been made over the past 24 hours, worth around $10 billion. The bulk sale of this size stands at $20 billion in the past week. Moreover, data also shows that &#8220;large holders&#8221; control 35% of ADA&#8217;s total supply. These entities act as a proxy to institutional players&#8217; and whale activities, showing how they may be investing and positioning. While it is unclear what knowledge the Cardano whales have, their activities suggest that they are buying the dip. This is considering that ADA is still down around 87% from 2021 peaks.  Besides whales buying in bulk, Cardano&#8217;s ecosystem is showing promising signs, with the blockchain remaining one of the most highly developed and used.  According to Santiment, 2.15 billion transactions were processed on Cardano. Typically, active networks, in both development and use, point to quality and confidence. The more there are projects and addresses, the higher the odds of the platform&#8217;s coin finding support. The spike in activity over the past few months, even with the general market lull, could be due to various non-fungible token (NFT) and decentralized finance (DeFi) projects launching. Djed, an algorithmic stablecoin, is already live on the mainnet. DeFi and NFT projects look to take advantage of Cardano&#8217;s EUTXO model. This system mirrors how Bitcoin functions but adds a layer of smart contracting, just like Ethereum. However, one of the main developments of Cardano in recent days is the release of the first Hydra Head on the mainnet. This layer-2 scaling solution uses state channels that extend the concept of payment channels. This technology can drive growth, possibly supporting ADA prices in the long haul. Related Reading: Cardano Launches First Hydra Head For L2 Scaling, But Why Is ADA Dropping? ADA Remains Bullish Even with the recent contraction, Cardano&#8217;s long-term prospects look good. Presently, whales appear to be accumulating, adding over 150 million ADA in just one month.  With big players bullish on the coin, doubling down on dips, ADA prices could recover. In the medium term, the ceiling remains at $0.46, marking April 2023 highs. -Featured Image From Canva, Chart From TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Despite a massive Cardano whale accumulation, ADA, its native currency, remains bearish, prompting questions about the strength of the underlying fundamentals and whether the leg up of Q1 2023 is over.</p>
<p>ADA&#8217;s volatility has been dropping in recent weeks despite a slew of positive developments, mainly from on-chain data. </p>

<p>As an illustration, the coin is down roughly 20% from April peaks and retesting a local support zone of around $0.38.</p>
<a href="https://www.tradingview.com/x/nk6FF3mS/" rel="nofollow"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/nk6FF3mS/" alt="Cardano Price On May 6| Source: ADAUSDT On Binance, TradingView" width="1280" height="595" /></a>
<h2>Whales Doubling Down, Activity Rising In Cardano</h2>
<p>Still, even in these market conditions, there are signs that ADA whales are accumulating in the ecosystem. Although the reason for the swarm is unclear, according to <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://app.intotheblock.com/coin/ADA/deep-dive?group=financials&amp;chart=largeTransactions" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">IntoTheBlock</a>, large transactions worth over $100,000 have been made over the past 24 hours, worth around $10 billion. The bulk sale of this size stands at $20 billion in the past week.</p>
<p>Moreover, data also shows that &#8220;large holders&#8221; control 35% of ADA&#8217;s total supply. These entities act as a proxy to institutional players&#8217; and whale activities, showing how they may be investing and positioning.</p>
<p>While it is unclear what knowledge the Cardano whales have, their activities suggest that they are buying the dip. This is considering that ADA is still down around 87% from 2021 peaks. </p>
<p>Besides whales buying in bulk, Cardano&#8217;s ecosystem is showing promising signs, with the blockchain remaining one of the most highly developed and used. </p>
<p>According to <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://embed.santiment.net/chart?ps=cardano&amp;pt=ADA&amp;df=2023-01-27T00%3A00%3A00.000Z&amp;emcg=1&amp;wm=price_usd%3Btransaction_volume_usd&amp;wax=0%3B1&amp;wc=%2326C953%3B%23FFCB47&amp;ws=%7B%22interval%22%3A%221d%22%7D%3B" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Santiment</a>, 2.15 billion transactions were processed on Cardano. Typically, active networks, in both development and use, point to quality and confidence. The more there are projects and addresses, the higher the odds of the platform&#8217;s coin finding support.</p>
<p>The spike in activity over the past few months, even with the general market lull, could be due to various non-fungible token (NFT) and decentralized finance (DeFi) projects launching. Djed, an algorithmic stablecoin, is already live on the mainnet. DeFi and NFT projects look to take advantage of Cardano&#8217;s EUTXO model. This system mirrors how Bitcoin functions but adds a layer of smart contracting, just like Ethereum.</p>
<p>However, one of the main developments of Cardano in recent days is the release of the first Hydra Head on the mainnet. This layer-2 scaling solution uses state channels that extend the concept of payment channels. This technology can drive growth, possibly supporting ADA prices in the long haul.</p>

<h2>ADA Remains Bullish</h2>
<p>Even with the recent contraction, Cardano&#8217;s long-term prospects look good. Presently, whales appear to be accumulating, adding over 150 million ADA in just one month. </p>
<p>With big players bullish on the coin, doubling down on dips, ADA prices could recover. In the medium term, the ceiling remains at $0.46, marking April 2023 highs.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Cardano-ADA-Whales-Accumulating-460x260.jpg" width="460" height="260" />	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
