<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
>

<channel>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.newsbtc.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<description>Bitcoin &#38; Cryptocurrency News Today</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 03:25:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Price Could See Fresh “Liftoff” if It’s Able to Hold One Key Level</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-liftoff-30k/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 03:25:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xbtusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=541203</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin price corrected gains and retested the $30,650 support. BTC could start a fresh increase if it stays above the $30,000 support zone. Bitcoin is holding gains above the $30,650 support zone. The price is trading above $30,700 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average. There is a key bullish trend line forming with support near $30,700 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Kraken). The pair could start a fresh increase if it stays above the $30,650 support zone. Bitcoin Price Remains Stable Bitcoin price struggled to clear the key $31,400 resistance zone. BTC started a downside correction below the $31,000 and $30,800 levels. The price declined below the 50% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $30,192 swing low to the $31,372 high. However, the bulls were seen active near the $30,650 support zone and the 100 hourly Simple moving average. Bitcoin also tested the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $30,192 swing low to the $31,372 high. It is now trading above $30,700 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average. There is also a key bullish trend line forming with support near $30,700 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair. Immediate resistance is near the $31,050 level. The first major resistance is near the $31,250 level, above which the price might start rise toward $31,400. Source: BTCUSD on TradingView.com A close above the $31,400 resistance could start another strong increase. The next major resistance is near the $32,000 level. Any more gains could open the doors for a move toward the $32,500 resistance zone. More Losses in BTC? If Bitcoin’s price fails to clear the $31,050 resistance, it could continue to move down. Immediate support on the downside is near the $30,650 level and the trend line and the 100 hourly Simple moving average. The next major support is near the $30,470 level, below which there could be a drop toward $30,200. Any more losses might send the price toward the $30,000 zone, under which there is a risk of a larger decline. Technical indicators: Hourly MACD – The MACD is now losing pace in the bullish zone. Hourly RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BTC/USD is below the 50 level. Major Support Levels – $30,650, followed by $30,200. Major Resistance Levels – $31,050, $31,400, and $32,000.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>Bitcoin price corrected gains and retested the $30,650 support. BTC could start a fresh increase if it stays above the $30,000 support zone.</em></p>
<ul>
<li>Bitcoin is holding gains above the $30,650 support zone.</li>
<li>The price is trading above $30,700 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average.</li>
<li>There is a key bullish trend line forming with support near $30,700 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could start a fresh increase if it stays above the $30,650 support zone.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Bitcoin Price Remains Stable</h2>
<p>Bitcoin price struggled to clear the key <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-key-trend-32k/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">$31,400 resistance zone</a>. BTC started a downside correction below the $31,000 and $30,800 levels.</p>
<p>The price declined below the 50% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $30,192 swing low to the $31,372 high. However, the bulls were seen active near the $30,650 support zone and the 100 hourly Simple moving average.</p>
<p>Bitcoin also tested the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $30,192 swing low to the $31,372 high. It is now trading above $30,700 and the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-holds-strong-30k/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">100 hourly Simple moving average</a>.</p>
<p>There is also a key bullish trend line forming with support near $30,700 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair. Immediate resistance is near the $31,050 level. The first major resistance is near the $31,250 level, above which the price might start rise toward $31,400.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-541204" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-2.png" alt="Bitcoin Price " width="1835" height="845" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-2.png 1835w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-2-460x212.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-2-860x396.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-2-768x354.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-2-1536x707.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-2-750x345.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-2-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1835px) 100vw, 1835px"/></p>
<p>Source: <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BTCUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">BTCUSD on TradingView.com</a></p>
<p>A close above the $31,400 resistance could start another strong increase. The next major resistance is near the $32,000 level. Any more gains could open the doors for a move toward the $32,500 resistance zone.</p>
<h2>More Losses in BTC?</h2>
<p>If Bitcoin’s price fails to clear the $31,050 resistance, it could continue to move down. Immediate support on the downside is near the $30,650 level and the trend line and the 100 hourly Simple moving average.</p>
<p>The next major support is near the $30,470 level, below which there could be a drop toward $30,200. Any more losses might send the price toward the $30,000 zone, under which there is a risk of a larger decline.</p>
<p>Technical indicators:</p>
<p>Hourly MACD – The MACD is now losing pace in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>Hourly RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BTC/USD is below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Levels – $30,650, followed by $30,200.</p>
<p>Major Resistance Levels – $31,050, $31,400, and $32,000.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/04/shutterstock_638895124-460x264.jpg" width="460" height="264" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Ordinals: This New BRC Standard Could Reduce Inscription Fees By 90%</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-ordinals-this-brc-standard-will-reduce-fees-by-90/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Opeyemi Sule]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 02:00:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin network]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Ordinals]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BRC-20]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BRC-69]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=541174</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Luminex, a Bitcoin Ordinals launchpad, has proposed a new standard called BRC-69, which will allegedly optimize the costs of inscribing on this network. This proposal comes barely a month after Bitcoin Ordinals’ developers introduced recursive inscriptions to address the block size limit of 4 MB. Unlike normal Ordinals inscriptions, recursive inscriptions can reference each others’ content through a special syntax. Related Reading: 75% Of Bitcoin Supply Now In Profit, Will A Drop Happen Here? BRC-69 Standard Can Reduce Inscription Fees By 90%: Luminex On Monday, June 3, Luminex introduced BRC-69, a new standard that will facilitate the creation of Recursive Ordinals collections. According to the launchpad, this BRC standard will help reduce inscription fees by 90%. In March 2023, the Ordinals protocol was updated to enable the minting of BRC-20 tokens, which have seen a significant level of adoption so far. According to data from Coingecko, there are currently 35,528 BRC-20 tokens in circulation, with a market cap of more than $249 million.  The increasing number of BRC-20 inscriptions has led to a scarcity of block space on the Bitcoin network. Consequently, BTC transaction fees have increased as there are more pending transactions. A quarterly report by IntoTheBlock revealed that the Bitcoin network fees surged by more than 300% in 2023 Q2. The BRC-20 standard &#8211; and the creation of new tokens &#8211; were reported to be one of the major driving forces of the increased on-chain fees. To ease this pressure on the network, Luminex has developed the BRC-69 standard, which it claims to be a &#8220;revolutionary standard&#8221;. It will help reduce the cost of inscriptions while helping to optimize the Bitcoin block space as the number of inscriptions rises, according to the launchpad. BRC-69 Standard To Cut Inscription Fees In 4 Steps The BRC-69 standard reduces inscription fees in a four-step process of “inscribe traits”, “deploy collection”, “compile collection”, and “mint assets”, Luminex claims. This means that minters only need to inscribe a single line of text instead of a full image. This text will serve as a reference, enabling the final image to be automatically rendered across Ordinals frontends, only using on-chain resources. “The end result? A flawlessly rendered image. Unlike other SVG recursive collections, these images can be dragged, dropped, and saved as typical image type Ordinals,” Luminex said. BTCUSD trading at $30,879 &#124; Source: BTCUSD chart from TradingView In addition to cost efficiency, Luminex’s proposal claims that the BRC-69 standard offers high flexibility and paves the way for other on-chain features. Some of these features include pre-reveal collection launching and on-chain reveals. It is worth mentioning that the Bitcoin Ordinals are still controversial in the cryptocurrency industry, as a large percentage of the Bitcoin community is opposed to the protocol. Many argue that this technology negatively impacts the efficiency and security of the Bitcoin network. Related Reading: Bitcoin Could Soar To $140,000 In Next Bull Cycle, Crypto Analysis Channel Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Luminex, a Bitcoin Ordinals launchpad, has proposed a new standard called BRC-69, which will allegedly optimize the costs of inscribing on this network.</p>
<p>This proposal comes barely a month after Bitcoin Ordinals’ developers introduced recursive inscriptions to address the block size limit of 4 MB. Unlike normal Ordinals inscriptions, recursive inscriptions can reference each others’ content through a special syntax.</p>

<h2>BRC-69 Standard Can Reduce Inscription Fees By 90%: Luminex</h2>
<p>On Monday, June 3, Luminex <a href="https://twitter.com/luminexio/status/1675832800761778183?s=46&amp;t=igyKw7IQy6t22lMOkrOmyA" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">introduced BRC-69</a>, a new standard that will facilitate the creation of Recursive Ordinals collections. According to the launchpad, this BRC standard will help reduce inscription fees by 90%.</p>
<p>In March 2023, the Ordinals protocol was updated to enable the minting of BRC-20 tokens, which have seen a significant level of adoption so far. According to <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/categories/brc-20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">data</a> from Coingecko, there are currently 35,528 BRC-20 tokens in circulation, with a market cap of more than $249 million. </p>
<p>The increasing number of BRC-20 inscriptions has led to a scarcity of block space on the Bitcoin network. Consequently, BTC transaction fees have increased as there are more pending transactions.</p>
<p>A <a href="http://intotheblock-5494544.hs-sites.com/q2-2023-on-chain?ecid=ACsprvtcCoNPXYjlNEIc-ENAuzncYw_gOQc9BOOKf6XeF_WYC0HVJVaj8KxvdkXhlnqJQVtHnnlG&amp;utm_campaign=Newsletter&amp;utm_medium=email&amp;_hsmi=264588763&amp;_hsenc=p2ANqtz-8Dypkvo672DQdX0AXwDVs3SDAWL3kCNiCPuHcodKNrfJrjjOIzFalX2PDo8eHLX8-88Z-cQZg46ogvfUssDb_UoQ4SaA&amp;utm_content=264588763&amp;utm_source=hs_email" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">quarterly report by IntoTheBlock</a> revealed that the Bitcoin network fees surged by more than 300% in 2023 Q2. The BRC-20 standard &#8211; and the creation of new tokens &#8211; were reported to be one of the major driving forces of the increased on-chain fees.</p>
<p>To ease this pressure on the network, Luminex has developed the BRC-69 standard, which it claims to be a &#8220;revolutionary standard&#8221;. It will help reduce the cost of inscriptions while helping to optimize the Bitcoin block space as the number of inscriptions rises, according to the launchpad.</p>
<h2>BRC-69 Standard To Cut Inscription Fees In 4 Steps</h2>
<p>The BRC-69 standard reduces inscription fees in a four-step process of “inscribe traits”, “deploy collection”, “compile collection”, and “mint assets”, Luminex claims. This means that minters only need to inscribe a single line of text instead of a full image.</p>
<p>This text will serve as a reference, enabling the final image to be automatically rendered across Ordinals frontends, only using on-chain resources. “The end result? A flawlessly rendered image. Unlike other SVG recursive collections, these images can be dragged, dropped, and saved as typical image type Ordinals,” Luminex said.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/WfxAuxQH/" alt="Bitcoin Ordinals" width="1013" height="601"/></p>

<p>In addition to cost efficiency, <a href="https://github.com/luminexord/brc69" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Luminex’s proposal</a> claims that the BRC-69 standard offers high flexibility and paves the way for other on-chain features. Some of these features include pre-reveal collection launching and on-chain reveals.</p>
<p>It is worth mentioning that the Bitcoin Ordinals are still <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-ordinal-nfts-minted-surpasses-500000-mark-whats-next/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">controversial</a> in the cryptocurrency industry, as a large percentage of the Bitcoin community is opposed to the protocol. Many argue that this technology negatively impacts the efficiency and security of the Bitcoin network.</p>





]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/iStock-1356804795-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Trader Bets Against Ethereum, Losses A Big Chunk Of The $2 Million Margin On GMX</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/ethereum/trader-bets-against-ethereum-losses-a-big-chunk-of-the-2-million-margin-on-gmx/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dalmas Ngetich]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 01:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DeFi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum bulls]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum prices]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[GMX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[trading]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=541187</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A trader’s big bet against Ethereum caused him to lose a big chunk of his $2 million margin. Considering the firm and steady increment of ETH prices over the last few weeks, more could be at stake.  In a series of screenshots shared on July 3 on Reddit, one trader on GMX has been aggressively “shorting” Ethereum with high leverage, a decision that has seen the trader lose hundreds of thousands in USD. GMX is a popular decentralized finance (DeFi) protocol that allows users to trade perpetual futures contracts, including those of ETH, with up to 50x leverage.  Ethereum Prices Up 20% In 2 Weeks Despite facing significant losses from the forced liquidation of their shorts, the trader appears unfazed and continues to double down, shorting with high leverage without concern. Since mid-June 2023, Ethereum prices have been rising, expanding 20% at spot rates. Floating above previous liquidation levels at around $1,900, the coin is now trading at about $1,945.Although buyers were unable to drive up spot rates further, the bulls are still in charge. The psychological price point of $2,000 is still the immediate resistance level, along with the April 2023 highs at $2,100. Sparked by fundamental activities and mostly confidence from the broader cryptocurrency community, Ethereum has been marching higher, tracking the performance of Bitcoin. The direct correlation of prices versus the USD between Bitcoin and Ethereum could have benefited bulls during the rally.   Related Reading: Federal Reserve Certifies 57 Organizations For Instant Payments System ‘FedNow’ Comments from the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), alleging that some of the native currencies of some of Ethereum’s competitors, including Algorand, Cardano, and Solana, are unregistered securities could have provided tailwinds for ETH, cementing its positions as a leading smart contracts platform. The SEC’s representatives, especially its chair, Gary Gensler, have remained non-committal in readily classifying the status of ETH. Any clarification could boost prices or force a sell-off depending on the agency&#8217;s classification. Trader’s Doubling Down on ETH Shorts Despite the steady rise of ETH over the past two weeks, the trader, records reveal, has been shorting ETH from when it was at around $1,700 to spot rates. However, the trader began aggressively shorting ETH from June 26.  In total, the trader opened two positions. One with a leverage of 19X was for $12 million, while the other with a leverage of 7X was for $1 million. As prices increased, the collateral representing $12 million from the 19X leverage position was closed. This didn’t stop the trader from opening another position. According to his trading history, another short position with a stop at $1,999 was opened, with leverage of 30X. Related Reading: TRX Bulls Charge Ahead As Tron Network Prepares For Major Upgrade Whether ETH prices will rise in the coming weeks is yet to be seen. All that’s evident is that the coin’s price has been firm, defying sellers who have been active from mid-April through to the first half of June. In the medium term, the $2,000 and $2,100 liquidation levels are critical price points that could shape ETH’s trajectory in the second half of 2023. Feature image from Canva, chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A trader’s big bet against Ethereum caused him to <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.reddit.com/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/14pt0dt/a_single_trader_short_sold_13m_in_eth/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">lose</a> a big chunk of his $2 million margin. Considering the firm and steady increment of ETH prices over the last few weeks, more could be at stake. </p>
<p>In a series of screenshots shared on July 3 on Reddit, one trader on GMX has been aggressively “shorting” Ethereum with high leverage, a decision that has seen the trader lose hundreds of thousands in USD. GMX is a popular decentralized finance (DeFi) protocol that allows users to trade perpetual futures contracts, including those of ETH, with up to 50x leverage. </p>
<h2>Ethereum Prices Up 20% In 2 Weeks</h2>
<p>Despite facing significant losses from the forced liquidation of their shorts, the trader appears unfazed and continues to double down, shorting with high leverage without concern.</p>
<p>Since mid-June 2023, Ethereum prices have been rising, expanding 20% at spot rates. Floating above previous liquidation levels at around $1,900, the coin is now trading at about $1,945.Although buyers were unable to drive up spot rates further, the bulls are still in charge. The psychological price point of $2,000 is still the immediate resistance level, along with the April 2023 highs at $2,100.</p>
<a href="https://www.tradingview.com/x/LdVvOtSg/" rel="nofollow"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/LdVvOtSg/" alt="ETH price on July 4| Source: ETHUSDT on Binance, TradingView" width="1226" height="595"/></a>
<p>Sparked by fundamental activities and mostly confidence from the broader cryptocurrency community, Ethereum has been marching higher, tracking the performance of Bitcoin. The direct correlation of prices versus the USD between Bitcoin and Ethereum could have benefited bulls during the rally.  </p>

<p>Comments from the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), alleging that some of the native currencies of some of Ethereum’s competitors, including Algorand, Cardano, and Solana, are unregistered securities could have provided tailwinds for ETH, cementing its positions as a leading smart contracts platform. </p>
<p>The SEC’s representatives, especially its chair, Gary Gensler, have remained non-committal in readily classifying the status of ETH. Any clarification could boost prices or force a sell-off depending on the agency&#8217;s classification.</p>
<h2>Trader’s Doubling Down on ETH Shorts</h2>
<p>Despite the steady rise of ETH over the past two weeks, the trader, records reveal, has been shorting ETH from when it was at around $1,700 to spot rates. However, the trader began aggressively shorting ETH from June 26. </p>
<p>In total, the trader opened two positions. One with a leverage of 19X was for $12 million, while the other with a leverage of 7X was for $1 million. As prices increased, the collateral representing $12 million from the 19X leverage position was closed. This didn’t stop the trader from opening another position. According to his trading history, another short position with a stop at $1,999 was opened, with leverage of 30X.</p>

<p>Whether ETH prices will rise in the coming weeks is yet to be seen. All that’s evident is that the coin’s price has been firm, defying sellers who have been active from mid-April through to the first half of June. In the medium term, the $2,000 and $2,100 liquidation levels are critical price points that could shape ETH’s trajectory in the second half of 2023.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ethereum-Prices-Fall-Trader-Shorts-460x260.jpg" width="460" height="260" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>SSV Network Unveils Plan For Decentralized ETH Staking Infrastructure</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/ethereum/ssv-network-unveils-plan-for-decentralized-eth-staking-infrastructure/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 00:00:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH staking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=541176</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The ssv.network has finally announced the launch of its mainnet, bringing a decentralized Ethereum (ETH) staking infrastructure to the Ethereum network. The launch follows more than two years of testing and refining, and the network is poised to revolutionize the staking industry. SSV Network&#8217;s Decentralized Infrastructure The ssv.network&#8217;s mainnet rollout plan includes four phases, each with its goals and provisions. The first phase, beginning in early Q2 2023, ensures that all mainnet parameters are correctly configured.  The second phase will introduce a complete set of verified operators, while the third phase will introduce builders utilizing the ssv.network infrastructure. Finally, the fourth phase will be the permissionless launch, inviting anyone to use the open protocol to build or stake. Related Reading: TRX Bulls Charge Ahead As Tron Network Prepares For Major Upgrade According to the announcement, the phased approach to the rollout is necessary to ensure that all the various actors and stakeholders in the network are aligned. But what are the benefits of this for the future of ETH staking? Decentralization: The ssv.network is a decentralized and permissionless network that aligns with the core principles of Ethereum. By embracing this vision, the network aims to bolster Ethereum&#8217;s resilience and empower the community to shape the future of staking. Fault tolerance: The ssv.network has been built to tackle fundamental Ethereum validator challenges, including fault tolerance. The network is designed to be resilient and able to handle failures in a decentralized manner. Security: The ssv.network has been designed to be secure, with multiple layers of security protocols to ensure the network is safe from attacks. Zero-coordination: The ssv.network has been designed to be a zero-coordination network, meaning that validators do not need to coordinate to validate blocks. Instead, the network uses a mesh-like structure that allows validators to validate blocks independently. Using the ssv.network for staking ETH provides a secure, resilient, and decentralized way to participate in the Ethereum network. The network&#8217;s focus on fault tolerance, security, zero-coordination, diversity, and its self-sustaining ecosystem, makes it an attractive option for anyone looking to stake ETH in the future. Shanghai Hardfork Sparks Surge In ETH Staking Deposits The recent implementation of the Shanghai hard fork has resulted in a surge in Ethereum staking deposits, according to analytics firm Glassnode.  The hard fork, activated on June 2nd, introduced several changes to the Ethereum network, including updates to the gas fee structure and EIP-1559. This new transaction fee mechanism aims to improve the user experience by reducing transaction fees and improving predictability. Glassnode&#8217;s data shows that deposit activity for staking ETH peaked on June 2nd, with over 13,595 new deposits worth over 408,000 ETH.  This surge in staking deposits suggests that investors and users are gaining confidence in Ethereum&#8217;s flexibility following the implementation of the hard fork. Staking allows users to earn rewards by holding and validating transactions on the network, and the recent surge in deposits indicates that more users are becoming interested in this process to participate in the network and earn passive income. Related Reading: 75% Of Bitcoin Supply Now In Profit, Will A Drop Happen Here? In contrast to staking deposits, ETH exchange deposit transactions remained flat at around 30,000 during the same period. This suggests that investors and users choose to hold and stake their ETH rather than trade or sell it on exchanges.  This is a positive sign for the Ethereum network, as staking provides a more stable and secure way to participate, compared to trading on exchanges, which can be subject to market volatility. As of the time of writing, ETH is trading at $1,948, struggling to break through the upper resistance level of $1,990. Over the last 24 hours, the cryptocurrency market has experienced a pullback, and ETH has declined by 0.8%. Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The ssv.network has finally <a href="https://blog.ssv.network/mainnet-has-arrived-learn-all-about-the-ssv-network-rollout-plan-and-each-phase-therein-844a8d6d29fa" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">announced </a>the launch of its mainnet, bringing a decentralized Ethereum (ETH) staking infrastructure to the Ethereum network. The launch follows more than two years of testing and refining, and the network is poised to revolutionize the staking industry.</p>
<h2>SSV Network&#8217;s Decentralized Infrastructure</h2>
<p>The ssv.network&#8217;s mainnet rollout plan includes four phases, each with its goals and provisions. The first phase, beginning in early Q2 2023, ensures that all mainnet parameters are correctly configured. </p>
<p>The second phase will introduce a complete set of verified operators, while the third phase will introduce builders utilizing the ssv.network infrastructure. Finally, the fourth phase will be the permissionless launch, inviting anyone to use the open protocol to build or stake.</p>

<p>According to the announcement, the phased approach to the rollout is necessary to ensure that all the various actors and stakeholders in the network are aligned. But what are the benefits of this for the future of ETH staking?</p>
<ul>
<li>Decentralization: The ssv.network is a decentralized and permissionless network that aligns with the core principles of Ethereum. By embracing this vision, the network aims to bolster Ethereum&#8217;s resilience and empower the community to shape the future of staking.</li>
<li>Fault tolerance: The ssv.network has been built to tackle fundamental Ethereum validator challenges, including fault tolerance. The network is designed to be resilient and able to handle failures in a decentralized manner.</li>
<li>Security: The ssv.network has been designed to be secure, with multiple layers of security protocols to ensure the network is safe from attacks.</li>
<li>Zero-coordination: The ssv.network has been designed to be a zero-coordination network, meaning that validators do not need to coordinate to validate blocks. Instead, the network uses a mesh-like structure that allows validators to validate blocks independently.</li>
</ul>
<p>Using the ssv.network for staking ETH provides a secure, resilient, and decentralized way to participate in the Ethereum network. The network&#8217;s focus on fault tolerance, security, zero-coordination, diversity, and its self-sustaining ecosystem, makes it an attractive option for anyone looking to stake ETH in the future.</p>
Shanghai Hardfork Sparks Surge In ETH Staking Deposits
<p>The recent implementation of the Shanghai hard fork has resulted in a surge in Ethereum staking deposits, <a href="https://twitter.com/glassnode/status/1676154285611003905?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">according </a>to analytics firm Glassnode. </p>
<p>The hard fork, activated on June 2nd, introduced several changes to the Ethereum network, including updates to the gas fee structure and EIP-1559. This new transaction fee mechanism aims to improve the user experience by reducing transaction fees and improving predictability.</p>
<p>Glassnode&#8217;s data shows that deposit activity for staking ETH peaked on June 2nd, with over 13,595 new deposits worth over 408,000 ETH. </p>
<p>This surge in staking deposits suggests that investors and users are gaining confidence in Ethereum&#8217;s flexibility following the implementation of the hard fork. Staking allows users to earn rewards by holding and validating transactions on the network, and the recent surge in deposits indicates that more users are becoming interested in this process to participate in the network and earn passive income.</p>

<p>In contrast to staking deposits, ETH exchange deposit transactions remained flat at around 30,000 during the same period. This suggests that investors and users choose to hold and stake their ETH rather than trade or sell it on exchanges. </p>
<p>This is a positive sign for the Ethereum network, as staking provides a more stable and secure way to participate, compared to trading on exchanges, which can be subject to market volatility.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/UDev8eb6/" alt="ETH" width="1815" height="858"/>
<p>As of the time of writing, ETH is trading at $1,948, struggling to break through the upper resistance level of $1,990. Over the last 24 hours, the cryptocurrency market has experienced a pullback, and ETH has declined by 0.8%.</p>
<p>Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/kanchanara-7cmA9ZL5dDk-unsplash-460x306.jpg" width="460" height="306" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Shiba Inu Records Accelerated Burn Rate, But Price Fails To Respond</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/shiba-inu-records-accelerated-burn-rate-but-price-fails-to-respond/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Best Owie]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 23:00:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Shiba Inu]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIB]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shib Burn]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIB price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIBUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIBUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=541063</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Shiba Inu is one of the meme coins that has managed to maintain its popularity in the crypto market as its community remains committed to reducing the circulating supply of the asset. To this end, there has been a significant increase in the SHIB burn rate recorded over the last 24 hours. However, the SHIB price has had a hard time keeping up with this burn rate. SHIB Burn Rate Jumps 540% According to the Shiba Inu burn tracking website, Shibburn, the SHIB burn rate saw a tremendous burn over the last 24 hours. In total, over 78 million tokens were burned, accounting for a 542% increase in burn rate compared to the previous day. Related Reading: Ethereum Eyes $2,000 As Crypto Market Shakes Off SEC Woes HOURLY SHIB UPDATE$SHIB Price: $0.00000776 (1hr 0.22% ▲ &#124; 24hr 1.32% ▲ ) Market Cap: $4,579,871,751 (1.35% ▲) Total Supply: 589,349,600,558,222 TOKENS BURNT Past 24Hrs: 78,248,958 (546.18% ▲) Past 7 Days: 233,385,451 (-78.87% ▼) — Shibburn (@shibburn) July 4, 2023 Now, it is important to keep in mind that this burn rate is notable because it follows multiple days of low burn rates. In fact, the meme coin opened the new week with a drastic decline in burn rate. Shibburn data shows that over the last seven days, the SHIB burn rate is down 78.87%. This indicates a return in positive momentum for the burn rate, which is helping to permanently remove tokens from circulation. Additionally, it also shows that Shiba Inu investors are getting more positive about burning tokens, which could work to help the price recover. SHIB price down over 90% from ATH &#124; Source: SHIBUSD on TradingView.com Shiba Inu Price Fails To Follow Burn Rate Despite the rapid rise in the Shiba Inu burn rate over the last day, the price of the digital asset has not responded in kind. SHIB is still lagging behind, recording losses even at a time when digital assets such as Bitcoin and Ethereum are back on the rise. SHIB is now one of the worst-performing coins when comparing its present price to its all-time high. The meme coin is now almost 91% down from its all-time high price back in 2021 with the vast majority of investors nursing losses on their holdings. Related Reading: Here’s What Caused Bitcoin’s Flash Crash To $29,000 However, the cryptocurrency is performing well compared to its cycle low. After hitting its lowest point this cycle back on June 10, it is 34% up from that level, although this barely makes a dent in the losses of its investors. At the time of this writing, SHIB is changing hands at a price of $0.0000076, according to data from Coinmarketcap. Its market cap has declined rapidly this year, pushing it down to $4.52 billion, making it the 19th-largest cryptocurrency in the space. SHIB’s daily trade volume is currently sitting at $115 million, a 3.24% from the previous day’s figures. Follow Best Owie on Twitter for market insights, updates, and the occasional funny tweet… Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="p2">Shiba Inu is one of the meme coins that has managed to maintain its popularity in the crypto market as its community remains committed to reducing the circulating supply of the asset. To this end, there has been a significant increase in the SHIB burn rate recorded over the last 24 hours. However, the SHIB price has had a hard time keeping up with this burn rate.</p>
<h2 class="p2">SHIB Burn Rate Jumps 540%</h2>
<p class="p2">According to the Shiba Inu burn tracking website, <a href="https://twitter.com/shibburn/status/1676123725089890304?s=20" rel="nofollow">Shibburn</a>, the SHIB burn rate saw a tremendous burn over the last 24 hours. In total, over 78 million tokens were burned, accounting for a 542% increase in burn rate compared to the previous day.</p>

<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">HOURLY SHIB UPDATE<a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24SHIB&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$SHIB</a> Price: $0.00000776 (1hr 0.22% ▲ | 24hr 1.32% ▲ )
Market Cap: $4,579,871,751 (1.35% ▲)
Total Supply: 589,349,600,558,222</p>
<p>TOKENS BURNT
Past 24Hrs: 78,248,958 (546.18% ▲)
Past 7 Days: 233,385,451 (-78.87% ▼)</p>
<p>— Shibburn (@shibburn) <a href="https://twitter.com/shibburn/status/1676123725089890304?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">July 4, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p class="p2">Now, it is important to keep in mind that this burn rate is notable because it follows multiple days of low burn rates. In fact, the meme coin opened the new week with a drastic decline in burn rate. Shibburn data shows that over the last seven days, the SHIB burn rate is down 78.87%.</p>
<p class="p2">This indicates a return in positive momentum for the burn rate, which is helping to permanently remove tokens from circulation. Additionally, it also shows that Shiba Inu investors are getting more positive about burning tokens, which could work to help the price recover.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/GMOtNS5i/" alt="Shiba Inu (SHIB) price chart from TradingView.com" width="2884" height="1724"/></p>

<h2 class="p2">Shiba Inu Price Fails To Follow Burn Rate</h2>
<p class="p2">Despite the rapid rise in the Shiba Inu burn rate over the last day, the price of the digital asset has not responded in kind. SHIB is still lagging behind, recording losses even at a time when digital assets such as Bitcoin and Ethereum are back on the rise.</p>
<p class="p2">SHIB is now one of the worst-performing coins when comparing its present price to its all-time high. The meme coin is now almost 91% down from its all-time high price back in 2021 with the vast majority of investors nursing losses on their holdings.</p>

<p class="p2">However, the cryptocurrency is performing well compared to its cycle low. After hitting its lowest point this cycle back on June 10, it is 34% up from that level, although this barely makes a dent in the losses of its investors.</p>
<p class="p2">At the time of this writing, SHIB is changing hands at a price of $0.0000076, according to data from Coinmarketcap. Its market cap has declined rapidly this year, pushing it down to $4.52 billion, making it the 19th-largest cryptocurrency in the space. SHIB’s daily trade volume is currently sitting at $115 million, a 3.24% from the previous day’s figures.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/iStock-1327123774-2-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Litecoin Primed For 13% Rally Soon Upon Breaking Past This Level</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/litecoin/litecoin-primed-for-13-rally-soon-upon-breaking-past-this-level/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[anushsamal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 22:00:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Litecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ltc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ltc/usd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LTCUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=541153</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Litecoin has demonstrated a consistently positive trend in recent weeks, reflecting a strong market sentiment. As the broader market has gained strength in recent trading sessions, Litecoin has managed to sustain its gains. The price of Bitcoin has surpassed $31,000 at present, resulting in an upward movement for other altcoins as well. Related Reading: XRP, Cardano Among Altcoins To Keep An Eye On: Santiment While Litecoin has not experienced significant changes in the past 24 hours, it has maintained a positive trajectory. On a weekly chart, however, the altcoin has surged by over 20%. This remarkable recovery began in June when Litecoin broke through the $70 price mark, and since then, the coin has gained more than 50%. From a technical outlook, the Litecoin outlook aligns with the bullish sentiment. Both demand and accumulation indicators on the chart have remained high, suggesting the possibility of further gains. However, there is an important resistance to consider. In the upcoming days, Litecoin is expected to experience a surge due to its halving event scheduled for 3rd August 2023. Additionally, the market capitalization of Litecoin has also improved, indicating an increase in demand for the cryptocurrency. Litecoin Price Analysis: One-Day Chart At the time of writing, LTC was priced at $106. Although the altcoin is below its resistance level of $108, this particular level is not the main obstacle. The crucial challenge for Litecoin lies in gaining sufficient strength to surpass the $115 resistance, a level at which the coin has historically faced rejection. In April of the previous year, Litecoin approached this level but could not sustain trading above it for the remainder of the year. Conversely, if Litecoin fails to break through the $115 resistance, it could experience a decline toward the $103 support level. Further downward movement from this point would bring LTC below the $100 mark, indicating a complete invalidation of the bullish intent. Technical Analysis The price surge from the $90 level in Litecoin has significantly bolstered investor confidence. The Relative Strength Index (RSI) indicator reached the overvalued zone, indicating increased buying activity. Although it retraced slightly from the overbought territory, it remained above the 60-mark, indicating sustained buying strength in the market. Furthermore, the LTC price movement was supported because it remained above the 20-Simple Moving Average (SMA) line. This suggests that buyers have assumed market control and are driving the price momentum. The Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD) indicator formed tall green histograms, indicating favorable buy signals for LTC. This suggests the potential for continued bullishness in the market. Additionally, the Bollinger Bands on the chart were wide open, indicating increased price volatility. The upper band coincided with one of the resistance levels at $108. Related Reading: Avalanche Stuck In A Range, Potential Shift Ahead If This Occurs This suggests that LTC will likely encounter price fluctuations and may face a barrier at the mentioned resistance level. The next trading sessions remain crucial for the altcoin. Featured image from UnSplash, charts from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Litecoin has demonstrated a consistently positive trend in recent weeks, reflecting a strong market sentiment. As the broader market has gained strength in recent trading sessions, Litecoin has managed to sustain its gains. The price of Bitcoin has surpassed $31,000 at present, resulting in an upward movement for other altcoins as well.</p>

<p>While Litecoin has not experienced significant changes in the past 24 hours, it has maintained a positive trajectory. On a weekly chart, however, the altcoin has surged by over 20%. This remarkable recovery began in June when Litecoin broke through the $70 price mark, and since then, the coin has gained more than 50%.</p>
<p>From a technical outlook, the Litecoin outlook aligns with the bullish sentiment. Both demand and accumulation indicators on the chart have remained high, suggesting the possibility of further gains. However, there is an important resistance to consider.</p>
<p>In the upcoming days, Litecoin is expected to experience a surge due to its halving event scheduled for 3rd August 2023. Additionally, the market capitalization of Litecoin has also improved, indicating an increase in demand for the cryptocurrency.</p>
<h2>Litecoin Price Analysis: One-Day Chart</h2>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-541158 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/LTCUSDT_2023-07-04_22-17-07.png" alt="Litecoin" width="1817" height="743" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/LTCUSDT_2023-07-04_22-17-07.png 1817w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/LTCUSDT_2023-07-04_22-17-07-460x188.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/LTCUSDT_2023-07-04_22-17-07-860x352.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/LTCUSDT_2023-07-04_22-17-07-768x314.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/LTCUSDT_2023-07-04_22-17-07-1536x628.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/LTCUSDT_2023-07-04_22-17-07-750x307.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/LTCUSDT_2023-07-04_22-17-07-1140x466.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1817px) 100vw, 1817px"/>
<p>At the time of writing, LTC was priced at $106. Although the altcoin is below its resistance level of $108, this particular level is not the main obstacle.</p>
<p>The crucial challenge for Litecoin lies in gaining sufficient strength to surpass the $115 resistance, a level at which the coin has historically faced rejection.</p>
<p>In April of the previous year, Litecoin approached this level but could not sustain trading above it for the remainder of the year.</p>
<p>Conversely, if Litecoin fails to break through the $115 resistance, it could experience a decline toward the $103 support level. Further downward movement from this point would bring LTC below the $100 mark, indicating a complete invalidation of the bullish intent.</p>
<h2>Technical Analysis</h2>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-541160 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/LTCUSDT_2023-07-04_22-17-38.png" alt="Litecoin" width="1817" height="743" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/LTCUSDT_2023-07-04_22-17-38.png 1817w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/LTCUSDT_2023-07-04_22-17-38-460x188.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/LTCUSDT_2023-07-04_22-17-38-860x352.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/LTCUSDT_2023-07-04_22-17-38-768x314.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/LTCUSDT_2023-07-04_22-17-38-1536x628.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/LTCUSDT_2023-07-04_22-17-38-750x307.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/LTCUSDT_2023-07-04_22-17-38-1140x466.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1817px) 100vw, 1817px"/>
<p>The price surge from the $90 level in Litecoin has significantly bolstered investor confidence. The Relative Strength Index (RSI) indicator reached the overvalued zone, indicating increased buying activity.</p>
<p>Although it retraced slightly from the overbought territory, it remained above the 60-mark, indicating sustained buying strength in the market.</p>
<p>Furthermore, the LTC price movement was supported because it remained above the 20-Simple Moving Average (SMA) line. This suggests that buyers have assumed market control and are driving the price momentum.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-541161 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/LTCUSDT_2023-07-04_22-17-57.png" alt="Litecoin" width="1817" height="743" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/LTCUSDT_2023-07-04_22-17-57.png 1817w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/LTCUSDT_2023-07-04_22-17-57-460x188.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/LTCUSDT_2023-07-04_22-17-57-860x352.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/LTCUSDT_2023-07-04_22-17-57-768x314.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/LTCUSDT_2023-07-04_22-17-57-1536x628.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/LTCUSDT_2023-07-04_22-17-57-750x307.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/LTCUSDT_2023-07-04_22-17-57-1140x466.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1817px) 100vw, 1817px"/>
<p>The Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD) indicator formed tall green histograms, indicating favorable buy signals for LTC. This suggests the potential for continued bullishness in the market.</p>
<p>Additionally, the Bollinger Bands on the chart were wide open, indicating increased price volatility. The upper band coincided with one of the resistance levels at $108.</p>

<p>This suggests that LTC will likely encounter price fluctuations and may face a barrier at the mentioned resistance level. The next trading sessions remain crucial for the altcoin.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/traxer-zuYihuQlJkg-unsplash-460x306.jpg" width="460" height="306" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Bulls Stampede: Bitfinex Report Points To Early Signs Of Bull Market</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-bulls-stampede-bitfinex-report-points-to-early-signs-of-bull-market/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 21:00:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=541135</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitfinex, one of the world&#8217;s leading cryptocurrency exchanges, has released a report indicating that Bitcoin (BTC) has been sold in profit since its initial break above $30,000, suggesting early signs of a bull market.  The report highlights two key on-chain metrics, the Spent Output Profit Ratio (SOPR) and Net Unrealised Profit and Loss (NUPL), which suggest that Bitcoin has entered the early stages of a bull market. Bitcoin Sold In Profit The report notes that BTC’s price broke above the crucial $29,500 mark for the second time this year on June 21st and had been bracketing in the range between this level and the $31,000 level since then.  This range has always acted as a pivotal point in deciding the trend for the crypto market and, as such, is a major psychological level. The SOPR has been above one for about two weeks now since the BTC price broke above the crucial $29,500 level, indicating that people are, on average, selling their Bitcoin at a profit. Related Reading: Solana (SOL) Price Targets 40% Rally Amid Strong Fundamentals The report also breaks down the events following the break above the $29,500 level and the subsequent range of the market between that and the $31,000 level from an order flow perspective.  It notes that there is a high probability that the move away from the current range for Bitcoin is decisive since a retest of the range after a move up or down would mean it is likely to act as a crucial rebound zone when and if the price returns to it. However, the report warns that the next move out of the current range will be decisive and violent, which is unusual for the BTC price of late.  BTC Dominates Digital Asset Flows  According to the latest Coin Shares report, investors continue to pour money into digital asset investment products, with a second week of inflows totaling $125 million. The last two weeks have seen inflows of $334 million, representing almost 1% of total assets under management (AuM).  Bitcoin remains the primary focus of investors, accounting for $123 million of inflows, or 98% of all digital asset flows. Recent price appreciation has seen AuM rise to $37 billion, matching the average AuM for 2022 and reaching the highest point since early June. Despite recent bullishness for Bitcoin, short-Bitcoin investment products saw their 10th week of outflows, totaling $0.9 million and representing 59% of AuM. Nevertheless, short-Bitcoin remains the second-best performing asset in terms of inflows year-to-date, with $60 million. Related Reading: Maker (MKR) Outperforms Top Coins With 12% Increase A Day, Will It Test $1100? On the other hand, a selection of altcoins saw minor inflows, with Ethereum leading the way at $2.7 million, followed by Cardano, Polygon, and XRP. Multi-asset and Solana saw minor outflows of $1.8 million and $0.8 million, respectively. The report suggests that investors remain bullish on Bitcoin, with inflows representing a significant portion of total assets under management. However, the continued outflows of short-Bitcoin investment products indicate some investors are betting against the cryptocurrency&#8217;s short-term performance. BTC has failed to consolidate above the $31,000 mark for two consecutive days. At the time of writing, BTC is trading at $30,900, representing a decline of 0.3% in the last 24 hours.  The failure to consolidate above $31,000 could indicate a lack of buyer interest, potentially leading to further downside pressure on the cryptocurrency. It remains to be seen whether BTC can regain its footing and make another attempt at breaking through this crucial level. Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com ]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitfinex, one of the world&#8217;s leading cryptocurrency exchanges, has released a <a href="https://blog.bitfinex.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitfinex-Alpha-61.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">report </a>indicating that Bitcoin (BTC) has been sold in profit since its initial break above $30,000, suggesting early signs of a bull market. </p>
<p>The report highlights two key on-chain metrics, the Spent Output Profit Ratio (SOPR) and Net Unrealised Profit and Loss (NUPL), which suggest that Bitcoin has entered the early stages of a bull market.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Sold In Profit</h2>
<p>The report notes that BTC’s price broke above the crucial $29,500 mark for the second time this year on June 21st and had been bracketing in the range between this level and the $31,000 level since then. </p>
<p>This range has always acted as a pivotal point in deciding the trend for the crypto market and, as such, is a major psychological level. The SOPR has been above one for about two weeks now since the BTC price broke above the crucial $29,500 level, indicating that people are, on average, selling their Bitcoin at a profit.</p>

<p>The report also breaks down the events following the break above the $29,500 level and the subsequent range of the market between that and the $31,000 level from an order flow perspective. </p>
<p>It notes that there is a high probability that the move away from the current range for Bitcoin is decisive since a retest of the range after a move up or down would mean it is likely to act as a crucial rebound zone when and if the price returns to it.</p>
<p>However, the report warns that the next move out of the current range will be decisive and violent, which is unusual for the BTC price of late. </p>
BTC Dominates Digital Asset Flows 
<p>According to the latest Coin Shares <a href="https://blog.coinshares.com/volume-138-digital-asset-fund-flows-weekly-report-e3fcb270729" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">report</a>, investors continue to pour money into digital asset investment products, with a second week of inflows totaling $125 million. The last two weeks have seen inflows of $334 million, representing almost 1% of total assets under management (AuM). </p>
<p>Bitcoin remains the primary focus of investors, accounting for $123 million of inflows, or 98% of all digital asset flows. Recent price appreciation has seen AuM rise to $37 billion, matching the average AuM for 2022 and reaching the highest point since early June.</p>
<p>Despite recent bullishness for Bitcoin, short-Bitcoin investment products saw their 10th week of outflows, totaling $0.9 million and representing 59% of AuM. Nevertheless, short-Bitcoin remains the second-best performing asset in terms of inflows year-to-date, with $60 million.</p>

<p>On the other hand, a selection of altcoins saw minor inflows, with Ethereum leading the way at $2.7 million, followed by Cardano, Polygon, and XRP. Multi-asset and Solana saw minor outflows of $1.8 million and $0.8 million, respectively.</p>
<p>The report suggests that investors remain bullish on Bitcoin, with inflows representing a significant portion of total assets under management. However, the continued outflows of short-Bitcoin investment products indicate some investors are betting against the cryptocurrency&#8217;s short-term performance.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/t7pDtp3v/" alt="Bitcoin " width="1814" height="858"/>
<p>BTC has failed to consolidate above the $31,000 mark for two consecutive days. At the time of writing, BTC is trading at $30,900, representing a decline of 0.3% in the last 24 hours. </p>
<p>The failure to consolidate above $31,000 could indicate a lack of buyer interest, potentially leading to further downside pressure on the cryptocurrency. It remains to be seen whether BTC can regain its footing and make another attempt at breaking through this crucial level.</p>
<p>Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/iStock-1392175988-1-460x248.jpg" width="460" height="248" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum Whale Transactions Jump Over 50% As ETH Eyes $2,000</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/ethereum/ethereum-whale-transactions-jump-over-50-as-eth-eyes-2000/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 20:00:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eth price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH whales]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum Whales]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[whales]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=541144</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Ethereum whales have been ramping up their activities on the blockchain as it eyes an important level. This time around, their recent spike in activity has been in the form of transactions. These whale transactions which are carrying at least $100,000, making it so only large holders could be behind the transactions, have been on the rise. Mostly, the Ethereum whales ramped up their activities following ETH’s price increase over the last week. The first spike was noticed after the crypto broke above $1,900 and as it has continued to maintain this level, there has been more consistency among the whales. Related Reading: Maker (MKR) Outperforms Top Coins With 12% Increase A Day, Will It Test $1100? IntoTheBlock data shows that ETH whales have doubled their transaction counts over a few days. This increase saw their total transactions go from 2,120 to 3,230 in two days. This jump in number of transactions translates to an over 54% increase in just 48 hours &#8211; from July 2 to July 4. In a 7-day period, almost $20 billion has been moved by ETH whales. ETH whale transactions cross 3,000 in two days &#124; Source: IntoTheBlock However, while this jump is significant in its own right, it is not unusual for Ethereum to see such a high number of large transactions. For example, toward the end of June, the total whale transactions had also spiked above the $3,000 level. Ethereum’s holder base is made up of a high number of whales when compared to its largest competitor Bitcoin. While the latter’s whale holders only make up 11% of the total holder base, Ethereum whale wallets account for 42% of its total wallets, according to data from IntoTheBlock. Hence, a high volume of large transactions happening in a short period is not out of place. How The Ethereum Whales Can Affect Price A high number of whale transactions can have significant impacts on the price of coins like Ethereum depending on what the holders of these coins intend to do with them. If these transactions carrying at least $100,000 worth of coins are for selling, then the price of ETH would see a downtrend. Related Reading: Bitcoin Could Soar To $140,000 In Next Bull Cycle, Crypto Analysis Channel However, since the price of ETH has remained relatively stable and maintained its hold on the $1,900 support, then it is likely that these whales are just moving their coins around without selling. Additionally, these on-chain transactions do not point toward a good volume of ETH flowing toward centralized exchanges, further giving credence to the fact that these whales are not moving their coins for selling purposes. Ethereum, on its own, has not had the best of days though as its trading volume is down significantly from Monday. It is currently sitting at $6 billion, a 27% decline from Monday’s figures. Nevertheless, its price is holding steady with meager gains of 0.1% as the coin trades at a price of $1,963. ETH price trending at $1,962 &#124; Source: ETHUSD on TradingView.com Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="p1">Ethereum whales have been ramping up their activities on the blockchain as it eyes an important level. This time around, their recent spike in activity has been in the form of transactions. These whale transactions which are carrying at least $100,000, making it so only large holders could be behind the transactions, have been on the rise.</p>
<p class="p1">Mostly, the Ethereum whales ramped up their activities following ETH’s price increase over the last week. The first spike was noticed after the crypto broke above $1,900 and as it has continued to maintain this level, there has been more consistency among the whales.</p>

<p class="p1">IntoTheBlock <a href="https://app.intotheblock.com/coin/ETH" rel="nofollow">data</a> shows that ETH whales have doubled their transaction counts over a few days. This increase saw their total transactions go from 2,120 to 3,230 in two days. This jump in number of transactions translates to an over 54% increase in just 48 hours &#8211; from July 2 to July 4. In a 7-day period, almost $20 billion has been moved by ETH whales.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-541146 aligncenter" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-04-at-17.36.05-460x289.png" alt="Ethereum (ETH) whales" width="460" height="289" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-04-at-17.36.05-460x289.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-04-at-17.36.05-860x541.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-04-at-17.36.05-768x483.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-04-at-17.36.05-1536x966.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-04-at-17.36.05-750x472.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-04-at-17.36.05-1140x717.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-04-at-17.36.05.png 1564w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px"/></p>

<p class="p1">However, while this jump is significant in its own right, it is not unusual for Ethereum to see such a high number of large transactions. For example, toward the end of June, the total whale transactions had also spiked above the $3,000 level.</p>
<p class="p1">Ethereum’s holder base is made up of a high number of whales when compared to its largest competitor Bitcoin. While the latter’s whale holders only make up 11% of the total holder base, Ethereum whale wallets account for 42% of its total wallets, according to data from IntoTheBlock. Hence, a high volume of large transactions happening in a short period is not out of place.</p>
<h2 class="p1">How The Ethereum Whales Can Affect Price</h2>
<p class="p1">A high number of whale transactions can have significant impacts on the price of coins like Ethereum depending on what the holders of these coins intend to do with them. If these transactions carrying at least $100,000 worth of coins are for selling, then the price of ETH would see a downtrend.</p>

<p class="p1">However, since the price of ETH has remained relatively stable and maintained its hold on the $1,900 support, then it is likely that these whales are just moving their coins around without selling. Additionally, these on-chain transactions do not point toward a good volume of ETH flowing toward centralized exchanges, further giving credence to the fact that these whales are not moving their coins for selling purposes.</p>
<p class="p1">Ethereum, on its own, has not had the best of days though as its trading volume is down significantly from Monday. It is currently sitting at $6 billion, a 27% decline from Monday’s figures. Nevertheless, its price is holding steady with meager gains of 0.1% as the coin trades at a price of $1,963.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/25s5ANF6/" alt="Ethereum (ETH) price chart from TradingView.com" width="2884" height="1724"/></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/iStock-1336958337-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Federal Reserve Certifies 57 Organizations For Instant Payments System &#8216;FedNow&#8217;</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/crypto/federal-reserve-certifies-57-organizations-for-instant-payments-system-fednow/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 19:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[federal reserve]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FedNow]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[transactions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[united states]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=541099</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The United States Federal Reserve has made a significant announcement regarding the certification of 57 organizations, including financial institutions and service providers, for the highly anticipated launch of the FedNow Service.  With major players in the banking industry, such as JPMorgan Chase, Bank of New York Mellon, US Bancorp, and Wells Fargo, among the certified entities named by the Fed, the stage is set for a transformative shift in the financial landscape. Testing And Certification Completion For FedNow The Federal Reserve has disclosed that 57 early adopter organizations have successfully completed formal testing and certification for the upcoming FedNow Service launch planned for late July. Related Reading: XRP, Cardano Among Altcoins To Keep An Eye On: Santiment This diverse group consists of financial institutions and service providers that are ready to send and receive transactions, supporting settlement and processing on behalf of participants. The US Department of the Treasury is also among the early adopters, reflecting the breadth of involvement in this groundbreaking initiative. Readiness and Final Trial Runs The certified organizations are currently undergoing final trial runs to confirm their readiness in handling live transactions over the new instant payments infrastructure.  This critical phase ensures that the participants can seamlessly embrace the capabilities of FedNow, providing enhanced payment experiences to their customers.  As part of this process, comprehensive testing and validation have been conducted to ensure compatibility, reliability, and optimal performance. The FedNow Service is designed to be a platform for innovation, allowing financial institutions to adopt and build upon its capabilities over time. With the goal of offering new instant payment services to their customers, these institutions are expected to leverage FedNow for various use cases such as account-to-account transfers, requests for payment, bill payments, and more.  Crypto total market cap continues to recover &#124; Source: Crypto Total Market Cap on TradingView.com This forward-looking approach fosters a dynamic and evolving financial ecosystem, catering to the changing needs of businesses and individuals alike. In addition to the early adopters, the Federal Reserve continues to collaborate with financial institutions planning to join the FedNow Service later in 2023 and beyond.  This ongoing effort aims to build a robust network that encompasses all 10,000 US financial institutions, ensuring nationwide reach and accessibility.  Related Reading: Solana (SOL) Price Targets 40% Rally Amid Strong Fundamentals By facilitating participation from organizations of all sizes and geographical locations, the Federal Reserve paves the way for a comprehensive and inclusive instant payment ecosystem. This instant payment system is set to revolutionize the US payment infrastructure, enabling individuals and businesses to make faster and more efficient transactions. Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The United States Federal Reserve has made a significant <a href="https://www.reuters.com/technology/fed-says-57-firms-set-use-fednow-instant-payments-after-late-july-launch-2023-06-29/" rel="nofollow">announcement</a> regarding the certification of 57 organizations, including financial institutions and service providers, for the highly anticipated launch of the FedNow Service. </p>
<p>With major players in the banking industry, such as JPMorgan Chase, Bank of New York Mellon, US Bancorp, and Wells Fargo, among the certified entities named by the Fed, the stage is set for a transformative shift in the financial landscape.</p>
<h2>Testing And Certification Completion For FedNow</h2>
<p>The Federal Reserve has disclosed that 57 early adopter organizations have successfully completed formal testing and certification for the upcoming FedNow Service launch planned for late July.</p>

<p>This diverse group consists of financial institutions and service providers that are ready to send and receive transactions, supporting settlement and processing on behalf of participants.</p>
<p>The US Department of the Treasury is also among the early adopters, reflecting the breadth of involvement in this groundbreaking initiative.</p>
<h2>Readiness and Final Trial Runs</h2>
<p>The certified organizations are currently undergoing final trial runs to confirm their readiness in handling live transactions over the new instant payments infrastructure. </p>
<p>This critical phase ensures that the participants can seamlessly embrace the capabilities of FedNow, providing enhanced payment experiences to their customers.</p>
<p> As part of this process, comprehensive testing and validation have been conducted to ensure compatibility, reliability, and optimal performance.</p>
<p>The FedNow Service is designed to be a platform for innovation, allowing financial institutions to adopt and build upon its capabilities over time. With the goal of offering new instant payment services to their customers, these institutions are expected to leverage FedNow for various use cases such as account-to-account transfers, requests for payment, bill payments, and more. </p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/R2V5VbNa/" alt="Total crypto market cap chart from TradingView.com (FedNow)" width="2884" height="1724"/></p>

<p>This forward-looking approach fosters a dynamic and evolving financial ecosystem, catering to the changing needs of businesses and individuals alike.</p>
<p>In addition to the early adopters, the Federal Reserve continues to collaborate with financial institutions planning to join the FedNow Service later in 2023 and beyond. </p>
<p>This ongoing effort aims to build a robust network that encompasses all 10,000 US financial institutions, ensuring nationwide reach and accessibility. </p>

<p>By facilitating participation from organizations of all sizes and geographical locations, the Federal Reserve paves the way for a comprehensive and inclusive instant payment ecosystem.</p>
<p>This instant payment system is set to revolutionize the US payment infrastructure, enabling individuals and businesses to make faster and more efficient transactions.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/iStock-939248364-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>TRX Bulls Charge Ahead As Tron Network Prepares For Major Upgrade</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/trx/trx-bulls-charge-ahead-as-tron-network-prepares-for-major-upgrade/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 18:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[TRON]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blockchain technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tron (TRX)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[TRX Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[TRXUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=541095</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Tron (TRX) Network is set to undergo a major upgrade on July 11th, and TRX and other key metrics have seen a steady uptrend as the upgrade approaches. The upcoming Periander upgrade brings significant enhancements to the Tron Network, while TRX experiences a surge in on-chain metrics. Tron Network&#8217;s latest update, Great Voyage—v4.7.2 (Periander), introduces four critical upgrades aimed at enhancing the functionality and usability of the network. These upgrades include an advanced Stake 2.0 mechanism, seamless compatibility with Ethereum&#8217;s EIP-3855, streamlined smart contract interface calling, and a revamped P2P network module. Tron&#8217;s Periander Upgrade The new Stake 2.0 mechanism offers users greater flexibility in staking and unstaking their resources, with the ability to customize lockup periods for delegated resources according to their individual needs.  The compatibility with Ethereum&#8217;s EIP-3855 promotes interoperability between the two ecosystems, attracting more developers to TRON and reducing migration costs for projects across both chains.  Related Reading: XRP, Cardano Among Altcoins To Keep An Eye On: Santiment On the other hand, the streamlined smart contract interface calling provides developers with estimated transaction fees for deploying their contracts, simplifying the development of smart contracts.  Finally, the revamped P2P network module enhances the connection efficiency, availability, scalability, and transmission efficiency of the TRON network. TRON founder Justin Sun emphasized the organization&#8217;s commitment to fostering the growth of the TRON ecosystem, attracting more developers, capital, and users to the platform.  With over 169 million users worldwide, TRON has processed more than 6 billion transactions and boasts a total value locked (TVL) of over $5 billion. It has built a comprehensive ecosystem encompassing NFTs, DeFi, GameFi, stablecoins, the metaverse, and cross-chain solutions, and hosts the largest USDT circulating supply worth over $46 billion, making it an industry leader. Overall, the TRON MainNet Periander upgrade brings significant improvements to the Tron Network, providing greater flexibility, compatibility, and efficiency to its users and developers. The upgrade encourages greater participation in the network, attracts more developers to the platform, and stimulates the growth of the ecosystem.  The revamped P2P network module provides a robust infrastructure that empowers developers and users to explore new possibilities and drive innovation within the TRON ecosystem. On-chain Metrics Show Bullish Trend For TRX As the TRON Network&#8217;s upgrade day approaches, the platform has experienced a notable uptick in its on-chain metrics, according to data from DeFiLlama.  Since the beginning of the month, TRX&#8217;s trading volume has seen a gradual increase, which indicates that there is growing demand for the token. In the last few days, TRX&#8217;s trading volume has reached over $9 million.  Additionally, the network activity on TRON has also been rising in recent weeks. On-chain activity, such as the number of transactions and unique addresses, is an essential metric to consider.  In the lead-up to the upgrade, TRON&#8217;s on-chain activity has increased, which suggests that there is a growing demand for TRX. In the last three days alone, there have been over 20 million transactions on the TRON network.  This growing network activity and usage of the TRON network are positive indicators for the TRON ecosystem and could lead to further growth in the future.  Related Reading: Coinbase Stock Soars Nearly 12% As BlackRock Reveals Surveillance Partnership On the flip side, TRX has been on an uptrend since June 20th, starting from a value of $0.06788 and now trading above the $0.07784 mark. This represents a considerable gain of 13% over the last 14 days and 4% in the seven-day period. However, TRX is currently facing its yearly high resistance at the same trading level. This could potentially create a delay in reaching new yearly highs if it is unable to surpass its nearest resistance. Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com ]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Tron (TRX) Network is set to undergo a major <a href="https://www.media-outreach.com/news/china/2023/07/03/230687/tron-mainnet-unveils-four-critical-upgrades-realizing-justin-suns-vision-of-substantial-ecosystem-investment/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">upgrade </a>on July 11th, and TRX and other key metrics have seen a steady uptrend as the upgrade approaches. The upcoming Periander upgrade brings significant enhancements to the Tron Network, while TRX experiences a surge in on-chain metrics.</p>
<p>Tron Network&#8217;s latest update, Great Voyage—v4.7.2 (Periander), introduces four critical upgrades aimed at enhancing the functionality and usability of the network. These upgrades include an advanced Stake 2.0 mechanism, seamless compatibility with Ethereum&#8217;s EIP-3855, streamlined smart contract interface calling, and a revamped P2P network module.</p>
<h2>Tron&#8217;s Periander Upgrade</h2>
<p>The new Stake 2.0 mechanism offers users greater flexibility in staking and unstaking their resources, with the ability to customize lockup periods for delegated resources according to their individual needs. </p>
<p>The compatibility with Ethereum&#8217;s EIP-3855 promotes interoperability between the two ecosystems, attracting more developers to TRON and reducing migration costs for projects across both chains. </p>

<p>On the other hand, the streamlined smart contract interface calling provides developers with estimated transaction fees for deploying their contracts, simplifying the development of smart contracts. </p>
<p>Finally, the revamped P2P network module enhances the connection efficiency, availability, scalability, and transmission efficiency of the TRON network.</p>
<p>TRON founder Justin Sun emphasized the organization&#8217;s commitment to fostering the growth of the TRON ecosystem, attracting more developers, capital, and users to the platform. </p>
<p>With over 169 million users worldwide, TRON has processed more than 6 billion transactions and boasts a total value locked (TVL) of over $5 billion. It has built a comprehensive ecosystem encompassing NFTs, DeFi, GameFi, stablecoins, the metaverse, and cross-chain solutions, and hosts the largest USDT circulating supply worth over $46 billion, making it an industry leader.</p>
<p>Overall, the TRON MainNet Periander upgrade brings significant improvements to the Tron Network, providing greater flexibility, compatibility, and efficiency to its users and developers. The upgrade encourages greater participation in the network, attracts more developers to the platform, and stimulates the growth of the ecosystem. </p>
<p>The revamped P2P network module provides a robust infrastructure that empowers developers and users to explore new possibilities and drive innovation within the TRON ecosystem.</p>
On-chain Metrics Show Bullish Trend For TRX
<p>As the TRON Network&#8217;s upgrade day approaches, the platform has experienced a notable uptick in its on-chain metrics, according to <a href="https://defillama.com/chain/Tron?users=true&amp;tvl=true&amp;txs=true&amp;volume=true" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">data </a>from DeFiLlama. </p>
<p>Since the beginning of the month, TRX&#8217;s trading volume has seen a gradual increase, which indicates that there is growing demand for the token. In the last few days, TRX&#8217;s trading volume has reached over $9 million. </p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-541098 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot_9-860x555.jpg" alt="TRX" width="860" height="555" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot_9-860x555.jpg 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot_9-460x297.jpg 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot_9-768x496.jpg 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot_9-750x484.jpg 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot_9.jpg 981w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/>
<p>Additionally, the network activity on TRON has also been rising in recent weeks. On-chain activity, such as the number of transactions and unique addresses, is an essential metric to consider. </p>
<p>In the lead-up to the upgrade, TRON&#8217;s on-chain activity has increased, which suggests that there is a growing demand for TRX. In the last three days alone, there have been over 20 million transactions on the TRON network. </p>
<p>This growing network activity and usage of the TRON network are positive indicators for the TRON ecosystem and could lead to further growth in the future. </p>

<p>On the flip side, TRX has been on an uptrend since June 20th, starting from a value of $0.06788 and now trading above the $0.07784 mark. This represents a considerable gain of 13% over the last 14 days and 4% in the seven-day period.</p>
<p>However, TRX is currently facing its yearly high resistance at the same trading level. This could potentially create a delay in reaching new yearly highs if it is unable to surpass its nearest resistance.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/pBC73mBM/" alt="TRX" width="1815" height="858"/>
<p>Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/traxer-nKjTPPwEAsE-unsplash-460x306.jpg" width="460" height="306" />	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
