<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
>

<channel>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.newsbtc.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<description>Bitcoin &#38; Cryptocurrency News Today</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 12:37:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Exchange Supply Continues To Slip, Holders Not Interested In Selling?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-exchange-supply-slip-holders-interested-selling/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hououin Kyouma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 12:37:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Exchange Supply]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Selling]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=541540</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[On-chain data shows that the Bitcoin exchange supply has only continued to decline despite the recent rally that the asset has observed. Bitcoin Exchange Supply Continues To Register Net Decline According to data from the on-chain analytics firm Glassnode, exchanges have continued to see withdrawals recently. The indicator of interest here is the &#8220;exchange balance,&#8221; which measures the total amount of Bitcoin that&#8217;s currently sitting in the wallets of all centralized exchanges. When the value of this metric goes up, it means that the investors are depositing a net number of coins to these platforms currently. As one of the main reasons why holders may transfer their BTC to exchanges is for selling-related purposes, this kind of trend can have short-term bearish consequences for the price. On the other hand, decreasing values of the indicator imply a net amount of the supply is leaving from the exchanges. Such a trend, when prolonged, can be a sign that the investors are accumulating at the moment. Naturally, this could be constructive for the cryptocurrency&#8217;s price. Now, here is a chart that shows the trend in the Bitcoin exchange balance over the last few years: The value of the metric seems to have been going downhill in recent days &#124; Source: Glassnode on Twitter As displayed in the above graph, the Bitcoin exchange balance had been in an overall uptrend during 2018 and 2019, but with the COVID crash in March 2020, a shift happened in the market and the indicator started moving in a downward trajectory. There was a break in this trend during the 2021 bull run, as the metric mostly moved sideways, with some increases coming near the top of the rallies. This deviation in the trend was possibly a result of investors depositing to take advantage of the profit-taking opportunity. Related Reading: 75% Of Bitcoin Supply Now In Profit, Will A Drop Happen Here? With the end of the bull market and the transition toward a bearish period, though, the indicator resumed its decline. Events like the 3AC Collapse and the FTX Crash saw the exchange balance dropping especially hard, as these platforms going down made investors more wary of keeping their coins in centralized custody. With the start of the Bitcoin rally this year, however, the metric once again started moving sideways as demand for selling returned. In the leadup to the local top in April, exchanges were receiving net deposits as their supply outright registered an increase. Interestingly, while investors were looking to sell during the price surge back then, the latest uplift in the price above the $30,000 level has actually seen the exchange balance only decline further. This trend of net withdrawals can be a sign that there isn&#8217;t much appetite for selling in the market currently, at least when compared to the demand for taking coins to self-custody. Related Reading: Solana Registers 20% Rise In Past Week, But Can SOL Keep This Up? With the latest drawdown, the Bitcoin exchange balance has dropped to 2.26 million BTC, which is the lowest the indicator has been since way back in March 2018. BTC Price At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading around $30,700, up 1% in the last week. Looks like the asset has gone stale recently &#124; Source: BTCUSD on TradingView Featured image from Kanchanara on Unsplash.com, charts from TradingView.com, Glassnode.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On-chain data shows that the Bitcoin exchange supply has only continued to decline despite the recent rally that the asset has observed.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Exchange Supply Continues To Register Net Decline</h2>
<p>According to data from the on-chain analytics firm <a href="https://twitter.com/glassnode/status/1676613484186935302" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Glassnode</a>, exchanges have continued to see withdrawals recently. The indicator of interest here is the &#8220;<a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/dormant-bitcoin-now-16-higher-than-btc-in-exchange-reserves/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">exchange balance</a>,&#8221; which measures the total amount of Bitcoin that&#8217;s currently sitting in the wallets of all centralized exchanges.</p>
<p>When the value of this metric goes up, it means that the investors are depositing a net number of coins to these platforms currently. As one of the main reasons why holders may transfer their BTC to exchanges is for selling-related purposes, this kind of trend can have short-term bearish consequences for the price.</p>
<p>On the other hand, decreasing values of the indicator imply a net amount of the supply is leaving from the exchanges. Such a trend, when prolonged, can be a sign that the investors are accumulating at the moment. Naturally, this could be constructive for the cryptocurrency&#8217;s price.</p>
<p>Now, here is a chart that shows the trend in the Bitcoin exchange balance over the last few years:</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone aligncenter" src="https://pbs.twimg.com/media/F0SG7AYWcAImzCK?format=jpg&amp;name=4096x4096" alt="Bitcoin Exchange Balance" width="4053" height="2334"/></p>

<p>As displayed in the above graph, the Bitcoin exchange balance had been in an overall uptrend during 2018 and 2019, but with the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-sentiment-social-red-covid-crash-bottom-signal/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">COVID crash</a> in March 2020, a shift happened in the market and the indicator started moving in a downward trajectory.</p>
<p>There was a break in this trend during the 2021 bull run, as the metric mostly moved sideways, with some increases coming near the top of the rallies. This deviation in the trend was possibly a result of investors depositing to take advantage of the profit-taking opportunity.</p>

<p>With the end of the bull market and the transition toward a bearish period, though, the indicator resumed its decline. Events like the 3AC Collapse and the FTX Crash saw the exchange balance dropping especially hard, as these platforms going down made investors more wary of keeping their coins in centralized custody.</p>
<p>With the start of the Bitcoin rally this year, however, the metric once again started moving sideways as demand for selling returned. In the leadup to the local top in April, exchanges were receiving net deposits as their supply outright registered an increase.</p>
<p>Interestingly, while investors were looking to sell during the price surge back then, the latest uplift in the price <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-rejects-31k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">above the $30,000 level</a> has actually seen the exchange balance only decline further.</p>
<p>This trend of net withdrawals can be a sign that there isn&#8217;t much appetite for selling in the market currently, at least when compared to the demand for taking coins to self-custody.</p>

<p>With the latest drawdown, the Bitcoin exchange balance has dropped to 2.26 million BTC, which is the lowest the indicator has been since way back in March 2018.</p>
<h2>BTC Price</h2>
<p>At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading around $30,700, up 1% in the last week.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium aligncenter" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/t7FoJyyQ/" alt="Bitcoin Price Chart" width="1534" height="881"/></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/kanchanara-WrP_TBcstU0-unsplash-460x306.jpg" width="460" height="306" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Solana Registers 20% Rise In Past Week, But Can SOL Keep This Up?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/solana/solana-registers-20-rise-past-week-can-sol-keep-up/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hououin Kyouma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 11:00:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Solana]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sol]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Solana Rally]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SOLUSD]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=541471</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Solana has observed an increase of more than 20% in the past week. Here&#8217;s what on-chain data says regarding whether this is sustainable or not. Solana Trading Volume Has Remained Low Despite Price Rise In its latest insight post, the on-chain analytics firm Santiment has looked at the underlying metrics of Solana to see what has been driving the latest increase in the price. The firm has looked at the &#8220;social volume&#8221; of the cryptocurrency for various social media platforms and has found that the asset has seen elevated interest on Reddit recently. Here, the social volume refers to a metric that measures the total number of unique posts or threads on a given social media platform that is making at least one mention of SOL. This metric can tell us about the degree of discussion that the coin is currently receiving on the website in question. Now, below is a chart that shows the trend in the Solana social volume on four major social media platforms: Telegram, Reddit, Twitter, and 4chan. Looks like the value of the metric has been relatively low for most of these platforms &#124; Source: Santiment As displayed in the above graph, the Solana social volume on Reddit has seen some spikes as the cryptocurrency has risen during the past week or so. The other platforms, however, haven&#8217;t observed that much discussion related to the asset. Related Reading: Blame The “Supermoon” If Bitcoin Crashes Or Rallies Towards $35,000 In July A notable spike in the social volume on Reddit also occurred before the coin&#8217;s 5% surge during the past 24 hours. This may imply that interest from users on the platform could partly be helping fuel the rise. In terms of the actual trading volume, though, SOL has continued to observe muted activity, despite the growth. Here is a chart that displays the trend in this indicator: The value of the metric hasn't been too high recently &#124; Source: Santiment Interestingly, the initial, strong rise that Solana enjoyed was accompanied by elevated volumes, but at the start of this month, the indicator&#8217;s value noted some decline. Since this drop in volume, SOL has mostly moved sideways. Generally, for any price rise to be sustainable, high trading volumes are required. This is due to the fact that participation from a large number of traders is needed to provide enough fuel for any such price move to go on. Related Reading: Bitcoin Cash (BCH) Registers 28% Gain – How Long Will It Last? Despite the sharp growth that Solana has observed today, the trading volume remaining at low values would suggest that the wider market isn&#8217;t finding the rally interesting enough to make moves on the network. Naturally, if the rally has to go on for an extended period, volumes may have to return to the market. There is also the fact that the SOL funding rates (a measure of the periodic fee that futures traders are exchanging between each other) on Binance and DyDx have become quite positive recently. Longs are dominating the market &#124; Source: Santiment From the graph, it&#8217;s visible that the earlier increase in the asset&#8217;s price may have been helped by shorts being liquidated in the market &#8211; as the funding rates had been highly negative then. As long contract holders are the majority force in the futures market now, the chances of a long squeeze taking place are higher now. In this case, if one does take place, the price would feel a bearish effect. SOL Price At the time of writing, Solana is trading around $20, up 20% in the last week. SOL has shot up in the past day &#124; Source: SOLUSD on TradingView Featured image from GuerrillaBuzz on Unsplash.com, charts from TradingView.com, Santiment.net]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Solana has observed an increase of more than 20% in the past week. Here&#8217;s what on-chain data says regarding whether this is sustainable or not.</p>
<h2>Solana Trading Volume Has Remained Low Despite Price Rise</h2>
<p>In its latest insight post, the on-chain analytics firm <a href="https://insights.santiment.net/read/solana-showing-signs-7336?fpr=twitter" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Santiment</a> has looked at the underlying metrics of Solana to see what has been driving the latest increase in the price.</p>
<p>The firm has looked at the &#8220;<a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/dogecoin-2/dogecoin-up-5-but-social-media-talk-remains-low-santiment/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">social volume</a>&#8221; of the cryptocurrency for various social media platforms and has found that the asset has seen elevated interest on Reddit recently.</p>
<p>Here, the social volume refers to a metric that measures the total number of unique posts or threads on a given social media platform that is making at least one mention of SOL. This metric can tell us about the degree of discussion that the coin is currently receiving on the website in question.</p>
<p>Now, below is a chart that shows the trend in the Solana social volume on four major social media platforms: Telegram, Reddit, Twitter, and 4chan.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone aligncenter" src="https://production-sanbase-images.s3.amazonaws.com/uploads/ca84ac009d9b67e9bbf9ee60c4b0881a5af5c5fc3486827b06d5f0028668682a_1688606181708_Screenshot%202023-07-05%20181600.png" alt="Solana Social Volume" width="3079" height="1749"/></p>

<p>As displayed in the above graph, the Solana social volume on Reddit has seen some spikes as the cryptocurrency has risen during the past week or so. The other platforms, however, haven&#8217;t observed that much discussion related to the asset.</p>

<p>A notable spike in the social volume on Reddit also occurred before the coin&#8217;s 5% surge during the past 24 hours. This may imply that interest from users on the platform could partly be helping fuel the rise.</p>
<p>In terms of the actual <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/pepe/pepe-surge-trading-volume-outshines-shib-and-doge-will-this-trend-continue/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">trading volume</a>, though, SOL has continued to observe muted activity, despite the growth.</p>
<p>Here is a chart that displays the trend in this indicator:</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone aligncenter" src="https://production-sanbase-images.s3.amazonaws.com/uploads/c91aa859665a658588d3a38155aaa390961fb2668e1e4412a8a51836731c5d38_1688604861680_Screenshot%202023-07-05%20175138.png" alt="Solana Trading Volume" width="3144" height="1672"/></p>

<p>Interestingly, the initial, strong rise that Solana enjoyed was accompanied by elevated volumes, but at the start of this month, the indicator&#8217;s value noted some decline. Since this drop in volume, SOL has mostly moved sideways.</p>
<p>Generally, for any price rise to be sustainable, high trading volumes are required. This is due to the fact that participation from a large number of traders is needed to provide enough fuel for any such price move to go on.</p>

<p>Despite the sharp growth that Solana has observed today, the trading volume remaining at low values would suggest that the wider market isn&#8217;t finding the rally interesting enough to make moves on the network. Naturally, if the rally has to go on for an extended period, volumes may have to return to the market.</p>
<p>There is also the fact that the SOL <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-funding-rates-bitmex-deep-red-why-bullish/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">funding rates</a> (a measure of the periodic fee that futures traders are exchanging between each other) on Binance and DyDx have become quite positive recently.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone aligncenter" src="https://production-sanbase-images.s3.amazonaws.com/uploads/ef74728f7edffa8e96d05b8a94018489673470699ef380b91e2f4a2b5d36c12c_1688604884219_Screenshot%202023-07-05%20175236.png" alt="Solana Funding Rates" width="3150" height="1672"/></p>

<p>From the graph, it&#8217;s visible that the earlier increase in the asset&#8217;s price may have been helped by shorts being liquidated in the market &#8211; as the funding rates had been highly negative then.</p>
<p>As long contract holders are the majority force in the futures market now, the chances of a long squeeze taking place are higher now. In this case, if one does take place, the price would feel a bearish effect.</p>
<h2>SOL Price</h2>
<p>At the time of writing, Solana is trading around $20, up 20% in the last week.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium aligncenter" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/7n5pw6iD/" alt="Solana Price Chart" width="1534" height="881"/></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/guerrillabuzz-cuK9BLM_mAQ-unsplash-460x259.jpg" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Breaking: Shiba Inu Lead Dev Reveals Shibarium Release Date, SHIB Up 3%</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/shiba-inu-lead-dev-reveals-shibarium-release-date/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jake Simmons]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 09:45:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Shiba Inu]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BONE]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIB]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shibarium]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Treat]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[World Paper]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=541472</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Breaking Shiba Inu news: The highly anticipated layer-2 solution Shibarium, along with other groundbreaking developments, is set to be unveiled at the upcoming Blockchain Futurist Conference and ETHToronto. Shiba Inu&#8217;s lead developer, Shytoshi Kusama, revealed in a new blog post today that these events will serve as platforms for showcasing Shibarium along with the finalized Worldpaper, introducing SHIB-branded projects, and shedding light on Treat. Sweet August For Shiba Inu Army Scheduled for August 15-16, 2023, ETHToronto and the Blockchain Futurist Conference will provide the perfect backdrop for Shiba Inu&#8217;s grand unveiling. ETHToronto is the official hackathon of the Blockchain Futurist Conference and a huge event for the entire Ethereum ecosystem. Related Reading: Recent 800 Billion Shiba Inu Dump Has Short Traders Worried – Here’s Why As the title sponsor, Shiba Inu solidifies its position as &#8220;a major player in the crypto space&#8221;, as emphasized by Kusama in the blog post. Remarkably, the release date aligns with SHIB&#8217;s approximate 3-year anniversary and being the birthplace of Eth. The SHIB community can expect an immersive experience, featuring presentations, demonstrations, and discussions that will reshape the future of Shiba Inu&#8217;s decentralized finance and governance. The highlight of these events will undoubtedly be the introduction of Shibarium, the highly anticipated cornerstone of Shiba Inu&#8217;s ecosystem. Shibarium aims to push the boundaries of scaling Ethereum, providing innovative solutions for the Shiba Inu community. The long-awaited L2 holds immense potential for revolutionizing the Shiba Inu ecosystem. Remarkably, the event is not only about Shibarium. As part of the events, all SHIB-branded projects will be unveiled, showcasing the project&#8217;s commitment to building a diverse and vibrant ecosystem. These projects, including Shib the Metaverse, Shibacals, Shiba Eternity, and Shiboshis, represent the multifaceted nature of Shiba Inu&#8217;s vision. As Kusama writes, there will also be new partnerships announced with Unification and Bad Idea.Ai. Furthermore, all projects that expressed interest in building with Shibarium Tech will be showcased at the conferences. Related Reading: Shiba Inu Records Surge In Daily New Addresses In Q2: A Sign Of Growing Interest? Shiba Inu&#8217;s lead developer also emphasized the significance of Treat, a pivotal component of the project&#8217;s governance framework. At the Blockchain Futurist Conference, Treat will be publicly detailed for the first time. The SHIB army can expect comprehensive insights into Treat&#8217;s functionality and its role in empowering the decentralized ecosystem. Kusama stated: At this venue [Blockchain Futurist Conference]], the finalized Worldpaper will be showcased, all Shib-branded projects will be unveiled, and Treat will be detailed publicly for the first time. Additionally, discussions and potential releases of the long-awaited L2 Shibarium are highly likely. SHIB Is Up 3% With the news, the countdown to the eagerly awaited Blockchain Futurist Conference, where Shiba Inu will take center stage, has begun, and with it, possibly, a renewed SHIB hype. At press time, SHIB was trading at $0.00000758 and has risen around 3% since the publication of Kusama&#8217;s blog post. This puts the SHIB price on the verge of a possible breakout from the downtrend channel that has been in place since early February. A significant rise above $0.000008 towards the 38.2% Fibonacci retracement level ($0.00000831) and a subsequent breakout above this resistance is needed to avoid a fakeout. Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Breaking Shiba Inu news: The highly anticipated layer-2 solution Shibarium, along with other groundbreaking developments, is set to be unveiled at the upcoming Blockchain Futurist Conference and ETHToronto. Shiba Inu&#8217;s lead developer, Shytoshi Kusama, <a href="https://twitter.com/LucieSHIB/status/1676871206555770881" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">revealed</a> in a new blog post today that these events will serve as platforms for showcasing Shibarium along with the finalized Worldpaper, introducing SHIB-branded projects, and shedding light on Treat.</p>
<h2>Sweet August For Shiba Inu Army</h2>
<p>Scheduled for August 15-16, 2023, ETHToronto and the Blockchain Futurist Conference will provide the perfect backdrop for Shiba Inu&#8217;s grand unveiling. ETHToronto is the official hackathon of the Blockchain Futurist Conference and a huge event for the entire Ethereum ecosystem.</p>

<p>As the title sponsor, Shiba Inu solidifies its position as &#8220;a major player in the crypto space&#8221;, as emphasized by Kusama in the blog post. Remarkably, the release date aligns with SHIB&#8217;s approximate 3-year anniversary and being the birthplace of Eth.</p>
<p>The SHIB community can expect an immersive experience, featuring presentations, demonstrations, and discussions that will reshape the future of Shiba Inu&#8217;s decentralized finance and governance. The highlight of these events will undoubtedly be the introduction of Shibarium, the highly anticipated cornerstone of Shiba Inu&#8217;s ecosystem.</p>
<p>Shibarium aims to push the boundaries of scaling Ethereum, providing innovative solutions for the Shiba Inu community. The long-awaited L2 holds immense <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/shibarium-reaches-new-milestones-as-anticipation-builds/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">potential</a> for revolutionizing the Shiba Inu ecosystem.</p>
<p>Remarkably, the event is not only about Shibarium. As part of the events, all SHIB-branded projects will be unveiled, showcasing the project&#8217;s commitment to building a diverse and vibrant ecosystem. These projects, including Shib the Metaverse, <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/shiba-inu-lead-developer-unveils-shibacals-advancing-shibarium-development/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Shibacals</a>, Shiba Eternity, and Shiboshis, represent the multifaceted nature of Shiba Inu&#8217;s vision.</p>
<p>As Kusama writes, there will also be new partnerships announced with Unification and Bad Idea.Ai. Furthermore, all projects that expressed interest in building with Shibarium Tech will be showcased at the conferences.</p>

<p>Shiba Inu&#8217;s lead developer also emphasized the significance of Treat, a pivotal component of the project&#8217;s governance framework. At the Blockchain Futurist Conference, Treat will be publicly detailed for the first time. The SHIB army can expect comprehensive insights into Treat&#8217;s functionality and its role in empowering the decentralized ecosystem. Kusama stated:</p>
<blockquote><p><strong>At this venue [Blockchain Futurist Conference]], the finalized Worldpaper will be showcased, all Shib-branded projects will be unveiled, and Treat will be detailed publicly for the first time. Additionally, discussions and potential releases of the long-awaited L2 Shibarium are highly likely.</strong></p></blockquote>
<h2>SHIB Is Up 3%</h2>
<p>With the news, the countdown to the eagerly awaited Blockchain Futurist Conference, where Shiba Inu will take center stage, has begun, and with it, possibly, a renewed SHIB hype.</p>
<p>At press time, SHIB was trading at $0.00000758 and has risen around 3% since the publication of Kusama&#8217;s blog post. This puts the SHIB price on the verge of a possible breakout from the downtrend channel that has been in place since early February. A significant rise above $0.000008 towards the 38.2% Fibonacci retracement level ($0.00000831) and a subsequent breakout above this resistance is needed to avoid a fakeout.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-541486 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/SHIBUSD_2023-07-06_11-19-18.png" alt="Shiba Inu SHIB price" width="3628" height="1672" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/SHIBUSD_2023-07-06_11-19-18.png 3628w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/SHIBUSD_2023-07-06_11-19-18-460x212.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/SHIBUSD_2023-07-06_11-19-18-860x396.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/SHIBUSD_2023-07-06_11-19-18-768x354.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/SHIBUSD_2023-07-06_11-19-18-1536x708.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/SHIBUSD_2023-07-06_11-19-18-2048x944.png 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/SHIBUSD_2023-07-06_11-19-18-750x346.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/SHIBUSD_2023-07-06_11-19-18-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 3628px) 100vw, 3628px"/>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/iStock-1311148884-460x316.jpg" width="460" height="316" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Cash (BCH) Registers 28% Gain &#8211; How Long Will It Last?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin-cash-bch-registers-28-gain-how-long-with-it-last/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 09:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BCH Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Cash]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=541463</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin Cash (BCH) is captivating the attention of the crypto community with its ongoing price surge. The recent inclusion of BCH on EDX, a Citadel Securities-backed crypto exchange, has sparked fresh interest in this digital asset.  As investors eagerly monitor its progress, the price of BCH on CoinGecko stands at $291.80, showcasing a 24-hour rally of nearly 7% and an impressive seven-day surge of 27.5%. Source: Coingecko The overall bullish sentiment in the crypto market has contributed to the positive trajectory of BCH. As cryptocurrencies gain mainstream acceptance and adoption, investors are seeking alternatives beyond the traditional giants like Bitcoin and Ethereum, and BCH has emerged as a viable contender. However, the question on everyone&#8217;s mind is whether Bitcoin Cash can sustain its current bullish streak. BCH Whales Pause Buying Spree Amidst Price Surge While the recent listing on EDX has undoubtedly played a part in this rally, on-chain data reveals an intriguing aspect of the price surge. A cluster of Bitcoin Cash whales holding significant amounts of 1 million to 10 million coins has emerged as a pivotal player in driving last month’s rally. Source: Santiment Between June 21 and June 30, these BCH whales accumulated 170,000 coins, which amounted to approximately $52.4 million in value. Their substantial purchases had a significant impact on the asset&#8217;s price, as whales possess substantial financial power and strategic influence on other investors. When whales buy more coins, it often leads to an increase in the asset&#8217;s price. Related Reading: Recent 800 Billion Shiba Inu Dump Has Short Traders Worried – Here’s Why However, an interesting development emerged in July. The same cluster of BCH whales, who were actively accumulating coins during the June rally, has conspicuously paused their buying spree. Specifically, between July 1 and July 4, their total BCH balances remained relatively stable, hovering around 1.51 million coins. BCH market cap currently at $5.6 billion. Chart: TradingView.com The Future Trajectory Of Bitcoin Cash The whales&#8217; decision to halt their buying activity raises questions about the current market sentiment surrounding Bitcoin Cash. Are these whales taking a cautious approach, waiting to assess the market before making further moves? Or does their pause indicate a temporary lull in the BCH price surge? Related Reading: Dwindling Optimism (OP) Value May Be A Result Of This Factor Understanding the behavior of large-scale investors such as whales is essential in predicting market trends. Their actions often influence the sentiments and decisions of other traders and investors. The temporary pause in their buying activity could potentially impact the short-term price dynamics of Bitcoin Cash. As the market eagerly watches Bitcoin Cash, the question arises as to whether the recent price surge can be sustained without the continued support of these influential whales. The coming weeks will shed light on the market&#8217;s overall sentiment and the role these whales will play in shaping the future trajectory of Bitcoin Cash. (This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk). Featured image from Crypto Economy]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin Cash (BCH) is captivating the attention of the crypto community with its ongoing price surge. The recent inclusion of BCH on EDX, a Citadel Securities-backed crypto exchange, has sparked fresh interest in this digital asset. </p>
<p>As investors eagerly monitor its progress, the price of <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/bitcoin-cash/usd" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">BCH on CoinGecko</a> stands at $291.80, showcasing a 24-hour rally of nearly 7% and an impressive seven-day surge of 27.5%.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-541464" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-32.png" alt="" width="1137" height="61" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-32.png 1137w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-32-460x25.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-32-860x46.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-32-768x41.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-32-750x40.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 1137px) 100vw, 1137px"/></p>

<p>The overall bullish sentiment in the crypto market has contributed to the positive trajectory of BCH. As cryptocurrencies gain mainstream acceptance and adoption, investors are seeking alternatives beyond the traditional giants like Bitcoin and Ethereum, and BCH has emerged as a viable contender.</p>
<p>However, the question on everyone&#8217;s mind is whether Bitcoin Cash can sustain its current bullish streak.</p>
<h2><strong>BCH Whales Pause Buying Spree Amidst Price Surge</strong></h2>
<p>While the recent listing on EDX has undoubtedly played a part in this rally, <a href="https://embed.santiment.net/chart?ps=bitcoin-cash&amp;pt=BCH&amp;df=2023-06-18T00%3A00%3A00.000Z&amp;dt=2023-07-04T00%3A00%3A00.000Z&amp;emcg=1&amp;wm=price_usd%3Bholders_distribution_combined_balance_1M_to_10M&amp;wax=0%3B1&amp;wc=%2326C953%3B%235275FF&amp;ws=%7B%22interval%22%3A%221d%22%7D%3B" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">on-chain data </a>reveals an intriguing aspect of the price surge. A cluster of Bitcoin Cash whales holding significant amounts of 1 million to 10 million coins has emerged as a pivotal player in driving last month’s rally.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-541466 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-33-860x386.png" alt="" width="860" height="386" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-33-860x386.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-33-460x207.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-33-768x345.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-33-1536x690.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-33-750x337.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-33-1140x512.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-33.png 1879w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/></p>

<p>Between June 21 and June 30, these BCH whales accumulated 170,000 coins, which amounted to approximately $52.4 million in value. Their substantial purchases had a significant impact on the asset&#8217;s price, as whales possess substantial financial power and strategic influence on other investors. When whales buy more coins, it often leads to an increase in the asset&#8217;s price.</p>

<p>However, an interesting development emerged in July. The same cluster of BCH whales, who were actively accumulating coins during the June rally, has conspicuously paused their buying spree. Specifically, between July 1 and July 4, their total BCH balances remained relatively stable, hovering around 1.51 million coins.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/ZJLoDKf7/" width="2475" height="1187"/></p>

<h2><strong>The Future Trajectory Of Bitcoin Cash</strong></h2>
<p>The whales&#8217; decision to halt their buying activity raises questions about the current market sentiment surrounding Bitcoin Cash. Are these whales taking a cautious approach, waiting to assess the market before making further moves? Or does their pause indicate a <a href="https://ambcrypto.com/bitcoin-cash-whats-the-best-entry-point-for-buyers-as-bch-goes-on-a-rally/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">temporary lull in the BCH price surge?</a></p>

<p>Understanding the behavior of large-scale investors such as whales is essential in predicting market trends. Their actions often influence the sentiments and decisions of other traders and investors. The temporary pause in their buying activity could potentially impact the short-term price dynamics of Bitcoin Cash.</p>
<p>As the market eagerly watches Bitcoin Cash, the question arises as to whether the recent price surge can be sustained without the continued support of these influential whales. The coming weeks will shed light on the market&#8217;s overall sentiment and the role these whales will play in shaping the future trajectory of Bitcoin Cash.</p>
<p><em>(This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk).</em></p>
<p><em>Featured image from Crypto Economy</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-35-460x257.png" width="460" height="257" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Recent 800 Billion Shiba Inu Dump Has Short Traders Worried &#8211; Here&#8217;s Why</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/recent-800-billion-shiba-inu-dump-has-short-traders-worried-heres-why/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 07:05:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BONE]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[meme coins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price action]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIB price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shiba Inu]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=541443</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Shiba Inu (SHIB) recently faced a major token dump of epic proportions, with a whopping 800 billion SHIB tokens being thrown into the market. But what caused this massive sell-off and what does it mean for the future of Shiba Inu? This major token offloading extravaganza went down on Binance alone, with traders ditching their SHIB for USDT. The Buying Selling View indicator revealed that this frenzy took place from 8:00 a.m. to 12:00 p.m. UTC. To understand the degree of the situation, let&#8217;s delve into the factors behind this recent market movement and explore the potential consequences for both short-term traders and long-term SHIB investors. What SHIB Offloading Means For Short-Term Traders When a massive token offloading event like the recent SHIB dump occurs, it creates a ripple effect that can have significant implications, especially for short-term sellers aiming for quick gains.  Related Reading: Dwindling Optimism (OP) Value May Be A Result Of This Factor Token dumps often result in increased market volatility, causing sudden price drops and erratic fluctuations. For short-term traders, this can be both a bane and boon. On one hand, volatility presents opportunities for quick profits if they time their trades well. On the other hand, it also raises the risk of unexpected losses if the market turns against their positions. Source: TradingView Massive offloading events tend to put downward pressure on the token&#8217;s price. The increased supply flooding the market can lead to price depreciation, which may discourage short-term traders from entering or maintaining their positions. This, in turn, can impact the overall trading sentiment and make it harder for traders to secure favorable gains. Related Reading: Lido (LDO) Sustains Weekly Run With 16% Gain – What Fuels It? Source: Coingecko As per CoinGecko, the price of SHIB currently stands at $0.00000743, reflecting a decline of 3.4% over the past 24 hours. However, despite this recent dip, SHIB has managed to rally by 2.8% over the course of the past seven days. SHIB market cap currently at $4.3 billion. Chart: TradingView.com SHIB Ecosystem Token&#8217;s Impressive Rally  Meanwhile, amidst all the action, Shiba Inu&#8217;s ecosystem token, Bone, experienced an astounding rally of over 25% in the past 14 days, delivering substantial returns to investors in the third quarter of 2023. This surge propelled the cryptocurrency&#8217;s price to surpass the $1 mark. However, after reaching a peak of $1.09, the price of Bone entered a correction phase and has been struggling to regain momentum on the charts. $BONE it’s time for $2-$3 serious pep talk pic.twitter.com/1MQgUHnXCw — 𝐋𝐔𝐂𝐈𝐄 (@LucieSHIB) July 3, 2023 LucieSHIB, a marketing specialist for Shiba Inu, recently took to Twitter and expressed optimism by stating that it&#8217;s time for Bone&#8217;s price to target the $2 to $3 range. While it remains to be seen whether Lucie&#8217;s prediction will come to fruition, only time will provide the answer to this intriguing question. (This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk). Featured image from Corporate Finance Institute]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Shiba Inu (SHIB) recently faced a major token dump of epic proportions, with a whopping 800 billion SHIB tokens being thrown into the market. But what caused this massive sell-off and what does it mean for the future of Shiba Inu?</p>
<p>This major token offloading extravaganza went down on Binance alone, with traders ditching their SHIB for USDT. The Buying Selling View indicator revealed that this frenzy took place from 8:00 a.m. to 12:00 p.m. UTC.</p>
<p>To understand the degree of the situation, let&#8217;s delve into the factors behind this recent market movement and explore the potential consequences for both short-term traders and long-term SHIB investors.</p>
<h2><strong>What SHIB Offloading Means For Short-Term Traders</strong></h2>
<p>When a massive token offloading event like the <a href="https://u.today/shiba-inus-800-billion-shib-dump-creates-epic-red-candle-chaos" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">recent SHIB dump</a> occurs, it creates a ripple effect that can have significant implications, especially for short-term sellers aiming for quick gains. </p>

<p>Token dumps often result in increased market volatility, causing sudden price drops and erratic fluctuations. For short-term traders, this can be both a bane and boon. On one hand, volatility presents opportunities for quick profits if they time their trades well. On the other hand, it also raises the risk of unexpected losses if the market turns against their positions.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-541451 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-29-860x436.png" alt="" width="860" height="436" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-29-860x436.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-29-460x233.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-29-768x389.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-29-1536x778.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-29-750x380.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-29-1140x578.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-29.png 1762w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/></p>

<p>Massive offloading events tend to put downward pressure on the token&#8217;s price. The increased supply flooding the market can lead to price depreciation, which may discourage short-term traders from entering or maintaining their positions. This, in turn, can impact the overall trading sentiment and make it harder for traders to secure favorable gains.</p>

<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-541453" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-30.png" alt="" width="1033" height="76" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-30.png 1033w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-30-460x34.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-30-860x63.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-30-768x57.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-30-750x55.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 1033px) 100vw, 1033px"/></p>

<p>As per <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/shiba-inu" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">CoinGecko</a>, the price of SHIB currently stands at $0.00000743, reflecting a decline of 3.4% over the past 24 hours. However, despite this recent dip, SHIB has managed to rally by 2.8% over the course of the past seven days.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/Aecg8Vr5/" width="2475" height="1187"/></p>

<h2><strong>SHIB Ecosystem Token&#8217;s Impressive Rally </strong></h2>
<p>Meanwhile, amidst all the action, Shiba Inu&#8217;s ecosystem token, Bone, experienced an <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/bone-shibaswap" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">astounding rally</a> of over 25% in the past 14 days, delivering substantial returns to investors in the third quarter of 2023. This surge propelled the cryptocurrency&#8217;s price to surpass the $1 mark. However, after reaching a peak of $1.09, the price of Bone entered a correction phase and has been struggling to regain momentum on the charts.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en"><a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24BONE&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$BONE</a></p>
<p>it’s time for $2-$3 serious pep talk <a href="https://t.co/1MQgUHnXCw" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/1MQgUHnXCw</a></p>
<p>— 𝐋𝐔𝐂𝐈𝐄 (@LucieSHIB) <a href="https://twitter.com/LucieSHIB/status/1675753955551326208?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">July 3, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p>LucieSHIB, a marketing specialist for Shiba Inu, recently took to Twitter and expressed optimism by stating that it&#8217;s time for Bone&#8217;s price to target the <a href="https://twitter.com/LucieSHIB/status/1675753955551326208" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">$2 to $3 range</a>. While it remains to be seen whether Lucie&#8217;s prediction will come to fruition, only time will provide the answer to this intriguing question.</p>
<p><em>(This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk).</em></p>
<p><em>Featured image from Corporate Finance Institute</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-31-460x303.png" width="460" height="303" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Celsius Starts Swapping Altcoins for Bitcoin, ETH; Chainlink, Aave, Others At Risk</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/celsius-swaps-altcoins-bitcoin-eth-chainlink-aave-at-risk/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jake Simmons]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 06:25:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[aave]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BNB]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[celsius]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[chainlink]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Link]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MATIC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Polygon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[UNI]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=541422</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bankrupt crypto lender Celsius Network has begun the process of swapping altcoins for Bitcoin (BTC) and Ethereum (ETH). The recent court approval (June 30) granted the company permission to convert its altcoin holdings into the two leading digital assets, raising concerns about a potential sell-off of popular altcoins. Celsius Network, known for its altcoin lending services, has been undergoing bankruptcy proceedings since July 2022 when it filed for Chapter 11 protection, revealing liabilities of up to $10 billion. The recent court ruling allows Celsius to convert its altcoins into BTC and ETH starting from July 1. LINK, AAVE And SNX Sell-Off Due To Celsius Coming? According to on-chain analysis provider Lookonchain, Celsius has been actively transferring altcoins to different wallets. Most of the altcoins have been moved to wallet address &#8220;0x4131&#8221;. Remarkably, Celsius made its first swap today. Lookonchain tweeted: Note that Celsius seems to be starting to swap altcoins for BTC and ETH. Currently: Most of the altcoins have been transferred to wallet&#8221;0x4131&#8243;. Transferred 1,393 StaFi( $rETH) to Wintermute Trading and received 1,393 $ETH.  The altcoins held by Celsius Network amount to approximately $164.5 million on the EVM chain, including: 3.16 million LINK ($19.9 million) 98,268 AAVE ($7.36 million) 2.9 million SNX ($6.2 million) 7.95 million TGBP ($5.49 million) 1,812 PAXG ($3.45 million) 12.650 BNB ($3.02 million) 3.841 million MATIC ($2.65 million) 419,899 UNI ($2.27 million) 9.25 million ZRX (2.00 million) In addition to the above, Celsius Network&#8217;s wallets also contain around $296 million worth of Bitcoin, $120 million worth of Ethereum, and approximately $100 million (in paper value) of its native token CEL. Yesterday, data from Arkham Intelligence revealed that Celsius moved around $70 million worth of altcoins and stablecoins to different wallets, including those related to crypto market maker Wintermute, crypto custodian Fireblocks, and stablecoin issuer Paxos. Related Reading: Blame The “Supermoon” If Bitcoin Crashes Or Rallies Towards $35,000 In July Today&#8217;s first swap of altcoins to Ethereum by Celsius Network raises concerns that the movements to new addresses was just the preparation for a potential sell-off for the aforementioned altcoins. LINK, AAVE and SNX could face a dump if Celsius sells these altcoins in one go, but the prices of MATIC, UNI, ZRX and BNB could also see a negative impact. It&#8217;s worth noting that while the court approval allows Celsius to convert altcoins into BTC and ETH, the exact details and timeline of the conversion process remain unclear. It is uncertain whether Celsius plans to sell all of its altcoins and in what proportion it intends to acquire BTC and ETH. Traders and investors holding the aforementioned altcoins should closely monitor market developments and prepare for possible market turbulence. Related Reading: Valkyrie Follows In BlackRock’s Footsteps, Refiles For Spot Bitcoin ETF Chainlink Price At Risk? Celsius&#8217; largest altcoin holding, Chainlink, could potentially see the most selling pressure, and the timing is conceivably bad. Just two weeks ago, the LINK price managed to climb back into the 1+ year trading range between $5.31 and $9.62. Earlier in the week, the LINK price was rejected at the 38.2% Fibonacci retracement level. A dump of Celsius could put the price in danger of falling again to the lower end of the trading range. LINK marines should therefore closely monitor the addresses by the bankrupt crypto lender. Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bankrupt crypto lender Celsius Network has begun the process of swapping altcoins for Bitcoin (BTC) and Ethereum (ETH). The recent court approval (June 30) granted the company permission to convert its altcoin holdings into the two leading digital assets, raising <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/cardano-solana-matic-sell-off-coming-today/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">concerns</a> about a potential sell-off of popular altcoins.</p>
<p>Celsius Network, known for its altcoin lending services, has been undergoing bankruptcy proceedings since July 2022 when it filed for Chapter 11 protection, revealing liabilities of up to $10 billion. The recent court ruling allows Celsius to convert its altcoins into BTC and ETH starting from July 1.</p>
<h2>LINK, AAVE And SNX Sell-Off Due To Celsius Coming?</h2>
<p>According to on-chain analysis provider Lookonchain, Celsius has been actively transferring altcoins to different wallets. Most of the altcoins have been moved to wallet address &#8220;0x4131&#8221;. Remarkably, Celsius made its first swap today. Lookonchain <a href="https://twitter.com/lookonchain/status/1676797417927372801" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">tweeted</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p><strong>Note that Celsius seems to be starting to swap altcoins for BTC and ETH. </strong><strong>Currently: Most of the altcoins have been transferred to wallet&#8221;0x4131&#8243;. Transferred 1,393 StaFi( $rETH) to Wintermute Trading and received 1,393 $ETH. </strong></p></blockquote>
<p>The altcoins held by Celsius Network amount to approximately $164.5 million on the EVM chain, including:</p>
<ul>
<li>3.16 million LINK ($19.9 million)</li>
<li>98,268 AAVE ($7.36 million)</li>
<li>2.9 million SNX ($6.2 million)</li>
<li>7.95 million TGBP ($5.49 million)</li>
<li>1,812 PAXG ($3.45 million)</li>
<li>12.650 BNB ($3.02 million)</li>
<li>3.841 million MATIC ($2.65 million)</li>
<li>419,899 UNI ($2.27 million)</li>
<li>9.25 million ZRX (2.00 million)</li>
</ul>
<p>In addition to the above, Celsius Network&#8217;s wallets also contain around $296 million worth of Bitcoin, $120 million worth of Ethereum, and approximately $100 million (in paper value) of its native token CEL.</p>
<p>Yesterday, data from Arkham Intelligence revealed that Celsius moved around $70 million worth of altcoins and stablecoins to different wallets, including those related to crypto market maker Wintermute, crypto custodian Fireblocks, and stablecoin issuer Paxos.</p>

<p>Today&#8217;s first swap of altcoins to Ethereum by Celsius Network raises concerns that the movements to new addresses was just the preparation for a potential sell-off for the aforementioned altcoins. LINK, AAVE and SNX could face a dump if Celsius sells these altcoins in one go, but the prices of MATIC, UNI, ZRX and BNB could also see a negative impact.</p>
<p>It&#8217;s worth noting that while the court approval allows Celsius to convert altcoins into BTC and ETH, the exact details and timeline of the conversion process remain unclear. It is uncertain whether Celsius plans to sell all of its altcoins and in what proportion it intends to acquire BTC and ETH.</p>
<p>Traders and investors holding the aforementioned altcoins should closely monitor market developments and prepare for possible market turbulence.</p>

<h2>Chainlink Price At Risk?</h2>
<p>Celsius&#8217; largest altcoin holding, Chainlink, could potentially see the most selling pressure, and the timing is conceivably bad. Just two weeks ago, the LINK price managed to climb back into the 1+ year trading range between $5.31 and $9.62.</p>
<p>Earlier in the week, the LINK price was rejected at the 38.2% Fibonacci retracement level. A dump of Celsius could put the price in danger of falling again to the lower end of the trading range. LINK marines should therefore closely monitor the addresses by the bankrupt crypto lender.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-541433 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/LINKUSD_2023-07-06_07-25-30.png" alt="Chainlink dump Celsius incoming?" width="3628" height="1672" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/LINKUSD_2023-07-06_07-25-30.png 3628w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/LINKUSD_2023-07-06_07-25-30-460x212.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/LINKUSD_2023-07-06_07-25-30-860x396.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/LINKUSD_2023-07-06_07-25-30-768x354.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/LINKUSD_2023-07-06_07-25-30-1536x708.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/LINKUSD_2023-07-06_07-25-30-2048x944.png 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/LINKUSD_2023-07-06_07-25-30-750x346.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/LINKUSD_2023-07-06_07-25-30-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 3628px) 100vw, 3628px"/>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/iStock-1367449613-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>ADA Price Indicators Suggest Cardano at Clear Risk of Further Declines</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/ada/ada-price-cardano-declines-0-262/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 05:21:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[ADA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[adausd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADAUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=541429</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Cardano’s price is declining from the $0.30 zone. ADA could continue to move down if it breaks the $0.280 support zone in the near term. ADA price is moving lower from the $0.302 zone against the US dollar. The price is trading below $0.290 and the 100 simple moving average (4 hours). There was a break below a key bullish trend line with support near $0.2960 on the 4-hour chart of the ADA/USD pair (data source from Kraken). The pair could slide further toward the $0.264 support zone. Cardano’s ADA Price Corrects Gains This past week, Cardano’s price started a decent recovery wave from the $0.264 support zone. The bulls managed to push the price above the $0.280 and $0.295 resistance levels. It even spiked above the $0.300 resistance. A high is formed near $0.3013 and the price is now correcting gains, similar to Bitcoin and Ethereum. There was a move below the 50% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $0.2675 swing low to the $0.3013 high. Besides, there was a break below a key bullish trend line with support near $0.2960 on the 4-hour chart of the ADA/USD pair. The price is now trading below $0.290 and the 100 simple moving average (4 hours). The price is now holding the $0.280 support. It is close to the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $0.2675 swing low to the $0.3013 high. On the upside, immediate resistance is near the $0.285 zone and the 100 simple moving average (4 hours). Source: ADAUSD on TradingView.com The first major resistance is forming near the $0.292 zone. The next key resistance might be $0.30. If there is an upside break above the $0.300 and $0.305 resistance levels, the price could start a decent increase. In the stated case, the price could even surpass the $0.320 resistance zone. More Losses in ADA? If Cardano’s price fails to climb above the $0.285 resistance level, it could continue to move down. Immediate support on the downside is near the $0.280 level. The next major support is near the $0.275 level. A downside break below the $0.275 level could open the doors for a fresh decline toward $0.262. The next major support is near the $0.250 level. Technical Indicators 4 hours MACD – The MACD for ADA/USD is gaining momentum in the bearish zone. 4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for ADA/USD is now below the 50 level. Major Support Levels – $0.280, $0.275, and $0.262. Major Resistance Levels – $0.285, $0.295, and $0.305.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>Cardano’s price is declining from the $0.30 zone. ADA could continue to move down if it breaks the $0.280 support zone in the near term.</em></p>
<ul>
<li>ADA price is moving lower from the $0.302 zone against the US dollar.</li>
<li>The price is trading below $0.290 and the 100 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There was a break below a key bullish trend line with support near $0.2960 on the 4-hour chart of the ADA/USD pair (data source from Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could slide further toward the $0.264 support zone.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Cardano’s ADA Price Corrects Gains</h2>
<p>This past week, Cardano’s price started a decent recovery wave from the $0.264 support zone. The bulls managed to push the price above the $0.280 and $0.295 resistance levels.</p>
<p>It even spiked above the $0.300 resistance. A high is formed near $0.3013 and the price is now correcting gains, similar to <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-rejects-31k/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Bitcoin</a> and <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-retests-1900/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Ethereum</a>. There was a move below the 50% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $0.2675 swing low to the $0.3013 high.</p>
<p>Besides, there was a break below a key bullish trend line with support near $0.2960 on the 4-hour chart of the ADA/USD pair. The price is now trading below $0.290 and the 100 simple moving average (4 hours).</p>
<p>The price is now holding the $0.280 support. It is close to the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $0.2675 swing low to the $0.3013 high. On the upside, immediate resistance is near the $0.285 zone and the 100 simple moving average (4 hours).</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-541431" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Cardano-ADA.png" alt="Cardano’s ADA Price" width="1835" height="845" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Cardano-ADA.png 1835w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Cardano-ADA-460x212.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Cardano-ADA-860x396.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Cardano-ADA-768x354.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Cardano-ADA-1536x707.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Cardano-ADA-750x345.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Cardano-ADA-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1835px) 100vw, 1835px"/></p>
<p>Source: <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/ADAUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">ADAUSD on TradingView.com</a></p>
<p>The first major resistance is forming near the $0.292 zone. The next key resistance might be $0.30. If there is an upside break above the $0.300 and $0.305 resistance levels, the price could start a decent increase. In the stated case, the price could even surpass the $0.320 resistance zone.</p>
<h2>More Losses in ADA?</h2>
<p>If Cardano’s price fails to climb above the $0.285 resistance level, it could continue to move down. Immediate support on the downside is near the $0.280 level.</p>
<p>The next major support is near the $0.275 level. A downside break below the $0.275 level could open the doors for a fresh decline toward $0.262. The next major support is near the $0.250 level.</p>
<p>Technical Indicators</p>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for ADA/USD is gaining momentum in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for ADA/USD is now below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Levels – $0.280, $0.275, and $0.262.</p>
<p>Major Resistance Levels – $0.285, $0.295, and $0.305.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/11/shutterstock_1334283245-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum Price Retests Uptrend Support But Can Bulls Save The Day</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-retests-1900/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 04:48:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=541423</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Ethereum price started a downside correction below $1,950 against the US Dollar. ETH is testing the $1,900 support and is showing a few bearish signs. Ethereum is correcting gains below the $1,950 zone. The price is trading below $1,940 and the 100-hourly Simple Moving Average. There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $1,925 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD (data feed via Kraken). The pair could start another increase unless there is a close below $1,900 in the near term. Ethereum Price Corrects Gains Ethereum’s price failed to clear the $1,975 resistance and started a downside correction. ETH traded below the $1,950 level and extended its decline, similar to Bitcoin. There was a move below the $1,920 support. Finally, the price spiked below $1,900. A low is formed near $1,894 and the price is now consolidating losses. It is now trading near the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the recent decline from the $1,974 swing high to the $1,894 low. Ether is trading below $1,940 and the 100-hourly Simple Moving Average. There is also a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $1,925 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD. Immediate resistance is near the $1,925 level the 100-hourly Simple Moving Average. The next major resistance is near the $1,945 level. It is close to the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the recent decline from the $1,974 swing high to the $1,894 low. Source: ETHUSD on TradingView.com A clear move above the $1,945 resistance could push the price toward $1,975. The main resistance is still near the $2,000 level, above which the price could start a decent increase. The next major resistance is near the $2,120 level. Any more gains could send Ether toward the $2,200 resistance. More Losses in ETH? If Ethereum fails to clear the $1,925 resistance or $1,945, it could continue to move down. Initial support on the downside is near the $1,900 level. The first major support is near the $1,870 level. The next major support is near the $1,820 level. If there is a move below the $1,820 support, the price could drop toward the $1,770 support level. Technical Indicators Hourly MACD – The MACD for ETH/USD is losing momentum in the bearish zone. Hourly RSI &#8211; The RSI for ETH/USD is now below the 50 level. Major Support Level – $1,900 Major Resistance Level – $1,945]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>Ethereum price started a downside correction below $1,950 against the US Dollar. ETH is testing the $1,900 support and is showing a few bearish signs.</em></p>
<ul>
<li>Ethereum is correcting gains below the $1,950 zone.</li>
<li>The price is trading below $1,940 and the 100-hourly Simple Moving Average.</li>
<li>There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $1,925 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD (data feed via Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could start another increase unless there is a close below $1,900 in the near term.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Ethereum Price Corrects Gains</h2>
<p>Ethereum’s price failed to clear the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-lacks-momentum-1950/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">$1,975 resistance</a> and started a downside correction. ETH traded below the $1,950 level and extended its decline, similar to Bitcoin.</p>
<p>There was a move below the $1,920 support. Finally, the price spiked below $1,900. A low is formed near $1,894 and the price is now consolidating losses. It is now trading near the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the recent decline from the $1,974 swing high to the $1,894 low.</p>
<p>Ether is trading below $1,940 and the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-rally-to-2200/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">100-hourly Simple Moving Average</a>. There is also a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $1,925 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD.</p>
<p>Immediate resistance is near the $1,925 level the 100-hourly Simple Moving Average. The next major resistance is near the $1,945 level. It is close to the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the recent decline from the $1,974 swing high to the $1,894 low.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-541424" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ethereum-3.png" alt="Ethereum Price" width="1835" height="845" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ethereum-3.png 1835w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ethereum-3-460x212.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ethereum-3-860x396.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ethereum-3-768x354.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ethereum-3-1536x707.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ethereum-3-750x345.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ethereum-3-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1835px) 100vw, 1835px"/></p>
<p>Source: <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/ETHUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">ETHUSD on TradingView.com</a></p>
<p>A clear move above the $1,945 resistance could push the price toward $1,975. The main resistance is still near the $2,000 level, above which the price could start a decent increase. The next major resistance is near the $2,120 level. Any more gains could send Ether toward the $2,200 resistance.</p>
<h2>More Losses in ETH?</h2>
<p>If Ethereum fails to clear the $1,925 resistance or $1,945, it could continue to move down. Initial support on the downside is near the $1,900 level.</p>
<p>The first major support is near the $1,870 level. The next major support is near the $1,820 level. If there is a move below the $1,820 support, the price could drop toward the $1,770 support level.</p>
<p>Technical Indicators</p>
<p>Hourly MACD<strong> – </strong>The MACD for ETH/USD is losing momentum in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>Hourly RSI<strong> &#8211; </strong>The RSI for ETH/USD is now below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Level – $1,900</p>
<p>Major Resistance Level – $1,945</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/iStock-1045986528-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Price Rejects $31K and Turns At Risk of Drop To $30K</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-rejects-31k/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 03:12:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xbtusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=541419</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin price failed to settle above $31,000 and corrected lower. BTC could continue to move down toward the $30,000 support zone. Bitcoin is correcting gains from the $31,000 and $31,250 resistance levels. The price is trading below $30,800 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average. There was a break below a connecting bullish trend line with support near $30,750 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Kraken). The pair could extend its decline and test the $30,000 support zone. Bitcoin Price Corrects Lower Bitcoin price failed to settle above the $31,000 resistance zone. BTC started a downside correction below the $31,000 and $30,850 levels. Besides, there was a break below a connecting bullish trend line with support near $30,750 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair. The bears were able to push the price below $30,250. A low is formed near $30,160 and the price is now consolidating losses. It is trading near the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the recent decline from the $31,373 swing high to the $30,160 low. Bitcoin is trading below $30,800 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average. Immediate resistance is near the $30,600 level. The first major resistance is near the $30,750 level and the 100 hourly Simple moving average. It is close to the 50% Fib retracement level of the recent decline from the $31,373 swing high to the $30,160 low, above which the price might retest $31,000. Source: BTCUSD on TradingView.com A close above the $31,000 resistance could start a steady increase. The next major resistance is near the $31,400 level. Any more gains could open the doors for a move toward the $32,000 resistance zone. More Losses in BTC? If Bitcoin’s price fails to clear the $31,750 resistance, it could continue to move down. Immediate support on the downside is near the $30,150 level and the recent low. The next major support is near the $30,000 level, below which there could be a drop toward $29,550. Any more losses might send the price toward the $29,200 zone in the coming sessions. Technical indicators: Hourly MACD – The MACD is now gaining pace in the bearish zone. Hourly RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BTC/USD is now below the 50 level. Major Support Levels – $30,150, followed by $30,000. Major Resistance Levels – $30,750, $31,000, and $31,400.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>Bitcoin price failed to settle above $31,000 and corrected lower. BTC could continue to move down toward the $30,000 support zone.</em></p>
<ul>
<li>Bitcoin is correcting gains from the $31,000 and $31,250 resistance levels.</li>
<li>The price is trading below $30,800 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average.</li>
<li>There was a break below a connecting bullish trend line with support near $30,750 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could extend its decline and test the $30,000 support zone.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Bitcoin Price Corrects Lower</h2>
<p>Bitcoin price failed to settle above the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-liftoff-30k/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">$31,000 resistance zone</a>. BTC started a downside correction below the $31,000 and $30,850 levels.</p>
<p>Besides, there was a break below a connecting bullish trend line with support near $30,750 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair. The bears were able to push the price below $30,250. A low is formed near $30,160 and the price is now consolidating losses.</p>
<p>It is trading near the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the recent decline from the $31,373 swing high to the $30,160 low. Bitcoin is trading below $30,800 and the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-key-trend-32k/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">100 hourly Simple moving average</a>.</p>
<p>Immediate resistance is near the $30,600 level. The first major resistance is near the $30,750 level and the 100 hourly Simple moving average. It is close to the 50% Fib retracement level of the recent decline from the $31,373 swing high to the $30,160 low, above which the price might retest $31,000.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-541420" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-3.png" alt="Bitcoin Price" width="1835" height="845" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-3.png 1835w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-3-460x212.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-3-860x396.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-3-768x354.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-3-1536x707.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-3-750x345.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-3-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1835px) 100vw, 1835px"/></p>
<p>Source: <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BTCUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">BTCUSD on TradingView.com</a></p>
<p>A close above the $31,000 resistance could start a steady increase. The next major resistance is near the $31,400 level. Any more gains could open the doors for a move toward the $32,000 resistance zone.</p>
<h2>More Losses in BTC?</h2>
<p>If Bitcoin’s price fails to clear the $31,750 resistance, it could continue to move down. Immediate support on the downside is near the $30,150 level and the recent low.</p>
<p>The next major support is near the $30,000 level, below which there could be a drop toward $29,550. Any more losses might send the price toward the $29,200 zone in the coming sessions.</p>
<p>Technical indicators:</p>
<p>Hourly MACD – The MACD is now gaining pace in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>Hourly RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BTC/USD is now below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Levels – $30,150, followed by $30,000.</p>
<p>Major Resistance Levels – $30,750, $31,000, and $31,400.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/04/shutterstock_1418423411-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Blame The &#8220;Supermoon&#8221; If Bitcoin Crashes Or Rallies Towards $35,000 In July</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/blame-the-supermoon-if-bitcoin-crashes-or-rallies-towards-35000-in-july/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dalmas Ngetich]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 03:00:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin bulls]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Supermoon]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=541410</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[If historical Bitcoin price performance leads, one trader is adamant that the coin is at a critical inflection point at spot rates. Based on astronomical patterns and moon arrangement, trading desk QCP Capital believes Bitcoin prices can swing higher in a bull run towards the $33,000 to $35,000 level, reversing following sharp losses in 2022. Conversely, after a recovery that has seen Bitcoin price rally 20% from mid-June 2023, there can be a contraction that may see the coin dip after an impressive performance in the past few trading weeks. Supermoons Coincide With Key Bitcoin Price Reversals Based on technical and fundamental actions, the trading desk cited the past performance of Bitcoin at different cyclical stages. For instance, when Bitcoin fell in the early days of 2020, primarily due to fears of the far-reaching consequences of lockdowns brought by the COVID-19 pandemic, it posted a 161% rally from early March to May 2020. The same was observed from mid-June to August 2022 when Bitcoin, at the depth of the last cyclical bear market, prices soared 43%. Marking peaks, Bitcoin corrected from the end of April to June 2021, falling 51% in a predominantly bullish market. According to the trading desk, major reversals in bearish and bullish runs occurred during a &#8220;supermoon.&#8221; In astrology, a supermoon is a full moon that forms when the moon is at its closest point to the Earth in its elliptical orbit. The moon appears brighter than usual during this time and happens only once or twice a year. A supermoon formed on July 4, and the trader believes Bitcoin is at a critical reaction point. Related Reading: AAVE Records 26% Weekly Gain, Looks To Break Key Resistance For years, there has been a belief that supermoons correlate with bullish markets. However, no scientific findings support this, and neither have statistical correlations. Still, based on the trader&#8217;s analysis, the multiple correlations and timing of peaks and bottoms of Bitcoin prices during supermoons can be used to predict BTC markets. Will Prices Rally Or Dump? While it is yet to be seen whether BTC will edge higher, breaking above $31,300 and rally towards the $35,000 zone, the trading desk says fundamental factors will play a critical role and remains bullish that BTC may rally to within the $33,000 to $35,000 liquidation zone. Overall, monitoring how the Federal Reserve of the United States will implement its monetary policies will be necessary in the future. Although inflation has been dropping, the trader observes that it has not fallen low enough to warrant a rate cut. Rate cuts tend to move the capital to store-of-value assets from which Bitcoin will likely benefit.  Related Reading: Analyst Says XRP Will Reach $100, Here’s Why On a more pessimistic side, the trading desk expresses caution saying BTC has strong resistance at spot levels since the recent leg up was most likely the fifth and the last wave from November 2022 lows. At the same time, the $33,000 to $35,000 resistance zone is a critical resistance trend line. For this reason, any dump may see BTC retest the $24,000 and $26,000 support zone. Feature image from Canva, chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>If historical Bitcoin price performance leads, one trader is adamant that the coin is at a critical inflection point at spot rates. Based on astronomical patterns and moon arrangement, trading desk QCP Capital <a href="https://twitter.com/QCPCapital/status/1676496245156872193" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">believes</a> Bitcoin prices can swing higher in a bull run towards the $33,000 to $35,000 level, reversing following sharp losses in 2022. Conversely, after a recovery that has seen Bitcoin price rally 20% from mid-June 2023, there can be a contraction that may see the coin dip after an impressive performance in the past few trading weeks.</p>
<h2>Supermoons Coincide With Key Bitcoin Price Reversals</h2>
<p>Based on technical and fundamental actions, the trading desk cited the past performance of Bitcoin at different cyclical stages. For instance, when Bitcoin fell in the early days of 2020, primarily due to fears of the far-reaching consequences of lockdowns brought by the COVID-19 pandemic, it posted a 161% rally from early March to May 2020. </p>
<p>The same was observed from mid-June to August 2022 when Bitcoin, at the depth of the last cyclical bear market, prices soared 43%. Marking peaks, Bitcoin corrected from the end of April to June 2021, falling 51% in a predominantly bullish market.</p>
<a href="https://www.tradingview.com/x/EnHdCvSf/" rel="nofollow"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/EnHdCvSf/" alt="BTC price on July 5| Source: BTCUSDT on Binance, TradingView" width="1226" height="595"/></a>
<p>According to the trading desk, major reversals in bearish and bullish runs occurred during a &#8220;supermoon.&#8221; In astrology, a supermoon is a full moon that forms when the moon is at its closest point to the Earth in its elliptical orbit. The moon appears brighter than usual during this time and happens only once or twice a year. A supermoon formed on July 4, and the trader believes Bitcoin is at a critical reaction point.</p>

<p>For years, there has been a belief that supermoons correlate with bullish markets. However, no scientific findings support this, and neither have statistical correlations. Still, based on the trader&#8217;s analysis, the multiple correlations and timing of peaks and bottoms of Bitcoin prices during supermoons can be used to predict BTC markets.</p>
<h2>Will Prices Rally Or Dump?</h2>
<p>While it is yet to be seen whether BTC will edge higher, breaking above $31,300 and rally towards the $35,000 zone, the trading desk says fundamental factors will play a critical role and remains bullish that BTC may rally to within the $33,000 to $35,000 liquidation zone. </p>
<p>Overall, monitoring how the Federal Reserve of the United States will implement its monetary policies will be necessary in the future. Although inflation has been dropping, the trader observes that it has not fallen low enough to warrant a rate cut. Rate cuts tend to move the capital to store-of-value assets from which Bitcoin will likely benefit. </p>

<p>On a more pessimistic side, the trading desk expresses caution saying BTC has strong resistance at spot levels since the recent leg up was most likely the fifth and the last wave from November 2022 lows. At the same time, the $33,000 to $35,000 resistance zone is a critical resistance trend line. </p>
<p>For this reason, any dump may see BTC retest the $24,000 and $26,000 support zone.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-supermoon-460x260.jpg" width="460" height="260" />	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
