<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
>

<channel>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.newsbtc.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<description>Bitcoin &#38; Cryptocurrency News Today</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 02:44:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Bulls Keep Pushing, Why Rally Isn’t Over Yet</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-bulls-pushing-30k/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 02:44:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xbtusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=539068</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin price is surging above $30,000. BTC is up over 10% and it seems like the bulls are not done yet and might be aiming for a move to $32,000. Bitcoin is gaining pace above the $30,000 resistance. The price is trading above $29,500 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average. There is a key bullish trend line forming with support near $30,250 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Kraken). The pair could rise further if it clears the $30,800 and $31,200 resistance levels. Bitcoin Price Extends Its Rally Bitcoin price started a major rally above the $28,500 resistance zone. BTC gained strength and was able to clear the key $29,200 resistance zone. It is up over 10% and there was a clear move above the $30,000 resistance. It traded close to $30,800. A high is formed near $30,794 and the price recently saw a minor downside correction. There was a move below the $30,500 level. The price dipped below the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the recent wave from the $28,660 swing low to the $30,794 high. Bitcoin price is now trading above $29,500 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average. There is also a key bullish trend line forming with support near $30,250 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair. Source: BTCUSD on TradingView.com It is again rising and trading above the $30,000 level. On the upside, the price is facing resistance near the $30,300 level. The next major resistance is near the $30,800 level. An upside break above the $30,800 resistance could start a fresh increase toward the $31,200 level. The next major resistance is near the $32,000 level, above which the bulls might send BTC toward the $32,500 resistance zone. Dips Present Buying Opportunity in BTC? If Bitcoin’s price fails to clear the $30,800 resistance, it could start a downside correction. Immediate support on the downside is near the $30,250 level and the trend line. The next major support is near the $29,750 level or the 50% Fib retracement level of the recent wave from the $28,660 swing low to the $30,794 high. The main support is now near $29,000, below which the price might drop toward the $28,500 support. Any more losses might send the price toward $27,500 in the near term. Technical indicators: Hourly MACD – The MACD is now gaining pace in the bullish zone. Hourly RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BTC/USD is in the overbought zone. Major Support Levels – $30,200, followed by $29,750. Major Resistance Levels – $30,300, $30,800, and $31,200.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>Bitcoin price is surging above $30,000. BTC is up over 10% and it seems like the bulls are not done yet and might be aiming for a move to $32,000.</em></p>
<ul>
<li>Bitcoin is gaining pace above the $30,000 resistance.</li>
<li>The price is trading above $29,500 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average.</li>
<li>There is a key bullish trend line forming with support near $30,250 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could rise further if it clears the $30,800 and $31,200 resistance levels.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Bitcoin Price Extends Its Rally</h2>
<p>Bitcoin price started a <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-eye-30k/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">major rally above the $28,500 resistance zone</a>. BTC gained strength and was able to clear the key $29,200 resistance zone. It is up over 10% and there was a clear move above the $30,000 resistance.</p>
<p>It traded close to $30,800. A high is formed near $30,794 and the price recently saw a minor downside correction. There was a move below the $30,500 level. The price dipped below the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the recent wave from the $28,660 swing low to the $30,794 high.</p>
<p>Bitcoin price is now trading above $29,500 and the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-extends-recovery-27k/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">100 hourly Simple moving average</a>. There is also a key bullish trend line forming with support near $30,250 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-539069" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-15.png" alt="Bitcoin Price" width="1835" height="845" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-15.png 1835w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-15-460x212.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-15-860x396.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-15-768x354.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-15-1536x707.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-15-750x345.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-15-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1835px) 100vw, 1835px"/></p>
<p>Source: <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BTCUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">BTCUSD on TradingView.com</a></p>
<p>It is again rising and trading above the $30,000 level. On the upside, the price is facing resistance near the $30,300 level. The next major resistance is near the $30,800 level. An upside break above the $30,800 resistance could start a fresh increase toward the $31,200 level. The next major resistance is near the $32,000 level, above which the bulls might send BTC toward the $32,500 resistance zone.</p>
<h2>Dips Present Buying Opportunity in BTC?</h2>
<p>If Bitcoin’s price fails to clear the $30,800 resistance, it could start a downside correction. Immediate support on the downside is near the $30,250 level and the trend line.</p>
<p>The next major support is near the $29,750 level or the 50% Fib retracement level of the recent wave from the $28,660 swing low to the $30,794 high. The main support is now near $29,000, below which the price might drop toward the $28,500 support. Any more losses might send the price toward $27,500 in the near term.</p>
<p>Technical indicators:</p>
<p>Hourly MACD – The MACD is now gaining pace in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>Hourly RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BTC/USD is in the overbought zone.</p>
<p>Major Support Levels – $30,200, followed by $29,750.</p>
<p>Major Resistance Levels – $30,300, $30,800, and $31,200.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/bitcoin_price_btc_1-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dogecoin Signal Bullish Momentum On Daily Chart, What&#8217;s Next?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/dogecoin/dogecoin-signal-bullish-momentum-on-daily-chart-whats-next/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ebo Victor]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 01:30:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[doge]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[elon musk]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tradecurve]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=539032</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Dogecoin emerged as a highly popular cryptocurrency, originating from the world of internet memes. Despite its initially modest beginnings and relatively low value, it has amassed a large and enthusiastic community of followers. Dogecoin has gained significant popularity and a passionate community of supporters. The value of Dogecoin has been influenced by celebrity endorsements and increased adoption as a payment method on mainstream platforms. Other altcoins, including TCRV associated with Tradecurve, have also demonstrated positive performance and growth trends. Related Reading: Dogecoin Price Prediction: DOGE Signals Fresh Rally If It Clears 100 SMA DOGECOIN: Community, Endorsements, And Performance The dedicated community has played a pivotal role in propelling the value of DOGE forward. Renowned figures such as Elon Musk, the CEO of Tesla, have continued to express their support for DOGE, contributing to its ongoing surge in popularity. Furthermore, the wider adoption of DOGE as a payment method on mainstream platforms and the influx of celebrity endorsements have further bolstered its growth. As of June 17, 2023, the trading value of DOGE stood at $0.062569. Throughout the previous week, its value experienced fluctuations, dropping as low as $0.059487 before climbing back up to $0.062845. When considering the past 30 days, DOGE has seen a decline of 15.7% in its overall value. However, in the weekly charts, it registered a growth of 5.5%, marking a 1.8% increase compared to the previous trading day. The volatility and expansion pattern witnessed by DOGE is not exclusive, as several other alternative cryptocurrencies have undergone similar processes. In general, the recent positive performance of Dogecoin has instilled greater confidence among investors. Nevertheless, it is important to acknowledge that other alternative coins have also demonstrated comparable growth trajectories. Related Reading: Conflux Gains 20% In 24 hours, Emerges On Top Gainers Chart Featured image from Shutterstock, charts from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Dogecoin emerged as a highly popular cryptocurrency, originating from the world of internet memes. Despite its initially modest beginnings and relatively low value, it has amassed a large and enthusiastic community of followers.</p>
<ul>
<li>Dogecoin has gained significant popularity and a passionate community of supporters.</li>
<li>The value of Dogecoin has been influenced by celebrity endorsements and increased adoption as a payment method on mainstream platforms.</li>
<li>Other altcoins, including TCRV associated with Tradecurve, have also demonstrated positive performance and growth trends.</li>
</ul>

<h2>DOGECOIN: Community, Endorsements, And Performance</h2>
<p>The dedicated community has played a pivotal role in propelling the value of DOGE forward. Renowned figures such as <a href="https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Elon_Musk" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Elon Musk</a>, the CEO of Tesla, have continued to express their support for DOGE, contributing to its ongoing surge in popularity.</p>
<p>Furthermore, the wider adoption of DOGE as a payment method on mainstream platforms and the influx of celebrity endorsements have further bolstered its growth.</p>
<p>As of June 17, 2023, the trading value of DOGE stood at $0.062569. Throughout the previous week, its value experienced fluctuations, dropping as low as $0.059487 before climbing back up to $0.062845.</p>
<p>When considering the past 30 days, DOGE has seen a decline of 15.7% in its overall value.</p>
<p>However, in the weekly charts, it registered a growth of 5.5%, marking a 1.8% increase compared to the previous trading day.</p>
<p>The volatility and expansion pattern witnessed by DOGE is not exclusive, as several other alternative cryptocurrencies have undergone similar processes.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/4V6HHuB9/" alt="Dogecoin Daily Chart " width="1888" height="656"/>
<p>In general, the recent positive performance of <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/dogecoin-price-prediction-doge-0-0685/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Dogecoin</a> has instilled greater confidence among investors. Nevertheless, it is important to acknowledge that other alternative coins have also demonstrated comparable growth trajectories.</p>





]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Dogecoin-Ordinals-460x260.jpg" width="460" height="260" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fantom (FTM) Shows Resilience, Gains 15% In A Single Day</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/fantom/fantom-ftm-shows-resilience-gains-15-in-a-single-day/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Opeyemi Sule]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 00:30:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Fantom]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fantom]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTM]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTMUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=539039</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Fantom (FTM) has been underperforming in the past few months, shedding virtually all the profits gained at the beginning of the year. However, the bulls seem to be back in control, as the cryptocurrency price indicates increased buying pressure. Related Reading: Bitcoin Price Breaks Above $30,000: Is The Bull Run Back On? Fantom Price Jumps By 15% In 24 Hours &#8211; Price Overview Since April 18, FTM has displayed downward price action, contributing to the coin&#8217;s negative market sentiment. However, the token’s price is bouncing and showing signs of a recovery by gaining more than 15% in the last 24 hours.  Meanwhile, Fantom has had a generally positive week, showing green on the weekly chart with a 10% price increase. This bullish momentum has slowed the coin’s descent to the yearly low of $0.1997. However, it is worth mentioning that the cryptocurrency is still a long way from its 2023 peak at $0.6345. Fantom reached this price point as far back as February 4 and has declined since, losing more than 53% of its value. According to data from CoinGecko, FTM currently trades at $0.2955, with a 24-hour trading volume of over $121 million. The trading volume experienced a 90.5% increase in the last day, indicating a recent surge in market activity.  FTM Price Approaches Significant Resistance Level During its descent, FTM broke the $0.34 support level, falling to a low of $0.21 on June 10. Interestingly, the FTM price formed an evening star candlestick on the daily chart, indicating a bullish reversal. And the price has been on an upswing since then. In addition to the evening star pattern, technical indicators signal a bullish reversal. For instance, the daily Relative Strength Index (RSI) shows a bullish momentum forming, having moved out of the oversold zone. However, it is yet to confirm the trend reversal, with its line barely crossing above 50. An RSI reading above 50 often indicates that a bullish run might be on the horizon, while the bears have the advantage when the RSI reading is below 50. Meanwhile, the daily Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD) line recently crossed above the signal line, another bullish indicator. &#160; FTMUSD trading at $0.302 &#124; Source: FTMUSD chart from TradingView Fantom looks set to target the $0.34 price zone, which is now expected to operate as resistance. Should the FTM price gather enough momentum and break this resistance level, it will likely hit the $0.54 level and perhaps reach a new 2023 peak. On the flip side, if the resistance level holds strong, the FTM bearish trend may continue. The token’s price may fall to a new yearly low beneath $0.1997 in this case. It is worth noting that this analysis is not investment advice. Traders are advised to do their due diligence before risking their funds. Related Reading: Bitcoin Cash Surges 20% In One Day As Market Rebounds, What’s Next? Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Fantom (FTM) has been underperforming in the past few months, shedding virtually all the profits gained at the beginning of the year. However, the bulls seem to be back in control, as the cryptocurrency price indicates increased buying pressure.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-price-breaks-above-30000-is-the-bull-run-back-on/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Bitcoin Price Breaks Above $30,000: Is The Bull Run Back On?</a></p>
<h2>Fantom Price Jumps By 15% In 24 Hours &#8211; Price Overview</h2>
<p>Since April 18, FTM has displayed downward price action, contributing to the coin&#8217;s negative market sentiment. However, the token’s price is bouncing and showing signs of a recovery by gaining more than 15% in the last 24 hours. </p>
<p>Meanwhile, Fantom has had a generally positive week, showing green on the weekly chart with a 10% price increase. This bullish momentum has slowed the coin’s descent to the yearly low of $0.1997.</p>
<p>However, it is worth mentioning that the cryptocurrency is still a long way from its 2023 peak at $0.6345. Fantom reached this price point as far back as February 4 and has declined since, losing more than 53% of its value.</p>
<p>According to <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/fantom" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">data from CoinGecko</a>, FTM currently trades at $0.2955, with a 24-hour trading volume of over $121 million. The trading volume experienced a 90.5% increase in the last day, indicating a recent surge in market activity. </p>
<h2>FTM Price Approaches Significant Resistance Level</h2>
<p>During its descent, FTM broke the $0.34 support level, falling to a low of $0.21 on June 10. Interestingly, the FTM price formed an evening star candlestick on the daily chart, indicating a bullish reversal. And the price has been on an upswing since then.</p>
<p>In addition to the evening star pattern, technical indicators signal a bullish reversal.</p>
<p>For instance, the daily Relative Strength Index (RSI) shows a bullish momentum forming, having moved out of the oversold zone. However, it is yet to confirm the trend reversal, with its line barely crossing above 50.</p>
<p>An RSI reading above 50 often indicates that a bullish run might be on the horizon, while the bears have the advantage when the RSI reading is below 50.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, the daily Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD) line recently crossed above the signal line, another bullish indicator.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/RsfHQGSw/" alt="Fantom" width="1013" height="601"/></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>

<p>Fantom looks set to target the $0.34 price zone, which is now expected to operate as resistance. Should the FTM price gather enough momentum and break this resistance level, it will likely hit the $0.54 level and perhaps reach a new 2023 peak.</p>
<p>On the flip side, if the resistance level holds strong, the FTM bearish trend may continue. The token’s price may fall to a new yearly low beneath $0.1997 in this case.</p>
<p>It is worth noting that this analysis is not investment advice. Traders are advised to do their due diligence before risking their funds.</p>





]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/iStock-1015828796-1536x878-1-460x263.jpg" width="460" height="263" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Miner Core Scientific Files for Chapter 11, Seeks Restructuring Amid Crypto Winter</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-miner-core-scientific-files-for-chapter-11-seeks-restructuring-amid-crypto-winter/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 23:00:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin miner]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Core Scientific]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=539047</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Core Scientific, a prominent Bitcoin mining company, has recently made headlines as it filed for Chapter 11 bankruptcy protection. The move comes as the crypto industry grapples with the enduring effects of the ongoing crypto winter, impacting various firms in the sector.  Core Scientific&#8217;s decision to seek bankruptcy protection is part of its strategy to implement a comprehensive restructuring plan to navigate the challenging market conditions. Amid a comprehensive review of potential alternatives and extensive discussions with stakeholders, Core Scientific has taken the step of filing for bankruptcy protection to enable the execution of a restructuring support agreement (RSA).  Related Reading: Bitcoin Cash Surges 20% In One Day As Market Rebounds, What’s Next? The company aims to swiftly address its financial challenges and emerge stronger from the restructuring process. As part of its commitment to transparently communicate its intentions, Core Scientific has filed voluntary petitions for reorganization under Chapter 11 of the US Bankruptcy Code in the US Bankruptcy Court for the Southern District of Texas. The Bitcoin miner has now joined a growing list of crypto firms seeking similar measures. However, the decision reflects the company&#8217;s dedication to implementing a comprehensive restructuring plan to address its financial situation amidst the crypto winter. Core Scientific Pursuing A Comprehensive Restructuring Plan To facilitate its restructuring efforts, Core Scientific has filed voluntary petitions for reorganization under Chapter 11 of the US Bankruptcy Code. With an estimated range of $1 billion to $10 billion in assets and a considerable number of creditors, the company is committed to swiftly navigating the restructuring process. During the Chapter 11 process, Core Scientific remains steadfast in its commitment to operating its existing self-mining and hosting operations, which have demonstrated positive cash flow. The company aims to leverage its state-of-the-art data centers to provide uninterrupted hosting services and self-mining capabilities while undergoing the restructuring process. Core Scientific first filed for bankruptcy in 2022 following the widespread contagion triggered by the FTX exchange collapse. Bitcoin miners suffered severe losses leading to the bankruptcy of multiple mining firms including Celsius Mining and Compute North. However, as the market has begun to recover and BTC&#8217;s price has moved above $30,000 once more, the headwinds for miners are starting to look better. Related Reading: Bitcoin Price Breaks Above $30,000: Is The Bull Run Back On? Core Scientific has already reported an increase in its BTC mining activities as prices have recovered, which has further propelled its ability to move through its current debt issues. The company already produced 1,314 BTC in the last month, a 16% increase from the prior month. As for its stock prices, Core Scientific&#8217;s stocks have suffered massive losses in the last two years. The company was valued at around $4 billion when it went public back in 2021 with its stock price reaching as high as $15. However, it has since lost most of its value with the stock price now sitting at $0.4455 and the company value at around $70 million. CORZQ falls to $0.4455 per share &#124; Source: Core Scientific, Inc. on TradingView.com Featured image from Forkast News, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Core Scientific, a prominent Bitcoin mining company, has recently made headlines as it filed for <a href="https://www.google.com/amp/s/www.fxstreet.com/amp/cryptocurrencies/news/bitcoin-miner-core-scientific-files-its-chapter-eleven-plan-202306210927" rel="nofollow">Chapter 11</a> bankruptcy protection. The move comes as the crypto industry grapples with the enduring effects of the ongoing crypto winter, impacting various firms in the sector. </p>
<p>Core Scientific&#8217;s decision to seek bankruptcy protection is part of its strategy to implement a comprehensive restructuring plan to navigate the challenging market conditions.</p>
<p>Amid a comprehensive review of potential alternatives and extensive discussions with stakeholders, Core Scientific has taken the step of filing for bankruptcy protection to enable the execution of a restructuring support agreement (RSA). </p>

<p>The company aims to swiftly address its financial challenges and emerge stronger from the restructuring process. As part of its commitment to transparently communicate its intentions, Core Scientific has filed voluntary petitions for reorganization under Chapter 11 of the US Bankruptcy Code in the US Bankruptcy Court for the Southern District of Texas.</p>
<p>The Bitcoin miner has now joined a growing list of crypto firms seeking similar measures. However, the decision reflects the company&#8217;s dedication to implementing a comprehensive restructuring plan to address its financial situation amidst the crypto winter.</p>
<h2>Core Scientific Pursuing A Comprehensive Restructuring Plan</h2>
<p>To facilitate its restructuring efforts, Core Scientific has filed voluntary petitions for reorganization under Chapter 11 of the US Bankruptcy Code. With an estimated range of $1 billion to $10 billion in assets and a considerable number of creditors, the company is committed to swiftly navigating the restructuring process.</p>
<p>During the Chapter 11 process, Core Scientific remains steadfast in its commitment to operating its existing self-mining and hosting operations, which have demonstrated positive cash flow. The company aims to leverage its state-of-the-art data centers to provide uninterrupted hosting services and self-mining capabilities while undergoing the restructuring process.</p>
<p>Core Scientific first filed for bankruptcy in 2022 following the widespread contagion triggered by the FTX exchange collapse. Bitcoin miners suffered severe losses leading to the bankruptcy of multiple mining firms including Celsius Mining and Compute North.</p>
<p>However, as the market has begun to recover and BTC&#8217;s price has moved above $30,000 once more, the headwinds for miners are starting to look better.</p>

<p>Core Scientific has already reported an increase in its BTC mining activities as prices have recovered, which has further propelled its ability to move through its current debt issues. The company already produced 1,314 BTC in the last month, a 16% increase from the prior month.</p>
<p>As for its stock prices, Core Scientific&#8217;s stocks have suffered massive losses in the last two years. The company was valued at around $4 billion when it went public back in 2021 with its stock price reaching as high as $15. However, it has since lost most of its value with the stock price now sitting at $0.4455 and the company value at around $70 million.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/YcNdabbB/" alt="Core Scientific price chart from TradingView.com (Bitcoin mining)" width="2884" height="1610"/></p>

<p>Featured image from Forkast News, chart from TradingView.com</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Core-scientific-bitcoin-miner-460x307.jpeg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Faces Tough Resistance At $30,000 &#8211; Can It Overcome The Hurdle?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-faces-tough-resistance-at-30000-can-it-overcome-the-hurdle/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 22:00:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=539026</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC), the largest cryptocurrency in the market, has demonstrated a strong shift in investor sentiment. Over the past 24 hours, BTC has surged by an impressive 9%, currently trading at $29,300.  However, Bitcoin still faces significant hurdles, with a resistance line placed at $29,500, as well as a key psychological level at $30,000 that has not been reached since April 19th.  BTC’s Moment Of Truth Material Indicators, a cryptocurrency data analysis firm, has identified a substantial resistance level for BTC at $30,000. This resistance level has been building and may impede the cryptocurrency&#8217;s upward momentum, potentially causing it to become range-bound, as has occurred several times this year. Related Reading: US Bitcoin Investor Trading Volume Rises, Stage Set For Another Massive Rally? If BTC fails to break through this resistance level, it could become trapped in a narrow trading range, limiting its potential for further growth. However, if it manages to overcome this hurdle, it could provide a strong bullish signal for investors and potentially lead to further price increases. One key factor that Material Indicators is watching is bid liquidity in the active trading range. Bid liquidity refers to the amount of buying power in the market and is a crucial indicator of investor sentiment and confidence in a particular asset. The company is closely monitoring how much bid liquidity moves into the active trading range to serve as support for BTC. In addition, Material Indicators is anticipating the testimony of Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell, which could impact the cryptocurrency markets. While the company does not expect any major surprises from Powell&#8217;s testimony, they recognize that these events can often lead to increased volatility and uncertainty in the markets. However, Bitcoin needs to maintain its bullish momentum and overcome the nearest resistance level of $29,500 to have a chance at breaching the crucial $30,000 line.  On the other hand, if this attempt fails, it will be crucial for BTC to consolidate above $29,000 and prevent any further downside movements. Bitcoin Set For Major Rally? Ted Talks Macro, a well-known cryptocurrency trader and host of a popular podcast has recently updated his macro view for BTC, highlighting several bullish factors that could drive the cryptocurrency&#8217;s price higher in the coming months. According to Ted, the market has now accepted above February&#8217;s highs and is forming a higher low on the weekly timeframe. This is a bullish signal that suggests BTC is on track for further gains. In March, Ted noted that the high-timeframe bull idea would be invalidated if BTC dropped back into the range below $24,500. However, this did not happen, and the bulls showed up to support the price of BTC. In addition to these technical factors, Ted identified several narratives that could drive sentiment over the coming quarters. These include the upcoming BTC halving, the launch of the Blackrock spot ETF (and other similar products), the Federal Reserve&#8217;s pause on interest rate hikes, and the launch of crypto exchanges by traditional finance giants. Related Reading: MATIC Price Gains Momentum, But Bulls Face Uncertainty Without Breaking Vital Resistance Based on these factors, Ted Talks Macro has set a target of $35,000 for BTC, which is now in play. This target represents a significant increase from BTC&#8217;s current price and suggests that the cryptocurrency market could be poised for a major rally in the months ahead. Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com ]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin (BTC), the largest cryptocurrency in the market, has demonstrated a strong shift in investor sentiment. Over the past 24 hours, BTC has surged by an impressive 9%, currently trading at $29,300. </p>
<p>However, Bitcoin still faces significant hurdles, with a resistance line placed at $29,500, as well as a key psychological level at $30,000 that has not been reached since April 19th. </p>
<h2>BTC’s Moment Of Truth</h2>
<p>Material Indicators, a cryptocurrency data analysis firm, has <a href="https://twitter.com/MI_Algos/status/1671498673090428933?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">identified </a>a substantial resistance level for BTC at $30,000. This resistance level has been building and may impede the cryptocurrency&#8217;s upward momentum, potentially causing it to become range-bound, as has occurred several times this year.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/us-bitcoin-investor-trading-volume-rises-stage-set-for-another-massive-rally/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">US Bitcoin Investor Trading Volume Rises, Stage Set For Another Massive Rally?</a></p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-539027" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Screenshot_58.jpg" alt="Bitcoin " width="581" height="541" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Screenshot_58.jpg 581w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Screenshot_58-460x428.jpg 460w" sizes="(max-width: 581px) 100vw, 581px"/>
<p>If BTC fails to break through this resistance level, it could become trapped in a narrow trading range, limiting its potential for further growth. However, if it manages to overcome this hurdle, it could provide a strong bullish signal for investors and potentially lead to further price increases.</p>
<p>One key factor that Material Indicators is watching is bid liquidity in the active trading range. Bid liquidity refers to the amount of buying power in the market and is a crucial indicator of investor sentiment and confidence in a particular asset. The company is closely monitoring how much bid liquidity moves into the active trading range to serve as support for BTC.</p>
<p>In addition, Material Indicators is anticipating the testimony of Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell, which could impact the cryptocurrency markets. While the company does not expect any major surprises from Powell&#8217;s testimony, they recognize that these events can often lead to increased volatility and uncertainty in the markets.</p>
<p>However, Bitcoin needs to maintain its bullish momentum and overcome the nearest resistance level of $29,500 to have a chance at breaching the crucial $30,000 line. </p>
<p>On the other hand, if this attempt fails, it will be crucial for BTC to consolidate above $29,000 and prevent any further downside movements.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Set For Major Rally?</h2>
<p>Ted Talks Macro, a well-known cryptocurrency trader and host of a popular podcast has recently <a href="https://twitter.com/tedtalksmacro/status/1671443688566710274?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">updated </a>his macro view for BTC, highlighting several bullish factors that could drive the cryptocurrency&#8217;s price higher in the coming months.</p>
<p>According to Ted, the market has now accepted above February&#8217;s highs and is forming a higher low on the weekly timeframe. This is a bullish signal that suggests BTC is on track for further gains.</p>
<p>In March, Ted noted that the high-timeframe bull idea would be invalidated if BTC dropped back into the range below $24,500. However, this did not happen, and the bulls showed up to support the price of BTC.</p>
<p>In addition to these technical factors, Ted identified several narratives that could drive sentiment over the coming quarters. These include the upcoming BTC halving, the launch of the Blackrock spot ETF (and other similar products), the Federal Reserve&#8217;s pause on interest rate hikes, and the launch of crypto exchanges by traditional finance giants.</p>

<p>Based on these factors, Ted Talks Macro has set a target of $35,000 for BTC, which is now in play. This target represents a significant increase from BTC&#8217;s current price and suggests that the cryptocurrency market could be poised for a major rally in the months ahead.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/JDDRCnA4/" alt="Bitcoin " width="1814" height="858"/>
<p>Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/iStock-1410473489-460x259.jpg" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>&#8220;Yes, This Is A Bull Market&#8221; Expert Explains Why Bitcoin Will Outperform Tesla&#8217;s +162%</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/yes-this-is-a-bull-market-expert-explains-why-bitcoin-will-outperform-teslas-162/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reynaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 21:00:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=538968</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin is finally showing some green over the past week as the cryptocurrency rose from the mid-area of its current levels. The number one crypto by market cap seems poised to extend its rally, can it finally break from its current range? Related Reading: Nansen Forecast For Bitcoin Bull Run: Regulatory Clarity And Lower Inflation As of this writing, Bitcoin (BTC) trades at $29,000 with an 8% profit in the last 24 hours. Over the last week, BTC’s price has displayed a similar performance recording a 12% profit. Other cryptocurrencies in the top 10 by market cap are experiencing profits, but BTC is outperforming other assets in the sector. Bitcoin Next Bull Run, Bad News For Tesla And Tech? The key to tracking Bitcoin’s next bull run could be its correlation with tech equities. The nascent crypto industry has been moving in tandem with this sector since 2021. At that time, the price of Bitcoin reached a new all-time high of around $69,000. The correlation with tech equities, as measured by the performance of the Nasdaq 100, has been decreasing over time and could continue this trajectory. According to the former hedge fund manager for Goldman Sachs, Raoul Pal, Bitcoin, and crypto are on track to outperform tech equities and “all other equities.” Despite the short-term turmoil in 2023, BTC’s price experienced a 75% increase year-to-date (YTD). In that sense, Ethereum (ETH), Tesla (TSLA), and other tech stocks have been rallying and will likely see further profits. As of this writing, ETH and TSLA experienced 50% and 160% profit, respectively. However, Pal believes BTC will take the crown in the short term as the cryptocurrency extend its “bull market.” According to Pal, the bear market for BTC ended in October 2022 as liquidity across the financial sector bottomed out. As seen in the chart below, liquidity and financial conditions have been improving, according to Pal. In the past, whenever liquidity increased, BTC and equities followed. Related Reading: US Bitcoin Investor Trading Volume Rises, Stage Set For Another Massive Rally? The expert added expanding on BTC’s capacity to outperform tech while breaking its long-term correlation with these financial assets: Yes, tech is VERY overbought. Yes, it will correct at some point. Yes, this is a bull market.  When tech corrects, crypto probably explodes to new highs on the year again too. Welcome to the Exponential Age. Cover image from Unsplash, chart from Tradingview]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Bitcoin is finally showing some green over the past week as the cryptocurrency rose from the mid-area of its current levels. The number one crypto by market cap seems poised to extend its rally, can it finally break from its current range? </strong></p>

<p>As of this writing, Bitcoin (BTC) trades at $29,000 with an 8% profit in the last 24 hours. Over the last week, BTC’s price has displayed a similar performance recording a 12% profit. Other cryptocurrencies in the top 10 by market cap are experiencing profits, but BTC is outperforming other assets in the sector.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-538991 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-1-860x410.png" alt="Bitcoin BTC BTCUSDT" width="860" height="410" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-1-860x410.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-1-460x219.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-1-768x366.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-1-1536x732.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-1-750x358.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-1-1140x543.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-1.png 1758w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/>
<h2>Bitcoin Next Bull Run, Bad News For Tesla And Tech?</h2>
<p>The key to tracking <a href="https://www.nasdaq.com/articles/bitcoin-continues-correlation-with-nasdaq-100-thus-far-in-2023" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Bitcoin’s next bull run could be its correlation with tech equities</a>. The nascent crypto industry has been moving in tandem with this sector since 2021.</p>
<p>At that time, the price of Bitcoin reached a new all-time high of around $69,000. The correlation with tech equities, as measured by the performance of the Nasdaq 100, has been decreasing over time and could continue this trajectory.</p>
<p>According to the former hedge fund manager for Goldman Sachs, Raoul Pal, Bitcoin, and crypto are on track to outperform tech equities and “all other equities.” Despite the short-term turmoil in 2023, BTC’s price experienced a 75% increase year-to-date (YTD).</p>
<p>In that sense, Ethereum (ETH), Tesla (TSLA), and other tech stocks have been rallying and will likely see further profits. As of this writing, ETH and TSLA experienced 50% and 160% profit, respectively.</p>
<p>However, Pal believes BTC will take the crown in the short term as the cryptocurrency extend its “bull market.” According to Pal, the bear market for BTC ended in October 2022 as liquidity across the financial sector bottomed out.</p>
<p>As seen in the chart below, liquidity and financial conditions have been improving, according to Pal. In the past, whenever liquidity increased, BTC and equities followed.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-538989 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-2-860x485.png" alt="Bitcoin BTC BTCUSDT Chart 2" width="860" height="485" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-2-860x485.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-2-460x259.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-2-768x433.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-2-1536x866.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-2-750x423.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-2-1140x643.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-2.png 1924w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/>

<p>The expert <a href="https://twitter.com/RaoulGMI/status/1671483635386441730" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">added</a> expanding on BTC’s capacity to outperform tech while breaking its long-term correlation with these financial assets:</p>
<blockquote><p>Yes, tech is VERY overbought. Yes, it will correct at some point. Yes, this is a bull market.  When tech corrects, crypto probably explodes to new highs on the year again too. Welcome to the Exponential Age.</p></blockquote>
<p>Cover image from Unsplash, chart from Tradingview</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-460x306.jpg" width="460" height="306" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Solana Bulls Must Overcome This Resistance To Avoid A 10% Plunge</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/solana/solana-bulls-must-overcome-this-resistance-to-avoid-a-10-plunge/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[anushsamal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 20:00:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Solana]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sol]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SOLSUDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SOLSUSD]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=539007</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[At present, the price of Solana (SOL) is showing signs of recovery from a corrective phase. However, to sustain the momentum, it is crucial for SOL to surpass a significant resistance level. In the past 24 hours, SOL has experienced a 4% increase in value. Over the course of the past week, the altcoin has displayed notable upward movement, gaining over 9%. Despite the recent price rise, the technical outlook for SOL still leans towards a bearish influence. Both the demand and accumulation for SOL have remained low, indicating a bearish sentiment. The volatility of Bitcoin, with its price reaching $28,900, has affected the overall market, including altcoins. Although some major altcoins have seen price appreciation, they are still struggling to break through immediate resistance levels. Related Reading: US Bitcoin Investor Trading Volume Rises, Stage Set For Another Massive Rally? The stability of the broader market is crucial for the future performance of SOL. The market capitalization of SOL has declined, indicating a higher selling strength in the market Solana Price Analysis: One-Day Chart At the time of writing, SOL was trading at $16.74. The altcoin has rebounded from the price level of $14.40 and is currently showing a steady appreciation on its chart. However, in order for the bullish momentum to strengthen, SOL needs to surpass the immediate resistance level of $17.20. If buyers fail to step in and drive the price higher, there is a possibility of a retracement in the chart. The local support level for SOL is situated at $15.21. If the coin is unable to sustain its position above this support level, it may further decline below $14.40. Technical Analysis Although SOL has recovered from the oversold territory, the buying strength remains relatively weak despite a slight improvement. This is evident from the Relative Strength Index (RSI) being below the half-line, indicating that sellers maintain control over the price action. Additionally, SOL has fallen below the 20-Simple Moving Average (SMA) line, suggesting that demand is still low and sellers are the driving force behind the market momentum. For a more positive outlook, it is essential for SOL to successfully surpass the $17 price level. This breakthrough would potentially attract renewed demand to the market. On the one-day chart, SOL has displayed mixed signals, including the emergence of buy signals. The Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD), which indicates momentum and potential shifts, has started forming green histograms associated with buy signals. This suggests the possibility of a positive price change for SOL in the future. Related Reading: Shiba Inu Breaks Through Crucial Resistance Point With 10% Climb On the other hand, the Chaikin Money Flow (CMF), which depicts capital inflows and outflows, has remained below the half-line. This indicates that capital inflows have been relatively low on the chart, implying a lack of significant buying pressure for SOL. Featured Image From UnSplash, Charts From TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>At present, the price of Solana (SOL) is showing signs of recovery from a corrective phase. However, to sustain the momentum, it is crucial for SOL to surpass a significant resistance level. In the past 24 hours, SOL has experienced a 4% increase in value.</p>
<p>Over the course of the past week, the altcoin has displayed notable upward movement, gaining over 9%. Despite the recent price rise, the technical outlook for SOL still leans towards a bearish influence. Both the demand and accumulation for SOL have remained low, indicating a bearish sentiment.</p>
<p>The volatility of Bitcoin, with its price reaching $28,900, has affected the overall market, including altcoins. Although some major altcoins have seen price appreciation, they are still struggling to break through immediate resistance levels.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/us-bitcoin-investor-trading-volume-rises-stage-set-for-another-massive-rally/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">US Bitcoin Investor Trading Volume Rises, Stage Set For Another Massive Rally?</a></p>
<p>The stability of the broader market is crucial for the future performance of SOL. The market capitalization of SOL has declined, indicating a higher selling strength in the market</p>
<h2>Solana Price Analysis: One-Day Chart</h2>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-539014 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/SOLUSD_2023-06-21_19-27-43.png" alt="Solana" width="1817" height="830" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/SOLUSD_2023-06-21_19-27-43.png 1817w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/SOLUSD_2023-06-21_19-27-43-460x210.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/SOLUSD_2023-06-21_19-27-43-860x393.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/SOLUSD_2023-06-21_19-27-43-768x351.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/SOLUSD_2023-06-21_19-27-43-1536x702.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/SOLUSD_2023-06-21_19-27-43-750x343.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/SOLUSD_2023-06-21_19-27-43-1140x521.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1817px) 100vw, 1817px"/>
<p>At the time of writing, SOL was trading at $16.74. The altcoin has rebounded from the price level of $14.40 and is currently showing a steady appreciation on its chart. However, in order for the bullish momentum to strengthen, SOL needs to surpass the immediate resistance level of $17.20.</p>
<p>If buyers fail to step in and drive the price higher, there is a possibility of a retracement in the chart. The local support level for SOL is situated at $15.21. If the coin is unable to sustain its position above this support level, it may further decline below $14.40.</p>
<h2>Technical Analysis</h2>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-539015 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/SOLUSD_2023-06-21_19-28-23.png" alt="Solana" width="1817" height="743" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/SOLUSD_2023-06-21_19-28-23.png 1817w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/SOLUSD_2023-06-21_19-28-23-460x188.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/SOLUSD_2023-06-21_19-28-23-860x352.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/SOLUSD_2023-06-21_19-28-23-768x314.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/SOLUSD_2023-06-21_19-28-23-1536x628.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/SOLUSD_2023-06-21_19-28-23-750x307.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/SOLUSD_2023-06-21_19-28-23-1140x466.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1817px) 100vw, 1817px"/>
<p>Although SOL has recovered from the oversold territory, the buying strength remains relatively weak despite a slight improvement. This is evident from the Relative Strength Index (RSI) being below the half-line, indicating that sellers maintain control over the price action.</p>
<p>Additionally, SOL has fallen below the 20-Simple Moving Average (SMA) line, suggesting that demand is still low and sellers are the driving force behind the market momentum.</p>
<p>For a more positive outlook, it is essential for SOL to successfully surpass the $17 price level. This breakthrough would potentially attract renewed demand to the market.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-539018 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/SOLUSD_2023-06-21_19-29-11.png" alt="Solana" width="1817" height="743" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/SOLUSD_2023-06-21_19-29-11.png 1817w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/SOLUSD_2023-06-21_19-29-11-460x188.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/SOLUSD_2023-06-21_19-29-11-860x352.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/SOLUSD_2023-06-21_19-29-11-768x314.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/SOLUSD_2023-06-21_19-29-11-1536x628.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/SOLUSD_2023-06-21_19-29-11-750x307.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/SOLUSD_2023-06-21_19-29-11-1140x466.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1817px) 100vw, 1817px"/>
<p>On the one-day chart, SOL has displayed mixed signals, including the emergence of buy signals. The Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD), which indicates momentum and potential shifts, has started forming green histograms associated with buy signals. This suggests the possibility of a positive price change for SOL in the future.</p>

<p>On the other hand, the Chaikin Money Flow (CMF), which depicts capital inflows and outflows, has remained below the half-line. This indicates that capital inflows have been relatively low on the chart, implying a lack of significant buying pressure for SOL.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/guerrillabuzz-5_asf_AsG-I-unsplash-2-460x259.jpg" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Rally Appears To Be Fueled By Derivatives, Will It Last?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-rally-appears-to-be-fueled-by-derivatives-will-it-last/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hououin Kyouma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 19:00:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Derivative Exchanges]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin rally]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin volume]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=538985</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[On-chain data shows that derivative exchanges have observed elevated activity as Bitcoin has rallied towards the $29,000 level. Bitcoin Spot Vs Derivative Trading Volume Ratio Has Been Quite Low Recently As pointed out by an analyst in a CryptoQuant post, the latest price increase is mainly driven by the derivatives. The indicator of interest here is the &#8220;trading volume ratio,&#8221; which measures the ratio between the Bitcoin trading volume on the spot exchanges and that on the derivative exchanges. The &#8220;trading volume&#8221; here naturally refers to the total amount of the cryptocurrency that investors are transacting/moving around on a platform or a group of platforms. When the value of the trading volume ratio is high, it means that the spot exchanges are observing a high amount of activity when compared to the derivative platforms. On the other hand, low values of the indicator imply the derivative exchanges are the ones seeing a relatively high volume at the moment. Now, here is a chart that shows the trend in the Bitcoin trading volume ratio over the past year: The value of the metric seems to have been quite low in recent days &#124; Source: CryptoQuant As displayed in the above graph, the Bitcoin trading volume ratio had taken a plunge back in March and has since moved mostly sideways around pretty low levels. This would suggest that there has been little spot activity in the market during this time, at least when compared to the volumes that the derivative exchanges have been observing. Interestingly, despite the price of the asset registering a sharp jump towards the $29,000 level during the past day, the ratio has failed to show any uptick, implying that the spot volumes continue to remain low relative to the derivatives activity. This fact would suggest that the latest rally may have in fact received its fuel from the derivatives, rather then the spot market. Historically, rallies that have started along with rising spot trading volumes have been the ones more likely to sustain for longer durations. Related Reading: Bitcoin Miners Deposit To Exchanges, What Does This Mean? From the chart, it&#8217;s visible that the Bitcoin price surge back in January of this year had kicked off when the trading volume ratio had been at relatively high levels. Similarly, the recovery rally back in March had also started when the indicator had seen an uplift (although a much smaller one). As mentioned earlier, the metric had plummeted shortly after this rally had occurred and has been at low levels since then. In this time, BTC has been unable to record any sustainable move. In the past day, however, things have obviously looked different, as the rapid price surge has been unlike anything the asset has displayed recently. Still, the fact that the spot volumes are still low means that the rally &#8220;appears weaker when compared to the solid rallies led by spot market at $16,000 and $19,000,&#8221; according to the quant. Related Reading: Bitcoin Whales Continue To Accumulate As BTC Makes Recovery Push It now remains to be seen if the ratio will continue to be low in the coming days, or if an uptick in spot activity would appear after all. BTC Price At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading around $29,100, up 12% in the last week. Looks like BTC has seen a sharp uplift in the last 24 hours &#124; Source: BTCUSD on TradingView Featured image from Kanchanara on Unsplash.com, charts from TradingView.com, CryptoQuant.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On-chain data shows that derivative exchanges have observed elevated activity as Bitcoin has rallied towards the $29,000 level.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Spot Vs Derivative Trading Volume Ratio Has Been Quite Low Recently</h2>
<p>As pointed out by an analyst in a CryptoQuant <a href="https://cryptoquant.com/insights/quicktake/64927364e926de4bebe7513f-BTC-is-returning-to-the-US" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">post</a>, the latest price increase is mainly driven by the derivatives. The indicator of interest here is the &#8220;trading volume ratio,&#8221; which measures the ratio between the Bitcoin trading volume on the spot exchanges and that on the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-miners-deposit-big-derivatives-exchanges/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">derivative exchanges</a>.</p>
<p>The &#8220;<a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/us-bitcoin-investor-trading-volume-rises-stage-set-for-another-massive-rally/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">trading volume</a>&#8221; here naturally refers to the total amount of the cryptocurrency that investors are transacting/moving around on a platform or a group of platforms.</p>
<p>When the value of the trading volume ratio is high, it means that the spot exchanges are observing a high amount of activity when compared to the derivative platforms. On the other hand, low values of the indicator imply the derivative exchanges are the ones seeing a relatively high volume at the moment.</p>
<p>Now, here is a chart that shows the trend in the Bitcoin trading volume ratio over the past year:</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone aligncenter" src="https://img.cryptoquant.com/226984/quicktake/ImK8SEpQk_a7c39f960f372c3a14f3588fc48350bc87ad90960e4f1f4035e77d0e5431f8bd.png" alt="Bitcoin Trading Volume Ratio" width="1280" height="806"/></p>

<p>As displayed in the above graph, the Bitcoin trading volume ratio had taken a plunge back in March and has since moved mostly sideways around pretty low levels.</p>
<p>This would suggest that there has been little spot activity in the market during this time, at least when compared to the volumes that the derivative exchanges have been observing.</p>
<p>Interestingly, despite the price of the asset registering a <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-eye-30k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">sharp jump towards the $29,000 level</a> during the past day, the ratio has failed to show any uptick, implying that the spot volumes continue to remain low relative to the derivatives activity.</p>
<p>This fact would suggest that the latest rally may have in fact received its fuel from the derivatives, rather then the spot market. Historically, rallies that have started along with rising spot trading volumes have been the ones more likely to sustain for longer durations.</p>

<p>From the chart, it&#8217;s visible that the Bitcoin price surge back in January of this year had kicked off when the trading volume ratio had been at relatively high levels.</p>
<p>Similarly, the recovery rally back in March had also started when the indicator had seen an uplift (although a much smaller one). As mentioned earlier, the metric had plummeted shortly after this rally had occurred and has been at low levels since then. In this time, BTC has been unable to record any sustainable move.</p>
<p>In the past day, however, things have obviously looked different, as the rapid price surge has been unlike anything the asset has displayed recently. Still, the fact that the spot volumes are still low means that the rally &#8220;appears weaker when compared to the solid rallies led by spot market at $16,000 and $19,000,&#8221; according to the quant.</p>

<p>It now remains to be seen if the ratio will continue to be low in the coming days, or if an uptick in spot activity would appear after all.</p>
<h2>BTC Price</h2>
<p>At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading around $29,100, up 12% in the last week.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium aligncenter" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/Td7CPisp/" alt="Bitcoin Price Chart" width="1534" height="911"/></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/kanchanara-4KJJezDyo3M-unsplash-2-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Conflux Gains 20% In 24 hours, Emerges On Top Gainers Chart</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/altcoin/conflux-gains-20-in-24-hours-emerges-on-top-gainers-chart/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Semilore Faleti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 18:00:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CFX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CFX price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[china]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conflux]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Top Giner]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=538984</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The crypto market is currently on a rebound, with several assets recording little gains in the last few hours. Conflux (CFX), one of the trendiest assets of 2023, has gained by 20.17% in the last 24 hours, emerging as the second biggest daily gainer, according to CoinMarketCap data. Prior to its price boost yesterday, Conflux had been on a bearish trend for most of the month, from $0.280 on June 1 to trade as low as $0.170 on June 16. Since the start of the month, the “Chinese MATIC” has lost about 33.33% of its market value.  Related Reading: Nansen Forecast For Bitcoin Bull Run: Regulatory Clarity And Lower Inflation CFX began trading around $0.179 yesterday before experiencing a price surge to hit a peak price of $0.221 in the early hours of today, June 21. Thereafter, the token witnessed a slight re-correction falling to a price of $0.213, and has remained around that price region since then. As of this writing, CFX changes hands at $0.217, with a 24-hour trading volume of $203 million &#8211; a result of a 387.97% trading volume surge in the past day. The cryptocurrency boasts a total market cap of $646 million, making it the 60th biggest token by market capitalization.  CFX Trading At $0.217 &#124; Source: CFXUSD Chart On Tradingview.com  Conflux In 2023 So Far Conflux began the year slowly, showing little to no significant price movement in January before commencing an impressive bullish run in mid-February, gaining over 500% in value to trade at $0.32 on February 22.  Thereafter, the Chinese no. 1 cryptocurrency experienced a significant price dip, sliding to a market price of $0.160 on March 12. This was followed by another upswing, which saw CFX hit its 2023 peak &#8211; so far &#8211; at $0.457 on March 20.  Subsequent to these price movements, CFX recorded additional weighty gains and losses. However, since mid-April, the CFX market has been rather bearish, losing over 95% of its value between April 12 and till date.  The Conflux Network aims to leverage blockchain technology, becoming a catalyst for the borderless economy. Founded in 2018, Conflux’s popularity mainly revolves around its prominent status as China&#8217;s only public blockchain.  Asides from its interesting price history, Conflux has also captured news headlines in 2023 due to its strategic partnerships, most notably its collaboration with China’s second-largest telecommunications company &#8211; China Telecom &#8211; to produce Blockchain-enabled SIM cards.  Could A Market Recovery Be On For Conflux?  Following CFX’s current surge, it appears the token could be attempting a market resurgence and perhaps attain the high price levels seen at the beginning of the year.  Related Reading: Shiba Inu Breaks Through Crucial Resistance Point With 10% Climb According to the prediction site Coincodex, the current sentiment surrounding the CFX token is neutral, while its Fear &#38; Greed Index is set to 59. The team at Coincodex also predicts CFX to maintain its bullish momentum for now, hitting a market price of $0.229 and $0.237 in 5 and 30 days, respectively.  That said, investors are reminded not to rely on predictions as financial advice but to conduct appropriate research before choosing to engage the market.  Featured Image:  Conflux Network, chart from Tradingview.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The crypto market is currently on a rebound, with several assets recording little gains in the last few hours. Conflux (CFX), one of the trendiest assets of 2023, has gained by 20.17% in the last 24 hours, emerging as the second biggest daily gainer, according to <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/conflux-network/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">CoinMarketCap data</a>.</p>
<p>Prior to its price boost yesterday, Conflux had been on a bearish trend for most of the month, from $0.280 on June 1 to trade as low as $0.170 on June 16. Since the start of the month, the “Chinese MATIC” has lost about 33.33% of its market value. </p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/nansen-forecasts-conditions-for-the-next-bitcoin-bull-run/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Nansen Forecast For Bitcoin Bull Run: Regulatory Clarity And Lower Inflation</a></p>
<p>CFX began trading around $0.179 yesterday before experiencing a price surge to hit a peak price of $0.221 in the early hours of today, June 21. Thereafter, the token witnessed a slight re-correction falling to a price of $0.213, and has remained around that price region since then.</p>
<p>As of this writing, CFX changes hands at $0.217, with a 24-hour trading volume of $203 million &#8211; a result of a 387.97% trading volume surge in the past day. The cryptocurrency boasts a total market cap of $646 million, making it the 60th biggest token by market capitalization. </p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/tEE1gedf/" alt="Conflux" width="1479" height="913"/></p>

<h2>Conflux In 2023 So Far</h2>
<p>Conflux began the year slowly, showing little to no significant price movement in January before commencing an impressive bullish run in mid-February, gaining over 500% in value to trade at $0.32 on February 22. </p>
<p>Thereafter, the Chinese no. 1 cryptocurrency experienced a significant price dip, sliding to a market price of $0.160 on March 12. This was followed by another upswing, which saw CFX hit its 2023 peak &#8211; so far &#8211; at $0.457 on March 20. </p>
<p>Subsequent to these price movements, CFX recorded additional weighty gains and losses. However, since mid-April, the CFX market has been rather bearish, losing over 95% of its value between April 12 and till date. </p>
<p>The Conflux Network aims to leverage blockchain technology, becoming a catalyst for the borderless economy. Founded in 2018, Conflux’s popularity mainly revolves around its prominent status as China&#8217;s only public blockchain. </p>
<p>Asides from its interesting price history, Conflux has also captured news headlines in 2023 due to its strategic partnerships, most notably its collaboration with China’s second-largest telecommunications company &#8211; <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/conflux-partners-with-china-telecom/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">China Telecom</a> &#8211; to produce Blockchain-enabled SIM cards. </p>
<h2>Could A Market Recovery Be On For Conflux? </h2>
<p>Following CFX’s current surge, it appears the token could be attempting a market resurgence and perhaps attain the high price levels seen at the beginning of the year. </p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/shiba-inu-notches-10-climb/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Shiba Inu Breaks Through Crucial Resistance Point With 10% Climb</a></p>
<p>According to the prediction site <a href="https://coincodex.com/crypto/conflux-network/price-prediction/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Coincodex</a>, the current sentiment surrounding the CFX token is neutral, while its Fear &amp; Greed Index is set to 59. The team at Coincodex also predicts CFX to maintain its bullish momentum for now, hitting a market price of $0.229 and $0.237 in 5 and 30 days, respectively. </p>
<p>That said, investors are reminded not to rely on predictions as financial advice but to conduct appropriate research before choosing to engage the market. </p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/og_image_default_87b4fea764-460x259.jpg" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Cash Surges 20% In One Day As Market Rebounds, What&#8217;s Next? </title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin-cash/bitcoin-cash-surges-20-in-one-day-as-market-rebounds-whats-next/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Kent Glory]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 17:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Cash]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BCH analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BCH Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BCHUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Cash (BCH)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=538982</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The crypto market entered an upward trajectory in the past 24 hours, with most coins, including Bitcoin Cash (BCH), making notable price moves. Speculations and anticipation around BlackRock’s spot BTC application, and the recent WisdomTree and Invesco filing, could be driving the surge. Also, the just-launched Wall Street-backed crypto exchange EDX must have contributed, to a large extent, to the improved market sentiment. The total crypto market cap has already increased 5.74% in the last 24 hours as Bitcoin tallies a 7.94% gain over the same time frame, propelling its weekly gain to 11.73%.  BCH Price Outlook Following the brief consolidation and sporadic price action triggered by heightened regulatory uncertainty, the bulls are leading the market. Assets prices ticked positive in the last 24 hours. As Bitcoin fights to break the $29,000 mark, its close relative, Bitcoin Cash, has put on an incredible performance in the background. Related Reading: Nansen Forecast For Bitcoin Bull Run: Regulatory Clarity And Lower Inflation Bitcoin Cash’s (BCH) price has surged over 21.20% in the last day with the recent bullish momentum. The asset&#8217;s remarkable performance pushed it atop the chartsand it is now the top-gaining coin of the day, June 21, with a 22.10% price gain in the last seven days. Bitcoin Cash&#8217;s appearance on the EDX exchange boosted social sentiment, massively pushing network activity. The token trading volume has increased massively from $76.86 million, recorded yesterday, June 20, to $382 million today. The increase represents over 493% in 24 hours. Also, BCH trades at $129.21, with a 21.20% price increase over the past 24 hours. What&#8217;s Behind The Price Rally? One of the reasons for BCH&#8217;s performance is the newly launched crypto exchange, EDX, backed by Fidelity Investments, Charles Schwab, and other Wall Street market leaders. The crypto exchange went live today, June 21, and currently, it supports only Bitcoin (BTC), Litecoin (LTC), Ethereum (ETH), and Bitcoin Cash (BCH). A crypto exchange supported by top Wall Street participants suggests more institutional investors and mainstream crypto adoption is underway. Now, investor sentiment has turned bullish following spot BTC ETF applications by three leading asset managers.  According to reports, BlackRock’s Bitcoin ETF application encouraged two others (WisdomTree Investment and Invesco) to step forward. The world&#8217;s largest asset manager filed for a spot Bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF) with the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) on June 15.  Related Reading: Why Are Bitcoin And Crypto Up Today? You Need To Know This The SEC had previously denied the approval of other firms&#8217; BTC ETF applications. However, many believe BlackRock would succeed due to its reputation and connections. This is also because BlackRock has a high success rate in previous ETF applications, hence the market’s optimism.  An approved BTC spot ETF would boost Bitcoin’s legitimacy and encourage institutional investment, improving the asset market outlook. As such, the market sentiment rapidly shifted. On June 20, the Fear &#38; Greed Index pointed towards &#8220;Neutral&#8221; but now flags Greed after today&#8217;s market rebound. Featured image from Pixabay and chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The crypto market entered an upward trajectory in the past 24 hours, with most coins, including Bitcoin Cash (BCH), making notable price moves. Speculations and anticipation around BlackRock’s spot BTC application, and the recent WisdomTree and Invesco filing, could be driving the surge.</p>
<p>Also, the just-launched Wall Street-backed crypto exchange EDX must have contributed, to a large extent, to the improved market sentiment. </p>
<p>The total crypto <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">market cap</a> has already increased 5.74% in the last 24 hours as <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Bitcoin</a> tallies a 7.94% gain over the same time frame, propelling its weekly gain to 11.73%. </p>
<h2><b>BCH Price Outlook</b></h2>
<p>Following the brief consolidation and sporadic price action triggered by heightened regulatory uncertainty, the bulls are leading the market. Assets prices ticked positive in the last 24 hours. As Bitcoin fights to break the $29,000 mark, its close relative, Bitcoin Cash, has put on an incredible performance in the background.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/nansen-forecasts-conditions-for-the-next-bitcoin-bull-run/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Nansen Forecast For Bitcoin Bull Run: Regulatory Clarity And Lower Inflation</a></p>
<p>Bitcoin Cash’s (BCH) price has surged over 21.20% in the last day with the recent bullish momentum. The asset&#8217;s remarkable performance pushed it atop the <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/gainers-losers/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">charts</a>and it is now the top-gaining coin of the day, June 21, with a 22.10% price gain in the last seven days.</p>
<p>Bitcoin Cash&#8217;s appearance on the EDX exchange boosted social sentiment, massively pushing network activity. The token trading volume has increased massively from $76.86 million, recorded yesterday, June 20, to $382 million today. The increase represents over 493% in 24 hours. Also, BCH trades at $129.21, with a 21.20% price increase over the past 24 hours.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/RIrj3wL5/" alt="BCHUSD price chart" width="980" height="538"/>
<h2><b>What&#8217;s Behind The Price Rally?</b></h2>
<p>One of the reasons for BCH&#8217;s performance is the newly launched crypto exchange, EDX, backed by Fidelity Investments, Charles Schwab, and other Wall Street market leaders. The crypto exchange went live today, June 21, and currently, it supports only Bitcoin (BTC), Litecoin (LTC), Ethereum (ETH), and Bitcoin Cash (BCH).</p>
<p>A crypto exchange supported by top Wall Street participants suggests more institutional investors and mainstream crypto adoption is underway. Now, investor sentiment has turned bullish following spot BTC ETF applications by three leading asset managers. </p>
<p>According to <a href="https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/wisdomtree-files-to-start-a-us-spot-bitcoin-etf-on-the-heels-of-blackrock-s-application-1.1935782" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">reports</a>, BlackRock’s Bitcoin ETF application encouraged two others (WisdomTree Investment and Invesco) to step forward. The world&#8217;s largest asset manager filed for a spot Bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF) with the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) on June 15. </p>

<p>The SEC had previously denied the approval of other firms&#8217; BTC ETF applications. However, many believe BlackRock would succeed due to its reputation and connections. This is also because BlackRock has a high success rate in previous ETF applications, hence the market’s optimism. </p>
<p>An approved BTC spot ETF would boost Bitcoin’s legitimacy and encourage institutional investment, improving the asset market outlook. As such, the market sentiment rapidly shifted. </p>
<p>On June 20, the Fear &amp; Greed <a href="https://alternative.me/crypto/fear-and-greed-index/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Index</a> pointed towards &#8220;Neutral&#8221; but now flags Greed after today&#8217;s market rebound.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BCH-460x325.jpg" width="460" height="325" />	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
