<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
>

<channel>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.newsbtc.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<description>Bitcoin &#38; Cryptocurrency News Today</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 07:14:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>PEPE Bulls Losing Steam? Fatigue Appears To Undermine Price Rally</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/pepe-bulls-losing-steam/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 07:40:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[meme coins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PEPE price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price action]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=541830</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[PEPE, once riding the waves of a bullish surge, finds itself in a precarious position as the price correction of Bitcoin (BTC)] reverberates across the market. Over the past 24 hours, the signs of exhaustion have become increasingly apparent, casting a shadow of doubt on PEPE&#8217;s recent gains.  The critical resistance hurdle at $0.00000172 looms large, presenting an insurmountable challenge for the bullish forces that once propelled PEPE&#8217;s ascent.  As the crypto realm holds its breath, all eyes are fixed on the fate of this whimsical digital asset, wondering if it can break free from the grip of resistance and soar to new heights. Related Reading: XRP Next Step: Here’s Why An Upward Move Could Be Likely PEPE Faces Bearish Pressure As Prices Experience A Slump PEPE&#8217;s price on CoinGecko currently stands at $0.00000157. Over the course of the past seven days, PEPE has experienced a slight decline of 2.5%. These recent figures have raised concerns among investors and analysts alike, as PEPE&#8217;s bullish momentum appears to be waning. Source: Coingecko For the past three weeks, PEPE had been enjoying a bullish fervor, displaying impressive price surges. The trend even persisted through the first week of July, as PEPE managed to break past the critical resistance level at $0.00000172. Source: PEPE/USDT on TradingView However, this triumph proved to be short-lived as declining trading volumes paved the way for bearish forces to seize control, putting a halt to the buying pressure. A PEPE price report further confirmed the recent weakening in PEPE&#8217;s performance. The Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD) recently displayed a bearish crossover, with a series of red bars appearing below the zero level. This signal indicates a potential shift in momentum towards the bearish side.  Seeking A Rebound: PEPE&#8217;s Future Prospects While Bitcoin&#8217;s current correction has undoubtedly influenced PEPE&#8217;s recent performance, it is important to remember that the cryptocurrency market is highly dynamic and subject to rapid changes. As Bitcoin stabilizes or regains momentum, it can inject renewed optimism and buying pressure into the market, potentially benefiting tokens like PEPE. PEPE seven-day price performance. Source: Coingecko. Related Reading: Recent 800 Billion Shiba Inu Dump Has Short Traders Worried – Here’s Why Furthermore, PEPE&#8217;s fate also depends on its own fundamentals and developments within its ecosystem. Positive news, partnerships, or adoption initiatives specific to PEPE can have a considerable impact on its price trajectory, even in the face of a broader influence of Bitcoin. (This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk). Featured image from The Guardian]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>PEPE, once riding the waves of a bullish surge, finds itself in a precarious position as the price correction of Bitcoin (BTC)] reverberates across the market. </p>
<p>Over the past 24 hours, the signs of exhaustion have become increasingly apparent, casting a shadow of doubt on PEPE&#8217;s recent gains. </p>
<p>The critical resistance hurdle at $0.00000172 looms large, presenting an insurmountable challenge for the bullish forces that once propelled PEPE&#8217;s ascent. </p>
<p>As the crypto realm holds its breath, all eyes are fixed on the fate of this whimsical digital asset, wondering if it can break free from the grip of resistance and soar to new heights.</p>

<h2><strong>PEPE Faces Bearish Pressure As Prices Experience A Slump</strong></h2>
<p><a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/pepe" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">PEPE&#8217;s price on CoinGecko</a> currently stands at $0.00000157. Over the course of the past seven days, PEPE has experienced a slight decline of 2.5%. These recent figures have raised concerns among investors and analysts alike, as PEPE&#8217;s bullish momentum appears to be waning.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-541835" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-45.png" alt="" width="1035" height="75" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-45.png 1035w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-45-460x33.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-45-860x62.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-45-768x56.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-45-750x54.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 1035px) 100vw, 1035px"/></p>

<p>For the past three weeks, PEPE had been enjoying a bullish fervor, displaying impressive price surges. The trend even persisted through the first week of July, as PEPE managed to break past the critical resistance level at $0.00000172. </p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-541836" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-46.png" alt="" width="1336" height="709" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-46.png 1336w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-46-460x244.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-46-860x456.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-46-768x408.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-46-750x398.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-46-1140x605.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1336px) 100vw, 1336px"/></p>

<p>However, this triumph proved to be short-lived as declining trading volumes paved the way for bearish forces to seize control, putting a halt to the buying pressure.</p>
<p>A <a href="https://ambcrypto.com/pepe-exhaustion-creeps-up-on-bulls/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">PEPE price report</a> further confirmed the recent weakening in PEPE&#8217;s performance. The Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD) recently displayed a bearish crossover, with a series of red bars appearing below the zero level. This signal indicates a potential shift in momentum towards the bearish side. </p>
<h2><strong>Seeking A Rebound: PEPE&#8217;s Future Prospects</strong></h2>
<p>While <a href="https://watcher.guru/news/bitcoin-investors-should-remain-flat-this-weekend-heres-why" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Bitcoin&#8217;s current correction</a> has undoubtedly influenced PEPE&#8217;s recent performance, it is important to remember that the cryptocurrency market is highly dynamic and subject to rapid changes. As Bitcoin stabilizes or regains momentum, it can inject renewed optimism and buying pressure into the market, potentially benefiting tokens like PEPE.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-541841" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-47.png" alt="" width="762" height="499" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-47.png 762w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-47-460x301.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-47-750x491.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 762px) 100vw, 762px"/></p>


<p>Furthermore, PEPE&#8217;s fate also depends on its own fundamentals and developments within its ecosystem. Positive news, partnerships, or adoption initiatives specific to PEPE can have a considerable impact on its price trajectory, even in the face of a broader influence of Bitcoin.</p>
<p><em>(This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk).</em></p>
<p><em>Featured image from The Guardian</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-48-460x332.png" width="460" height="332" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>XRP Next Step: Here&#8217;s Why An Upward Move Could Be Likely</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/xrp-next-step-heres-why-an-upward-move-could-be-likely/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 05:34:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price action]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ripple labs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrp]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=541824</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[XRP&#8217;s price performance has been underwhelming recently, with a notable decline from its previous highs. Regulatory uncertainties surrounding Ripple Labs, the company behind XRP, have played a significant role in dampening investor sentiment.  The ongoing legal battle between Ripple and the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) regarding the classification of XRP as a security has raised concerns about the asset&#8217;s long-term viability. However, despite these challenges, there are reasons to remain cautiously optimistic about XRP&#8217;s future. Related Reading: Recent 800 Billion Shiba Inu Dump Has Short Traders Worried – Here’s Why XRP Shows Potential For A Reversal Despite Recent Declines XRP, currently priced at $0.467053 according to CoinGecko, has experienced a marginal decline of 0.5% over the past 24 hours and a slight drop of 0.3% over the past seven days. However, despite dropping toward the $0.46 level, which serves as the lower border of a descending price channel, there are indications that a likely upward shift may be on the horizon. Up until a breakout to the upper border, which denotes a potential trend reversal, descending price channels are often bearish patterns. In line with this downward trend, XRP has been trading at regularly lower highs and lows. The currency is currently experiencing a significant decline in its value, and it is approaching the lower limit of a trading channel. This decline has created an environment that holds the potential for a potential recovery to take place. When a currency approaches the bottom border of a trading channel, it suggests that it has reached a support level, a point at which there is increased demand for the currency, which could lead to a reversal in its downward trend. XRP market cap currently at $24.3 billion. Chart: TradingView.com According to an XRP price report, when a cryptocurrency reaches the lower border of a descending channel, it often signifies a critical juncture where buying pressure may overcome selling pressure, leading to a reversal in the price direction. While past performance is not indicative of future results, this development suggests that XRP may be poised for an upward movement in the foreseeable future. Ripple Labs&#8217; UBRI Thrives With Global Expansion Meanwhile, Ripple has achieved significant milestones in its University Blockchain Research Initiative (UBRI), a key operational initiative. With a philanthropic commitment of $50 million, the program has successfully onboarded 50 partners from various sectors, Ripple announced on Twitter. 1/ In 2018, Ripple’s UBRI program launched with a $50M philanthropic commitment to leading universities around the world to support academic research, technical development, and innovation in blockchain and crypto. https://t.co/B1DBYNiSdV — Ripple (@Ripple) July 7, 2023 The UBRI program, focused on academic research related to blockchain technology, has made remarkable progress. It has awarded 590 fellowships and scholarships, providing support to aspiring researchers and students. Additionally, the initiative has played a vital role in facilitating the publication of over 1,000 research articles and presentations, contributing to the advancement of knowledge in the field. Related Reading: Compound (COMP) Token Rallies Over 100% After CEO Quits – Details The success of the UBRI program is further highlighted by its global reach, as it is now active on six continents across the world.  (This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk). Featured image from Shutterstock]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>XRP&#8217;s price performance has been underwhelming recently, with a notable decline from its previous highs. Regulatory uncertainties surrounding Ripple Labs, the company behind XRP, have played a significant role in dampening investor sentiment. </p>
<p>The ongoing legal battle between Ripple and the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) regarding the classification of XRP as a security has raised concerns about the asset&#8217;s long-term viability.</p>
<p>However, despite these challenges, there are reasons to remain cautiously optimistic about XRP&#8217;s future.</p>

<h2><strong>XRP Shows Potential For A Reversal Despite Recent Declines</strong></h2>
<p>XRP, currently priced at $0.467053 according to <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/xrp" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">CoinGecko</a>, has experienced a marginal decline of 0.5% over the past 24 hours and a slight drop of 0.3% over the past seven days. </p>
<p>However, despite dropping toward the $0.46 level, which serves as the lower border of a descending price channel, there are indications that a likely upward shift may be on the horizon.</p>
<p>Up until a breakout to the upper border, which denotes a potential trend reversal, descending price channels are often bearish patterns. In line with this downward trend, XRP has been trading at regularly lower highs and lows.</p>
<p>The currency is currently experiencing a significant decline in its value, and it is approaching the lower limit of a trading channel. This decline has created an environment that holds the potential for a potential recovery to take place.</p>
<p>When a currency approaches the bottom border of a trading channel, it suggests that it has reached a support level, a point at which there is increased demand for the currency, which could lead to a reversal in its downward trend.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/jJZrt6De/" width="2475" height="1187"/></p>

<p>According to an <a href="https://u.today/xrps-next-move-should-aim-upward-heres-why" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">XRP price report</a>, when a cryptocurrency reaches the lower border of a descending channel, it often signifies a critical juncture where buying pressure may overcome selling pressure, leading to a reversal in the price direction. </p>
<p>While past performance is not indicative of future results, this development suggests that XRP may be poised for an upward movement in the foreseeable future.</p>
<h2><strong>Ripple Labs&#8217; UBRI Thrives With Global Expansion</strong></h2>
<p>Meanwhile, Ripple has achieved significant milestones in its University Blockchain Research Initiative (UBRI), a key operational initiative. With a philanthropic commitment of $50 million, the program has successfully onboarded 50 partners from various sectors, <a href="https://twitter.com/Ripple/status/1677302826375204867" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Ripple announced on Twitter</a>.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">1/ In 2018, Ripple’s UBRI program launched with a $50M philanthropic commitment to leading universities around the world to support academic research, technical development, and innovation in blockchain and crypto. <a href="https://t.co/B1DBYNiSdV" rel="nofollow">https://t.co/B1DBYNiSdV</a></p>
<p>— Ripple (@Ripple) <a href="https://twitter.com/Ripple/status/1677302826375204867?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">July 7, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p>The UBRI program, focused on academic research related to blockchain technology, has made remarkable progress. It has awarded 590 fellowships and scholarships, providing support to aspiring researchers and students. </p>
<p>Additionally, the initiative has played a vital role in facilitating the publication of over 1,000 research articles and presentations, contributing to the advancement of knowledge in the field.</p>

<p>The success of the UBRI program is further highlighted by its global reach, as it is now active on six continents across the world. </p>
<p><em>(This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk).</em></p>
<p><em>Featured image from Shutterstock</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-44-460x255.png" width="460" height="255" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Circle Intervenes, Freezes $63 Million From Multichain Hack</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/circle-intervenes-freezes-63-million-from-multichain-hack/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dalmas Ngetich]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 02:00:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fantom]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hack]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[multichain]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=541817</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Circle, the official issuer of USDC, the second largest stablecoin by circulating supply, has frozen $63 million from the Multichain hack. Compiled Etherscan data on July 7 shows that the stablecoin issuer froze $27.65 million, $30.1 million, and $5.5 million in three transactions, hampering the hacker&#8217;s cash-out efforts. Multichain Hacked, Circle Intervenes Multichain, a cross-chain protocol router, was hacked on July 7, resulting in the loss of over $126 million worth of various tokens. The exploit came after the attacker illegally accessed Multichain&#8217;s Multi-Party Computation (MPC) address, which stores funds locked between blockchains. Subsequently, the hacker withdrew funds from the address and moved them to an externally controlled wallet. The Fantom Bridge was adversely affected by this outflow as the hacker withdrew various tokens, including wBTC, USDC, and USDT. There were a handful of other altcoins that the hacker stole.  Related Reading: Arbitrum DAO Locks $770 Million In ARB Tokens Into Vesting Contract: Implications For ARB Funds were also stripped from the Moonriver Bridge, with observers noting that at least $6.8 million worth of various coins, including USDC, were moved to an external address. It is also reported that an address associated with Multichain connecting with Dogecoin also lost over $600,000. The stolen USDC has now been frozen and cannot be moved, a relief for the community. However, it is not clear whether Circle will reverse funds to Multichain. In the past, Tether Holdings and Circle, the centralized issuers of the world&#8217;s most liquid stablecoins, have intervened to prevent bad actors from cashing out. Hack Compounding Multichain&#8217;s Woes, Bitcoin Firm Peckshield, a blockchain security firm, was the first to pick out the unusual transfers of over $118 million worth of assets from Multichain&#8217;s Fantom and Moonriver bridges. The firm went on to tag the team behind the cross-chain protocol, who immediately acted. In response to the hack, Multichain said the outflow was &#8220;abnormal&#8221; and halted all activity while recommending users pause their protocol and revoke all contracts approval.  Related Reading: Hackers Have Stolen $30 Billion In Crypto Since 2012, SlowMist Report Finds Although the Multichain team had assured the community that the private keys controlling asset movements through the bridge are secure and stored on-chain, their technology appears to have flaws, resulting in the hack. The hack marks what has also been a tumultuous past few weeks. Besides delayed transactions and what the team described as &#8220;multiple issues,&#8221; the founder is missing. Despite the attack, Bitcoin prices are firm when writing. The coin is above the $30,000 psychological support, rejecting bear pressure from July 6. However, FTM, the native currency of Fantom, is free-falling, dumping 20% from July highs. Feature image from Canva, chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Circle, the official issuer of USDC, the second largest stablecoin by circulating supply, has frozen $63 million from the Multichain hack. Compiled Etherscan data on July 7 <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.reddit.com/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/14tdtbp/circle_freezes_three_addresses_linked_to_the/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">shows</a> that the stablecoin issuer froze $27.65 million, $30.1 million, and $5.5 million in three transactions, hampering the hacker&#8217;s cash-out efforts.</p>
<h2>Multichain Hacked, Circle Intervenes</h2>
<p>Multichain, a cross-chain protocol router, was hacked on July 7, resulting in the loss of over $126 million worth of various tokens. The exploit came after the attacker illegally accessed Multichain&#8217;s Multi-Party Computation (MPC) address, which stores funds locked between blockchains.</p>
<p>Subsequently, the hacker withdrew funds from the address and moved them to an externally controlled wallet. The Fantom Bridge was adversely affected by this outflow as the hacker withdrew various tokens, including wBTC, USDC, and USDT. There were a handful of other altcoins that the hacker stole. </p>

<p>Funds were also stripped from the Moonriver Bridge, with observers noting that at least $6.8 million worth of various coins, including USDC, were moved to an external address. It is also reported that an address associated with Multichain connecting with Dogecoin also lost over $600,000.</p>
<p>The stolen USDC has now been frozen and cannot be moved, a relief for the community. However, it is not clear whether Circle will reverse funds to Multichain. In the past, Tether Holdings and Circle, the centralized issuers of the world&#8217;s most liquid stablecoins, have intervened to prevent bad actors from cashing out.</p>
<h2>Hack Compounding Multichain&#8217;s Woes, Bitcoin Firm</h2>
<p>Peckshield, a blockchain security firm, was the first to <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://twitter.com/peckshield/status/1677031203772289030" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">pick out</a> the unusual transfers of over $118 million worth of assets from Multichain&#8217;s Fantom and Moonriver bridges. The firm went on to tag the team behind the cross-chain protocol, who immediately acted.</p>
<p>In response to the hack, Multichain <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://twitter.com/MultichainOrg/status/1677096839731097600" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">said</a> the outflow was &#8220;abnormal&#8221; and halted all activity while recommending users pause their protocol and revoke all contracts approval. </p>

<p>Although the Multichain team had assured the community that the private keys controlling asset movements through the bridge are secure and stored on-chain, their technology appears to have flaws, resulting in the hack. The hack marks what has also been a tumultuous past few weeks. Besides delayed transactions and what the team described as &#8220;multiple issues,&#8221; the founder is missing.</p>
<p>Despite the attack, Bitcoin prices are firm when writing. The coin is above the $30,000 psychological support, rejecting bear pressure from July 6. However, FTM, the native currency of Fantom, is free-falling, dumping 20% from July highs.</p>
<a href="https://www.tradingview.com/x/AjLjXJJQ/" rel="nofollow"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/AjLjXJJQ/" alt="FTM price on July 7| Source: FTMUSDT on Binance, TradingView" width="1226" height="595"/></a>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Crypto-news-Template4-460x260.png" width="460" height="260" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Polygon Labs CEO Steps Down, Chief Legal Officer Takes The Helm</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/matic-analysis/polygon-labs-ceo-steps-down-chief-legal-officer-takes-the-helm/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 01:00:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[MATIC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Matic Network]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[maticusdt]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Polygon]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=541812</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Polygon Labs, the company behind the Polygon blockchain, has announced management changes as it undergoes a rebrand to the next chapter of its corporate development, known as &#8220;Polygon 2.0.&#8221;  The company has promoted its chief legal officer, Marc Boiron, to the position of CEO, while President Ryan Wyatt will step down at the end of July and serve in an advisory role. Major Leadership Shake-Up According to a press release shared with CoinDesk, Boiron&#8217;s appointment signals the company&#8217;s commitment to nurture and expand the global Polygon community of developers, builders, and users. Boiron, who has been with the firm since 2020, has extensive experience in the blockchain and cryptocurrency space, having worked in various legal and regulatory roles. Related Reading: Hackers Have Stolen $30 Billion In Crypto Since 2012, SlowMist Report Finds Furthermore, Rebecca Rettig, who joined the company in February as chief policy officer, will assume Boiron&#8217;s former role as chief legal officer. Co-founder Sandeep Nailwal will serve as executive chairman, overseeing the company&#8217;s strategic direction and partnerships. In a tweet announcing his departure, CEO Ryan Wyatt stated:  It&#8217;s bittersweet to share that I am leaving Polygon Labs at the end of the month! Marc Boiron, our Chief Legal Officer, will be stepping up &#38; leading working closely with Sandeep Nailwal! For me, I&#8217;ll be advising Polygon, investing, &#38; staying in the industry! More to come later. Polygon runs two of the most closely watched networks for scaling Ethereum transactions, and its rebrand to &#8220;Polygon 2.0&#8221; signals a new phase of growth and development for the company.  The management changes are part of a broader restructuring effort at the blockchain firm, aimed at positioning the company for long-term success in the rapidly evolving blockchain and cryptocurrency space. The expected focus of the rebrand to &#8220;Polygon 2.0&#8221; is to expand the company&#8217;s user base and developer community and enhance the platform&#8217;s features and capabilities. This will involve a renewed focus on community-building and innovation as the company seeks to position itself for long-term success. The rebrand is expected to signal a new phase of growth and development for Polygon as it continues to run two of the most closely watched networks for scaling Ethereum transactions.  Polygon 2.0 Architecture Revealed On the 29th of June, the firm already gave a hint of what to expect from Polygon 2.0. According to Polygon&#8217;s blog post, this new chapter aims to provide “unlimited” scalability and unified liquidity.  The proposed architecture consists of four protocol layers, each designed to operate together and enable an important process within the network. These layers include the Staking Layer, the Interop Layer, the Execution Layer, and the Proving Layer.  The Staking Layer is a Proof of Stake (PoS)-based protocol that leverages Polygon&#8217;s native token (MATIC) to provide decentralization to participating Polygon chains.  Related Reading: Arbitrum DAO Locks $770 Million In ARB Tokens Into Vesting Contract: Implications For ARB On the other hand, the Interop Layer facilitates secure and seamless cross-chain messaging within the Polygon ecosystem. At the same time, the Execution Layer enables any Polygon chain to produce sequenced batches of transactions.  With these developments, Polygon 2.0 is expected to offer a more robust and versatile platform that can support a wider range of use cases and applications while providing a more seamless and user-friendly experience for developers and users alike.  Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com ]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Polygon Labs, the company behind the Polygon blockchain, has announced management changes as it undergoes a rebrand to the next chapter of its corporate development, known as &#8220;Polygon 2.0.&#8221; </p>
<p>The company has promoted its chief legal officer, Marc Boiron, to the position of CEO, while President Ryan Wyatt will step down at the end of July and serve in an advisory role.</p>
<h2>Major Leadership Shake-Up</h2>
<p>According to a press release shared with <a href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2023/07/07/polygon-labs-promotes-boiron-to-ceo-president-wyatt-to-depart/#:~:text=Polygon%20Labs%2C%20the%20company%20behind,serve%20in%20an%20advisory%20role." target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">CoinDesk</a>, Boiron&#8217;s appointment signals the company&#8217;s commitment to nurture and expand the global Polygon community of developers, builders, and users.</p>
<p>Boiron, who has been with the firm since 2020, has extensive experience in the blockchain and cryptocurrency space, having worked in various legal and regulatory roles.</p>

<p>Furthermore, Rebecca Rettig, who joined the company in February as chief policy officer, will assume Boiron&#8217;s former role as chief legal officer. Co-founder Sandeep Nailwal will serve as executive chairman, overseeing the company&#8217;s strategic direction and partnerships.</p>
<p>In a <a href="https://twitter.com/Fwiz/status/1677322803563864065?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">tweet </a>announcing his departure, CEO Ryan Wyatt stated: </p>
<blockquote><p>It&#8217;s bittersweet to share that I am leaving Polygon Labs at the end of the month! Marc Boiron, our Chief Legal Officer, will be stepping up &amp; leading working closely with Sandeep Nailwal! For me, I&#8217;ll be advising Polygon, investing, &amp; staying in the industry! More to come later.</p></blockquote>
<p>Polygon runs two of the most closely watched networks for scaling Ethereum transactions, and its rebrand to &#8220;Polygon 2.0&#8221; signals a new phase of growth and development for the company. </p>
<p>The management changes are part of a broader restructuring effort at the blockchain firm, aimed at positioning the company for long-term success in the rapidly evolving blockchain and cryptocurrency space.</p>
<p>The expected focus of the rebrand to &#8220;Polygon 2.0&#8221; is to expand the company&#8217;s user base and developer community and enhance the platform&#8217;s features and capabilities. This will involve a renewed focus on community-building and innovation as the company seeks to position itself for long-term success.</p>
<p>The rebrand is expected to signal a new phase of growth and development for Polygon as it continues to run two of the most closely watched networks for scaling Ethereum transactions. </p>
Polygon 2.0 Architecture Revealed
<p>On the 29th of June, the firm already gave a hint of what to expect from Polygon 2.0. <a href="https://polygon.technology/blog/polygon-2-0-protocol-vision-and-architecture" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">According </a>to Polygon&#8217;s blog post, this new chapter aims to provide “unlimited” scalability and unified liquidity. </p>
<p>The proposed architecture consists of four protocol layers, each designed to operate together and enable an important process within the network. These layers include the Staking Layer, the Interop Layer, the Execution Layer, and the Proving Layer. </p>
<p>The Staking Layer is a Proof of Stake (PoS)-based protocol that leverages Polygon&#8217;s native token (MATIC) to provide decentralization to participating Polygon chains. </p>

<p>On the other hand, the Interop Layer facilitates secure and seamless cross-chain messaging within the Polygon ecosystem. At the same time, the Execution Layer enables any Polygon chain to produce sequenced batches of transactions. </p>
<p>With these developments, Polygon 2.0 is expected to offer a more robust and versatile platform that can support a wider range of use cases and applications while providing a more seamless and user-friendly experience for developers and users alike. </p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/C3SuMJK2/" alt="Polygon " width="1815" height="858"/>
<p>Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/nick-fewings-5RjdYvDRNpA-unsplash-1-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Analysts Puts Bitcoin At $125,000 By 2024, How Is This Possible?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/analyst-puts-bitcoin-at-125000-by-2024-how-is-this-possible/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Best Owie]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 23:00:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Halving]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Spot ETFs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Matrixport]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=541734</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Matrixport, a crypto financial services platform, has always been bullish on Bitcoin, especially in 2023. So its latest prediction for the digital asset comes as no surprise to investors. This time around, Matrixport analysts have predicted that the price of BTC will push forward to as high as $125,000 by the end of 2024. A 310% Increase For Bitcoin? The current forecast by Matrixport analysts for Bitcoin will see the cryptocurrency rally as high as 310% if it does come to pass. This prediction, however, was not just thrown around without expected catalysts that would trigger such a rally, which is outlined in the report. Related Reading: Rapid Rise In Cardano’s TVL Points Toward Bullish Sentiment Around ADA For BTC to reach as high as $125,000 by the end of 2024, Matrixport expects that the potential approval of the Bitcoin Spot ETFs filed by investing giants such as BlackRock and Fidelity Investments, among others, could be the push it needs. 2024 is important for these Bitcoin Spot ETF filings because the final date for a decision from the United States Securities and Exchanges Commission (SEC) is in 2024. This is because the SEC gets three opportunities to postpone its decision, which it likely will. So a decision on whether or not investors will be able to trade a Spot BTC ETF is expected in February 2024 at the latest, as outlined in this Bitcoinist report. “With the potential approval of the BlackRock Bitcoin ETF and other institutional providers, the demand for Bitcoin could continue to support prices into our $45,000 year-end target,” Matrixport says in the report. “There is no obvious indication of what will drive the next bull market, but the data indicates that Bitcoin could continue to rally into the 2024 halving.” BTC Multiple Bullish Catalysts For BTC In 2024 As Matrixport mentions in its report, the Bitcoin Spot ETF filings are not the only bullish events that could drive a bull market in 2024. Another important event is the BTC halving event which is less than a year away now. This event will see the block rewards for the blockchain cut down in half from 6.25 BTC per mined block to 3.125 BTC per mined block. Next BTC halving is less than a year away &#124; Source: Binance This decrease in the rate at which new BTC is being brought into circulation, coupled with the fact that the digital asset possesses a very limited supply, has always triggered each bull market. So even if expectations for the Spot ETFs do not play out and the SEC does reject the filings, it will likely only be a short-lived bearish momentum as the halving will take place only a few months after. Related Reading: BlackRock CEO Larry Fink Says Bitcoin Is Digital Gold, So What’s The Digital Silver? Going by historical performance, the BTC price has been known to rise more than 100% as expectations around the halving event grow. Given this, it is possible that BTC does reach a price of $125,000 by the end of 2024, according to the Matrixport report. Follow Best Owie on Twitter for market insights, updates, and the occasional funny tweet… Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="p2">Matrixport, a crypto financial services platform, has always been bullish on Bitcoin, especially in 2023. So its latest prediction for the digital asset comes as no surprise to investors. This time around, Matrixport analysts have predicted that the price of BTC will push forward to as high as $125,000 by the end of 2024.</p>
<h2 class="p2">A 310% Increase For Bitcoin?</h2>
<p class="p2">The current <a href="https://www.matrixport.com/institutions/research/matrix-on-target/531?utm_content=255761706&amp;utm_medium=social&amp;utm_source=linkedin&amp;hss_channel=lcp-14716238" rel="nofollow">forecast</a> by Matrixport analysts for Bitcoin will see the cryptocurrency rally as high as 310% if it does come to pass. This prediction, however, was not just thrown around without expected catalysts that would trigger such a rally, which is outlined in the report.</p>

<p class="p2">For BTC to reach as high as $125,000 by the end of 2024, Matrixport expects that the potential approval of the Bitcoin Spot ETFs filed by investing giants such as BlackRock and Fidelity Investments, among others, could be the push it needs.</p>
<p class="p2">2024 is important for these Bitcoin Spot ETF filings because the final date for a decision from the United States Securities and Exchanges Commission (SEC) is in 2024. This is because the SEC gets three opportunities to postpone its decision, which it likely will. So a decision on whether or not investors will be able to trade a Spot BTC ETF is expected in February 2024 at the latest, as outlined in this Bitcoinist <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/here-are-the-important-events-for-bitcoin/" rel="nofollow">report</a>.</p>
<p class="p2">“With the potential approval of the BlackRock Bitcoin ETF and other institutional providers, the demand for Bitcoin could continue to support prices into our $45,000 year-end target,” Matrixport says in the report. “There is no obvious indication of what will drive the next bull market, but the data indicates that Bitcoin could continue to rally into the 2024 halving.”</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/XumdBwob/" alt="Bitcoin (BTC) price chart from TradingView.com" width="2884" height="1758"/></p>
<p>BTC</p>
<h2 class="p2">Multiple Bullish Catalysts For BTC In 2024</h2>
<p class="p2">As Matrixport mentions in its report, the Bitcoin Spot ETF filings are not the only bullish events that could drive a bull market in 2024. Another important event is the BTC halving event which is less than a year away now. This event will see the block rewards for the blockchain cut down in half from 6.25 BTC per mined block to 3.125 BTC per mined block.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-541741 aligncenter" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-07-at-13.00.41-460x254.png" alt="Bitcoin halving schedule" width="460" height="254" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-07-at-13.00.41-460x254.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-07-at-13.00.41-860x476.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-07-at-13.00.41-768x425.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-07-at-13.00.41-750x415.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-07-at-13.00.41.png 1052w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px"/></p>

<p class="p2">This decrease in the rate at which new BTC is being brought into circulation, coupled with the fact that the digital asset possesses a very limited supply, has always triggered each bull market. So even if expectations for the Spot ETFs do not play out and the SEC does reject the filings, it will likely only be a short-lived bearish momentum as the halving will take place only a few months after.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/blackrock-ceo-larry-fink-says-bitcoin-is-digital-gold-so-whats-the-digital-silver/?swcfpc=1">BlackRock CEO Larry Fink Says Bitcoin Is Digital Gold, So What’s The Digital Silver?</a></p>
<p class="p2">Going by historical performance, the BTC price has been known to rise more than 100% as expectations around the halving event grow. Given this, it is possible that BTC does reach a price of $125,000 by the end of 2024, according to the Matrixport report.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/iStock-1258091878-460x306.jpg" width="460" height="306" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ripple Head Of Policy Calls For UK To Join Global Trend Of CBDC Adoption</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/ripple/ripple-head-of-policy-calls-for-uk-to-join-global-trend-of-cbdc-adoption/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 21:30:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CBDCs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple (XRP) Price Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrpusdt]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=541799</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[In an interview with the Digital Pound Foundation, Ripple Head of Policy Susan Friedman shared her positive outlook on London&#8217;s potential as a crypto hub, highlighting its dedication to developing ecosystems for crypto assets and Central Bank Digital Currencies (CBDCs).  Ripple Advocates For Encouraging CBDC Ecosystem Development Friedman noted that Ripple&#8217;s goal is to advocate for global policy frameworks that encourage ecosystem development for crypto assets, including CBDCs.  She expressed excitement for what is happening in the UK, as London and the government have taken a proactive approach to fintech and CBDCs. She cited the work of the Bank of England with the digital pound and the government&#8217;s consideration of all viewpoints when implementing a CBDC. According to Friedman, digital currencies and CBDCs are a natural evolution of how individuals and countries exchange value, given that current currencies were created in a less globalized world.  Related Reading: Ethereum Address Creation Spikes, Adoption On The Rise? She also believes CBDCs can offer the same protection as fiat and that most countries looking to implement CBDCs are exploring CBDs to solve specific domestic challenges. Ultimately, she believes all countries must develop a strategy to implement CBDCs to efficiently interact with the global market. Ripple&#8217;s head of policy also sees CBDCs and cryptocurrencies as encouraging financial inclusion, increasing access to financial services for under and unbanked populations, and increasing the speed and efficiency of payments. She believes that digital currencies can also help reduce energy use and environmental resources by reducing the printing of paper money and minting coins. However, Friedman acknowledged that central banks globally are struggling to encourage this technology while maintaining financial stability and control of their monetary systems. She believes that there can be interoperability between these currencies in a way that maintains financial stability for all countries. In conclusion, Friedman&#8217;s positive outlook on London&#8217;s potential as a crypto hub reflects Ripple&#8217;s dedication to advocating for global policy frameworks that encourage ecosystem development for crypto assets and CBDCs.  Her insights into the comparable security and protections of CBDCs and their potential to encourage financial inclusion and reduce energy use highlight the benefits of this technology.  As countries worldwide explore the implementation of CBDCs, interoperability and maintaining financial stability will be critical factors to consider. XRP Enters Crucial Phase Market analyst Egrag Crypto has shared his insights on the next 100 days for XRP, highlighting key levels of support and resistance for investors to watch. As the market enters the third quarter of 2023, he believes this will be a make-it-or-break-it phase for XRP, with the potential for significant price movements. According to Egrag Crypto, XRP&#8217;s support levels are currently at $0.4570, $0.4250, and $0.4200, with major support at $0.3850. On the other hand, the resistance levels for XRP are currently locked at $0.48 and $0.50, with major resistance at $0.54 and $0.58.  These levels may provide investors with an indication of where XRP&#8217;s price may move in the coming months. Related Reading: Surging Demand For Bitcoin Ordinals Propels Q2 Trading Volume To $210M However, Egrag Crypto also notes that the ongoing legal proceedings between Ripple and the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) regarding XRP&#8217;s status as a security could significantly impact the cryptocurrency&#8217;s price. The decision by Judge Torres could sling-shot the price of XRP in either direction, depending on the verdict and subsequent actions. Despite this uncertainty, Egrag Crypto advises investors to stay level-headed and maintain a long-term perspective. Short-term volatility can be unpredictable, and emotions can run high. He recommends continuing with a dollar-cost averaging (DCA) strategy, as he believes in the potential of XRP and utility in the evolving digital economy. At the time of writing, XRP is trading at $0.4657, following the overall trend of the market, experiencing a 0.4% decline in the past 24 hours Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com ]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In an <a href="https://twitter.com/digitalpoundfdn/status/1676971301494292480?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">interview </a>with the Digital Pound Foundation, Ripple Head of Policy Susan Friedman shared her positive outlook on London&#8217;s potential as a crypto hub, highlighting its dedication to developing ecosystems for crypto assets and Central Bank Digital Currencies (CBDCs). </p>
<h2>Ripple Advocates For Encouraging CBDC Ecosystem Development</h2>
<p>Friedman noted that Ripple&#8217;s goal is to advocate for global policy frameworks that encourage ecosystem development for crypto assets, including CBDCs. </p>
<p>She expressed excitement for what is happening in the UK, as London and the government have taken a proactive approach to fintech and CBDCs. She cited the work of the Bank of England with the digital pound and the government&#8217;s consideration of all viewpoints when implementing a CBDC.</p>
<p>According to Friedman, digital currencies and CBDCs are a natural evolution of how individuals and countries exchange value, given that current currencies were created in a less globalized world. </p>

<p>She also believes CBDCs can offer the same protection as fiat and that most countries looking to implement CBDCs are exploring CBDs to solve specific domestic challenges. Ultimately, she believes all countries must develop a strategy to implement CBDCs to efficiently interact with the global market.</p>
<p>Ripple&#8217;s head of policy also sees CBDCs and cryptocurrencies as encouraging financial inclusion, increasing access to financial services for under and unbanked populations, and increasing the speed and efficiency of payments. She believes that digital currencies can also help reduce energy use and environmental resources by reducing the printing of paper money and minting coins.</p>
<p>However, Friedman acknowledged that central banks globally are struggling to encourage this technology while maintaining financial stability and control of their monetary systems. She believes that there can be interoperability between these currencies in a way that maintains financial stability for all countries.</p>
<p>In conclusion, Friedman&#8217;s positive outlook on London&#8217;s potential as a crypto hub reflects Ripple&#8217;s dedication to advocating for global policy frameworks that encourage ecosystem development for crypto assets and CBDCs. </p>
<p>Her insights into the comparable security and protections of CBDCs and their potential to encourage financial inclusion and reduce energy use highlight the benefits of this technology. </p>
<p>As countries worldwide explore the implementation of CBDCs, interoperability and maintaining financial stability will be critical factors to consider.</p>
XRP Enters Crucial Phase
<p>Market analyst Egrag Crypto has shared his <a href="https://twitter.com/egragcrypto/status/1677244062129160193?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">insights </a>on the next 100 days for XRP, highlighting key levels of support and resistance for investors to watch. As the market enters the third quarter of 2023, he believes this will be a make-it-or-break-it phase for XRP, with the potential for significant price movements.</p>
<p>According to Egrag Crypto, XRP&#8217;s support levels are currently at $0.4570, $0.4250, and $0.4200, with major support at $0.3850. On the other hand, the resistance levels for XRP are currently locked at $0.48 and $0.50, with major resistance at $0.54 and $0.58. </p>
<p>These levels may provide investors with an indication of where XRP&#8217;s price may move in the coming months.</p>

<p>However, Egrag Crypto also notes that the ongoing legal proceedings between Ripple and the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) regarding XRP&#8217;s status as a security could significantly impact the cryptocurrency&#8217;s price. The decision by Judge Torres could sling-shot the price of XRP in either direction, depending on the verdict and subsequent actions.</p>
<p>Despite this uncertainty, Egrag Crypto advises investors to stay level-headed and maintain a long-term perspective. Short-term volatility can be unpredictable, and emotions can run high. He recommends continuing with a dollar-cost averaging (DCA) strategy, as he believes in the potential of XRP and utility in the evolving digital economy.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/3CiujcEv/" alt="Ripple" width="1815" height="858"/>
<p>At the time of writing, XRP is trading at $0.4657, following the overall trend of the market, experiencing a 0.4% decline in the past 24 hours</p>
<p>Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/chris-lawton-QPOaQ2Kp80c-unsplash-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hackers Have Stolen $30 Billion In Crypto Since 2012, SlowMist Report Finds</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/crypto/30-billion-in-crypto-since-2012/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 20:00:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto hacks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hacks]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=541803</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Due to the anonymity cryptocurrencies provide, the crypto industry is known to be targeted by hackers and other malicious players. This has left many wondering just how much digital currency has been pilfered from right under the nose of the industry over the years.  Now, the latest report by blockchain security firm SlowMist seems to have the answer. According to the recently released report, hackers and scammers have made off with a staggering $30 billion in cryptocurrency since 2012.  Details Of The Report The SlowMist team analyzed 1,101 hacking incidents to determine how much crypto has been stolen to date and how they were stolen. Their findings show that hackers and scammers employ a variety of methods, with the top ones being contract vulnerability attacks, rug pulls, flash loan attacks, scams, leaking of private keys, and good old phishing attacks to gain access to people&#8217;s crypto accounts and wallets.  Related Reading: Cardano Foundation Collaborates With Epoch Sports And Merchandise For Lacrosse Championship 2023 The most lucrative year for malicious players came in 2021 during the extended crypto hype, with over $9.7 billion stolen in 236 attacks.  In total, the amount stolen in the last decade came up to a little over $30 billion. And given that the overall market cap of all cryptocurrencies is now at $1.14 trillion, the amount reported stolen is over 2.5% of the total market cap. Over $30 billion stolen in 10 years &#124; Source: SlowMist Exchanges And Ethereum Ecosystem Hit The Most Exchanges have always long been a prime target for hackers looking to steal crypto due to their large holdings and the SlowMist report reflects that.  In total, over 118 attacks were carried out on exchanges, resulting in over $10.9 billion being lost. The biggest of these could be traced back to the $534 million lost in the 2018 Japanese exchange Coincheck hack and the 2014 Mt. Gov hack resulting in a loss of over $473 million. Total market cap chart sitting at $1.139 trillion &#124; Source: Crypto Total Market Cap on TradingView.com In terms of attacks on blockchain ecosystems, Ethereum came out on top with 217 attacks and over $3.1 billion being pilfered away. This should come as no surprise, considering Ethereum is home to most Web3 projects. The BSC and EOS ecosystems followed closely with 162 and 119 attacks, respectively. Additionally, over $200 million were lost in NFT attacks, while bridge attacks led to $2 billion in losses.  What’s Next For The Crypto Industry? The staggering numbers in SlowMist&#8217;s report are a reminder that crypto, for all its promise, also has a dark side. However, attacks seem to have been slowing down as many projects have started to improve their security. With more than a trillion dollars at stake, reducing theft should be a collaborative effort across the entire crypto landscape.  Related Reading: Arbitrum DAO Locks $770 Million In ARB Tokens Into Vesting Contract: Implications For ARB According to the latest report by Beosin, a blockchain security firm, losses from Web3 scams and hacks dropped dramatically in H1 2023. Data from SlowMist&#8217;s report also shows that the total amount of money lost to blockchain hackers has been declining since 2021. Featured image from ETF Trends, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Due to the anonymity cryptocurrencies provide, the crypto industry is known to be targeted by hackers and other malicious players. This has left many wondering just how much digital currency has been pilfered from right under the nose of the industry over the years.</p>
<p> Now, the latest report by blockchain security firm SlowMist seems to have the answer. According to the recently released <a href="https://hacked.slowmist.io/statistics/?c=all&amp;d=2023" rel="nofollow">report</a>, hackers and scammers have made off with a staggering $30 billion in cryptocurrency since 2012. </p>
<h2>Details Of The Report</h2>
<p>The SlowMist team analyzed 1,101 hacking incidents to determine how much crypto has been stolen to date and how they were stolen. Their findings show that hackers and scammers employ a variety of methods, with the top ones being contract vulnerability attacks, rug pulls, flash loan attacks, scams, leaking of private keys, and good old phishing attacks to gain access to people&#8217;s crypto accounts and wallets. </p>

<p>The most lucrative year for malicious players came in 2021 during the extended crypto hype, with over $9.7 billion stolen in 236 attacks. </p>
<p>In total, the amount stolen in the last decade came up to a little over $30 billion. And given that the overall market cap of all cryptocurrencies is now at $1.14 trillion, the amount reported stolen is over 2.5% of the total market cap.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-541804 aligncenter" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-07-at-20.41.50-460x279.png" alt="Crypto hacks" width="460" height="279" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-07-at-20.41.50-460x279.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-07-at-20.41.50-860x521.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-07-at-20.41.50-768x465.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-07-at-20.41.50-1536x931.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-07-at-20.41.50-2048x1241.png 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-07-at-20.41.50-750x454.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-07-at-20.41.50-1140x691.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px"/></p>

<h2>Exchanges And Ethereum Ecosystem Hit The Most</h2>
<p>Exchanges have always long been a prime target for hackers looking to steal crypto due to their large holdings and the SlowMist report reflects that. </p>
<p>In total, over 118 attacks were carried out on exchanges, resulting in over $10.9 billion being lost. The biggest of these could be traced back to the $534 million lost in the 2018 Japanese exchange Coincheck hack and the 2014 Mt. Gov hack resulting in a loss of over $473 million.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/mhO5dS8o/" alt="Crypto total market cap chart from TradingView.com" width="2884" height="1758"/></p>

<p>In terms of attacks on blockchain ecosystems, Ethereum came out on top with 217 attacks and over $3.1 billion being pilfered away. This should come as no surprise, considering Ethereum is home to most Web3 projects. </p>
<p>The BSC and EOS ecosystems followed closely with 162 and 119 attacks, respectively. Additionally, over $200 million were lost in NFT attacks, while bridge attacks led to $2 billion in losses. </p>
What’s Next For The Crypto Industry?
<p>The staggering numbers in SlowMist&#8217;s report are a reminder that crypto, for all its promise, also has a dark side. However, attacks seem to have been slowing down as many projects have started to improve their security. With more than a trillion dollars at stake, reducing theft should be a collaborative effort across the entire crypto landscape. </p>

<p>According to the latest report by Beosin, a blockchain security firm, losses from Web3 scams and hacks dropped dramatically in H1 2023. Data from SlowMist&#8217;s report also shows that the total amount of money lost to blockchain hackers has been declining since 2021.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Crypto-hacks-460x345.jpeg" width="460" height="345" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Arbitrum DAO Locks $770 Million In ARB Tokens Into Vesting Contract: Implications For ARB</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/arb/arbitrum-dao-locks-tokens-into-vesting-contract/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samuel Edyme]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 19:00:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[ARB]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Arbitrum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ARBUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Token]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=541778</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Arbitrum DAO recently took a step toward addressing an obstacle. The DAO has committed to locking 700 million ARB tokens, valued at an estimated $770 million, into a vesting contract to foster transparent governance and accountability, per a community proposal.  The approval for this commitment came from an improvement proposal introduced during a contentious period within the Arbitrum ecosystem. The specifics of this commitment involve gradually releasing these funds to the Arbitrum Foundation over four years. Details Of The Vesting Contract The new initiative, aptly termed AIP 1.1, solves recent disagreements concerning Arbitrum&#8217;s internal governance. Earlier this year, the project was embroiled in controversy due to a proposal for a &#8216;special grants&#8217; program. Related Reading: Arbitrum Gains Tempered By Obstacles, Hindering ARB’s Further Upswing This controversial program was originally designed to assign more than 700 million ARB tokens directly to the Arbitrum Foundation. These funds, representing $1 billion at the time, were proposed to be directed toward backing projects utilizing Arbitrum&#8217;s advanced technology. The sheer magnitude of the allocation sparked concerns about the transparency of a project whose ethos is grounded in collective decision-making. This resulted in an alternate proposal to redirect the funds from the Foundation back to the DAO, which was subsequently rejected. To satisfy the concerns of the community, the proposal AIP-1.1 was introduced. This strategic proposal aimed to impose stricter controls on the allocation of the DAO&#8217;s treasury. This plan empowers the DAO with the authority to modify the vesting period, allowing them to lengthen, shorten, or even halt the vesting process entirely. This move towards financial transparency marks a milestone for Arbitrum&#8217;s DAO, reinforcing its commitment to its decentralized and democratic ethos. It not only provides a check on the arbitrary allocation of funds but also ensures that decisions align with the interests of the Arbitrum community. Implications for Arbitrum Securing $770 million in ARB tokens through a vesting contract is a significant event for Arbitrum&#8217;s DAO. By taking this action, the Arbitrum Foundation can establish a consistent source of funding and demonstrate to the community at large their dedication to transparency and accountability. The measure could also impact the market dynamics for the ARB token. With a significant amount of the tokens locked up, the reduced supply could potentially influence its price. This further underscores the importance of this step by the Arbitrum DAO, as its ramifications extend beyond governance to directly influencing the ecosystem&#8217;s dynamics. Related Reading: Arbitrum Airdrop Success: Metrics Soar Higher Across The Board Furthermore, this development within the Arbitrum ecosystem signifies the project&#8217;s maturity and commitment to its democratic ideals. It exemplifies how DAOs can effectively manage significant resources while maintaining transparency and accountability, setting a precedent for other similar organizations in the crypto ecosystem.  Meanwhile, over the past 24 hours, Arbitrum&#8217;s native token ARB has witnessed an upward trend of 2.3%. This bullish trend comes after the asset has seen slight retracement in the past week, dropping by nearly 2%. ARB currently has a market price of $1.12 at the time of writing. Featured image from iStock, Chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Arbitrum DAO recently took a step toward addressing an obstacle. The DAO has committed to locking 700 million ARB tokens, valued at an estimated $770 million, into a <a href="https://arbiscan.io/address/0x15533b77981cDa0F85c4F9a485237DF4285D6844#code" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">vesting contract</a> to foster transparent governance and accountability, per a community proposal. </p>
<p>The approval for this commitment came from an improvement proposal introduced during a contentious period within the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/ethereum-cancun-upgrade-arbitrum-optimism-will-profit/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Arbitrum ecosystem</a>. The specifics of this commitment involve gradually releasing these funds to the Arbitrum Foundation over four years.</p>
<h2>Details Of The Vesting Contract</h2>
<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w" dir="ltr">The new <a href="https://www.tally.xyz/gov/arbitrum/proposal/70545629960586317780628692755032548222173912190231545322320044688071893662480" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">initiative</a>, aptly termed AIP 1.1, solves recent disagreements concerning Arbitrum&#8217;s internal governance. Earlier this year, the project was <a href="https://twitter.com/0xedenau/status/1642502145839890432?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">embroiled in controversy</a> due to a proposal for a &#8216;special grants&#8217; program.</p>

<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w" dir="ltr">This controversial <a href="https://snapshot.org/#/arbitrumfoundation.eth/proposal/0x3be7368a662d1cf12fa4da768d626edbc013be0dc7b994fef2e24d9a54e4033a" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">program</a> was originally designed to assign more than 700 million ARB tokens directly to the Arbitrum Foundation. These funds, representing $1 billion at the time, were proposed to be directed toward backing projects utilizing Arbitrum&#8217;s advanced technology.</p>
<p>The sheer magnitude of the allocation sparked concerns about the transparency of a project whose ethos is grounded in collective decision-making. This resulted in an alternate proposal to redirect the funds from the Foundation back to the DAO, which was subsequently <a href="https://snapshot.org/#/arbitrumfoundation.eth/proposal/0x3ae4c725f7cb82d450b6fe8517178b2a0a51d1105beaad0adb421df1bc8f8cc4" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">rejected</a>.</p>
<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w" dir="ltr">To satisfy the concerns of the community, the proposal AIP-1.1 was introduced. This strategic proposal aimed to impose stricter controls on the allocation of the DAO&#8217;s treasury. This <a href="https://twitter.com/arbitrum/status/1677011772148965379?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">plan</a> empowers the DAO with the authority to modify the vesting period, allowing them to lengthen, shorten, or even halt the vesting process entirely.</p>
<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w" dir="ltr">This move towards financial transparency marks a milestone for<a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/arbitrum-gains-tempered-by-obstacles-hindering-arbs-further-upswing/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener "> Arbitrum&#8217;s DAO</a>, reinforcing its commitment to its decentralized and democratic ethos. It not only provides a check on the arbitrary allocation of funds but also ensures that decisions align with the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/arb/arbitrum-rises-20-in-a-week-amidst-whale-activity/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">interests of the Arbitrum community</a>.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Implications for Arbitrum</h2>
<p>Securing $770 million in ARB tokens through a vesting contract is a significant event for Arbitrum&#8217;s DAO. By taking this action, the Arbitrum Foundation can establish a consistent source of funding and demonstrate to the community at large their dedication to transparency and accountability.</p>
<p>The measure could also impact the market dynamics for the ARB token. With a significant amount of the tokens locked up, the reduced supply could potentially influence its price. </p>
<p>This further underscores the importance of this step by the Arbitrum DAO, as its ramifications extend beyond governance to directly influencing the ecosystem&#8217;s dynamics.</p>

<p>Furthermore, this development within the Arbitrum ecosystem signifies the project&#8217;s maturity and commitment to its democratic ideals. It exemplifies how DAOs can effectively manage significant resources while maintaining transparency and accountability, setting a precedent for other similar organizations in the crypto ecosystem. </p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/iRsNJpQp/" alt="Arbitrum (ARB) price chart on TradingView" width="2770" height="1556"/>
<p>Meanwhile, over the past 24 hours, <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/arb/arbitrum-arb-fallout-70-price-drop-but-these-charts-reveal-its-true-value/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Arbitrum&#8217;s native token ARB</a> has witnessed an upward trend of 2.3%. This bullish trend comes after the asset has seen slight retracement in the past week, dropping by nearly 2%. ARB currently has a market price of $1.12 at the time of writing.</p>
<p>Featured image from iStock, Chart from TradingView</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/nicolas-hippert-J4eTN9GqhzI-unsplash-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cardano Foundation Collaborates With Epoch Sports And Merchandise For Lacrosse Championship 2023</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/cardano/cardano-foundation-collaborates-with-epoch-sports-and-merchandise-for-lacrosse-championship-2023/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[anushsamal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 18:00:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cardano]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[2023 World Lacrosse Men Championship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[adausd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADAUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano Foundation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Epoch Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Merchandise]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NFT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=541776</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Cardano Foundation has recently announced a technical partnership with Epoch Sports and Merchandise. Epoch Sports is a prominent US-based sports brand, and Merchandise, a comprehensive full-stack apparel ecosystem. This alliance aims to introduce a limited edition jersey that will be authenticated using blockchain technology. Related Reading: Bitcoin Short-Term Holders Continue Exchange Inflows, But Price Holds On During the 2023 World Lacrosse Men&#8217;s Championship, 6000 Limited Edition Commemorative Jerseys had already been distributed. The limited run of commemorative lacrosse jerseys showcases a near-field communication (NFC) Epoch branded patch. This patch includes a digital jersey version embedded as a non-fungible token (NFT). By leveraging this technology, the physical garment becomes intrinsically connected to a secure blockchain, providing proof of the jersey&#8217;s authenticity. Epoch Sports and Merchandise have outlined their plans to release the remaining NFC-enabled Commemorative Jerseys, accompanied by connected NFTs, on the official web store of the 2023 World Lacrosse Championship. The NFC patches incorporated into the jerseys serve a dual purpose. They also grant the consumers access to a range of exclusive rewards and special offers. Cardano&#8217;s Collaboration Aims To Enhance IP Protection And Tackle Counterfeiting The technical collaboration between the Cardano Foundation, Epoch Sports, and Merchandise aims to promote blockchain adoption within the licensed merchandise industry while bolstering the protection of licensed intellectual property (IP). By securely linking NFC chips to a blockchain record in the form of non-fungible tokens (NFTs), traditional licensed IP hologram tags on sports apparel will be replaced. According to the press release, this guarantees authenticity for purchasers and empowers license owners to combat counterfeiting effectively. For real-time visualization of all on-chain records on the Cardano blockchain, Pool.pm serves as a reference tool. Pool.pm provides an overview of the blockchain, allowing users to access the on-chain records. Frederik Gregaard, the CEO of the Cardano Foundation, said: Our work with Merchandise and Epoch Sports showcases the utility and accessibility of Cardano’s blockchain: any merchant can adopt blockchain solutions to give reassurance and confidence to customers that they are buying genuine articles. Diversifying blockchain adoption is a core part of the Cardano Foundation mission, and it’s fantastic to see more and more companies putting blockchain solutions into practice. Merchandise&#8217;s CEO, Alex Phelan, expressed enthusiasm about collaborating with the Cardano Foundation, highlighting it as a milestone in the licensed apparel industry. He emphasized that the partnership sets new intellectual property protection benchmarks and fosters fan engagement. Related Reading: Compound (COMP) Token Rallies Over 100% After CEO Quits – Details James Micelli, Principal of Epoch Sports, acknowledged the immense potential of blockchain deployment in empowering consumers. James Micelli, Principal of Epoch Sports, acknowledged the immense potential of blockchain deployment in empowering consumers. Featured image from Cardano Feed, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Cardano Foundation has recently<a href="https://cardanofoundation.org/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow"> announced</a> a technical partnership with Epoch Sports and Merchandise. Epoch Sports is a prominent US-based sports brand, and Merchandise, a comprehensive full-stack apparel ecosystem. This alliance aims to introduce a limited edition jersey that will be authenticated using blockchain technology.</p>

<p>During the 2023 World Lacrosse Men&#8217;s Championship, 6000 Limited Edition Commemorative Jerseys had already been distributed.</p>
<p>The limited run of commemorative lacrosse jerseys showcases a near-field communication (NFC) Epoch branded patch. This patch includes a digital jersey version embedded as a non-fungible token (NFT).</p>
<p>By leveraging this technology, the physical garment becomes intrinsically connected to a secure blockchain, providing proof of the jersey&#8217;s authenticity.</p>
<p>Epoch Sports and Merchandise have outlined their plans to release the remaining NFC-enabled Commemorative Jerseys, accompanied by connected NFTs, on the official web store of the 2023 World Lacrosse Championship.</p>
<p>The NFC patches incorporated into the jerseys serve a dual purpose. They also grant the consumers access to a range of exclusive rewards and special offers.</p>
<h2>Cardano&#8217;s Collaboration Aims To Enhance IP Protection And Tackle Counterfeiting</h2>
<p>The technical collaboration between the Cardano Foundation, Epoch Sports, and Merchandise aims to promote blockchain adoption within the licensed merchandise industry while bolstering the protection of licensed intellectual property (IP).</p>
<p>By securely linking NFC chips to a blockchain record in the form of non-fungible tokens (NFTs), traditional licensed IP hologram tags on sports apparel will be replaced. According to the press release, this guarantees authenticity for purchasers and empowers license owners to combat counterfeiting effectively.</p>
<p>For real-time visualization of all on-chain records on the Cardano blockchain, Pool.pm serves as a reference tool. Pool.pm provides an overview of the blockchain, allowing users to access the on-chain records.</p>
<p>Frederik Gregaard, the CEO of the Cardano Foundation, said:</p>
<blockquote><p>Our work with Merchandise and Epoch Sports showcases the utility and accessibility of Cardano’s blockchain: any merchant can adopt blockchain solutions to give reassurance and confidence to customers that they are buying genuine articles. Diversifying blockchain adoption is a core part of the Cardano Foundation mission, and it’s fantastic to see more and more companies putting blockchain solutions into practice.</p></blockquote>
<p>Merchandise&#8217;s CEO, Alex Phelan, expressed enthusiasm about collaborating with the Cardano Foundation, highlighting it as a milestone in the licensed apparel industry. He emphasized that the partnership sets new intellectual property protection benchmarks and fosters fan engagement.</p>

<p>James Micelli, Principal of Epoch Sports, acknowledged the immense potential of blockchain deployment in empowering consumers. James Micelli, Principal of Epoch Sports, acknowledged the immense potential of blockchain deployment in empowering consumers.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-541780 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ADAUSD_2023-07-07_22-32-15.png" alt="Cardano" width="1817" height="830" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ADAUSD_2023-07-07_22-32-15.png 1817w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ADAUSD_2023-07-07_22-32-15-460x210.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ADAUSD_2023-07-07_22-32-15-860x393.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ADAUSD_2023-07-07_22-32-15-768x351.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ADAUSD_2023-07-07_22-32-15-1536x702.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ADAUSD_2023-07-07_22-32-15-750x343.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ADAUSD_2023-07-07_22-32-15-1140x521.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1817px) 100vw, 1817px"/>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/positive-new-developments-noted-for-the-cardano-blockchain-1200x675-1-460x259.jpg" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Surging Demand For Bitcoin Ordinals Propels Q2 Trading Volume To $210M</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/surging-demand-for-bitcoin-ordinals-propels-to-210m/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samuel Edyme]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 16:30:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NFTs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ordinals]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=541768</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin Ordinals&#8217; unique non-fungible token (NFT) inscriptions on the Bitcoin blockchain have recently registered over $210 million in trading volume in the first half of 2023 alone. This new wave of innovation, coupled with the volume recorded so far, demonstrates the potential that lies within the intersection of blockchain technology and digital artistry. Bitcoin Ordinals&#8217; Q2 Performance Defies Expectations In a recent quarterly report from DappRadar, a rise in trading volume was documented for Bitcoin in the second quarter of 2023. The data, characterized by notable fluctuations, attributes this heightened trading activity to an increased interest in Ordinals, suggesting a marked shift in trader preferences and investment strategies. Related Reading: Bitcoin Ordinals: This New BRC Standard Could Reduce Inscription Fees By 90% Bitcoin Ordinals, once an emerging player in the crypto market, has now gained significant traction, establishing itself as a potential innovator in the industry. The trading volume of Ordinals has demonstrated a growth trajectory, as detailed in DappRadar&#8217;s report. The trading volume for Ordinals started the year modestly, registering a mere $7.18 million in the first quarter. However, as the innovation gained increased visibility and trader confidence, there was an upturn in trading activity. The second quarter of 2023 saw Bitcoin Ordinals&#8217; trading volume skyrocket to $210.7 million, a figure that represents a 2,834% increase from the preceding quarter. This upswing in trading activity underscores its growth in the digital asset market and indicates the potential for continued extension in the quarters to come. It is worth noting that Bitcoin Ordinals&#8217; performance is not a passing trend; instead, it signals a shift in how investors and enthusiasts approach NFTs in the digital assets space. The rising acceptance and trading volume of Bitcoin Ordinals reveals a positive trajectory, which has successfully harnessed the power of non-fungible tokens. Furthermore, Bitcoin Ordinals&#8217; journey from a relatively obscure blockchain project to a formidable player in the NFT space reflects the nature of the digital asset landscape. Its growth narrative, as underscored by its Q2 performance, sets the stage for more innovation and market expansion in the world of nonfungible tokens. User Engagement And Marketplaces Fuel Growth DappRadar&#8217;s report also highlighted Bitcoin Ordinals trades in Q2 &#8211; over 550,000 &#8211; driven by more than 151,000 unique traders. This surge in trading activity attests to its rapidly growing appeal within the crypto community in 2023. Data from a blockchain analytics dashboard on Dune, maintained by @domo, affirm these observations, highlighting a significant rise in individual users beginning in May 2023. Related Reading: Dormant Bitcoin Supply Peaks As Institutional Investors Show Increased Involvement This expansion is mirrored across several trading platforms, where UniSat &#8211; an open-source Chrome extension supporting Bitcoin Ordinals &#38; BRC-20 tokens &#8211; along with Magic Eden and Ordinals Wallet, commands a substantial share of distinct users. Meanwhile, over the past week, BTC has been in a downward trend dropping by 2.5%. However, in the past 24 hours, the asset appears to be picking up with an increase of nearly 1%. At the time of writing, BTC trades at a price of $30,320, after trading above the $31,000 mark a few days ago. Featured image from iStock, Chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin Ordinals&#8217; unique non-fungible token (NFT) <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-ordinals-achieve-milestone-with-over-10m-inscriptions-as-creator-rodarmor-departs/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">inscriptions</a> on the Bitcoin blockchain have recently registered over $210 million in trading volume in the first half of 2023 alone. This <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin-ordinals-releases-upgrade-to-address-cursed-inscriptions-problem/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">new wave of innovation, coupled with the volume recorded so far,</a> demonstrates the potential that lies within the intersection of blockchain technology and digital artistry.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Bitcoin Ordinals&#8217; Q2 Performance Defies Expectations</h2>
<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w" dir="ltr">In a recent quarterly <a href="https://dappradar.com/blog/state-of-the-dapp-industry-in-q2-2023" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">report</a> from DappRadar, a rise in trading volume was documented for Bitcoin in the second quarter of 2023. The data, characterized by notable fluctuations, attributes this heightened trading activity to an increased interest in Ordinals, suggesting a marked shift in trader preferences and investment strategies.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-ordinals-this-brc-standard-will-reduce-fees-by-90/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Bitcoin Ordinals: This New BRC Standard Could Reduce Inscription Fees By 90%</a></p>
<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w" dir="ltr">Bitcoin Ordinals, once an emerging player in the crypto market, has now gained significant traction, establishing itself as a potential innovator in the industry.</p>
<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w" dir="ltr">The trading volume of Ordinals has demonstrated a growth trajectory, as detailed in DappRadar&#8217;s report. The trading volume for Ordinals started the year modestly, registering a mere $7.18 million in the first quarter. However, as the innovation gained increased visibility and trader confidence, there was an upturn in trading activity.</p>
<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w" dir="ltr">The second quarter of 2023 saw Bitcoin Ordinals&#8217; trading volume skyrocket to $210.7 million, a figure that represents a 2,834% increase from the preceding quarter. This upswing in trading activity underscores its growth in the digital asset market and indicates the potential for continued extension in the quarters to come.</p>
<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w" dir="ltr">It is worth noting that <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-ordinals-this-brc-standard-will-reduce-fees-by-90/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Bitcoin Ordinals&#8217;</a> performance is not a passing trend; instead, it signals a shift in how investors and enthusiasts approach NFTs in the digital assets space. </p>
<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w" dir="ltr">The rising acceptance and trading volume of Bitcoin Ordinals reveals a positive trajectory, which has successfully harnessed the power of non-fungible tokens.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Furthermore, Bitcoin Ordinals&#8217; journey from a relatively obscure blockchain project to a formidable player in the NFT space reflects the nature of the digital asset landscape. Its growth narrative, as underscored by its Q2 performance, sets the stage for more innovation and market expansion in the world of nonfungible tokens.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">User Engagement And Marketplaces Fuel Growth</h2>
<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w" dir="ltr">DappRadar&#8217;s report also highlighted Bitcoin Ordinals trades in Q2 &#8211; over 550,000 &#8211; driven by more than 151,000 unique traders. This surge in trading activity attests to its rapidly growing appeal within the crypto community in 2023.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://s3.cointelegraph.com/uploads/2023-07/bf5d8722-9324-41fe-be5b-b6f8d6f87ed0.png" alt="Bitcoin Ordinals marketplace data." width="2513" height="967"/>
<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w" dir="ltr">Data from a blockchain analytics <a href="https://dune.com/domo/ordinals-marketplaces" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">dashboard</a> on Dune, maintained by @domo, affirm these observations, highlighting a significant rise in individual users beginning in May 2023.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/dormant-bitcoin-supply-peaks-as-institutional-investors/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Dormant Bitcoin Supply Peaks As Institutional Investors Show Increased Involvement</a></p>
<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w" dir="ltr">This expansion is mirrored across several trading platforms, where UniSat &#8211; an open-source Chrome extension supporting Bitcoin Ordinals &amp; BRC-20 tokens &#8211; along with Magic Eden and Ordinals Wallet, commands a substantial share of distinct users.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://s3.cointelegraph.com/uploads/2023-07/8a9c82e0-0bb6-4cd4-90a7-dacb301c0354.png" alt="Bitcoin Ordinals unique users on the marketplace." width="1245" height="485"/>
<p dir="ltr">Meanwhile, over the past week, <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/dormant-bitcoin-supply-peaks-as-institutional-investors/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">BTC</a> has been in a downward trend dropping by 2.5%. However, in the past 24 hours, the asset appears to be picking up with an increase of nearly 1%. At the time of writing, <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/nft/as-bitcoin-rips-above-30000-bugs-discovered-on-ordinals-protocol/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">BTC trades at a price of $30,320</a>, after trading above the $31,000 mark a few days ago.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/GdPHZrlY/" alt="Bitcoin (BTC)’s price chart on TradingView" width="2770" height="1556"/>
<p dir="ltr">Featured image from iStock, Chart from TradingView</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/iStock-1305092068-750x536-1-460x329.jpg" width="460" height="329" />	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
