<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
>

<channel>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.newsbtc.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<description>Bitcoin &#38; Cryptocurrency News Today</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 23:24:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Gods Unchained launches on Epic Games Store, GODS Spikes 50%</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/gods-unchained-launches-on-epic-games-store-gods-spikes-50/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dalmas Ngetich]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 01:00:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blockchain game]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain games]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Epic Games Store]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[GODS]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gods Unchained]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Immutable Studio]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=539478</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Gods Unchained, a blockchain card trading game developed by Immutable Studio, has launched on Epic Games Store (EGS). Following this launch, GODS, the native token of the Gods Unchained ecosystem, has rallied 50% from June 2023 lows, expanding in line with the broader cryptocurrency markets spearheaded by Bitcoin, which is currently trading above $31,000. Gods Unchained launches on Epic Games Store The game recently announced its debut on Epic Games Store, a digital gaming distribution platform with over 230 million PC gamers, including a community of digital trading card enthusiasts.  As one of the original web3 games, Gods Unchained has been at the forefront of decentralized gaming. Now, intending to attract more mainstream trading card game and strategy gamers, Gods Unchained is undergoing an update, with an updated logo and updated visuals across different points, which would launch with the Epic Games Store release. Related Reading: MATIC Price Recovery Hits Roadblock, When Will Bulls Break Through? The PC game also teased a mobile-friendly design focused on onboarding new users. In a comment about the launch Daniel Paez, the executive producer of Gods Unchained, said EGS will introduce the web3 game to a “massive audience of traditional PC gamers and TCG enthusiasts.&#8221; Blockchain gaming, NFT activity recovering The deployment on EGS is timely. Specifically, it is when the cryptocurrency market is recovering after months of lower lows in 2022. During the last bear cycle, cryptocurrency prices crashed from 2021 peaks, impacting activity. Out of this, there was a significant contraction in non-fungible tokens (NFT) activity, which translated to low activity. In the Gods Unchained blockchain games, all trading cards are represented as unique NFTs. These represent ownership and can be transferred between users, even exchanged for cash or other cryptocurrencies. Since trading cards vary in rarity, the value assigned to each can change. According to DappRadar, unique active wallets (UAWs) remain stable at around 1,150 but lower than 2021 peaks when it spiked to over 4,000. At the same time, Gods Unchained generated over $745,000 in active transaction values. At the moment, GODS, the native token of the Gods Unchained game, is rising in sync with the broader cryptocurrency market. GODS is trading at $0.16, up 50% from June lows. GODSUSDT Candlestick arrangement shows that the token is bottoming up after dropping 75% from February 2023 highs. Last year, Immutable Studio, the developer of Gods Unchained, had to let go of multiple employees, including a senior game designer James Wakeham. These restructuring efforts resulted in a 6% reduction in the company&#8217;s workforce, yet, Immutable Games remained optimistic about its future. Related Reading: FLOKI Soars 26% In A Single Week, Shares 2023 Roadmap Update At the time, a spokesperson for the studio said the decision was to help them “achieve its goal of creating the next generation of web3 games.”  Feature Image From Canva, Chart From TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Gods Unchained, a blockchain card trading game developed by Immutable Studio, has launched on Epic Games Store (EGS). Following this launch, GODS, the native token of the Gods Unchained ecosystem, has rallied 50% from June 2023 lows, expanding in line with the broader cryptocurrency markets spearheaded by Bitcoin, which is currently trading above $31,000.</p>
<h2>Gods Unchained launches on Epic Games Store</h2>
<p>The game recently <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://blog.godsunchained.com/2023/06/22/gods-unchained-launches-on-epic-games-store/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">announced</a> its debut on Epic Games Store, a digital gaming distribution platform with over 230 million PC gamers, including a community of digital trading card enthusiasts. </p>
<p>As one of the original web3 games, Gods Unchained has been at the forefront of decentralized gaming. Now, intending to attract more mainstream trading card game and strategy gamers, Gods Unchained is undergoing an update, with an updated logo and updated visuals across different points, which would launch with the Epic Games Store release.</p>

<p>The PC game also teased a mobile-friendly design focused on onboarding new users. In a comment about the launch Daniel Paez, the executive producer of Gods Unchained, said EGS will introduce the web3 game to a “massive audience of traditional PC gamers and TCG enthusiasts.&#8221;</p>
<h2>Blockchain gaming, NFT activity recovering</h2>
<p>The deployment on EGS is timely. Specifically, it is when the cryptocurrency market is recovering after months of lower lows in 2022. During the last bear cycle, cryptocurrency prices crashed from 2021 peaks, impacting activity. Out of this, there was a significant contraction in non-fungible tokens (NFT) activity, which translated to low activity.</p>
<p>In the Gods Unchained blockchain games, all trading cards are represented as unique NFTs. These represent ownership and can be transferred between users, even exchanged for cash or other cryptocurrencies. Since trading cards vary in rarity, the value assigned to each can change.</p>
<p>According to DappRadar, unique active wallets (UAWs)<a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://dappradar.com/dapp/gods-unchained/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow"> remain</a> stable at around 1,150 but lower than 2021 peaks when it spiked to over 4,000. At the same time, Gods Unchained generated over $745,000 in active transaction values.</p>
<p>At the moment, GODS, the native token of the Gods Unchained game, is rising in sync with the broader cryptocurrency market. GODS is trading at $0.16, up 50% from June lows. GODSUSDT Candlestick arrangement shows that the token is bottoming up after dropping 75% from February 2023 highs.</p>
<a href="https://www.tradingview.com/x/jSvWCUiV/" rel="nofollow"><img decoding="async" class="size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/jSvWCUiV/" alt="GODS price on June 23| Source: GODSUSDT from Binance, TradingView" width="1226" height="595" loading="lazy"/></a>
<p>Last year, Immutable Studio, the developer of Gods Unchained, had to let go of multiple employees, including a senior game designer James Wakeham. These restructuring efforts resulted in a 6% reduction in the company&#8217;s workforce, yet, Immutable Games remained optimistic about its future.</p>

<p>At the time, a spokesperson for the studio <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.kotaku.com.au/2022/07/australian-studio-immutable-redundancies/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">said</a> the decision was to help them “achieve its goal of creating the next generation of web3 games.” </p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Crypto-news-Template23-460x260.jpg" width="460" height="260" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Just Gained Over 18% In Seven Days: What’s Happened When This Has Occurred In The Past?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-just-gained-over-18-in-seven-days-whats-happened-when-this-has-occurred-in-the-past/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[dbthequant]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 23:18:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=539433</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[By the completion of its daily candle on Wednesday, Bitcoin had gained over 18% in just seven consecutive sessions, abruptly ending the steady drift lower which had dominated its price action since Bitcoin put in its mid-April high above 30,000. How unusual is this magnitude gain in only a week’s time, and what’s happened in the past after similarly robust rallies? Let’s take a closer look at Bitcoin’s price history to find out. Bitcoin’s Price History Suggests Higher Prices Ahead As we examine Bitcoin’s price history for which there is reliable data (2011 to the present), the number one cryptocurrency by market cap has experienced numerous instances of gains greater than or equal to +18% over the span of seven days. Bitcoin gains &#62;= 18% in Seven Days &#124; BTCUSD on TradingView.com Related Reading: Bitcoin Recovers Above Critical Level, Why Bulls Could Be Ready To Charge Because the number of occurrences will vary depending on holding time, we’ll start by listing the number of times this has happened next to our hypothetical hold times of 7 days through 90 days. Holding time is defined as the amount of time one held Bitcoin before exiting. For example, if one hypothetically purchased Bitcoin following the trigger event (i.e., +18% over the span of seven days) and sold it 30 days later, this would be a holding time of 30 days. Bitcoin Occurrences of +18% Gains in Seven Consecutive Days by Holding Time (2011 &#8211; Present) 98 occurrences using a 7-day hold time 73 occurrences using a 15-day hold time 57 occurrences using a 30-day hold time 30 occurrences using a 90-day hold time Clearly, gains of this magnitude in just a week’s time are not uncommon for Bitcoin, an asset with numerous instances of large price advances especially when considering its relatively short price history compared to traditional risk assets. Bitcoin Results Slightly Less Bullish In Recent Years While a gain of over 18% in such a brief time period may lead some traders to lean bearish, the data suggests otherwise, with historical average results clearly positive across the board for all holding times from 2011 to the present. &#160; Bitcoin gains &#62;= 18% in Seven Consecutive Days with Various Hold Times. 2011 &#8211; Present. Because Bitcoin’s early price history experienced arguably outsized gains relative to its more recent history, let’s take a look at average results for the same degree of gains in a week’s time but only examining data for the last five years (6/23/18 to the present). Bitcoin gains &#62;= 18% in Seven Consecutive Days with Various Hold Times. Last Five Years. While once again results are positive across the board, the hypothetical results over more recent data are significantly lower, with the average 90-day return of +25.6% over the past five years a far cry from the +109.4% returns for the same 90-day window over the full price history from 2011 to the present. Related Reading: Bitcoin Price Surges 8% And Defies Gravity – Bulls Eye $30K While some traders may argue that the past five years is less representative data due to the occurrence of two major bear markets for Bitcoin and crypto more broadly, Bitcoin has shown positive follow through on average for both time periods across all the hold times we examined. While the past does not predict the future, the recent powerful price advance appears to suggest that Bitcoin is poised for greater gains in relatively near future. DB the Quant is the author of the REKTelligence Report newsletter on Substack. Follow @REKTelligence on Twitter for evidence-based crypto market research and analysis. Important Note: This content is strictly educational in nature and should not be considered investment advice. Featured images created with Tableau. Charts from TradingView.com.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>By the completion of its daily candle on Wednesday, Bitcoin had gained over 18% in just seven consecutive sessions, abruptly ending the steady drift lower which had dominated its price action since Bitcoin put in its mid-April high above 30,000. How unusual is this magnitude gain in only a week’s time, and what’s happened in the past after similarly robust rallies? Let’s take a closer look at Bitcoin’s price history to find out.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin’s Price History Suggests Higher Prices Ahead</h2>
<p>As we examine Bitcoin’s price history for which there is reliable data (2011 to the present), the number one cryptocurrency by market cap has experienced numerous instances of gains greater than or equal to +18% over the span of seven days.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium wp-image-539434 aligncenter" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/CHART_BTC_7D-Gain_062323-460x318.png" alt="" width="460" height="318" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/CHART_BTC_7D-Gain_062323-460x318.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/CHART_BTC_7D-Gain_062323-860x595.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/CHART_BTC_7D-Gain_062323-768x531.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/CHART_BTC_7D-Gain_062323-750x518.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/CHART_BTC_7D-Gain_062323-1140x788.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/CHART_BTC_7D-Gain_062323.png 1150w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px"/></p>
Bitcoin gains &gt;= 18% in Seven Days | <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BTCUSD/?exchange=INDEX" rel="nofollow">BTCUSD on TradingView.com</a>

Because the number of occurrences will vary depending on holding time, we’ll start by listing the number of times this has happened next to our hypothetical hold times of 7 days through 90 days. Holding time is defined as the amount of time one held Bitcoin before exiting. For example, if one hypothetically purchased Bitcoin following the trigger event (i.e., +18% over the span of seven days) and sold it 30 days later, this would be a holding time of 30 days.

<p><strong>Bitcoin Occurrences of +18% Gains in Seven Consecutive Days by Holding Time (2011 &#8211; Present)</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>98 occurrences using a 7-day hold time</li>
<li>73 occurrences using a 15-day hold time</li>
<li>57 occurrences using a 30-day hold time</li>
<li>30 occurrences using a 90-day hold time</li>
</ul>
<p>Clearly, gains of this magnitude in just a week’s time are not uncommon for Bitcoin, an asset with numerous instances of large price advances especially when considering its relatively short price history compared to traditional risk assets.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Results Slightly Less Bullish In Recent Years</h2>
<p>While a gain of over 18% in such a brief time period may lead some traders to lean bearish, the data suggests otherwise, with historical average results clearly positive across the board for all holding times from 2011 to the present.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium wp-image-539436 aligncenter" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Hold-Times_ALL-DATA2-460x285.png" alt="" width="460" height="285" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Hold-Times_ALL-DATA2-460x285.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Hold-Times_ALL-DATA2-860x534.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Hold-Times_ALL-DATA2-768x477.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Hold-Times_ALL-DATA2-750x465.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Hold-Times_ALL-DATA2.png 975w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px"/></p>
Bitcoin gains &gt;= 18% in Seven Consecutive Days with Various Hold Times. 2011 &#8211; Present.
<p>Because Bitcoin’s early price history experienced arguably outsized gains relative to its more recent history, let’s take a look at average results for the same degree of gains in a week’s time but only examining data for the last five years (6/23/18 to the present).</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium wp-image-539437 aligncenter" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Hold-Times_Last-5-Years2-460x285.png" alt="" width="460" height="285" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Hold-Times_Last-5-Years2-460x285.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Hold-Times_Last-5-Years2-860x534.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Hold-Times_Last-5-Years2-768x477.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Hold-Times_Last-5-Years2-750x465.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Hold-Times_Last-5-Years2.png 975w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px"/></p>
Bitcoin gains &gt;= 18% in Seven Consecutive Days with Various Hold Times. Last Five Years.
<p>While once again results are positive across the board, the hypothetical results over more recent data are significantly lower, with the average 90-day return of +25.6% over the past five years a far cry from the +109.4% returns for the same 90-day window over the full price history from 2011 to the present.</p>

<p>While some traders may argue that the past five years is less representative data due to the occurrence of two major bear markets for Bitcoin and crypto more broadly, Bitcoin has shown positive follow through on average for both time periods across all the hold times we examined. While the past does not predict the future, the recent powerful price advance appears to suggest that Bitcoin is poised for greater gains in relatively near future.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/iStock-1314042576-460x288.jpg" width="460" height="288" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Mask Foundation Moves 2.5 Million Tokens To Exchanges, Huge Dip Incoming?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/altcoin/mask-foundation-moves-2-5-million-tokens-to-exchanges/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samuel Edyme]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 23:00:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Loononchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mask]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MASKUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=539425</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[In the volatile and unpredictable world of cryptocurrencies, major transactions often signal impending market movements. Recently, Lookonchain, an on-chain analytics firm, reported a substantial transfer of MASK tokens, initiated by the Mask Network Foundation. According to their findings, the foundation moved nearly 3 million MASK tokens out of its wallets, an event that could potentially lead to significant market fluctuations. At the time of writing, the token was trading at $3.69, following a decline of over 2.5% over the past 24 hours. The noteworthy shift of 2.5 million MASK tokens, equating to over $9 million, could potentially trigger further price variations. Related Reading: DeFi Liquidity Pool: A Guide to Liquidity Pool Token The intent behind the substantial token transfer remains speculative, prompting varied interpretations within the crypto community. Mask Network Foundation transferred 3M $MASK ($11.25M) out today. Among them, 2.5M $MASK ($9.4M) was transferred to #Binance and #OKX. And 500K $MASK was transferred out 1 hour ago, which may be transferred to #OKX later.https://t.co/mBI4PbZaLa pic.twitter.com/BXQNceMuxs — Lookonchain (@lookonchain) June 23, 2023 Mask Network Foundation&#8217;s Large-scale Transfer According to Lookonchain, the Mask Network Foundation distributed 2.5 million tokens, which are worth more than $9 million, between Binance and OKX. An additional 500,000 tokens were also transferred out of the foundation&#8217;s wallets, but they have not yet surfaced on any exchange platform so far. Related Reading: Bitcoin Cash (BCH) Continues To Rise While Market Sees Correction This particular move has led to speculations of an impending sell-off within the next 24-48 hours. Meanwhile, the transfer could signify the Mask Network Foundation&#8217;s strategy to bolster market-making activities. By moving a significant number of the tokens to exchange platforms, the foundation could be aiming to stimulate trading volume and attract a wider range of traders to the project. Despite the 2.5% drop in MASK&#8217;s value, the move could potentially stabilize the token&#8217;s price by fostering liquidity and demand in the market. While it&#8217;s too early to definitively predict the impact of these transactions on MASK&#8217;s market position, the movements undeniably indicate an upcoming shift in the MASK network token market. MASK&#8217;s Latest Price Action The MASK token price has increased in the past 7 days, with the token breaking multiple resistance levels. MASK is currently trading at $3.70, up by nearly 10% over the past week. However, over the past 24 hours, MASK has seen a slight decline down by 2.5%. Though it is not certain if there has been any huge sell-off yet of the tokens transferred to exchanges, the token has plunged from its 24-hour high of $3.84. The token currently has a market capitalization of $302.6 Million, making it rank 107th among the largest cryptocurrency by market cap. MASK&#8217;s daily trading volume has also significantly moved in the past 7 days. The token&#8217;s volume has surged from as low as $31 million last Friday to as high as $93 million in the past 24 hours. Related Reading: Apple’s Vision Pro Launch Impacts Metaverse, Why This Token Recorded 160% In Profits The slight decline in the token&#8217;s price can be attributed to either the trader&#8217;s fear of such a massive influx into exchanges or the overall bearish sentiment in the cryptocurrency market. Featured image from iStock, Chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In the volatile and unpredictable world of cryptocurrencies, major transactions often signal impending market movements. Recently, Lookonchain, an on-chain analytics firm, <a href="https://twitter.com/lookonchain/status/1672147459626401794?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">reported</a> a substantial transfer of MASK tokens, initiated by the Mask Network Foundation. </p>
<p>According to their findings, the foundation moved nearly 3 million MASK tokens out of its wallets, an event that could potentially lead to significant market fluctuations.</p>
<p>At the time of writing, the token was trading at $3.69, following a decline of over 2.5% over the past 24 hours. The noteworthy shift of 2.5 million MASK tokens, equating to over $9 million, could potentially trigger further price variations.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/company/defi-liquidity-pool-a-guide-to-liquidity-pool-token/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">DeFi Liquidity Pool: A Guide to Liquidity Pool Token</a></p>
<p>The intent behind the substantial token transfer remains speculative, prompting varied interpretations within the crypto community.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Mask Network Foundation transferred 3M <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24MASK&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$MASK</a> ($11.25M) out today.</p>
<p>Among them, 2.5M <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24MASK&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$MASK</a> ($9.4M) was transferred to <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Binance?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#Binance</a> and <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/OKX?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#OKX</a>.</p>
<p>And 500K <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24MASK&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$MASK</a> was transferred out 1 hour ago, which may be transferred to <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/OKX?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#OKX</a> later.<a href="https://t.co/mBI4PbZaLa" rel="nofollow">https://t.co/mBI4PbZaLa</a> <a href="https://t.co/BXQNceMuxs" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/BXQNceMuxs</a></p>
<p>— Lookonchain (@lookonchain) <a href="https://twitter.com/lookonchain/status/1672147459626401794?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">June 23, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<h2>Mask Network Foundation&#8217;s Large-scale Transfer</h2>
<p>According to Lookonchain, the Mask Network Foundation distributed 2.5 million <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/ripple/root-network-set-to-reward-its-validators-stakers-with-xrp-tokens/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">tokens</a>, which are worth more than $9 million, between Binance and OKX. An additional 500,000 tokens were also transferred out of the foundation&#8217;s wallets, but they have not yet surfaced on any exchange platform so far.</p>

<p>This particular move has led to speculations of an impending sell-off within the next 24-48 hours. Meanwhile, the transfer could signify the Mask Network Foundation&#8217;s strategy to bolster market-making activities. </p>
<p>By moving a significant number of the tokens to exchange platforms, the foundation could be aiming to stimulate trading volume and attract a wider range of traders to the project. Despite the 2.5% drop in MASK&#8217;s value, the move could potentially stabilize the token&#8217;s price by fostering liquidity and demand in the market.</p>
<p>While it&#8217;s too early to definitively predict the impact of these transactions on MASK&#8217;s market position, the movements undeniably indicate an upcoming shift in the MASK network token market. </p>
<h2>MASK&#8217;s Latest Price Action</h2>
<p>The MASK token price has increased in the past 7 days, with the token breaking multiple resistance levels. MASK is currently trading at $3.70, up by nearly 10% over the past week. However, over the past 24 hours, MASK has seen a slight decline down by 2.5%.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/FNg2pQeD/" alt="MASK token price chart on TradingView" width="2770" height="1556"/>
<p>Though it is not certain if there has been any huge sell-off yet of the tokens transferred to exchanges, the token has plunged from its 24-hour high of $3.84. <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/shiba-inu-ai-meme-token-partners-with-shibarium/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">The token</a> currently has a market capitalization of $302.6 Million, making it rank 107th among the largest cryptocurrency by market cap.</p>
<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w" dir="ltr">MASK&#8217;s daily trading volume has also significantly moved in the past 7 days. The token&#8217;s volume has surged from as low as $31 million last Friday to as high as $93 million in the past 24 hours.</p>

<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w" dir="ltr">The slight decline in the token&#8217;s price can be attributed to either the trader&#8217;s fear of such a massive influx into exchanges or the overall bearish sentiment in the cryptocurrency market. </p>
<p dir="ltr">Featured image from iStock, Chart from TradingView</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/Bitcoin-shorts-460x306.jpeg" width="460" height="306" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Analyst Predicts: Bitcoin (BTC) To Reach $69,000 And Above In 2023</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/crypto-analyst-predicts-bitcoin-to-reach-above-in-2023/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samuel Edyme]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 22:00:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=539398</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[As the world of crypto continues to evolve, traders and analysts are closely monitoring the Bitcoin (BTC) charts for clues about future price movements. Among them, the popular analyst known as Credible Crypto has shared his insights, predicting a new all-time high for Bitcoin by 2023. The prognosis relies on the assumption of a continuing &#8220;parabolic advance&#8221; that could drive the token beyond its previous peak of $69,000. Predicting A Parabolic Advance For Bitcoin The essence of Credible Crypto&#8217;s prediction lies in the nature of Bitcoin&#8217;s &#8220;parabolic advance.&#8221; This concept describes a situation where momentum in the price of an asset increases exponentially until it reaches its peak. Related Reading: Nansen Forecast For Bitcoin Bull Run: Regulatory Clarity And Lower Inflation According to Credible Crypto, such advances have been evident in Bitcoin&#8217;s history, as observed during its ascents from $3,000 to $14,000 and from $10,000 to $60,000.  Bitcoin’s recent performance, characterized by firm support at $25,000 on monthly timeframes, is considered by Credible Crypto as potentially setting the stage for another round of parabolic advance. This new climb, the analyst suggests, should produce monthly moves of more than $10,000, filling the $40,000 gap to the previous all-time high. A &#8216;Logical&#8217; Guess For New Heights While cautioning that these are estimations based on current market conditions, the trader puts forth October 2023 as a &#8220;fairly logical guesstimate&#8221; for when Bitcoin could reach its new all-time high. He clarifies that it&#8217;s not a definitive prediction, but rather an estimation based on the logic of Bitcoin&#8217;s past behavior.  The analyst noted: I am not saying we MUST hit new all-time highs by October, I AM saying I do think we will hit new ATH by the end of this year, and if someone forced me to pick a month in which I think this will occur it would be October. Let’s see how things play out. Meanwhile, over the past 7 days, Bitcoin has made significant moves. The asset has shown a huge recovery from its recent bloodbath amid the United States Security and Exchange Commission (SEC) lawsuit on the two largest crypto exchanges, Binance and Coinbase. Bitcoin has tapped a notable high of above $30,000 bringing the asset to record a nearly 20% gain to its value in the past 7 days. Notably, BTC&#8217;s surge comes amid financial giants such as BlackRock embracing the crypto future. BlackRock, which is the world&#8217;s largest asset manager, last week disclosed its latest plan to launch a Bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF) if it gets approved by the US regulator, sparking an incredibly rally in the price of BTC. Related Reading: BlackRock Inches Closer To Launching Bitcoin ETF: Potential Impact On BTC Price At the time of writing, Bitcoin currently trades above $30,000 after trading below that price range throughout last week. In the past 7 days, Bitcoin’s total market capitalization has also seen a boost of 18.1%, amounting to an additional $90 billion. The market capitalization of Bitcoin presently hovers at $585.2 billion, an increase from last Friday&#8217;s $494 billion. Featured image from Unsplash, Chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>As the world of crypto continues to evolve, traders and analysts are closely monitoring the Bitcoin (BTC) charts for clues about future price movements. Among them, the popular analyst known as Credible Crypto has <a href="https://twitter.com/CredibleCrypto/status/1671959219627757568?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">shared</a> his insights, predicting a new all-time high for Bitcoin by 2023. </p>
<p>The prognosis relies on the assumption of a continuing &#8220;parabolic advance&#8221; that could drive the token beyond its previous peak of $69,000.</p>
<h2>Predicting A Parabolic Advance For Bitcoin</h2>
<p>The essence of Credible Crypto&#8217;s prediction lies in the nature of Bitcoin&#8217;s &#8220;parabolic advance.&#8221; This concept describes a situation where momentum in the price of an asset increases exponentially until it <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/nansen-forecasts-conditions-for-the-next-bitcoin-bull-run/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">reaches its peak</a>.</p>

<p>According to Credible Crypto, such advances have been evident in Bitcoin&#8217;s history, as observed during its ascents from $3,000 to $14,000 and from $10,000 to $60,000. </p>
<p>Bitcoin’s recent performance, characterized by firm support at $25,000 on monthly timeframes, is considered by Credible Crypto as potentially setting the stage for another round of parabolic advance. This new climb, the analyst suggests, should produce monthly moves of more than $10,000, filling the $40,000 gap to the previous all-time high.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium wp-image-539408" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/FzPzD8zagAEe0ob-460x241.jpeg" alt="Analysis from Credible Crypto on Twitter" width="460" height="241" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/FzPzD8zagAEe0ob-460x241.jpeg 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/FzPzD8zagAEe0ob-860x450.jpeg 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/FzPzD8zagAEe0ob-768x402.jpeg 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/FzPzD8zagAEe0ob-750x393.jpeg 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/FzPzD8zagAEe0ob-1140x597.jpeg 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/FzPzD8zagAEe0ob.jpeg 1200w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px"/>
<h2>A &#8216;Logical&#8217; Guess For New Heights</h2>
<p>While cautioning that these are estimations based on current market conditions, the trader puts forth October 2023 as a &#8220;fairly logical guesstimate&#8221; for when <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-market-dominance-peaks-in-nearly-two-years/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Bitcoin</a> could reach its new all-time high. He clarifies that it&#8217;s not a definitive prediction, but rather an estimation based on the logic of Bitcoin&#8217;s past behavior. </p>
<p>The analyst noted:</p>
<blockquote><p>I am not saying we MUST hit new all-time highs by October, I AM saying I do think we will hit new ATH by the end of this year, and if someone forced me to pick a month in which I think this will occur it would be October. Let’s see how things play out.</p></blockquote>
<p>Meanwhile, over the past 7 days, <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/nansen-forecasts-conditions-for-the-next-bitcoin-bull-run/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Bitcoin has made significant moves</a>. The asset has shown a huge recovery from its recent bloodbath amid the United States Security and Exchange Commission (SEC) lawsuit on the two largest crypto exchanges, Binance and Coinbase.</p>
<p>Bitcoin has tapped a notable <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-price-on-shaky-ground-market-analysts-warn-potential-fall/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">high of above $30,000</a> bringing the asset to record a nearly 20% gain to its value in the past 7 days. Notably, BTC&#8217;s surge comes amid financial giants such as BlackRock embracing the crypto future.</p>
<p>BlackRock, which is the world&#8217;s largest asset manager, last week<a href="http://BlackRock Inches Closer To Launching Bitcoin ETF: Potential Impact On BTC Price" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow"> disclosed its latest plan</a> to launch a Bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF) if it gets approved by the US regulator, sparking an incredibly rally in the price of BTC.</p>

<p>At the time of writing, Bitcoin currently trades above $30,000 after trading below that price range throughout last week.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/78Nb0oRp/" alt="Bitcoin (BTC)’s price chart on TradingView" width="2770" height="1556"/>
<p>In the past 7 days, Bitcoin’s total market capitalization has also seen a boost of 18.1%, amounting to an additional $90 billion. The market capitalization of Bitcoin presently hovers at $585.2 billion, an increase from last Friday&#8217;s $494 billion.</p>
<p>Featured image from Unsplash, Chart from TradingView</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/andre-francois-mckenzie-iGYiBhdNTpE-unsplash-2-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Future Hangs In The Balance: What To Expect In The Coming Weeks</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-future-hangs-in-the-balance-what-to-expect-in-the-coming-weeks/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 21:00:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=539428</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin, the leading cryptocurrency by market capitalization, seems to have entered a phase of consolidation above the $30,000 mark following a notable surge of over 10% on Tuesday.  While the price movement has generated a lot of interest among investors, it remains uncertain whether Bitcoin will maintain its upward momentum or experience a pullback in the coming days. Bitcoin Uncertain Trajectory Ben Lilly, a well-known cryptocurrency analyst, and economist, recently shared his thoughts on the current state of Bitcoin&#8217;s price action and its potential future trajectory.  In a recent analysis, Lilly dubbed the current price movement the &#8220;Larry Fink Pump,&#8221; referencing the recent announcement by BlackRock&#8217;s CEO Larry Fink regarding the company&#8217;s increased interest and application for a  Bitcoin spot ETF. While the pump has caused some excitement among investors, Lilly notes that several factors could cause the rally to falter.  Related Reading: Bitcoin Investor Sentiment Suggests BTC Rally Is Far From Over For one, Bitcoin has already wiped out the remaining high-leverage liquidity to the upside, and the Cumulative Volume Delta (CVD) spot seems to have lost its short-lived trend already.  Additionally, the fuel meter discussed in a recent Alpha Bites episode by Benjamin Skew of Jarvis Labs LLC has dropped significantly from its pre-pump levels, which could indicate a bearish case for Bitcoin in the short term. Despite these potential bearish factors, Lilly remains optimistic about Bitcoin&#8217;s future. He notes that the $24,000 level is still sitting there and could be had if the price breaks the 200-day moving average, which is currently creeping above it. If this happens, he predicts that Bitcoin could drop to $21,000-$22,000. However, Lilly also sees the possibility of an upside scenario for BTC. He notes that low-leverage liquidity sits at $32,000, and he would &#8220;love to see it taken out.&#8221;  Looking at the returns by trading session, he points out that the New York session seems to be leading the way. He notes that when the trend of the New York session ends, there&#8217;s a bit of a lag before the price responds to the downside, suggesting that the June options max pain of $25,000 may not happen. Lilly also highlights the recent increase in the whale holding chart, as seen in the chart below, which indicates that large Bitcoin holders, commonly referred to as whales, are once again accumulating the cryptocurrency.  This is the first time a trend like this has been observed since mid-January, suggesting that there may have been significant accumulation happening before the recent surge in BTC’s price. Related Reading: Is Chainlink The Most Undervalued Altcoin? It’s Do Or Die For LINK Overall, Lilly concludes that investors should not be quick to fade this Bitcoin rally. While there are potential bearish factors at play, there are also several bullish indicators. Investors should track the data to see if the trend continues and be prepared for potential volatility events in the future. At the time of writing, Bitcoin has maintained a stable price for several days. The cryptocurrency is currently trading at $30,100 and has managed to stay in positive territory, with a slight increase of 0.6% over the past 24 hours. Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com ]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin, the leading cryptocurrency by market capitalization, seems to have entered a phase of consolidation above the $30,000 mark following a notable surge of over 10% on Tuesday. </p>
<p>While the price movement has generated a lot of interest among investors, it remains uncertain whether Bitcoin will maintain its upward momentum or experience a pullback in the coming days.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Uncertain Trajectory</h2>
<p>Ben Lilly, a well-known cryptocurrency analyst, and economist, recently <a href="https://twitter.com/MrBenLilly/status/1672085368777129986?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">shared his thoughts </a>on the current state of Bitcoin&#8217;s price action and its potential future trajectory. </p>
<p>In a recent analysis, Lilly dubbed the current price movement the &#8220;Larry Fink Pump,&#8221; referencing the recent announcement by BlackRock&#8217;s CEO Larry Fink regarding the company&#8217;s increased interest and application for a  Bitcoin spot ETF.</p>
<p>While the pump has caused some excitement among investors, Lilly notes that several factors could cause the rally to falter. </p>

<p>For one, Bitcoin has already wiped out the remaining high-leverage liquidity to the upside, and the Cumulative Volume Delta (CVD) spot seems to have lost its short-lived trend already. </p>
<p>Additionally, the fuel meter discussed in a recent Alpha Bites episode by Benjamin Skew of Jarvis Labs LLC has dropped significantly from its pre-pump levels, which could indicate a bearish case for Bitcoin in the short term.</p>
<p>Despite these potential bearish factors, Lilly remains optimistic about Bitcoin&#8217;s future. He notes that the $24,000 level is still sitting there and could be had if the price breaks the 200-day moving average, which is currently creeping above it. If this happens, he predicts that Bitcoin could drop to $21,000-$22,000.</p>
<p>However, Lilly also sees the possibility of an upside scenario for BTC. He notes that low-leverage liquidity sits at $32,000, and he would &#8220;love to see it taken out.&#8221; </p>
<p>Looking at the returns by trading session, he points out that the New York session seems to be leading the way. He notes that when the trend of the New York session ends, there&#8217;s a bit of a lag before the price responds to the downside, suggesting that the June options max pain of $25,000 may not happen.</p>
<p>Lilly also highlights the recent increase in the whale holding chart, as seen in the chart below, which indicates that large Bitcoin holders, commonly referred to as whales, are once again accumulating the cryptocurrency. </p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large wp-image-539429" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Screenshot_1-860x328.jpg" alt="Bitcoin " width="860" height="328" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Screenshot_1-860x328.jpg 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Screenshot_1-460x176.jpg 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Screenshot_1-768x293.jpg 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Screenshot_1-750x286.jpg 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Screenshot_1-1140x435.jpg 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Screenshot_1.jpg 1464w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/>
<p>This is the first time a trend like this has been observed since mid-January, suggesting that there may have been significant accumulation happening before the recent surge in BTC’s price.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/chainlink/chainlink-most-undervalued-altcoin-do-or-die-link/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Is Chainlink The Most Undervalued Altcoin? It’s Do Or Die For LINK</a></p>
<p>Overall, Lilly concludes that investors should not be quick to fade this Bitcoin rally. While there are potential bearish factors at play, there are also several bullish indicators. Investors should track the data to see if the trend continues and be prepared for potential volatility events in the future.</p>
<p>At the time of writing, Bitcoin has maintained a stable price for several days. The cryptocurrency is currently trading at $30,100 and has managed to stay in positive territory, with a slight increase of 0.6% over the past 24 hours.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/tsFd6kWa/" alt="Bitcoin " width="1814" height="858"/>
<p>Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/iStock-1316129074-460x251.jpg" width="460" height="251" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>LEO Token Shows Positive Moves As Major Coins Suffer Volatility</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/leo/leo-token-shows-positive-moves-as-major-coins-suffer-volatility/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Kent Glory]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 20:00:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[LEO]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LEO analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LEO price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LEOUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[UNUS SED LEO]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=539411</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitfinex’s utility token, LEO, stands out from the crowd with positive moves amid the market-wide downturn that suppressed most coins. It saw an 8.69% price increase on the day and added 11.42% over the past seven days, which placed it among the top-gaining coins on the last day. LEO token’s move today follows a consistent price increase since June 20, after Bitfinex announced a public grant to support the open-source development of Qubes OS in partnership with Tether, USDT stablecoin issuer. LEO Outperforms Top Coins With Recent Action LEO&#8217;s value did not only strengthen against the dollar but outperformed the two market forerunners, Bitcoin and Ethereum, in terms of 24-hour price change. At the time of writing, LEO is up 9% against Bitcoin and nearly 8% against Ethereum. The bullish momentum presented in LEO&#8217;s price movement suggests a move to conquer the $4 psychological level.  Related Reading: Is Chainlink The Most Undervalued Altcoin? It’s Do Or Die For LINK The token&#8217;s price stalled at the consolidation channel between $3.51 and $3.6 over the past weeks. But currently, LEO is trading at a low of $3.63 and a high of $3.93. Also, its bull-bear power is neutral, indicating a fierce struggle to prevail between the bears and the bulls as the histogram bars show long green candle stick patterns. Notably, the token has bounced off the 200 Exponential Moving Average, indicating a golden cross, meaning LEO is witnessing an upward trend due to a strong buying interest. It also suggests the bulls are in action to trigger a further uptrend. The Relative Strength Index (RSI) has exceeded 78, meaning the asset is leaving the overbought territory. This move indicates that LEO&#8217;s price is approaching a swing rejection where it could break its last record high. BitFinex/Tether Grant May Have Influenced LEO’s Price Momentum Qubes OS is a free, open-source security-oriented desktop operating system that touts itself as a reasonably secure OS. It allows users to secure through compartmentalization. And Qubes OS aims to provide security and enhanced privacy through isolation.  Bitfinex and Tether&#8217;s 100,000 USDT grant highlights went toward the company to support projects that drive the development of secure and decentralized technologies. In a statement, Paolo Ardoino, CTO of Tether and Bitfinex, said the firms recognize that privacy and security are paramount in the digital age. Related Reading: Stacks (STX) Succumbs To Market Correction, Slides By 10% In The Last Day Also, the LEO token&#8217;s price move could have gained momentum through the brief market rebound over the last 48 hours. As of yesterday, June 22, LEO closed with a 0.6% price increase when the global crypto market capitalization improved by 3%. Although the market retraced slightly, LEO’s momentum only peaked, suggesting stronger market forces at play. Featured image from Pixabay and chart from Pixabay]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitfinex’s utility token, LEO, stands out from the crowd with positive moves amid the market-wide downturn that suppressed most coins. It saw an 8.69% price increase on the day and added 11.42% over the past seven days, which placed it among the top-gaining coins on the last day.</p>
<p>LEO token’s move today follows a consistent price increase since June 20, after Bitfinex <a href="https://blog.bitfinex.com/media-releases/tether-and-bitfinex-announce-public-grant-to-support-qubes-os/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">announced</a> a public grant to support the open-source development of Qubes OS in partnership with Tether, USDT stablecoin issuer.</p>
<h2>LEO Outperforms Top Coins With Recent Action</h2>
<p>LEO&#8217;s value did not only strengthen against the dollar but outperformed the two market forerunners, <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Bitcoin and Ethereum</a>, in terms of 24-hour price change. At the time of writing, LEO is up 9% against Bitcoin and nearly 8% against Ethereum. The bullish momentum presented in LEO&#8217;s price movement suggests a move to conquer the $4 psychological level. </p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/chainlink/chainlink-most-undervalued-altcoin-do-or-die-link/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Is Chainlink The Most Undervalued Altcoin? It’s Do Or Die For LINK</a></p>
<p>The token&#8217;s price stalled at the consolidation channel between $3.51 and $3.6 over the past weeks. But currently, LEO is trading at a low of $3.63 and a high of $3.93. Also, its bull-bear power is neutral, indicating a fierce struggle to prevail between the bears and the bulls as the histogram bars show long green candle stick patterns.</p>
<p>Notably, the token has bounced off the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/LEOUSD/technicals/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">200 Exponential Moving Average</a>, indicating a golden cross, meaning LEO is witnessing an upward trend due to a strong buying interest. It also suggests the bulls are in action to trigger a further uptrend.</p>
<p>The <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/ideas/relativestrengthindex/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Relative Strength Index (RSI)</a> has exceeded 78, meaning the asset is leaving the overbought territory. This move indicates that LEO&#8217;s price is approaching a swing rejection where it could break its last record high.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/OIHnrBLq/" alt="LEOUSD price chart" width="980" height="538"/>
<h2>BitFinex/Tether Grant May Have Influenced LEO’s Price Momentum</h2>
<p>Qubes OS is a free, open-source security-oriented desktop operating system that touts itself as a reasonably secure OS. It allows users to secure through compartmentalization. And Qubes OS aims to provide security and enhanced privacy through isolation. </p>
<p>Bitfinex and Tether&#8217;s 100,000 USDT grant highlights went toward the company to support projects that drive the development of secure and decentralized technologies. </p>
<p>In a statement, Paolo Ardoino, CTO of Tether and Bitfinex, said the firms recognize that privacy and security are paramount in the digital age.</p>

<p><a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/unus-sed-leo/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Also, the LEO token&#8217;s price</a> move could have gained momentum through the brief market rebound over the last 48 hours. As of yesterday, June 22, LEO closed with a 0.6% price increase when the global crypto market capitalization improved by 3%. Although the market retraced slightly, LEO’s momentum only peaked, suggesting stronger market forces at play.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/LEO-460x291.jpg" width="460" height="291" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin SOPR Bounces Into Profit Zone, What Does This Mean?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-sopr-bounces-into-profit-zone-what-mean/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hououin Kyouma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 19:00:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Profit-Taking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin SOPR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=539395</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[On-chain data shows the Bitcoin Spent Output Profit Ratio (SOPR) has bounced back into the profit zone with the latest rally above $30,000. Bitcoin SOPR Has Successfully Retested 1.0 Support Line According to data from the on-chain analytics firm Glassnode, investors are now selling their coins at a profit. The &#8220;SOPR&#8221; is an indicator that tells us whether profit-taking or loss-taking is dominant in the Bitcoin market currently. When the value of this metric is greater than 1.0, it means that the profits being realized by the investors are higher than the losses currently. On the other hand, the values of the indicator under this mark suggest the market as a whole is moving/selling coins at a loss. The SOPR being exactly equal to 1.0 naturally suggests that the average investor is just breaking even on their selling at the moment, as the total amount of profits being harvested in the market is equal to the losses. Now, here is a chart that shows the trend in the Bitcoin SOPR over the past year: Looks like the value of the metric seems to have shot up in recent days &#124; Source: Glassnode on Twitter Note that the version of the SOPR being used here is the &#8220;entity-adjusted&#8221; one, meaning that it only takes into account the transactions made between separate entities on the network and not all individual wallets. Related Reading: Bitcoin 30-Day Price Range Foreshadowed The Rally, Here’s How An &#8220;entity&#8221; here refers to a single address or a collection of addresses that Glassnode has determined to belong to the same investor. As transfers where a holder moves coins to a different wallet of theirs aren&#8217;t actually sales at all, they aren&#8217;t relevant to the SOPR, and so, removing them from the data makes the indicator more accurate. As you can see in the above graph, the entity-adjusted SOPR has been mostly at values above 1.0 during the last few months, a trend that makes sense as the asset has observed a rally in this period, which is bound to have put investors into notable profits. Back in March, however, the indicator had deviated away from this profit-taking trend, as the Bitcoin price had taken a significant hit. This deviation didn&#8217;t last for too long, though, as the metric returned to values above 1.0 as the rally resumed. Historically, the transition line between these two zones, that is, the 1.0 level, has had an interesting relationship with the price. During bearish trends, this line has proved to be a resistance point for the coin, while in bullish trends, it has often acted as support. Related Reading: Bitcoin Whales Show Most Active Hour In 3 Months As BTC Breaks $30,000 Recently, as Bitcoin had been struggling, the SOPR had observed a slight drop under the 1.0 level again, although the deviation was pretty small when compared to the instance in March. As it has happened many times in the past, it would appear that the 1.0 retest has provided a bounce to BTC this time as well, as the cryptocurrency has rallied towards the $30,000 mark. The Bitcoin SOPR has surged above 1.0 with this rebound, implying that the investors are now once again harvesting a large amount of profits. BTC Price At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading around $30,100, up 17% in the last week. BTC has slowed down since the sharp jump &#124; Source: BTCUSD on TradingView Featured image from Kanchanara on Unsplash.com, charts from TradingView.com, Glassnode.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On-chain data shows the Bitcoin Spent Output Profit Ratio (SOPR) has bounced back into the profit zone with the latest rally above $30,000.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin SOPR Has Successfully Retested 1.0 Support Line</h2>
<p>According to data from the on-chain analytics firm <a href="https://twitter.com/glassnode/status/1671893319654461444" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Glassnode</a>, investors are now selling their coins at a profit. The &#8220;<a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-decision-point-asopr-retests-crucial-level/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">SOPR</a>&#8221; is an indicator that tells us whether profit-taking or loss-taking is dominant in the Bitcoin market currently.</p>
<p>When the value of this metric is greater than 1.0, it means that the profits being realized by the investors are higher than the losses currently. On the other hand, the values of the indicator under this mark suggest the market as a whole is moving/selling coins at a loss.</p>
<p>The SOPR being exactly equal to 1.0 naturally suggests that the average investor is just breaking even on their selling at the moment, as the total amount of profits being harvested in the market is equal to the losses.</p>
<p>Now, here is a chart that shows the trend in the Bitcoin SOPR over the past year:</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone aligncenter" src="https://pbs.twimg.com/media/FzPAlJhaMAYOoT5?format=jpg&amp;name=4096x4096" alt="Bitcoin SOPR" width="4053" height="2334"/></p>

<p>Note that the version of the SOPR being used here is the &#8220;entity-adjusted&#8221; one, meaning that it only takes into account the transactions made between separate entities on the network and not all individual wallets.</p>

<p>An &#8220;entity&#8221; here refers to a single address or a collection of addresses that Glassnode has determined to belong to the same investor. As transfers where a holder moves coins to a different wallet of theirs aren&#8217;t actually sales at all, they aren&#8217;t relevant to the SOPR, and so, removing them from the data makes the indicator more accurate.</p>
<p>As you can see in the above graph, the entity-adjusted SOPR has been mostly at values above 1.0 during the last few months, a trend that makes sense as the asset has observed a rally in this period, which is bound to have put investors into notable profits.</p>
<p>Back in March, however, the indicator had deviated away from this profit-taking trend, as the Bitcoin price had taken a <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-retests-20000-violent-selloff/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">significant hit</a>. This deviation didn&#8217;t last for too long, though, as the metric returned to values above 1.0 as the rally resumed.</p>
<p>Historically, the transition line between these two zones, that is, the 1.0 level, has had an interesting relationship with the price. During bearish trends, this line has proved to be a resistance point for the coin, while in bullish trends, it has often acted as support.</p>

<p>Recently, as Bitcoin had been struggling, the SOPR had observed a slight drop under the 1.0 level again, although the deviation was pretty small when compared to the instance in March.</p>
<p>As it has happened many times in the past, it would appear that the 1.0 retest has provided a bounce to BTC this time as well, as the cryptocurrency has <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-bulls-gear-up-to-test-31000-resistance-as-market-optimism-grows/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">rallied towards the $30,000 mark</a>.</p>
<p>The Bitcoin SOPR has surged above 1.0 with this rebound, implying that the investors are now once again harvesting a large amount of profits.</p>
<h2>BTC Price</h2>
<p>At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading around $30,100, up 17% in the last week.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium aligncenter" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/KSKD1KQX/" alt="Bitcoin Price Chart" width="1534" height="911"/></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/kanchanara-9pCV2MB65y8-unsplash-3-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>MATIC Price Recovery Hits Roadblock, When Will Bulls Break Through?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/matic/matic-price-recovery-hits-roadblock-when-will-bulls-break-through/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[anushsamal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 18:00:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[MATIC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MATICUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[maticusdt]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Polygon]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=539397</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The MATIC price recovery has faced a hurdle in recent trading sessions, despite its impressive rebound after surpassing the $0.50 level. Although the altcoin experienced a notable 18% appreciation on the weekly chart, it lost 3% of its market value within the past 24 hours. The overall sentiment remains bearish as demand and accumulation for MATIC have remained low. While buying strength attempted to recover, it has not fully aligned with investor expectations. To reignite demand in the market, the altcoin must overcome immediate resistance levels. Surpassing these resistance levels will be key for the altcoin to rally and overcome significant barriers. The decline in MATIC market capitalization indicates a decrease in buying strength. Related Reading: Breaking Through This Ceiling Will Propel XRP By Another 12% MATIC Price Analysis: One-Day Chart At the time of writing, MATIC was valued at $0.66. The coin faced resistance at $0.68, but surpassing this level could potentially drive the price toward $0.73. With further potential MATIC may reach $0.77. However, breaching the $0.73 resistance is expected to be challenging for MATIC. Conversely, if buyers fail to emerge in the upcoming trading sessions, the coin may continue to decline. MATIC may move towards its local support level of $0.59, and with a further push downward, the altcoin may trade near $0.57. The recent session&#8217;s trading volume for MATIC also decreased, indicating that sellers had control over the price. This joins in to paint a very bearish outlook for the coin. Technical Analysis Despite a slight recovery in buying strength, the altcoin&#8217;s uptick may not be sustained unless it moves above the $0.68 level. The Relative Strength Index (RSI) experienced a marginal increase but remained below the half-line, indicating a prevailing dominance of selling pressure. Additionally, the asset&#8217;s price fell below the 20-Simple Moving Average (SMA) line, reflecting weak demand and suggesting that sellers are currently driving the market&#8217;s price momentum. Positive signs are, however, emerging for MATIC on its daily chart, indicating a potential bullish trend. The formation of buy signals suggests an increase in buying interest, but for this trend to be sustained, continued growth in demand is necessary. The Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD), which tracks price momentum and reversals, has shown green histograms tied to buy signals on the chart. However, the Chaikin Money Flow indicator remains below the half-line, indicating a lower inflow of capital compared to the outflow. Related Reading: Bitcoin Investor Sentiment Suggests BTC Rally Is Far From Over With consistent growth in demand though, even if by slow buildup, the altcoin has the potential to overcome immediate hurdles and achieve further gains. However, if the price remains at its current level, there is a possibility of another dip. Featured Image From UnSplash, Charts From TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The MATIC price recovery has faced a hurdle in recent trading sessions, despite its impressive rebound after surpassing the $0.50 level. Although the altcoin experienced a notable 18% appreciation on the weekly chart, it lost 3% of its market value within the past 24 hours.</p>
<p>The overall sentiment remains bearish as demand and accumulation for MATIC have remained low. While buying strength attempted to recover, it has not fully aligned with investor expectations.</p>
<p>To reignite demand in the market, the altcoin must overcome immediate resistance levels. Surpassing these resistance levels will be key for the altcoin to rally and overcome significant barriers. The decline in MATIC market capitalization indicates a decrease in buying strength.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/breaking-through-this-ceiling-will-propel-xrp-by-another-12/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Breaking Through This Ceiling Will Propel XRP By Another 12%</a></p>
<h2>MATIC Price Analysis: One-Day Chart</h2>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-539400 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/MATICUSD_2023-06-23_18-23-28.png" alt="MATIC" width="1817" height="830" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/MATICUSD_2023-06-23_18-23-28.png 1817w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/MATICUSD_2023-06-23_18-23-28-460x210.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/MATICUSD_2023-06-23_18-23-28-860x393.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/MATICUSD_2023-06-23_18-23-28-768x351.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/MATICUSD_2023-06-23_18-23-28-1536x702.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/MATICUSD_2023-06-23_18-23-28-750x343.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/MATICUSD_2023-06-23_18-23-28-1140x521.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1817px) 100vw, 1817px"/>
<p>At the time of writing, MATIC was valued at $0.66. The coin faced resistance at $0.68, but surpassing this level could potentially drive the price toward $0.73. With further potential MATIC may reach $0.77. However, breaching the $0.73 resistance is expected to be challenging for MATIC.</p>
<p>Conversely, if buyers fail to emerge in the upcoming trading sessions, the coin may continue to decline. MATIC may move towards its local support level of $0.59, and with a further push downward, the altcoin may trade near $0.57.</p>
<p>The recent session&#8217;s trading volume for MATIC also decreased, indicating that sellers had control over the price. This joins in to paint a very bearish outlook for the coin.</p>
<h2>Technical Analysis</h2>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-539402 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/MATICUSD_2023-06-23_18-24-23.png" alt="MATIC" width="1817" height="743" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/MATICUSD_2023-06-23_18-24-23.png 1817w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/MATICUSD_2023-06-23_18-24-23-460x188.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/MATICUSD_2023-06-23_18-24-23-860x352.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/MATICUSD_2023-06-23_18-24-23-768x314.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/MATICUSD_2023-06-23_18-24-23-1536x628.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/MATICUSD_2023-06-23_18-24-23-750x307.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/MATICUSD_2023-06-23_18-24-23-1140x466.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1817px) 100vw, 1817px"/>
<p>Despite a slight recovery in buying strength, the altcoin&#8217;s uptick may not be sustained unless it moves above the $0.68 level. The Relative Strength Index (RSI) experienced a marginal increase but remained below the half-line, indicating a prevailing dominance of selling pressure.</p>
<p>Additionally, the asset&#8217;s price fell below the 20-Simple Moving Average (SMA) line, reflecting weak demand and suggesting that sellers are currently driving the market&#8217;s price momentum.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-539406 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/MATICUSD_2023-06-23_18-24-53.png" alt="MATIC" width="1817" height="743" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/MATICUSD_2023-06-23_18-24-53.png 1817w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/MATICUSD_2023-06-23_18-24-53-460x188.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/MATICUSD_2023-06-23_18-24-53-860x352.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/MATICUSD_2023-06-23_18-24-53-768x314.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/MATICUSD_2023-06-23_18-24-53-1536x628.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/MATICUSD_2023-06-23_18-24-53-750x307.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/MATICUSD_2023-06-23_18-24-53-1140x466.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1817px) 100vw, 1817px"/>
<p>Positive signs are, however, emerging for MATIC on its daily chart, indicating a potential bullish trend. The formation of buy signals suggests an increase in buying interest, but for this trend to be sustained, continued growth in demand is necessary.</p>
<p>The Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD), which tracks price momentum and reversals, has shown green histograms tied to buy signals on the chart. However, the Chaikin Money Flow indicator remains below the half-line, indicating a lower inflow of capital compared to the outflow.</p>

<p>With consistent growth in demand though, even if by slow buildup, the altcoin has the potential to overcome immediate hurdles and achieve further gains. However, if the price remains at its current level, there is a possibility of another dip.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/what_is_polygon_matic-460x259.png" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>FLOKI Soars 26% In A Single Week, Shares 2023 Roadmap Update</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/altcoin/floki-soars-26-a-week-shares-2023-roadmap-update/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Opeyemi Sule]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 17:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FLOKI]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Floki Inu]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=539362</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Floki Inu (FLOKI), the popular meme coin, has been on a steady rise in the past few days both in price performance and general adoption. Exactly a week ago, crypto giant Binance added the cryptocurrency to the Metaverse and Gaming sections on its exchange.  After a slow start, the price of FLOKI seems to be finally leveraging the positive sentiment surrounding it. FLOKI Surges 26% In 7 Days &#8211; Price Action FLOKI has registered a significant 25.9% price rise in the past seven days, having broken out of the consolidation zone earlier this week. The price of Floki Inu started moving sideways after falling almost vertically on June 10, losing more than 20% of its value in a single day. Related Reading: Floki Inu Dull, Motionless Following Binance Metaverse Integration – Here’s Why It appears that the token might be gaining some momentum at the moment, albeit with only a 1% price increase in the last 24 hours. FLOKI is currently being held at a key resistance and would need to breach this threshold if it is to continue on its upward trajectory. FLOKIUSD trading at $0.0000261117 &#124; Source: FLOKIUSD chart from TradingView Moreover, it is worth noting that the daily Relative Strength Index, an indicator that tracks the balance between buying and selling pressure, has barely crossed the 50 mark. This indicates that a bullish run is still uncertain. As of this writing, Floki Inu changes hands for $0.00002687, with a 24-hour trading volume of more than $78.4 million. According to data from CoinGecko, the coin is currently 52% away from its 2023 high reached on February 17. FLOKI INU Shares 2023 Roadmap Update  On June 22, 2023, Floki Inu’s official Twitter account released a tweet giving an update on the ecosystem’s 2023 roadmap. It is a summary of some of the projects their developers have in the pipeline. The first item on the roadmap update is a major upgrade for the FlokiFi Locker, a protocol for securing digital assets, such as Liquidity Pool (LP) tokens, NFTs, and fungible assets. This advancement, which is being touted as FlokiFi’s biggest upgrade yet, will integrate native payments, burn mechanisms, a referral program, and other functionalities. Source: Floki Inu Furthermore, the tweet mentioned a “major DeFi lending and borrowing integration”, which will allow users to collateralize their FLOKI tokens to borrow other cryptocurrencies from “the biggest lending protocol on the BNB chain”. Meanwhile, a staking program is being tested at the moment and will launch as soon as internal checks are over. Related Reading: PEPE Leapfrogs With 72% Rally – What’s Behind The Surprise Vigor? A new and improved FlokiFi design is also in the works. Other projects mentioned in the 2023 roadmap update include Project TL and Valhalla. All of these developments are expected to occur by the end of 2023. Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Floki Inu (FLOKI), the popular meme coin, has been on a steady rise in the past few days both in price performance and general adoption. Exactly a week ago, crypto giant Binance added the cryptocurrency to the Metaverse and Gaming sections on its exchange. </p>
<p>After a slow start, the price of FLOKI seems to be finally leveraging the positive sentiment surrounding it.</p>
<h2>FLOKI Surges 26% In 7 Days &#8211; Price Action</h2>
<p>FLOKI has registered a significant 25.9% price rise in the past seven days, having broken out of the consolidation zone earlier this week. The price of Floki Inu started moving sideways after falling almost vertically on June 10, losing more than 20% of its value in a single day.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/floki-inu-dull-and-motionless-following-binance-metaverse-integration-heres-why/amp/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Floki Inu Dull, Motionless Following Binance Metaverse Integration – Here’s Why</a></p>
<p>It appears that the token might be gaining some momentum at the moment, albeit with only a 1% price increase in the last 24 hours. FLOKI is currently being held at a key resistance and would need to breach this threshold if it is to continue on its upward trajectory.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.tradingview.com/x/rOZ2KvV9/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/GEwVreup/" alt="FLOKI" width="1013" height="601"/></a></p>

<p>Moreover, it is worth noting that the daily Relative Strength Index, an indicator that tracks the balance between buying and selling pressure, has barely crossed the 50 mark. This indicates that a bullish run is still uncertain.</p>
<p>As of this writing, Floki Inu changes hands for $0.00002687, with a 24-hour trading volume of more than $78.4 million. According to <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/floki" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">data from CoinGecko</a>, the coin is currently 52% away from its 2023 high reached on February 17.</p>
<h2>FLOKI INU Shares 2023 Roadmap Update </h2>
<p>On June 22, 2023, Floki Inu’s official Twitter account released a <a href="https://twitter.com/realflokiinu/status/1671864786764668928?s=46&amp;t=ywn4FpkMT2vhon1Gt2XeXQ" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">tweet</a> giving an update on the ecosystem’s 2023 roadmap. It is a summary of some of the projects their developers have in the pipeline.</p>
<p>The first item on the roadmap update is a major upgrade for the FlokiFi Locker, a protocol for securing digital assets, such as Liquidity Pool (LP) tokens, NFTs, and fungible assets. This advancement, which is being touted as FlokiFi’s biggest upgrade yet, will integrate native payments, burn mechanisms, a referral program, and other functionalities.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium wp-image-539377 aligncenter" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/photo_2023-06-23_12-55-07-460x460.jpg" alt="FLOKI" width="460" height="460" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/photo_2023-06-23_12-55-07-460x460.jpg 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/photo_2023-06-23_12-55-07-858x860.jpg 858w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/photo_2023-06-23_12-55-07-200x200.jpg 200w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/photo_2023-06-23_12-55-07-768x770.jpg 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/photo_2023-06-23_12-55-07-42x42.jpg 42w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/photo_2023-06-23_12-55-07-75x75.jpg 75w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/photo_2023-06-23_12-55-07-350x350.jpg 350w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/photo_2023-06-23_12-55-07-750x752.jpg 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/photo_2023-06-23_12-55-07-1140x1143.jpg 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/photo_2023-06-23_12-55-07.jpg 1277w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px"/></p>

<p>Furthermore, the tweet mentioned a “major DeFi lending and borrowing integration”, which will allow users to collateralize their FLOKI tokens to borrow other cryptocurrencies from “the biggest lending protocol on the BNB chain”. Meanwhile, a staking program is being tested at the moment and will launch as soon as internal checks are over.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/pepe-bulls-run-wild-with-72-rally/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">PEPE Leapfrogs With 72% Rally – What’s Behind The Surprise Vigor?</a></p>
<p>A new and improved FlokiFi design is also in the works. Other projects mentioned in the 2023 roadmap update include Project TL and Valhalla. All of these developments are expected to occur by the end of 2023.</p>



]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/iStock-1015828796-1536x878-1-460x263.jpg" width="460" height="263" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Unstoppable Rise: Price Breaks Through $31,000 Setting New Annual High</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/breaking-news-ticker/bitcoin-unstoppable-rise-price-breaks-through-31000-setting-new-annual-high/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 16:30:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Breaking News Ticker]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=539453</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC), the largest cryptocurrency in the market, is continuing its unstoppable uptrend. After consolidating for a short period between $29,900 and $30,300, BTC has marked a new annual high and breached the $31,000 mark, which it had not surpassed since June 2022.  As of this writing, the leading cryptocurrency in the market is trading at $31,300, representing a surge of over 4% in the last 24 hours. Related Reading: Ethereum Bullsh Signal: Supply On Exchanges Continues To Hit New All-Time Lows This recent price increase is a positive development for Bitcoin, demonstrating the resilience and potential for continued growth and adoption in the cryptocurrency market. The consolidation period that preceded this new high indicates that investors were likely accumulating BTC in anticipation of a breakout.  Could Bitcoin Reach $35,000 Soon? There&#8217;s good news for Bitcoin bulls, as the cryptocurrency has broken its nearest resistance level at $31,000 and aims to reach $31,500. If Bitcoin can break this last bear threshold, the road to $35,000 may be served on a silver platter for the bulls.  Additionally, the recent news of Blackrock&#8217;s Bitcoin spot ETF and major Wall Street giants expressing interest in investing in Bitcoin may further fuel investor sentiment and propel Bitcoin&#8217;s bull run. However, Bitcoin must hold its current price level to prevent this price action from being just a short squeeze followed by a further pullback. If the current price level is sustained, it could provide a solid foundation for continued growth and upward momentum. As the chart above indicates, Bitcoin’s ADX (Average Directional Index) is currently peaking upwards, signifying the current trend&#8217;s strength. The ADX is a technical indicator commonly used to quantify the strength of a trend in the financial markets. The ADX calculation is based on a moving average of the price range expansion over a given period. It measures the degree to which a market is trending, and it provides traders with a way to identify the strength of a trend and determine whether it is worth trading. When the ADX rises, the trend gains strength, while a falling ADX indicates that the trend is losing momentum. A high ADX reading suggests a strong trend is in place, while a low ADX reading suggests that the market is in a range-bound or choppy state. Related Reading: Stacks (STX) Succumbs To Market Correction, Slides By 10% In The Last Day Bitcoin&#8217;s ongoing uptrend shows no signs of slowing down, and the cryptocurrency is gaining momentum, causing concern for bears. However, the influx of new investors entering the BTC market may increase its volatility, posing the risk of liquidating late long positions that could impede Bitcoin&#8217;s bullish movement. Overall, Bitcoin&#8217;s recent performance is a trend to watch in the coming weeks and months, as it will likely have a significant impact on the broader cryptocurrency market and may attract increased attention from investors, regulators, and the public. Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin (BTC), the largest cryptocurrency in the market, is continuing its unstoppable uptrend. After consolidating for a short period between $29,900 and $30,300, BTC has marked a new annual high and breached the $31,000 mark, which it had not surpassed since June 2022. </p>
<p>As of this writing, the leading cryptocurrency in the market is trading at $31,300, representing a surge of over 4% in the last 24 hours.</p>

<p>This recent price increase is a positive development for Bitcoin, demonstrating the resilience and potential for continued growth and adoption in the cryptocurrency market. The consolidation period that preceded this new high indicates that investors were likely accumulating BTC in anticipation of a breakout. </p>
<h2>Could Bitcoin Reach $35,000 Soon?</h2>
<p>There&#8217;s good news for Bitcoin bulls, as the cryptocurrency has broken its nearest resistance level at $31,000 and aims to reach $31,500. If Bitcoin can break this last bear threshold, the road to $35,000 may be served on a silver platter for the bulls. </p>
<p>Additionally, the recent news of Blackrock&#8217;s Bitcoin spot ETF and major Wall Street giants expressing interest in investing in Bitcoin may further fuel investor sentiment and propel Bitcoin&#8217;s bull run.</p>
<p>However, Bitcoin must hold its current price level to prevent this price action from being just a short squeeze followed by a further pullback. If the current price level is sustained, it could provide a solid foundation for continued growth and upward momentum.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/Q7v6cZXV/" alt="Bitcoin " width="1814" height="858"/>
<p>As the chart above indicates, Bitcoin’s ADX (Average Directional Index) is currently peaking upwards, signifying the current trend&#8217;s strength. The ADX is a technical indicator commonly used to quantify the strength of a trend in the financial markets.</p>
<p>The ADX calculation is based on a moving average of the price range expansion over a given period. It measures the degree to which a market is trending, and it provides traders with a way to identify the strength of a trend and determine whether it is worth trading.</p>
<p>When the ADX rises, the trend gains strength, while a falling ADX indicates that the trend is losing momentum. A high ADX reading suggests a strong trend is in place, while a low ADX reading suggests that the market is in a range-bound or choppy state.</p>

<p>Bitcoin&#8217;s ongoing uptrend shows no signs of slowing down, and the cryptocurrency is gaining momentum, causing concern for bears. However, the influx of new investors entering the BTC market may increase its volatility, posing the risk of liquidating late long positions that could impede Bitcoin&#8217;s bullish movement.</p>
<p>Overall, Bitcoin&#8217;s recent performance is a trend to watch in the coming weeks and months, as it will likely have a significant impact on the broader cryptocurrency market and may attract increased attention from investors, regulators, and the public.</p>
<p>Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/iStock-157559643-1-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
