<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
>

<channel>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.newsbtc.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<description>Bitcoin &#38; cryptocurrency news today, price &#38; technical analysis</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 03:51:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Ethereum Price Trims Gains and Could Revisit Key Range Support</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-trims-gains-1790/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 03:51:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=534750</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Ethereum price failed to surpass $1,880 and declined against the US Dollar. ETH is struggling and might continue lower toward the $1,790 support. Ethereum is currently moving lower from the $1,880 resistance zone. The price is trading below $1,830 and the 100-hourly Simple Moving Average. There is a connecting bearish trend line forming with resistance near $1,840 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD (data feed via Kraken). The pair could accelerate lower toward the $1,790 and $1,780 levels. Ethereum Price Fails Again Ethereum’s price attempted a fresh increase above the $1,850 resistance zone. However, ETH bears remained active near the $1,880 level and the price started another decline, similar to Bitcoin. The price declined from the $1,873 high and traded below the $1,850 support. There was a clear move below the 50% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $1,792 swing low to the $1,873 high. Ether price is now trading below $1,830 and the 100-hourly Simple Moving Average. There is also a connecting bearish trend line forming with resistance near $1,840 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD. Immediate resistance is near the $1,830 zone and the 100-hourly Simple Moving Average. Source: ETHUSD on TradingView.com The first major resistance is near the $1,840 level and the trend line. A close above the $1,840 resistance could send Ether toward $1,880. The next resistance sits near $1,920, above which Ethereum could rise toward $2,000. Any more gains above the $2,000 resistance zone could start a steady increase toward the $2,120 resistance. More Losses in ETH? If Ethereum fails to clear the $1,840 resistance, it could continue to move down. Initial support on the downside is near the $1,810 level and the 76.4% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $1,792 swing low to the $1,873 high. The next major support is near the $1,790 zone. The main support sits at $1,770. If there is a close below the $1,770 support, the price could gain bearish momentum. In the stated case, the price might drop toward the $1,720 support zone. Any more losses may perhaps spark a move toward the $1,650 support zone in the coming sessions. Technical Indicators Hourly MACD – The MACD for ETH/USD is gaining momentum in the bearish zone. Hourly RSI &#8211; The RSI for ETH/USD is below the 50 level. Major Support Level – $1,775 Major Resistance Level – $1,840]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>Ethereum price failed to surpass $1,880 and declined against the US Dollar. ETH is struggling and might continue lower toward the $1,790 support.</em></p>
<ul>
<li>Ethereum is currently moving lower from the $1,880 resistance zone.</li>
<li>The price is trading below $1,830 and the 100-hourly Simple Moving Average.</li>
<li>There is a connecting bearish trend line forming with resistance near $1,840 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD (data feed via Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could accelerate lower toward the $1,790 and $1,780 levels.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Ethereum Price Fails Again</h2>
<p>Ethereum’s price attempted a fresh increase above the $1,850 resistance zone. However, ETH bears remained active near the $1,880 level and the price started another decline, similar to <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-fails-again-27500/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Bitcoin</a>.</p>
<p>The price declined from the $1,873 high and traded below the $1,850 support. There was a clear move below the 50% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $1,792 swing low to the $1,873 high. Ether price is now trading below $1,830 and the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-breakout-1880/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">100-hourly Simple Moving Average</a>.</p>
<p>There is also a connecting bearish trend line forming with resistance near $1,840 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD. Immediate resistance is near the $1,830 zone and the 100-hourly Simple Moving Average.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-534751" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ethereum-15.png" alt="Ethereum Price" width="1834" height="845" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ethereum-15.png 1834w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ethereum-15-460x212.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ethereum-15-860x396.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ethereum-15-768x354.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ethereum-15-1536x708.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ethereum-15-750x346.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ethereum-15-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1834px) 100vw, 1834px"/></p>
<p>Source: <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/ETHUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">ETHUSD on TradingView.com</a></p>
<p>The first major resistance is near the $1,840 level and the trend line. A close above the $1,840 resistance could send Ether toward $1,880. The next resistance sits near $1,920, above which Ethereum could rise toward $2,000. Any more gains above the $2,000 resistance zone could start a steady increase toward the $2,120 resistance.</p>
<h2>More Losses in ETH?</h2>
<p>If Ethereum fails to clear the $1,840 resistance, it could continue to move down. Initial support on the downside is near the $1,810 level and the 76.4% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $1,792 swing low to the $1,873 high.</p>
<p>The next major support is near the $1,790 zone. The main support sits at $1,770. If there is a close below the $1,770 support, the price could gain bearish momentum. In the stated case, the price might drop toward the $1,720 support zone. Any more losses may perhaps spark a move toward the $1,650 support zone in the coming sessions.</p>
<p>Technical Indicators</p>
<p>Hourly MACD<strong> – </strong>The MACD for ETH/USD is gaining momentum in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>Hourly RSI<strong> &#8211; </strong>The RSI for ETH/USD is below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Level – $1,775</p>
<p>Major Resistance Level – $1,840</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/iStock-1353098829-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Price Fails Again But This Support Could Spark Fresh Increase</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-fails-again-27500/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 03:12:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xbtusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=534744</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin price is struggling to clear the $27,500 resistance. BTC could attempt another increase if it stays above the $27,000 support. Bitcoin is still struggling to gain pace above the $27,400 and $27,500 levels. The price is trading above $27,000 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average. There was a break above a major bearish trend line with resistance near $27,140 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Kraken). The pair could start a fresh increase if it stays above the $27,000 pivot level. Bitcoin Price Revisits Support Bitcoin price started a decent increase from the $26,550 zone. BTC was able to clear the $26,850 and $27,000 resistance levels. It also sparked some positive moves in Ethereum. During the increase, there was a break above a major bearish trend line with resistance near $27,140 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair. The pair spiked above the $27,400 resistance but there was no upside continuation. A high is formed near $27,511 and the price is now moving lower. There was a move below the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $26,536 swing low to the $27,511 high. Bitcoin price is now trading above $27,000 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average. It is also testing the broken trend line at $27,150. Immediate resistance on the upside is near the $27,280 level. The next major resistance is near the $27,400 level. The main resistance is still near $27,500. A close above the $27,500 resistance zone might send the price toward the $28,200 resistance zone. Source: BTCUSD on TradingView.com The next key resistance is near $28,500, above which the price might start a strong increase toward the $29,200 resistance. Any more gains might send the price toward the $30,000 level. Fresh Decline in BTC? If Bitcoin’s price fails to clear the $27,500 resistance, it could start another decline. Immediate support on the downside is near the $27,000 level and the 100 hourly Simple moving average. The 50% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $26,536 swing low to the $27,511 high is also near $27,000. The next major support is near the $26,850 zone, below which the price might revisit the $26,550 support. Any more losses might take Bitcoin toward the $26,000 level in the near term. Technical indicators: Hourly MACD – The MACD is now losing pace in the bullish zone. Hourly RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BTC/USD is now near the 50 level. Major Support Levels – $27,000, followed by $26,550. Major Resistance Levels – $27,280, $27,400, and $27,500.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>Bitcoin price is struggling to clear the $27,500 resistance. BTC could attempt another increase if it stays above the $27,000 support.</em></p>
<ul>
<li>Bitcoin is still struggling to gain pace above the $27,400 and $27,500 levels.</li>
<li>The price is trading above $27,000 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average.</li>
<li>There was a break above a major bearish trend line with resistance near $27,140 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could start a fresh increase if it stays above the $27,000 pivot level.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Bitcoin Price Revisits Support</h2>
<p>Bitcoin price started a <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-increase-27550/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">decent increase</a> from the $26,550 zone. BTC was able to clear the $26,850 and $27,000 resistance levels. It also sparked some positive moves in Ethereum.</p>
<p>During the increase, there was a break above a major bearish trend line with resistance near $27,140 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair. The pair spiked above the $27,400 resistance but there was no upside continuation. A high is formed near $27,511 and the price is now moving lower.</p>
<p>There was a move below the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $26,536 swing low to the $27,511 high. Bitcoin price is now trading above $27,000 and the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-holds-support-26550/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">100 hourly Simple moving average</a>. It is also testing the broken trend line at $27,150.</p>
<p>Immediate resistance on the upside is near the $27,280 level. The next major resistance is near the $27,400 level. The main resistance is still near $27,500. A close above the $27,500 resistance zone might send the price toward the $28,200 resistance zone.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-534745" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-17.png" alt="Bitcoin Price" width="1834" height="845" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-17.png 1834w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-17-460x212.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-17-860x396.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-17-768x354.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-17-1536x708.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-17-750x346.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-17-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1834px) 100vw, 1834px"/></p>
<p>Source: <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BTCUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">BTCUSD on TradingView.com</a></p>
<p>The next key resistance is near $28,500, above which the price might start a strong increase toward the $29,200 resistance. Any more gains might send the price toward the $30,000 level.</p>
<h2>Fresh Decline in BTC?</h2>
<p>If Bitcoin’s price fails to clear the $27,500 resistance, it could start another decline. Immediate support on the downside is near the $27,000 level and the 100 hourly Simple moving average.</p>
<p>The 50% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $26,536 swing low to the $27,511 high is also near $27,000. The next major support is near the $26,850 zone, below which the price might revisit the $26,550 support. Any more losses might take Bitcoin toward the $26,000 level in the near term.</p>
<p>Technical indicators:</p>
<p>Hourly MACD – The MACD is now losing pace in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>Hourly RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BTC/USD is now near the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Levels – $27,000, followed by $26,550.</p>
<p>Major Resistance Levels – $27,280, $27,400, and $27,500.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/Depositphotos_78872860_s-2019-1-460x293.jpg" width="460" height="293" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fantom (FTM) Secret Weapon: Could This Project Be The Next Big Thing In Crypto?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/fantom/fantom-ftm-secret-weapon-could-this-project-be-the-next-big-thing-in-crypto/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 21:00:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Fantom]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fantom]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantom (FTM)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTMUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=534736</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Fantom (FTM) is a blockchain project that has gained attention in the crypto space for its unique features and potential. Despite a recent dip in key metrics such as Total Value Locked (TVL), the project has something special that many believe is worth attention. Related Reading: Avalanche Breaks $14 Price Level, Yet Remains Hinged On Crucial Resistance Is Fantom Poised To Disrupt The Crypto World? One of the most important metrics for any blockchain project is TVL, which represents the amount of money invested or held in the network. According to the data researcher for Dune Analytics under the pseudonym “OxFinish”, for Fantom, TVL saw a massive uptrend in the autumn of 2021 during the second Bitcoin run to an all-time high (ATH) but has since fallen to its lowest point in almost two years, currently sitting at approximately $292 million. Interestingly, the TVL correlates perfectly with Stablecoin Market Capitalization, the easiest thing to bridge between blockchains, as seen in the chart above.  Moreover, according to Ox, FTM’s price is highly correlated with active users, as evidenced by the recent mini &#8220;Altcoin Season&#8221; surges in network activity when the price increases. Social dominance and USD transaction volume have also fallen, indicating a complex interdependence of key metrics within the ecosystem. The Rising Star Of Fantom&#8217;s DeFi Ecosystem Despite the above, Fantom has a vibrant ecosystem of projects building on it, with one decentralized exchange (DEX) standing out as the backbone of the network: SpookySwap. SpookySwap currently has over 22% of TVL dominance, with only GMX on Arb having a slightly higher percentage at approximately 24%. At one point, the TVL of SpookySwap was higher than the TVL of Avalanche. As an automated market maker (AMM), SpookySwap enables users to trade any ERC20 token on the Fantom network without needing an order book. Instead, the platform uses complex algorithms to determine the price of tokens based on supply and demand. This approach makes it easy for users to trade tokens quickly and efficiently while ensuring that prices remain stable. Furthermore, SpookySwap offers a range of features and benefits that make it attractive to users. It leverages the high speed and low transaction fees of the Fantom network to provide a seamless and efficient trading experience for users. Additionally, it offers a range of advanced features such as limit orders, liquidity provision incentives, and a range of trading pairs. Despite the departure of Andre Cronje, the Fantom creator, the Fantom ecosystem continues to grow and innovate, with SpookySwap leading the way. However, the rise of different Layer 2 (L2) solutions in the crypto space provides comparable benefits to Fantom, making attracting and retaining users more challenging. Related Reading: Is Cardano Poised for A Price Surge? A Look At Its Tight Consolidation However, according to Ox, Looking at the metrics and recent innovations, there is still plenty of potential for Fantom to rise in the next bull market. Although, it will require the project to continue to innovate and stay ahead of the curve to stand out in an increasingly crowded marketplace. Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com ]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Fantom (FTM) is a blockchain project that has gained attention in the crypto space for its unique features and potential. Despite a recent dip in key metrics such as Total Value Locked (TVL), the project has something special that many believe is worth attention.</p>

<h2><b>Is Fantom Poised To Disrupt The Crypto World?</b></h2>
<p>One of the most important metrics for any blockchain project is TVL, which represents the amount of money invested or held in the network. <a href="https://twitter.com/0xFinish/status/1660705432330190848?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">According </a>to the data researcher for Dune Analytics under the pseudonym “OxFinish”, for Fantom, TVL saw a massive uptrend in the autumn of 2021 during the second Bitcoin run to an all-time high (ATH) but has since fallen to its lowest point in almost two years, currently sitting at approximately $292 million.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large wp-image-534738" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/FwwC0JwacAE-7by-860x306.jpg" alt="Fantom" width="860" height="306" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/FwwC0JwacAE-7by-860x306.jpg 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/FwwC0JwacAE-7by-460x164.jpg 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/FwwC0JwacAE-7by-768x273.jpg 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/FwwC0JwacAE-7by-1536x547.jpg 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/FwwC0JwacAE-7by-2048x729.jpg 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/FwwC0JwacAE-7by-750x267.jpg 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/FwwC0JwacAE-7by-1140x406.jpg 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/>
<p>Interestingly, the TVL correlates perfectly with Stablecoin Market Capitalization, the easiest thing to bridge between blockchains, as seen in the chart above. </p>
<p>Moreover, according to Ox, FTM’s price is highly correlated with active users, as evidenced by the recent mini &#8220;Altcoin Season&#8221; surges in network activity when the price increases. Social dominance and USD transaction volume have also fallen, indicating a complex interdependence of key metrics within the ecosystem.</p>
<b>The Rising Star Of Fantom&#8217;s DeFi Ecosystem</b>
<p>Despite the above, Fantom has a vibrant ecosystem of projects building on it, with one decentralized exchange (DEX) standing out as the backbone of the network: SpookySwap. SpookySwap currently has over 22% of TVL dominance, with only GMX on Arb having a slightly higher percentage at approximately 24%. At one point, the TVL of SpookySwap was higher than the TVL of Avalanche.</p>
<p>As an automated market maker (AMM), SpookySwap enables users to trade any ERC20 token on the Fantom network without needing an order book. Instead, the platform uses complex algorithms to determine the price of tokens based on supply and demand. This approach makes it easy for users to trade tokens quickly and efficiently while ensuring that prices remain stable.</p>
<p>Furthermore, SpookySwap offers a range of features and benefits that make it attractive to users. It leverages the high speed and low transaction fees of the Fantom network to provide a seamless and efficient trading experience for users. Additionally, it offers a range of advanced features such as limit orders, liquidity provision incentives, and a range of trading pairs.</p>
<p>Despite the departure of Andre Cronje, the Fantom creator, the Fantom ecosystem continues to grow and innovate, with SpookySwap leading the way. However, the rise of different Layer 2 (L2) solutions in the crypto space provides comparable benefits to Fantom, making attracting and retaining users more challenging.</p>

<p>However, according to Ox, Looking at the metrics and recent innovations, there is still plenty of potential for Fantom to rise in the next bull market. Although, it will require the project to continue to innovate and stay ahead of the curve to stand out in an increasingly crowded marketplace.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/sjKJzcI5/" alt="Fantom" width="1814" height="858"/>
<p>Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/tandem-x-visuals-5Tu5NRhXric-unsplash-361x460.jpg" width="361" height="460" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Avalanche Breaks $14 Price Level, Yet Remains Hinged On Crucial Resistance</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/avalanche/avalanche-breaks-14-price-level-yet-remains-hinged-on-crucial-resistance/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[anushsamal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 20:00:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Avalanche]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AVAX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AVAXUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AVAXUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=534724</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[During the recent weekend, Avalanche (AVAX) witnessed a significant surge in selling pressure, resulting in a bearish breakout. As a consequence, the price of AVAX dipped close to a multi-month low of $13.8. However, on the 24-hour chart, the altcoin displayed a slight upward movement, showing some appreciation. On the other hand, the weekly chart depicted lacklustre performance for AVAX. The technical outlook for Avalanche remains bearish, as both demand and accumulation levels have remained low. The price action of AVAX has been influenced by the undecided nature of Bitcoin (BTC), which recently re-entered the $27,000 range. Related Reading: XRP Aims For $0.50, Hinges on Breaking Through This Price Level This has caused other altcoins, including AVAX, to exhibit uncertainty on their respective charts. The overhead resistance level for AVAX holds significant importance, as surpassing this level could trigger a rally for the altcoin. Conversely, if sellers exert further pressure, AVAX may break its consolidation and fall below its immediate support level, thereby strengthening the bearish sentiment. Broader market strength is necessary for AVAX to reclaim its overhead ceiling. The decline in the market capitalization of AVAX indicates a decrease in buying strength at the current time. Avalanche Price Analysis: One-Day Chart At the time of writing, AVAX was priced at $14.70. It is currently trading in close proximity to its immediate resistance level of $15. A breakthrough above $15 has the potential to propel the altcoin towards $15.80 and ultimately $16. The involvement of buyers in the market is crucial to generate demand and facilitate AVAX&#8217;s upward price movement. On the downside, if AVAX fails to sustain its current price level, it may find support at $14 before potentially trading below that level. The recent trading session showed a decline in the amount of AVAX traded, indicating the dominance of sellers in the market. Technical Analysis Throughout May and part of April, AVAX experienced consistently low buying pressure, reflecting a limited demand for the altcoin. The Relative Strength Index (RSI) was below the 40-mark, indicating that sellers had a greater presence than buyers at the time of writing. Furthermore, the AVAX price fell below the 20-Simple Moving Average (20-SMA) line, demonstrating that sellers were the driving force behind the price momentum in the market. A significant move above the $15 price level would help AVAX surpass the 20-SMA line, suggesting a potential shift in momentum and possibly attracting more buying interest. Although AVAX recently returned to the $14 price zone, there are no clear indications of buying strength according to technical indicators. The Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD), provides insights into price momentum. It formed only one green histogram, which does not necessarily signify buy signals at this point. Related Reading: Litecoin Surpasses $90, But This Level Remains Crucial For The Altcoin The Bollinger Bands, which reflect price volatility and fluctuations, have remained wide, indicating that the possibility of price fluctuations cannot be ruled out in the upcoming trading sessions. Featured Image From UnSplash, Charts From TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[









<p>During the recent weekend, Avalanche (AVAX) witnessed a significant surge in selling pressure, resulting in a bearish breakout. As a consequence, the price of AVAX dipped close to a multi-month low of $13.8.</p>
<p>However, on the 24-hour chart, the altcoin displayed a slight upward movement, showing some appreciation. On the other hand, the weekly chart depicted lacklustre performance for AVAX.</p>
<p>The technical outlook for Avalanche remains bearish, as both demand and accumulation levels have remained low. The price action of AVAX has been influenced by the undecided nature of Bitcoin (BTC), which recently re-entered the $27,000 range.</p>

<p>This has caused other altcoins, including AVAX, to exhibit uncertainty on their respective charts. The overhead resistance level for AVAX holds significant importance, as surpassing this level could trigger a rally for the altcoin.</p>
<p>Conversely, if sellers exert further pressure, AVAX may break its consolidation and fall below its immediate support level, thereby strengthening the bearish sentiment.</p>
<p>Broader market strength is necessary for AVAX to reclaim its overhead ceiling. The decline in the market capitalization of AVAX indicates a decrease in buying strength at the current time.</p>
<h2>Avalanche Price Analysis: One-Day Chart</h2>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-534729 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/AVAXUSD_2023-05-24_00-06-23.png" alt="Avalanche" width="1817" height="743" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/AVAXUSD_2023-05-24_00-06-23.png 1817w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/AVAXUSD_2023-05-24_00-06-23-460x188.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/AVAXUSD_2023-05-24_00-06-23-860x352.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/AVAXUSD_2023-05-24_00-06-23-768x314.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/AVAXUSD_2023-05-24_00-06-23-1536x628.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/AVAXUSD_2023-05-24_00-06-23-750x307.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/AVAXUSD_2023-05-24_00-06-23-1140x466.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1817px) 100vw, 1817px"/>














<p>At the time of writing, AVAX was priced at $14.70. It is currently trading in close proximity to its immediate resistance level of $15. A breakthrough above $15 has the potential to propel the altcoin towards $15.80 and ultimately $16.</p>
<p>The involvement of buyers in the market is crucial to generate demand and facilitate AVAX&#8217;s upward price movement. On the downside, if AVAX fails to sustain its current price level, it may find support at $14 before potentially trading below that level. The recent trading session showed a decline in the amount of AVAX traded, indicating the dominance of sellers in the market.</p>
<h2>Technical Analysis</h2>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-534731 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/AVAXUSD_2023-05-24_00-10-45.png" alt="Avalanche" width="1817" height="743" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/AVAXUSD_2023-05-24_00-10-45.png 1817w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/AVAXUSD_2023-05-24_00-10-45-460x188.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/AVAXUSD_2023-05-24_00-10-45-860x352.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/AVAXUSD_2023-05-24_00-10-45-768x314.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/AVAXUSD_2023-05-24_00-10-45-1536x628.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/AVAXUSD_2023-05-24_00-10-45-750x307.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/AVAXUSD_2023-05-24_00-10-45-1140x466.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1817px) 100vw, 1817px"/>






<p>Throughout May and part of April, AVAX experienced consistently low buying pressure, reflecting a limited demand for the altcoin. The Relative Strength Index (RSI) was below the 40-mark, indicating that sellers had a greater presence than buyers at the time of writing.</p>
<p>Furthermore, the AVAX price fell below the 20-Simple Moving Average (20-SMA) line, demonstrating that sellers were the driving force behind the price momentum in the market.</p>
<p>A significant move above the $15 price level would help AVAX surpass the 20-SMA line, suggesting a potential shift in momentum and possibly attracting more buying interest.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-534732 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/AVAXUSD_2023-05-24_00-17-15.png" alt="Avalanche" width="1817" height="743" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/AVAXUSD_2023-05-24_00-17-15.png 1817w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/AVAXUSD_2023-05-24_00-17-15-460x188.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/AVAXUSD_2023-05-24_00-17-15-860x352.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/AVAXUSD_2023-05-24_00-17-15-768x314.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/AVAXUSD_2023-05-24_00-17-15-1536x628.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/AVAXUSD_2023-05-24_00-17-15-750x307.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/AVAXUSD_2023-05-24_00-17-15-1140x466.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1817px) 100vw, 1817px"/>
<p>Although AVAX recently returned to the $14 price zone, there are no clear indications of buying strength according to technical indicators.</p>
<p>The Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD), provides insights into price momentum. It formed only one green histogram, which does not necessarily signify buy signals at this point.</p>

<p>The Bollinger Bands, which reflect price volatility and fluctuations, have remained wide, indicating that the possibility of price fluctuations cannot be ruled out in the upcoming trading sessions.</p>











]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/shubham-s-web3-KmofXXd8cus-unsplash-460x259.jpg" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Is Cardano Poised for A Price Surge? A Look At Its Tight Consolidation</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/cardano/consolidation-of-cardano-price-tightens-when-to-expect-a-breakout/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[anushsamal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 19:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cardano]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[adausd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADAUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=534677</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Cardano price has consistently remained below the $0.38 zone for the past two weeks, indicating a strong presence of sellers in the market. Despite attempts by buyers to regain strength over the past month, their efforts have been feeble, unable to overcome the bearish sentiment. This persistent bearish price action has resulted in a notable breach of the crucial demand and support zone between $0.37 and $0.38.Over the last 24 hours, ADA has made a slight upward movement on its chart, but the progress has been limited. Similarly, on the weekly chart, ADA has not shown significant advancement. The technical outlook for ADA reflects bearish pressure and a lack of buying strength. Related Reading: Litecoin Surpasses $90, But This Level Remains Crucial For The Altcoin Demand and accumulation remain low as a consequence. Many altcoins have indicated minor price increases, with Bitcoin returning to the $27,000 price. ADA must maintain trading above its immediate support line to break out of its current narrow trading range. If ADA surpasses its overhead resistance, the altcoin could potentially experience a substantial rally in the following trading sessions. The decrease in ADA&#8217;s market capitalization suggests an increase in sellers outweighing buyers in the market. Cardano Price Analysis: One-Day Chart At the time of writing, the price of ADA was $0.37. The altcoin is currently experiencing tight price movement within a highly constricted range. Additionally, ADA is approaching a critical support level at $0.36. On the upside, there is an overhead resistance at $0.38.  A successful breakthrough above this level could drive ADA&#8217;s price toward $0.40. However, if the price fails to sustain its current level, it could drop below $0.36. This would lead to a trading range near $0.34. The recent session showed a decrease in the amount of ADA traded, indicating a slow buying strength. Technical Analysis Throughout this month, ADA has struggled to generate substantial buying strength due to low demand. The Relative Strength Index (RSI) currently sits below the midpoint, signaling that selling pressure has prevailed in the market. Furthermore, the altcoin price has recently dropped below the 20-Simple Moving Average (20-SMA) line, indicating that sellers have been driving the price momentum. For ADA to experience a breakout, the price would need to attempt to rise above the 20-SMA line. While other technical indicators may not signal ADA bullishness, the one-day chart reveals some buy signals. The Moving Average Divergence Convergence (MACD) has shown green histograms, indicating a positive price action and momentum. Related Reading: Litecoin’s MVRV Has Surged, Why This Is Bearish However, the Parabolic SAR is yet to reflect this positive price action, as the dotted lines remain positioned above the price candlesticks. Featured Image From UnSplash, Charts From TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Cardano price has consistently remained below the $0.38 zone for the past two weeks, indicating a strong presence of sellers in the market. Despite attempts by buyers to regain strength over the past month, their efforts have been feeble, unable to overcome the bearish sentiment.</p>
<p>This persistent bearish price action has resulted in a notable breach of the crucial demand and support zone between $0.37 and $0.38.Over the last 24 hours, ADA has made a slight upward movement on its chart, but the progress has been limited.</p>
<p>Similarly, on the weekly chart, ADA has not shown significant advancement. The technical outlook for ADA reflects bearish pressure and a lack of buying strength.</p>

<p>Demand and accumulation remain low as a consequence. Many altcoins have indicated minor price increases, with Bitcoin returning to the $27,000 price. ADA must maintain trading above its immediate support line to break out of its current narrow trading range.</p>
<p>If ADA surpasses its overhead resistance, the altcoin could potentially experience a substantial rally in the following trading sessions. The decrease in ADA&#8217;s market capitalization suggests an increase in sellers outweighing buyers in the market.</p>
<h2>Cardano Price Analysis: One-Day Chart</h2>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-534678 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ADAUSD_2023-05-23_21-01-31.png" alt="Cardano" width="1816" height="830" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ADAUSD_2023-05-23_21-01-31.png 1816w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ADAUSD_2023-05-23_21-01-31-460x210.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ADAUSD_2023-05-23_21-01-31-860x393.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ADAUSD_2023-05-23_21-01-31-768x351.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ADAUSD_2023-05-23_21-01-31-1536x702.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ADAUSD_2023-05-23_21-01-31-750x343.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ADAUSD_2023-05-23_21-01-31-1140x521.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1816px) 100vw, 1816px"/>
<p>At the time of writing, the price of ADA was $0.37. The altcoin is currently experiencing tight price movement within a highly constricted range. Additionally, ADA is approaching a critical support level at $0.36.</p>
<p>On the upside, there is an overhead resistance at $0.38.  A successful breakthrough above this level could drive ADA&#8217;s price toward $0.40.</p>
<p>However, if the price fails to sustain its current level, it could drop below $0.36. This would lead to a trading range near $0.34. The recent session showed a decrease in the amount of ADA traded, indicating a slow buying strength.</p>
<h2>Technical Analysis</h2>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-534679 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ADAUSD_2023-05-23_21-02-01.png" alt="Cardano" width="1816" height="743" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ADAUSD_2023-05-23_21-02-01.png 1816w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ADAUSD_2023-05-23_21-02-01-460x188.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ADAUSD_2023-05-23_21-02-01-860x352.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ADAUSD_2023-05-23_21-02-01-768x314.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ADAUSD_2023-05-23_21-02-01-1536x628.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ADAUSD_2023-05-23_21-02-01-750x307.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ADAUSD_2023-05-23_21-02-01-1140x466.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1816px) 100vw, 1816px"/>
<p>Throughout this month, ADA has struggled to generate substantial buying strength due to low demand. The Relative Strength Index (RSI) currently sits below the midpoint, signaling that selling pressure has prevailed in the market.</p>
<p>Furthermore, the altcoin price has recently dropped below the 20-Simple Moving Average (20-SMA) line, indicating that sellers have been driving the price momentum. For ADA to experience a breakout, the price would need to attempt to rise above the 20-SMA line.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-534680 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ADAUSD_2023-05-23_21-02-26.png" alt="Cardano" width="1816" height="743" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ADAUSD_2023-05-23_21-02-26.png 1816w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ADAUSD_2023-05-23_21-02-26-460x188.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ADAUSD_2023-05-23_21-02-26-860x352.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ADAUSD_2023-05-23_21-02-26-768x314.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ADAUSD_2023-05-23_21-02-26-1536x628.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ADAUSD_2023-05-23_21-02-26-750x307.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ADAUSD_2023-05-23_21-02-26-1140x466.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1816px) 100vw, 1816px"/>
<p>While other technical indicators may not signal ADA bullishness, the one-day chart reveals some buy signals. The Moving Average Divergence Convergence (MACD) has shown green histograms, indicating a positive price action and momentum.</p>

<p>However, the Parabolic SAR is yet to reflect this positive price action, as the dotted lines remain positioned above the price candlesticks.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/traxer-fL_7F7rwvS0-unsplash-3-460x306.jpg" width="460" height="306" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Santiment Explains How Bitcoin Investor Mentality Influenced Recent Price Action</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/santiment-explains-bitcoin-investor-mentality-price/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hououin Kyouma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 18:00:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin sentiment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Santiment]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=534610</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Santiment has broken down how the recent action in the Bitcoin price may have been affected by the prevailing sentiment in the market. Trends In Bitcoin Social Volume May Have Influenced The Price Recently As the on-chain analytics firm Santiment explained, BTC generally moves in the direction the crowd isn&#8217;t expecting. The relevant indicator is the &#8220;social volume,&#8221; which measures the total number of social media text documents discussing a given term or topic. The social media text documents here refer to a collection of social media posts collected by Santiment that have been sourced from various popular platforms like Twitter, Reddit, and Telegram. This indicator only checks whether a text document in this collection mentions the term at least once; posts with more than one mention of the topic are still given the same weight as a document that only does it once. To use this indicator for pinpointing discussions related to market sentiment, the analytics firm first found the social volume of Bitcoin and cryptocurrency in general. Then it filtered it for some specific terms that refer to the investors&#8217; mentality. Related Reading: How Does Current Bitcoin Rally Compare With Historical Ones? Here is a chart that shows the trend in the Bitcoin social volume for negative and positive sentiments over the last week: The trend in the two market sentiments for BTC over the last few days &#124; Source: Santiment on Twitter The terms used here to separate the discussions related to positive sentiment are buy, bullish, and bottom. Similarly, sell, top, and bearish are some of the terms that have been used for finding negative talks. In the graph, Santiment has marked the pattern that the social volumes of these sentiments followed during the past couple of days. On the 21st, following the decline in the asset&#8217;s price, the indicator&#8217;s value for the negative mentality observed a large spike. Related Reading: Former MicroStrategy CEO Says Bitcoin Rally Just Getting Started This means that social media discussions had gotten quite bearish when this price drop occurred. However, once this mentality shift happened, the cryptocurrency saw a local bottom formation. Over the next day, the coin saw some rise and broke back above the $27,000 level. While this rise was taking place, the sentiment again turned positive. By the time the price went above $27,000, though, the social volume of the greedy sentiment had reached pretty high values. Like when the negative sentiment had become overwhelming, the bottom had formed, a top occurred following this positive mentality spike. Historically, the Bitcoin market has generally always moved like this; whenever the sentiment becomes too unbalanced towards any particular side, the market tends to show moves opposite to this sentiment held by the majority. BTC Price Since Santiment posted its analysis and the flush in the positive sentiment, Bitcoin has again risen above the $27,000 mark. When writing, the coin is floating around $27,300, up 1% in the past week. BTC has observed an uplift during the past day &#124; Source: BTCUSD on TradingView Featured image from Thought Catalog on Unsplash.com, charts from TradingView.com, Santiment.net]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Santiment has broken down how the recent action in the Bitcoin price may have been affected by the prevailing sentiment in the market.</p>
<h2>Trends In Bitcoin Social Volume May Have Influenced The Price Recently</h2>
<p>As the on-chain analytics firm Santiment <a href="https://twitter.com/santimentfeed/status/1660676280407461889" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">explained</a>, BTC generally moves in the direction the crowd isn&#8217;t expecting. The relevant indicator is the &#8220;<a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/altcoin/internet-computer-icp-social-dominance-hits-top-in/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">social volume</a>,&#8221; which measures the total number of social media text documents discussing a given term or topic.</p>
<p>The social media text documents here refer to a collection of social media posts collected by Santiment that have been sourced from various popular platforms like Twitter, Reddit, and Telegram.</p>
<p>This indicator only checks whether a text document in this collection mentions the term at least once; posts with more than one mention of the topic are still given the same weight as a document that only does it once.</p>
<p>To use this indicator for pinpointing discussions related to <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-rebounds-27100-spike-in-bearish-sentiment/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">market sentiment</a>, the analytics firm first found the social volume of Bitcoin and cryptocurrency in general. Then it filtered it for some specific terms that refer to the investors&#8217; mentality.</p>

<p>Here is a chart that shows the trend in the Bitcoin social volume for negative and positive sentiments over the last week:</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone aligncenter" src="https://pbs.twimg.com/media/Fwvnq1-aIAY08d-?format=jpg&amp;name=4096x4096" alt="Bitcoin Social Volume" width="2816" height="1821"/></p>

<p>The terms used here to separate the discussions related to positive sentiment are buy, bullish, and bottom. Similarly, sell, top, and bearish are some of the terms that have been used for finding negative talks.</p>
<p>In the graph, Santiment has marked the pattern that the social volumes of these sentiments followed during the past couple of days. On the 21st, following the decline in the asset&#8217;s price, the indicator&#8217;s value for the negative mentality observed a large spike.</p>

<p>This means that social media discussions had gotten quite bearish when this price drop occurred. However, once this mentality shift happened, the cryptocurrency saw a local bottom formation.</p>
<p>Over the next day, the coin saw some rise and broke back above the $27,000 level. While this rise was taking place, the sentiment again turned positive.</p>
<p>By the time the price went above $27,000, though, the social volume of the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-investors-remain-greedy-despite-low-momentum-why/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">greedy</a> sentiment had reached pretty high values. Like when the negative sentiment had become overwhelming, the bottom had formed, a top occurred following this positive mentality spike.</p>
<p>Historically, the Bitcoin market has generally always moved like this; whenever the sentiment becomes too unbalanced towards any particular side, the market tends to show moves opposite to this sentiment held by the majority.</p>
<h2>BTC Price</h2>
<p>Since Santiment posted its analysis and the flush in the positive sentiment, Bitcoin has again risen above the $27,000 mark. When writing, the coin is floating around $27,300, up 1% in the past week.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium aligncenter" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/UvTBEcGp/" alt="Bitcoin Price Chart" width="1533" height="911"/></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/thought-catalog-I0TDRP0fj6Y-unsplash-460x345.jpg" width="460" height="345" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Here&#8217;s What The Metrics Say About Polygon&#8217;s (MATIC) Uptrend</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/matic-analysis/heres-what-the-metrics-say-about-polygons-matic-uptrend/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Eli Dambel]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 17:00:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[MATIC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[maticusdt]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Polygon]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=534670</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The price of Polygon (MATIC) and other notable crypto assets has been experiencing some volatility recently. The fluctuations present in the MATIC market can present traders and investors with profit-earning opportunities. Within the last seven days, the price has witnessed a significant increase of 3.25%, indicating strong momentum from the bulls. Analyzing The Polygon (MATIC) Bullish Momentum Polygon is the scaling solution for Ethereum and the network’s increasing adoption could increase its price as the demand grows over the long term. As of today, the price of Polygon (MATIC) is at $0.8861 in the last 24 hours, representing an increase of 1.64%. This price movement suggests a positive market sentiment and a growing demand for the asset. It also indicates that the bulls are in control of the market. Also, MATIC Dominance &#38; Social sentiments are above 50%, indicating neutral pressure.  Since both the market dominance and social sentiment are rising above 50%, it implies that MATIC has a positive sentiment among investors in the crypto market. The MATIC/USDT pair has formed a bullish flag pattern, suggesting a potential trend reversal and an end-to-downtrend movement. The breakout that occurred in the bullish flag pattern may be considered a confirmation of a trend reversal for traders and investors. As the asset trades between its support and resistance levels of $0.8399 &#38; $0.9086, traders are watching these levels closely for possible breakouts. Related Reading: Shibarium Developers Say Each On-Chain Transaction Will Burn SHIB Tokens If MATIC breaks above the significant resistance level, it will trigger a bullish trend. The next support and resistance level will be at $0.5142 and 1.5799.  However, if MATIC breaks below the $0.7536 support level, it could signal a bearish trend, and traders may look for selling opportunities.  MATIC bears are currently trying to build momentum, but the bulls strongly hold their respective positions. This indicates a consolidation phase and a potential long-term uptrend if the bulls maintain this strong momentum. MATIC Technical Analysis Using Indicators The token has been on a downtrend since April 18, when the bears took control of the market. But recently, the asset has been showing signs of a potential trend reversal. The Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD) trades above the signal line. This indicates a potential bullish trend in the market. Also, the histogram is above zero with strong green, confirming the bullish sentiment. Related Reading: Shiba Inu All Green Today – What’s The Energy Behind The Glow? Additionally, the Relative Strength Index (RSI) momentum oscillator has a reading of 42.35, suggesting neutral pressure from the bulls and bears.  The market trades below the 50-Day and 200-Day Simple Moving Averages (SMA). This suggests a possible bearish movement. Nevertheless, the token bounced off a critical support level of $0.88 and may attempt to continue the bullish move. Featured image from Pixabay and chart from Tradingview]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The price of Polygon (MATIC) and other notable crypto assets has been experiencing some volatility recently. The fluctuations present in the MATIC market can present traders and investors with profit-earning opportunities.</p>
<p>Within the last seven days, the price has witnessed a significant increase of <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/polygon/" rel="nofollow">3.25%,</a> indicating strong momentum from the bulls.</p>
<h2>Analyzing The Polygon (MATIC) Bullish Momentum</h2>
<p>Polygon is the scaling solution for Ethereum and the network’s increasing adoption could increase its price as the demand grows over the long term. As of today, the price of Polygon (MATIC) is at $0.8861 in the last 24 hours, representing an increase of 1.64%.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-534672 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/MATICUSDT_2023-05-23_19-28-43-860x471.png" alt="Polygon (MATIC) Price Enters An Upward Trend, What Do The Metrics Suggest?" width="860" height="471" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/MATICUSDT_2023-05-23_19-28-43-860x471.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/MATICUSDT_2023-05-23_19-28-43-460x252.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/MATICUSDT_2023-05-23_19-28-43-768x420.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/MATICUSDT_2023-05-23_19-28-43-750x411.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/MATICUSDT_2023-05-23_19-28-43-1140x624.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/MATICUSDT_2023-05-23_19-28-43.png 1529w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/>
<p>This price movement suggests a positive market sentiment and a growing demand for the asset. It also indicates that the bulls are in control of the market. Also, MATIC<a href="https://cfgi.io/polygon-fear-greed-index/" rel="nofollow"> Dominance &amp; Social sentiments </a>are above 50%, indicating neutral pressure. </p>
<p>Since both the market dominance and social sentiment are rising above 50%, it implies that MATIC has a positive sentiment among investors in the crypto market.</p>
<p>The MATIC/USDT pair has formed a bullish flag pattern, suggesting a potential trend reversal and an end-to-downtrend movement.</p>
<p>The breakout that occurred in the bullish flag pattern may be considered a confirmation of a trend reversal for traders and investors. As the asset trades between its support and resistance levels of $0.8399 &amp; $0.9086, traders are watching these levels closely for possible breakouts.</p>

<p>If MATIC breaks above the significant resistance level, it will trigger a bullish trend. The next support and resistance level will be at $0.5142 and 1.5799. </p>
<p>However, if MATIC breaks below the $0.7536 support level, it could signal a bearish trend, and traders may look for selling opportunities. </p>
<p>MATIC bears are currently trying to build momentum, but the bulls strongly hold their respective positions. This indicates a consolidation phase and a potential long-term uptrend if the bulls maintain this strong momentum.</p>
<h2>MATIC Technical Analysis Using Indicators</h2>
<p>The token has been on a downtrend since April 18, when the bears took control of the market. But recently, the asset has been showing signs of a potential trend reversal. </p>
<p>The Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD) trades above the signal line. This indicates a potential bullish trend in the market. Also, the histogram is above zero with strong green, confirming the bullish sentiment.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/shiba-inu-all-green-today/?swcfpc=1">Shiba Inu All Green Today – What’s The Energy Behind The Glow?</a></p>
<p>Additionally, the Relative Strength Index (RSI) momentum oscillator has a reading of 42.35, suggesting neutral pressure from the bulls and bears. </p>
<p>The market trades below the 50-Day and 200-Day Simple Moving Averages (SMA). This suggests a possible bearish movement. Nevertheless, the token bounced off a critical support level of $0.88 and may attempt to continue the bullish move.</p>
<p>Featured image from Pixabay and chart from Tradingview</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/polygon.jpeg-1-460x240.jpg" width="460" height="240" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>XRP Aims For $0.50, Hinges on Breaking Through This Price Level</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/xrp-aims-for-0-50-hinges-on-breaking-through-this-price-level/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[anushsamal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 16:00:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrp]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrpusdt]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=534501</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Despite the prevailing bearish sentiment in the market last week, Ripple (XRP) bulls showcased their resilience by securing gains. XRP stood out among the top 20 cryptocurrency assets, recording impressive weekly gains of over 8%. Although the daily chart displayed a relatively modest increase of more than 1%, it was enough to maintain the bullish momentum. The technical outlook for XRP revealed an improvement in buying strength, with demand and accumulation indicators reflecting a recovery on the daily chart. Related Reading: How Does Current Bitcoin Rally Compare With Historical Ones? However, the price movement of major altcoins remained uncertain as Bitcoin slipped back into the $26,000 price level. The future trajectory of XRP will depend on the performance of BTC in the upcoming trading sessions. Buyers will gain further strength if BTC exhibits improvement, leading to increased demand for XRP. Conversely, if demand fails to rise significantly, it could impede the growth of the XRP price. Another positive sign was the recovery of market capitalization, indicating increased demand and buying strength. XRP Price Analysis: One-Day Chart As of the time of writing, Ripple (XRP) was trading at $0.46. The altcoin demonstrated a significant breakthrough by surpassing the crucial resistance level of $0.44, increasing demand for the asset. Moving forward, the next obstacle for XRP lies at the overhead resistance of $0.48, which is expected to pose a tough challenge for the coin. However, if the altcoin manages to overcome this resistance level, it could potentially target the $0.50 mark. Conversely, a decline from the current price level would bring XRP down to $0.44, potentially even below the $0.42 price mark. The recent session witnessed a positive momentum for XRP, as indicated by the green volume bar of the altcoin traded. Technical Analysis Upon the price breakthrough above the $0.44 level, buyers swiftly entered the market, exhibiting a surge in demand for the altcoin. This heightened interest is further supported by the Relative Strength Index (RSI), which currently positions itself above the half-line, just below the 60-mark. This indicates that buying strength outweighs selling strength at the present moment, underlining the positive sentiment surrounding the altcoin. Furthermore, the asset&#8217;s price has risen above the 20-Simple Moving Average (SMA) line, suggesting that buyers were driving the price momentum in the market. The increase in demand for the altcoin is reflected in the buy signals observed on the one-day chart for XRP. The Awesome Oscillator determines price direction and momentum. It generated small green signals closely tied to buy signals for the altcoin. Related Reading: Shiba Inu Struggles To Initiate A Breakout: Will It Defy Resistance And Rebound? This suggests a positive price action for the coin, highlighting the potential for further upward movement. Additionally, the Bollinger Bands, which measure price volatility and potential fluctuations, maintained a wide range. However, the parallel alignment of the bands indicates that the altcoin may trade within a relatively narrow range in the upcoming trading sessions. Featured Image From iStock, Charts From TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Despite the prevailing bearish sentiment in the market last week, Ripple (XRP) bulls showcased their resilience by securing gains. XRP stood out among the top 20 cryptocurrency assets, recording impressive weekly gains of over 8%. Although the daily chart displayed a relatively modest increase of more than 1%, it was enough to maintain the bullish momentum.</p>
<p>The technical outlook for XRP revealed an improvement in buying strength, with demand and accumulation indicators reflecting a recovery on the daily chart.</p>

<p>However, the price movement of major altcoins remained uncertain as Bitcoin slipped back into the $26,000 price level. The future trajectory of XRP will depend on the performance of BTC in the upcoming trading sessions.</p>
<p>Buyers will gain further strength if BTC exhibits improvement, leading to increased demand for XRP. Conversely, if demand fails to rise significantly, it could impede the growth of the XRP price. Another positive sign was the recovery of market capitalization, indicating increased demand and buying strength.</p>
<h2>XRP Price Analysis: One-Day Chart</h2>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-534506 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSD_2023-05-23_00-46-51.png" alt="XRP" width="1816" height="743" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSD_2023-05-23_00-46-51.png 1816w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSD_2023-05-23_00-46-51-460x188.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSD_2023-05-23_00-46-51-860x352.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSD_2023-05-23_00-46-51-768x314.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSD_2023-05-23_00-46-51-1536x628.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSD_2023-05-23_00-46-51-750x307.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSD_2023-05-23_00-46-51-1140x466.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1816px) 100vw, 1816px"/>
<p>As of the time of writing, Ripple (XRP) was trading at $0.46. The altcoin demonstrated a significant breakthrough by surpassing the crucial resistance level of $0.44, increasing demand for the asset.</p>
<p>Moving forward, the next obstacle for XRP lies at the overhead resistance of $0.48, which is expected to pose a tough challenge for the coin. However, if the altcoin manages to overcome this resistance level, it could potentially target the $0.50 mark.</p>
<p>Conversely, a decline from the current price level would bring XRP down to $0.44, potentially even below the $0.42 price mark. The recent session witnessed a positive momentum for XRP, as indicated by the green volume bar of the altcoin traded.</p>
<h2>Technical Analysis</h2>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-534507 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSD_2023-05-23_00-47-19.png" alt="XRP" width="1816" height="743" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSD_2023-05-23_00-47-19.png 1816w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSD_2023-05-23_00-47-19-460x188.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSD_2023-05-23_00-47-19-860x352.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSD_2023-05-23_00-47-19-768x314.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSD_2023-05-23_00-47-19-1536x628.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSD_2023-05-23_00-47-19-750x307.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSD_2023-05-23_00-47-19-1140x466.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1816px) 100vw, 1816px"/>
<p>Upon the price breakthrough above the $0.44 level, buyers swiftly entered the market, exhibiting a surge in demand for the altcoin. This heightened interest is further supported by the Relative Strength Index (RSI), which currently positions itself above the half-line, just below the 60-mark.</p>
<p>This indicates that buying strength outweighs selling strength at the present moment, underlining the positive sentiment surrounding the altcoin.</p>
<p>Furthermore, the asset&#8217;s price has risen above the 20-Simple Moving Average (SMA) line, suggesting that buyers were driving the price momentum in the market.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-534508 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSD_2023-05-23_00-47-38.png" alt="XRP" width="1817" height="743" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSD_2023-05-23_00-47-38.png 1817w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSD_2023-05-23_00-47-38-460x188.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSD_2023-05-23_00-47-38-860x352.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSD_2023-05-23_00-47-38-768x314.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSD_2023-05-23_00-47-38-1536x628.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSD_2023-05-23_00-47-38-750x307.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSD_2023-05-23_00-47-38-1140x466.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1817px) 100vw, 1817px"/>
<p>The increase in demand for the altcoin is reflected in the buy signals observed on the one-day chart for XRP. The Awesome Oscillator determines price direction and momentum. It generated small green signals closely tied to buy signals for the altcoin.</p>

<p>This suggests a positive price action for the coin, highlighting the potential for further upward movement. Additionally, the Bollinger Bands, which measure price volatility and potential fluctuations, maintained a wide range. However, the parallel alignment of the bands indicates that the altcoin may trade within a relatively narrow range in the upcoming trading sessions.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/istockphoto-947893638-612x612-1-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Data Suggests Small Holders Will Drive Next Cardano (ADA) Rally</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/ada/data-suggests-small-holders-will-drive-next-cardano-ada-rally/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Best Owie]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 15:00:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[ADA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADA holders]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADA price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[adausd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADAUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=534648</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Over the course of 2023, the movement of Cardano (ADA) has been more on the bullish side. Despite the reversal over the last few weeks, the bullish momentum has not completely died out. However, what is most interesting about this trend is the fact that the smaller investors seem to be the major driver behind it, not the large whales. Cardano Small Investors Continue To Accumulate Through the course of 2023, the smaller Cardano investors have been at the forefront of the ADA accumulation. This is seen from January through to May where their collective holdings have continued to rise. These investors holding between 1,000-10,000 coins and 10,000-100,000 coins have steadily grown their holdings over the last six months. Related Reading: Meme Coin Season May Be Over As PEPE, SHIB, DOGE, Continue Decline Where the whales were skewed toward selling than buying, these retail investors were heavily on the buy side. As a result, their collective holdings have grown from around 17% of the total supply to over 18.1%. As a result, these smaller wallets holding between 1,000-100,000 coins now account for 6.29 billion out of the 34.79 billion total supply. Their accumulation trend also coincides with the rise in the price of ADA over this time which is illustrated in the chart below. There were dips in their holdings where there was presumably some profit-taking. However, the general trend continued toward the upside, bringing their holdings to new highs. Small ADA holders increase holdings in six months &#124; Source: Santiment During this time, the holdings of larger investors holding between 10,000,000-100,000,000 coins dropped drastically. This suggests that while the smaller holders were responsible for the price increase, larger holders were the culprits behind the price crash as their total holdings went from 12.1% of the total supply to 11.11% in April. What Will Trigger The Next ADA Rally? Currently, the price of ADA is still down, suggesting that investors are very wary about buying the token. However, if the accumulation trend among smaller wallets continues, there could be more upside to come. An added advantage of small wallets leading the accumulation trend is that it enables a broader distribution of the token, which helps to sustain bull rallies. Related Reading: Shiba Inu Falls Below Critical Support, Is It Time For You To Buy? ADA is still seeing significant resistance at the $0.38 level, but given that bears are still weak at this point, its inability to beat this resistance can be explained by the general low momentum in the market. When the price of Bitcoin picks up once more, $0.38 will be quickly surpassed with the next important level sitting at $0.4. At the time of writing, ADA is changing hands at a price of $0.37. It’s down 0.21% on the 24-hour chart but seeing gains of 1.73% on the weekly chart. ADA price trending at $0.37 &#124; Source: ADAUSD on TradingView.com Follow Best Owie on Twitter for market insights, updates, and the occasional funny tweet… Featured image from Guarda Wallet, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="p2">Over the course of 2023, the movement of Cardano (ADA) has been more on the bullish side. Despite the reversal over the last few weeks, the bullish momentum has not completely died out. However, what is most interesting about this trend is the fact that the smaller investors seem to be the major driver behind it, not the large whales.</p>
<h2 class="p2">Cardano Small Investors Continue To Accumulate</h2>
<p class="p2">Through the course of 2023, the smaller Cardano investors have been at the forefront of the ADA accumulation. This is seen from January through to May where their collective holdings have continued to rise. These investors holding between 1,000-10,000 coins and 10,000-100,000 coins have steadily grown their holdings over the last six months.</p>

<p class="p2">Where the whales were skewed toward selling than buying, these retail investors were heavily on the buy side. As a result, their collective holdings have grown from around 17% of the total supply to over 18.1%. As a result, these smaller wallets holding between 1,000-100,000 coins now account for 6.29 billion out of the 34.79 billion total supply.</p>
<p class="p2">Their accumulation trend also coincides with the rise in the price of ADA over this time which is illustrated in the chart below. There were dips in their holdings where there was presumably some profit-taking. However, the general trend continued toward the upside, bringing their holdings to new highs.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-534650 aligncenter" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Screenshot-2023-05-23-at-13.42.10-460x350.png" alt="Cardano (ADA) small holders" width="460" height="350" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Screenshot-2023-05-23-at-13.42.10-460x350.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Screenshot-2023-05-23-at-13.42.10-860x655.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Screenshot-2023-05-23-at-13.42.10-768x585.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Screenshot-2023-05-23-at-13.42.10-1536x1169.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Screenshot-2023-05-23-at-13.42.10-2048x1559.png 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Screenshot-2023-05-23-at-13.42.10-750x571.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Screenshot-2023-05-23-at-13.42.10-1140x868.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px"/></p>

<p class="p2">During this time, the holdings of larger investors holding between 10,000,000-100,000,000 coins dropped drastically. This suggests that while the smaller holders were responsible for the price increase, larger holders were the culprits behind the price crash as their total holdings went from 12.1% of the total supply to 11.11% in April.</p>
<h2 class="p2">What Will Trigger The Next ADA Rally?</h2>
<p class="p2">Currently, the price of ADA is still down, suggesting that investors are very wary about buying the token. However, if the accumulation trend among smaller wallets continues, there could be more upside to come. An added advantage of small wallets leading the accumulation trend is that it enables a broader distribution of the token, which helps to sustain bull rallies.</p>

<p class="p2">ADA is still seeing significant resistance at the $0.38 level, but given that bears are still weak at this point, its inability to beat this resistance can be explained by the general low momentum in the market. When the price of Bitcoin picks up once more, $0.38 will be quickly surpassed with the next important level sitting at $0.4.</p>
<p class="p2">At the time of writing, ADA is changing hands at a price of $0.37. It’s down 0.21% on the 24-hour chart but seeing gains of 1.73% on the weekly chart.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/d1YG7Vyq/" alt="Cardano (ADA) price chart from TradingView.com" width="2888" height="1724"/></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Cardano-ADA-2-460x293.png" width="460" height="293" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Avalanche (AVAX) Trading Volume Skyrockets Amid Sustained Price Growth</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/avalanche/avalanche-avax-trading-volume-skyrockets-amid-sustained-price-growth/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Eli Dambel]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 14:00:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Avalanche]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AVAXUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bears]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bulls]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=534634</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Avalanche (AVAX) is gaining today as it seeks to retain its gains in the last 24 hours. Its trading volume is up by over 18% today, possibly sustaining its price recovery attempt. Notably, AVAX entered the month of May with a bullish momentum trading at $16.66 on May 1, 2023. However, the bears have kept AVAX&#8217;s price at $14 since May 18.  It now approaches the $15 price level seeking to rediscover its positive price form. The increased trading volume today implies that more activities are ongoing on the network. This surging interest in the network might help AVAX sustain its uptrend.  A return to $21 remains likely for the asset in the long term. AVAX Price Moves AVAX is gaining today, forming a higher high on the daily chart. The bulls are intent on mounting a recovery rally. However, the bears are still active in the market. Related Reading: How Does Current Bitcoin Rally Compare With Historical Ones? Since AVAX still trades below its 50-day and 200-day Simple Moving Averages (SMA), the asset will likely see a further price decline in the short and long term. The SMA&#8217;s display sell signals prompting traders to take short positions in the market today. However, some indicators are pointing to a price recovery for AVAX soon. For instance, the Relative Strength Index (RSI) is 38.53 and close to the oversold region.  The RSI indicator mirrors the bearish trend that began on May 18, 2023, but the indicator is moving upwards, hinting at a potential trend reversal for the asset.   Although the AVAX&#8217;s Moving Average Convergence/Divergence (MACD) is just breaking above its signal line and showing convergence, its histogram bars display small green bars hinting at a potential trend reversal to the upside.  A close look at the chart structure shows that AVAX entered a downtrend on April 19, 2023. But it found support on May 22, sparking hope for a price recovery.  What&#8217;s Ahead For Avalanche? AVAX has found valuable support at the $14.29 price level, a pivot point for the asset. It is currently trading above its closest resistance level of $14.29. However, the bears are still active in the market, intent on keeping it below the next resistance level of $15.21. From historical price behavior, AVAX pivoted on the $14.29 support on March 11, 2023, rallying to $21.29 on April 18, with dips in between. It replayed the same action on May 22 and will likely rally again to the $21 price level in the longer time frame. Related Reading: Former MicroStrategy CEO Says Bitcoin Rally Just Getting Started Note that crypto assets are volatile and can deviate from historical price action. Therefore sound technical and fundamental analysis is essential for trading. Featured image from Pixabay and chart from Tradingview.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Avalanche (AVAX) is <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/avalanche/" rel="nofollow">gaining today</a> as it seeks to retain its gains in the last 24 hours. Its trading volume is up by over 18% today, possibly sustaining its price recovery attempt.</p>
<p>Notably, AVAX entered the month of May with a bullish momentum trading at $16.66 on May 1, 2023. However, the bears have kept AVAX&#8217;s price at $14 since May 18. </p>
<p>It now approaches the $15 price level seeking to rediscover its positive price form. The increased trading volume today implies that more activities are ongoing on the network.</p>
<p>This surging interest in the network might help AVAX sustain its uptrend.  A return to $21 remains likely for the asset in the long term.</p>
<h2>AVAX Price Moves</h2>
<p>AVAX is gaining today, forming a higher high on the daily chart. The bulls are intent on mounting a recovery rally. However, the bears are still active in the market.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/how-current-bitcoin-rally-compare-with-historical/">How Does Current Bitcoin Rally Compare With Historical Ones?</a></p>
<p>Since AVAX still trades below its 50-day and 200-day Simple Moving Averages (SMA), the asset will likely see a further price decline in the short and long term. The SMA&#8217;s display sell signals prompting traders to take short positions in the market today.</p>
<p>However, some indicators are pointing to a price recovery for AVAX soon. For instance, the Relative Strength Index (RSI) is 38.53 and close to the oversold region. </p>
<p>The RSI indicator mirrors the bearish trend that began on May 18, 2023, but the indicator is moving upwards, hinting at a potential trend reversal for the asset.  </p>
<p>Although the AVAX&#8217;s Moving Average Convergence/Divergence (MACD) is just breaking above its signal line and showing convergence, its histogram bars display small green bars hinting at a potential trend reversal to the upside. </p>
<p>A close look at the chart structure shows that AVAX entered a downtrend on April 19, 2023. But it found support on May 22, sparking hope for a price recovery. </p>
<h2>What&#8217;s Ahead For Avalanche?</h2>
<p>AVAX has found valuable support at the $14.29 price level, a pivot point for the asset. It is currently trading above its closest resistance level of $14.29. However, the bears are still active in the market, intent on keeping it below the next resistance level of $15.21.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-534643 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/AVAXUSDT_2023-05-23_17-28-16-860x471.png" alt="Avalanche (AVAX) Trading Volume Skyrockets Amid Sustained Price Growth" width="860" height="471" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/AVAXUSDT_2023-05-23_17-28-16-860x471.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/AVAXUSDT_2023-05-23_17-28-16-460x252.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/AVAXUSDT_2023-05-23_17-28-16-768x420.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/AVAXUSDT_2023-05-23_17-28-16-750x411.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/AVAXUSDT_2023-05-23_17-28-16-1140x624.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/AVAXUSDT_2023-05-23_17-28-16.png 1529w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/>
<p>From historical price behavior, AVAX pivoted on the $14.29 support on March 11, 2023, rallying to $21.29 on April 18, with dips in between. It replayed the same action on May 22 and will likely rally again to the $21 price level in the longer time frame.</p>

<p>Note that crypto assets are volatile and can deviate from historical price action. Therefore sound technical and fundamental analysis is essential for trading.</p>
<p>Featured image from Pixabay and chart from Tradingview.com</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/c5ee3a6ef69847dda30cdf3e0dfa123e-1-460x259.png" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
