<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	 xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" >

<channel>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://newsbtc.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://newsbtc.com</link>
	<description>Bitcoin &#38; cryptocurrency news today, price &#38; technical analysis</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 23:39:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<link>https://newsbtc.com</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>GMX Generates More Fees than BNB Smart Chain and Bitcoin</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/defi/gmx-fees-than-bnb-smart-chain-and-bitcoin/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dalmas Ngetich]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 23:39:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[DeFi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Avalanche]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BNB Smart Chain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[GMX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Uniswap]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=516816</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[GMX, the perpetual trading decentralized exchange (DEX) allowing up to 50X leverage, now generates more trading fees than the BNB Smart Chain (BSC) and Bitcoin. GMX Is The Third Most Active Platform According to statistics, GMX&#8217;s 1-day fee on January 19 was around $589,000, while BSC and Bitcoin on-chain fees, over the same period, stood at $524,232 and $328,935, respectively.  Ethereum and Uniswap are the only two major protocols more active than the perpetual trading decentralized exchange, per the above data. During this time, the total Gas fees accrued in Ethereum exceeded $5 million. In Uniswap, it was over $2.1 million, roughly 4x GMX&#8217;s and BSC&#8217;s daily fees. Related Reading: Binance USD (BUSD) Exchange Reserves Dry Up, Reason Behind Bitcoin’s Slowdown? GMX supports trading various coins, including BTC, ETH, and AVAX. As of writing, GMX had $96,802,651,673 in total trading volume with open interest, that is, the number of opened positions, long and short, of $207,102,720. Meanwhile, over 208,000 active traders were using the platform to trade on Arbitrum and Avalanche. GMX launched on Arbitrum and Avalanche, considering their scalability and low fees versus Ethereum. Arbitrum is Ethereum&#8217;s layer-2 platform permitting scalable and low-fee trading fees. On the other hand, Avalanche is scalable and boasts the fastest settlement time in crypto. By launching on these two platforms, GMX says it allows users to save on costs by entering and exiting positions with minimal spread and zero price impact.  Traders take the profits of selling positions in USDC and the quote token when they go long. GMX prices are based on Chainlink&#8217;s decentralized oracles to prevent price manipulations.   Trading Fees As A Measure Of Activity Trading fees generated by a dApp or on a blockchain are a crucial activity indicator. Despite the tendency of users to opt for protocols offering near-zero fees, the decentralized nature of blockchains means validators or entities securing core infrastructures must be compensated.  In decentralized finance dApps like Uniswap and GMX, trading fees generated from swapping activities are distributed to liquidity providers (LPs). There are also governance tokens that are distributed. Anyone can be an LP. Related Reading: How Uniswap Was Saved From Critical Vulnerability By This Security Firm In September 2020, Uniswap distributed UNI to users who had, in one way or another, used the protocol to swap tokens before the airdrop distributing date. Currently, UNI trades at $6.1. Interestingly for GMX, the 1-day trading fee of $589,000 posted on January 19 exceeds the total average amount accrued over the past trading week of $565,682. The same trend can be observed in the top-5 most active platforms. Making extensions on this could point to renewed interest from users and traders using the protocol in one way or another. In GMX, it could mean more traders are posting traders, aiming to clip the market and turn in a profit. Coincidentally, the upswing in trading fees is recorded when the cryptocurrency market appears to be bottoming up after losses. At least, this was the trend in 2022.  Featured image from GMX, charts from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>GMX, the perpetual trading decentralized exchange (DEX) allowing up to 50X leverage, now <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptofees.info/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">generates</a> more trading fees than the BNB Smart Chain (BSC) and Bitcoin.</p>
<h2>GMX Is The Third Most Active Platform</h2>
<p>According to statistics, GMX&#8217;s 1-day fee on January 19 was around $589,000, while BSC and Bitcoin on-chain fees, over the same period, stood at $524,232 and $328,935, respectively. </p>
<img class="wp-image-516818 size-full" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/GMX-Crypto-Fees.png" alt="GMX Crypto Fees" width="786" height="488" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/GMX-Crypto-Fees.png 786w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/GMX-Crypto-Fees-460x286.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/GMX-Crypto-Fees-768x477.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/GMX-Crypto-Fees-750x466.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 786px) 100vw, 786px" />
<p>Ethereum and Uniswap are the only two major protocols more active than the perpetual trading decentralized exchange, per the above data. During this time, the total Gas fees accrued in Ethereum exceeded $5 million. In Uniswap, it was over $2.1 million, roughly 4x GMX&#8217;s and BSC&#8217;s daily fees.</p>

<p>GMX supports trading various coins, including BTC, ETH, and AVAX. As of writing, GMX had $96,802,651,673 in total trading volume with open interest, that is, the number of opened positions, long and short, of $207,102,720. Meanwhile, over 208,000 active traders were using the platform to trade on Arbitrum and Avalanche. GMX launched on Arbitrum and <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/avalanche-makes-32-rally/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Avalanche</a>, considering their scalability and low fees versus Ethereum.
</p>
<p>Arbitrum is Ethereum&#8217;s layer-2 platform permitting scalable and low-fee trading fees. On the other hand, Avalanche is scalable and boasts the fastest settlement time in crypto. By launching on these two platforms, GMX says it allows users to save on costs by entering and exiting positions with minimal spread and zero price impact. </p>
<p>Traders take the profits of selling positions in USDC and the quote token when they go long. GMX prices are based on Chainlink&#8217;s decentralized oracles to prevent price manipulations.  </p>
<h2>Trading Fees As A Measure Of Activity</h2>
<p>Trading fees generated by a dApp or on a blockchain are a crucial activity indicator. Despite the tendency of users to opt for protocols offering near-zero fees, the decentralized nature of blockchains means validators or entities securing core infrastructures must be compensated. </p>
<p>In decentralized finance dApps like Uniswap and GMX, trading fees generated from swapping activities are distributed to liquidity providers (LPs). There are also governance tokens that are distributed. Anyone can be an LP.</p>

<p>In September 2020, Uniswap distributed UNI to users who had, in one way or another, used the protocol to swap tokens before the airdrop distributing date. Currently, UNI trades at $6.1.</p>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-516817 size-full" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/UNIUSDT.png" alt="Uniswap daily price" width="1270" height="498" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/UNIUSDT.png 1270w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/UNIUSDT-460x180.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/UNIUSDT-860x337.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/UNIUSDT-768x301.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/UNIUSDT-750x294.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/UNIUSDT-1140x447.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1270px) 100vw, 1270px" />
<p>Interestingly for GMX, the 1-day trading fee of $589,000 posted on January 19 exceeds the total average amount accrued over the past trading week of $565,682. The same trend can be observed in the top-5 most active platforms. Making extensions on this could point to renewed interest from users and traders using the protocol in one way or another.</p>
<p>In GMX, it could mean more traders are posting traders, aiming to clip the market and turn in a profit. Coincidentally, the upswing in trading fees is recorded when the cryptocurrency market appears to be bottoming up after losses. At least, this was the trend in 2022. </p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/GMX-460x259.png" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Scaramucci: FTX Cannot Be Saved, Sam Betrayed Me</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/scaramucci-ftx-cannot-be-saved-sam-betrayed-me/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dalmas Ngetich]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 22:00:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Scaramucci]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=516805</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Anthony Scaramucci, the founder of Skybridge Capital, thinks failed crypto exchange FTX cannot be saved following its bankruptcy filing.  Ex-FTX Boss&#8217; Betrayal In an exclusive interview while attending the World Economic Forum in Davos, Switzerland, the founder and American entrepreneur opined that there is no way the exchange could be saved.  Still, Scaramucci considers the founder of FTX, Sam Bankman-Fried, a friend who was given a seat at the table of “high-profile people.” The problem is he feels betrayed that Sam turned out to be “delusional” and allegedly a fraud. Whether Sam will end up in jail or not, he adds, is up to the jury and the presiding judge. FTX, at its peak, was among one of the largest cryptocurrency exchanges in the world, offering what was, at that time, thought to be a solid trading platform for hundreds of thousands, if not millions, of users.  Related Reading: 59% of Bitcoin Holders Are Sitting On Profits However, as the crypto market cratered and Bitcoin slid toward this week&#8217;s trade range of around $20k, cracks began to emerge in FTX. &#160; Eventually, an explosive piece revealing the misdoings of its founder, Sam Bankman-Fried, and several accounting errors in their finances broke the camel’s back. FTX halted customer withdrawals before news broke out that they were filing for Chapter 11 Bankruptcy protection in the United States. It later emerged that FTX and its trading wing, Alameda Research, had misappropriated billions of customer funds. Anthony Scaramucci: Skybridge Capital Is Patient Considering the evidence presented and claims from the restructuring officer in charge of FTX bankruptcy proceedings, Anthony Scaramucci said nothing is to be done. He divulged that his fund wasn&#8217;t spared by the crypto winter and the FTX contagion as market prices slumped, affecting their revenue. Their core fund, Anthony said, was down 30 percent in 2022. In January 2023, there were signs of recovery, and their core funds are up double digits. Scaramucci also confirmed that Skybridge Capital is “completed unleveraged” and owns its inventory.  Asked whether he lost money last year, he confirmed that his Bitcoin (BTC) is intact and didn’t lose any monies since he didn’t use leverage. Leverage is a trader borrows money to trade. The borrowed funds, together with the deposit, act as a margin allowing for higher profits. Still, there can be losses if a trader’s an incorrect prognosis. Traders can lose all their deposits if they use leverage and trade any other asset, including crypto.  Anthony revealed that though FTX finds itself in crisis and could dissolve, the exchange was one of the early investors of Skybridge Capital, buying 30% of the fund. As part of the deal, the fund bought 10 percent of FTX’s FTT token only to sell it for a loss of $9.5 million.  Related Reading: FTX’s FTT Token Spikes 43%, A Revival In The Works? Despite this, Antony said they are patient and waiting for “what the bankruptcy people say” so that they can buy back their shares. The fund, he explains, isn’t going to blame the disgraced founder of FTX for all woes in the crypto market or Skybridge Capital. Overall, he remains confident in crypto&#8217;s prospects. Featured image from Harvard Political Review, Charts from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Anthony Scaramucci, the founder of Skybridge Capital, thinks failed crypto exchange FTX cannot be saved following its bankruptcy filing. </p>
<h2>Ex-FTX Boss&#8217; Betrayal</h2>
<p>In an exclusive interview while attending the World Economic Forum in Davos, Switzerland, the founder and American entrepreneur <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://twitter.com/CoinDesk/status/1615755411021242368" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">opined</a> that there is no way the exchange could be saved. </p>
<p>Still, Scaramucci considers the founder of FTX, Sam Bankman-Fried, a friend who was given a seat at the table of “high-profile people.” The problem is he feels betrayed that Sam turned out to be “delusional” and allegedly a fraud.
</p>
<p>Whether Sam will end up in jail or not, he adds, is up to the jury and the presiding judge.</p>
<p><a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/solana-up-45-in-last-week/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">FTX</a>, at its peak, was among one of the largest cryptocurrency exchanges in the world, offering what was, at that time, thought to be a solid trading platform for hundreds of thousands, if not millions, of users. </p>

<p>However, as the crypto market <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-diamond-hands-dumped-84-5k-btc-ftx-collapse/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">cratered</a> and Bitcoin slid toward this week&#8217;s trade range of around $20k, cracks began to emerge in FTX.
</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-516811 size-full" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Screenshot273.png" alt="bitcoin daily chart" width="1287" height="529" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Screenshot273.png 1287w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Screenshot273-460x189.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Screenshot273-860x353.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Screenshot273-768x316.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Screenshot273-750x308.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Screenshot273-1140x469.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1287px) 100vw, 1287px" />
<p>Eventually, an explosive piece revealing the misdoings of its founder, Sam Bankman-Fried, and several accounting errors in their finances broke the camel’s back. FTX halted customer withdrawals before news broke out that they were filing for Chapter 11 Bankruptcy protection in the United States. It later emerged that FTX and its trading wing, Alameda Research, had misappropriated billions of customer funds.</p>
<h2>Anthony Scaramucci: Skybridge Capital Is Patient
</h2>
<p>Considering the evidence presented and claims from the restructuring officer in charge of FTX bankruptcy proceedings, Anthony Scaramucci said nothing is to be done. </p>
<p>He divulged that his fund wasn&#8217;t spared by the crypto winter and the FTX contagion as market prices slumped, affecting their revenue. Their core fund, Anthony said, was down 30 percent in 2022. In January 2023, there were signs of recovery, and their core funds are up double digits. Scaramucci also confirmed that Skybridge Capital is “completed unleveraged” and owns its inventory. </p>
<p>Asked whether he lost money last year, he <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/how-bitcoin-demonetizes-gold-skybridge-capitals-founder-makes-the-case/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">confirmed</a> that his Bitcoin (BTC) is intact and didn’t lose any monies since he didn’t use leverage. Leverage is a trader borrows money to trade. The borrowed funds, together with the deposit, act as a margin allowing for higher profits. Still, there can be losses if a trader’s an incorrect prognosis. Traders can lose all their deposits if they use leverage and trade any other asset, including crypto. </p>
<p>Anthony revealed that though FTX finds itself in crisis and could dissolve, the exchange was one of the early investors of Skybridge Capital, buying 30% of the fund. As part of the deal, the fund bought 10 percent of FTX’s FTT token only to sell it for a loss of $9.5 million. </p>

<p>Despite this, Antony said they are patient and waiting for “what the bankruptcy people say” so that they can buy back their shares. The fund, he explains, isn’t going to blame the disgraced founder of FTX for all woes in the crypto market or <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/skybridge-capital-applies-for-cryptocurrency-etf-and-accumulates-100-million-for-algo-fund/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Skybridge Capital</a>. Overall, he remains confident in crypto&#8217;s prospects.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Anthony_Scaramucci_at_SALT_Conference_2016-scaled-1-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Will Dogecoin Dip To Local Support As The Coin Trades Sideways?</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/dogecoin/will-dogecoin-support-coin-trade-sideway/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[anushsamal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 20:07:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[doge]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dogeusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dogeusdt]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=516790</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Dogecoin started losing value as soon as it fell outside its ascending parallel channel. At the moment, Dogecoin is trading laterally. Over the last 24 hours, DOGE went up by 0.3%, which confirms that the coin was stuck in a consolidated price region. Last week, Dogecoin brought in close to 4% gains. The technical outlook for the Dogecoin price depicted that bearish momentum had set in. Demand and accumulation for the meme-coin depreciated when it started to trade sideways. Related Reading: Tezos Approaches The ‘Mumbai Upgrade’, What’s Next For XTZ? The meme coin noted a price pullback after it breached the $0.88 resistance level. Over the last few days, Dogecoin has witnessed a substantial influx of buyers; however, selling pressure has amplified at press time. Overall, the meme coin has a bullish structure as it has managed to keep its price above the 200-Simple Moving Average line. In the shorter time frame, Dogecoin might retrace close to the $0.74 level before recovering or falling in value further. The market capitalization of DOGE declined slightly, indicating that selling pressure has mounted on the chart. Dogecoin Price Analysis: One-Day Chart DOGE was trading at $0.81 at the time of writing. The coin corrected itself after it reached the $0.88 price level. Immediate resistance for the meme coin stood at $0.87, close to the 61.8% Fibonacci retracement level. Moving past the $0.87 mark can push DOGE to the $0.104 resistance mark. On the other hand, if Dogecoin fails to stay above the $0.74 support level, it can fall to $0.66. If demand picks up slightly, it is unlikely that Dogecoin will fall below the $0.74 price floor. The amount of Dogecoin traded in the last session decreased, indicating that there has been a fall in buying pressure. Technical Analysis The meme coin has depicted a fall in demand as buyers started to decline on the daily chart. The Relative Strength Index (RSI) retraced after it stood close to the 70-mark, signifying excess buyers over sellers. This signified that the meme coin was correcting itself at press time. The RSI, however, remained above the 50-mark, indicating that buying strength was greater than selling strength. Dogecoin price was above the 20-Simple Moving Average (SMA), indicating that buyers were in control of price momentum in the market. It was also above the 50-SMA (yellow) and 200-SMA (green) lines, indicating bullishness. The coin, however, formed a death cross where the 200-SMA line crossed over the 20-SMA line. A death cross is accompanied by a significant fall in value. The meme-coin continued to display buy signals on the one-day chart. The Moving Average Convergence Divergence, which indicates price momentum and trend reversal, depicted green signal bars tied to buy signals. Related Reading: Bitcoin Bulls Hold The Line At $20,700, But Bigger Losses Are Imminent? These green histograms were shrinking, indicating that it was probably not a good time to buy the asset. In resonance with the same, the Bollinger Bands that suggest volatility widened apart, implying that the price would significantly change over the next trading session. Featured Image From UnSplash, Charts From TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Dogecoin started losing value as soon as it fell outside its ascending parallel channel. At the moment, Dogecoin is trading laterally. Over the last 24 hours, DOGE went up by 0.3%, which confirms that the coin was stuck in a consolidated price region.</p>
<p>Last week, Dogecoin brought in close to 4% gains. The technical outlook for the Dogecoin price depicted that bearish momentum had set in. Demand and accumulation for the meme-coin depreciated when it started to trade sideways.</p>

<p>The meme coin noted a price pullback after it breached the $0.88 resistance level. Over the last few days, Dogecoin has witnessed a substantial influx of buyers; however, selling pressure has amplified at press time.</p>
<p>Overall, the meme coin has a bullish structure as it has managed to keep its price above the 200-Simple Moving Average line. In the shorter time frame, Dogecoin might retrace close to the $0.74 level before recovering or falling in value further. The market capitalization of DOGE declined slightly, indicating that selling pressure has mounted on the chart.</p>
<h2>Dogecoin Price Analysis: One-Day Chart</h2>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-516796 size-full" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/DOGEUSD_2023-01-19_22-28-46.png" alt="Dogecoin" width="1816" height="830" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/DOGEUSD_2023-01-19_22-28-46.png 1816w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/DOGEUSD_2023-01-19_22-28-46-460x210.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/DOGEUSD_2023-01-19_22-28-46-860x393.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/DOGEUSD_2023-01-19_22-28-46-768x351.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/DOGEUSD_2023-01-19_22-28-46-1536x702.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/DOGEUSD_2023-01-19_22-28-46-750x343.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/DOGEUSD_2023-01-19_22-28-46-1140x521.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1816px) 100vw, 1816px" />
<p>DOGE was trading at $0.81 at the time of writing. The coin corrected itself after it reached the $0.88 price level. Immediate resistance for the meme coin stood at $0.87, close to the 61.8% Fibonacci retracement level. Moving past the $0.87 mark can push DOGE to the $0.104 resistance mark.</p>
<p>On the other hand, if Dogecoin fails to stay above the $0.74 support level, it can fall to $0.66. If demand picks up slightly, it is unlikely that Dogecoin will fall below the $0.74 price floor. The amount of Dogecoin traded in the last session decreased, indicating that there has been a fall in buying pressure.</p>
<h2>Technical Analysis</h2>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-516798 size-full" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/DOGEUSD_2023-01-19_22-29-26.png" alt="Dogecoin" width="1816" height="743" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/DOGEUSD_2023-01-19_22-29-26.png 1816w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/DOGEUSD_2023-01-19_22-29-26-460x188.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/DOGEUSD_2023-01-19_22-29-26-860x352.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/DOGEUSD_2023-01-19_22-29-26-768x314.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/DOGEUSD_2023-01-19_22-29-26-1536x628.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/DOGEUSD_2023-01-19_22-29-26-750x307.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/DOGEUSD_2023-01-19_22-29-26-1140x466.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1816px) 100vw, 1816px" />
<p>The meme coin has depicted a fall in demand as buyers started to decline on the daily chart. The Relative Strength Index (RSI) retraced after it stood close to the 70-mark, signifying excess buyers over sellers. This signified that the meme coin was correcting itself at press time.</p>
<p>The RSI, however, remained above the 50-mark, indicating that buying strength was greater than selling strength. Dogecoin price was above the 20-Simple Moving Average (SMA), indicating that buyers were in control of price momentum in the market.</p>
<p>It was also above the 50-SMA (yellow) and 200-SMA (green) lines, indicating bullishness. The coin, however, formed a death cross where the 200-SMA line crossed over the 20-SMA line. A death cross is accompanied by a significant fall in value.</p>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-516800 size-full" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/DOGEUSD_2023-01-19_22-29-54.png" alt="Dogecoin" width="1816" height="743" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/DOGEUSD_2023-01-19_22-29-54.png 1816w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/DOGEUSD_2023-01-19_22-29-54-460x188.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/DOGEUSD_2023-01-19_22-29-54-860x352.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/DOGEUSD_2023-01-19_22-29-54-768x314.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/DOGEUSD_2023-01-19_22-29-54-1536x628.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/DOGEUSD_2023-01-19_22-29-54-750x307.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/DOGEUSD_2023-01-19_22-29-54-1140x466.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1816px) 100vw, 1816px" />
<p>The meme-coin continued to display buy signals on the one-day chart. The Moving Average Convergence Divergence, which indicates price momentum and trend reversal, depicted green signal bars tied to buy signals.</p>

<p>These green histograms were shrinking, indicating that it was probably not a good time to buy the asset. In resonance with the same, the Bollinger Bands that suggest volatility widened apart, implying that the price would significantly change over the next trading session.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/guerrillabuzz-blockchain-pr-agency-X39ph908rpE-unsplash-460x259.jpg" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance USD (BUSD) Exchange Reserves Dry Up, Reason Behind Bitcoin&#8217;s Slowdown?</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/binance-usd-reserve-bitcoin-slowdown/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hououin Kyouma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 18:00:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance USD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance USD Exchange Reserve]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BUSD Exchange Reserve]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[stablecoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=516718</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[On-chain data shows the Binance USD (BUSD) exchange reserves have declined recently, a factor that may be behind Bitcoin&#8217;s slowdown. Binance USD (BUSD) Exchange Reserves Have Gone Down As pointed out by an analyst in a CryptoQuant post, there was a very large inflow of $250 million BUSD just a while ago. The &#8220;exchange reserve&#8221; is an indicator that measures the total amount of a cryptocurrency (which, in the present case, is Binance USD) currently being stored on wallets of centralized exchanges. Generally, investors swap their coins for stablecoins like BUSD when they want to avoid the volatility associated with other cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin. When these holders feel that prices are right to reenter the volatile markets, they shift their stables back into their desired coins. This can act as buying pressure for the specific crypto that they are swapping into. Investors usually make use of exchanges to swap these coins, which means that whenever the exchange reserve of a stablecoin like BUSD rises, it presents the possibility that holders want to buy back into volatile cryptocurrencies. A large enough increase in the stablecoin reserve can result in a high amount of buying pressure for other coins, and can therefore have a bullish effect on their prices. Related Reading: Bitcoin Drops To $20,700 As Miner Outflows Surge Now, here is a chart that shows the trend in the Binance USD exchange reserve (specifically for spot exchanges) over the past couple of months: The value of the metric seems to have been going down in recent days &#124; Source: CryptoQuant As you can see in the above graph, the Binance USD exchange reserve observed a rapid increase a while back. Since then, however, the metric has been steadily declining and has hit significantly lower values now. But from the chart, it&#8217;s apparent that while the BUSD reserve was coming down from high values, Bitcoin had been rallying instead. This means that holders might have been actively swapping the stablecoin for BTC, thus providing a boost to its price. The graph also displays data for a metric called the &#8220;exchange netflow,&#8221; which tells us the net number of coins entering or exiting exchange wallets. When this metric has a positive value, it means investors are depositing a net amount of the asset to exchanges currently, while negative values suggest net withdrawals are taking place. A while ago, there was a huge positive spike in the Binance USD exchange netflow of around $250 million (which is what caused the reserve to blow up). This inflow may have been what helped the recent BTC rally. Related Reading: Asian Traders Behind Most Of Bitcoin’s Recent Gains, Report Reveals However, since then, there have only been outflows, which have taken the reserve back to the same level as before this $250 million spike. This suggests that buying pressure from this inflow has now dried up, which could be one of the factors responsible for the latest slowdown in Bitcoin&#8217;s rally. BTC Price At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading around $20,700, up 14% in the last week. Bitcoin plunges down &#124; Source: BTCUSD on TradingView Featured image from Nicholas Cappello on Unsplash.com, charts from TradingView.com, CryptoQuant.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On-chain data shows the Binance USD (BUSD) exchange reserves have declined recently, a factor that may be behind Bitcoin&#8217;s slowdown.</p>
<h2>Binance USD (BUSD) Exchange Reserves Have Gone Down</h2>
<p>As pointed out by an analyst in a CryptoQuant <a href="https://cryptoquant.com/quicktake/63c8b51c710f9e4c68968cfd-250-million-BUSD-inflow-affected-BTC-price-increase-but-scenario-has-changed" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">post</a>, there was a very large inflow of $250 million BUSD just a while ago. The &#8220;<a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/usdc-exchange-reserve-spikes-push-bitcoin-up/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">exchange reserve</a>&#8221; is an indicator that measures the total amount of a cryptocurrency (which, in the present case, is Binance USD) currently being stored on wallets of centralized exchanges.</p>
<p>Generally, investors swap their coins for <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/cardano/launch-for-djed-cardano-stablecoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">stablecoins</a> like BUSD when they want to avoid the volatility associated with other cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin. When these holders feel that prices are right to reenter the volatile markets, they shift their stables back into their desired coins. This can act as buying pressure for the specific crypto that they are swapping into.</p>
<p>Investors usually make use of exchanges to swap these coins, which means that whenever the exchange reserve of a stablecoin like BUSD rises, it presents the possibility that holders want to buy back into volatile cryptocurrencies. A large enough increase in the stablecoin reserve can result in a high amount of buying pressure for other coins, and can therefore have a bullish effect on their prices.</p>

<p>Now, here is a chart that shows the trend in the Binance USD exchange reserve (specifically for spot exchanges) over the past couple of months:</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone aligncenter" src="https://img.cryptoquant.com/201529/quicktake/mDT0T_2db27a6007dcd75cdc78c858a3ffd45e6e48e684cc8c106be1f3a984f83e6b9b.png" alt="Binance USD (BUSD) Exchange Reserve " width="1280" height="572" /></p>

<p>As you can see in the above graph, the Binance USD exchange reserve observed a rapid increase a while back. Since then, however, the metric has been steadily declining and has hit significantly lower values now.</p>
<p>But from the chart, it&#8217;s apparent that while the BUSD reserve was coming down from high values, Bitcoin had been rallying instead. This means that holders might have been actively swapping the stablecoin for BTC, thus providing a boost to its price.</p>
<p>The graph also displays data for a metric called the &#8220;<a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-bearish-signal-exchange-netflows-spike-up/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">exchange netflow</a>,&#8221; which tells us the net number of coins entering or exiting exchange wallets. When this metric has a positive value, it means investors are depositing a net amount of the asset to exchanges currently, while negative values suggest net withdrawals are taking place.</p>
<p>A while ago, there was a huge positive spike in the Binance USD exchange netflow of around $250 million (which is what caused the reserve to blow up). This inflow may have been what helped the recent BTC rally.</p>

<p>However, since then, there have only been outflows, which have taken the reserve back to the same level as before this $250 million spike. This suggests that buying pressure from this inflow has now dried up, which could be one of the factors responsible for the latest slowdown in Bitcoin&#8217;s rally.</p>
<h2>BTC Price</h2>
<p>At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading around $20,700, up 14% in the last week.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone wp-image-516770 size-large aligncenter" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/chart-30-860x477.png" alt="Bitcoin Price Chart" width="860" height="477" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/chart-30-860x477.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/chart-30-460x255.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/chart-30-768x426.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/chart-30-750x416.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/chart-30.png 973w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" /></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/nicholas-cappello-Wb63zqJ5gnE-unsplash-460x306.jpg" width="460" height="306" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Might Fall Below $20,000 Before Bull Rally Resumes, Analyst Says</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-might-fall-below-20000/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Best Owie]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 17:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin analyst]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=516709</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The last two weeks have been incredible for the price of bitcoin. The digital asset has been able to successfully make its way out of a depressing bear trend and reached two-month highs in the process. However, with the recent pullback, there may be a bit more pain for bitcoin investors before the upward rally continues. Analyst Justin Bennett Says Bitcoin Below $20,000 Is Possible In a new issue of his crypto trading newsletter, analyst Justin Bennett reveals some bearish tendencies of the market. He first points to the fact that the market has enjoyed a good amount of gains, adding as much as 28% to its value in just the last 18 days. But as is expected after such a rally, a market correction has pulled back the price of the digital asset. Related Reading: Bitcoin Price: Investors Predict 12% Decline For BTC In Next Two Weeks While there have been speculations that this pullback would only be temporary, Bennett explains that it could go a lot further. Now, the analyst does not take away from the bull trend that bitcoin is currently on but rather presents a scenario where the price of the cryptocurrency could back to below $20,000 before the rally resumes. BTC could see sub-$20,000 before rally resumes &#124; Source: Cryptocademy BTC has already fallen back into the $20,000 region as of the time of this writing, giving credence to Bennett’s analysis. However, with key support for the digital asset now resting at $20,000, bears could pull the price as close to this support as possible before the bears take over once more. “I like Bitcoin higher toward $25,000 and potentially $29,000, but not without a pullback into the $20,000 region first,” Bennett said in his newsletter. Factors That Drive This Pullback In the same newsletter, Bennett points to the PPI data release that underwhelmed the market. In the end, the much-anticipated release was lower than expected, triggering fatigue in the market. Bitcoin had fallen below $21,000 as a result of this. Also pointing to the US Dollar Index (DXY), the analyst explained the movement of this index on the back of the PPI data release would’ve been bullish for assets such as BTC. “But I think markets got ahead of themselves, so a lot of that bullishness was already priced in,” Bennett added. BTC corrects downward following rally &#124; Source: BTCUSD on TradingView.com Since this pullback has pushed the price of BTC dangerously close to the 5-day moving average, it should come as no surprise if the cryptocurrency were to lose another couple of hundred dollars off its value in the coming days. Related Reading: Bitcoin On Exchanges Drop By 44%, Could This Fuel More BTC Rally? However, the bullish trend is expected to continue shortly as trading volume remains high, and investor sentiment reaching 9-month highs, sitting very close to greed on the Crypto Fear &#38; Greed Index. BTC is trading at $20,779 at the time of this writing. Its price is down 2.18% in the last 24 hours, but up 14.54% in a 7-day period. Follow Best Owie on Twitter for market insights, updates, and the occasional funny tweet… Featured image from CryptoSlate, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="p2">The last two weeks have been incredible for the price of bitcoin. The digital asset has been able to successfully make its way out of a depressing bear trend and reached two-month highs in the process. However, with the recent pullback, there may be a bit more pain for bitcoin investors before the upward rally continues.</p>
<h2 class="p2">Analyst Justin Bennett Says Bitcoin Below $20,000 Is Possible</h2>
<p class="p2">In a new issue of his <a href="https://cryptocademy.com/free/issue-367-trading-the-crypto-pullback/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">crypto trading newsletter</a>, analyst Justin Bennett reveals some bearish tendencies of the market. He first points to the fact that the market has enjoyed a good amount of gains, adding as much as 28% to its value in just the last 18 days. But as is expected after such a rally, a market correction has pulled back the price of the digital asset.</p>

<p class="p2">While there have been speculations that this pullback would only be temporary, Bennett explains that it could go a lot further. Now, the analyst does not take away from the bull trend that bitcoin is currently on but rather presents a scenario where the price of the cryptocurrency could back to below $20,000 before the rally resumes.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-516710 aligncenter" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-below-20000-460x260.png" alt="Bitcoin below $20,000" width="460" height="260" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-below-20000-460x260.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-below-20000-860x486.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-below-20000-768x434.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-below-20000-1536x867.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-below-20000-750x423.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-below-20000-1140x644.png 1140w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-below-20000.png 2044w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px" /></p>

<p class="p2">BTC has already fallen back into the $20,000 region as of the time of this writing, giving credence to Bennett’s analysis. However, with key support for the digital asset now resting at $20,000, bears could pull the price as close to this support as possible before the bears take over once more.</p>
<p class="p2">“I like Bitcoin higher toward $25,000 and potentially $29,000, but not without a pullback into the $20,000 region first,” Bennett said in his newsletter.</p>
<h2 class="p2">Factors That Drive This Pullback</h2>
<p class="p2">In the same newsletter, Bennett points to the PPI data release that underwhelmed the market. In the end, the much-anticipated release was lower than expected, triggering fatigue in the market. Bitcoin had fallen below $21,000 as a result of this.</p>
<p class="p2">Also pointing to the US Dollar Index (DXY), the analyst explained the movement of this index on the back of the PPI data release would’ve been bullish for assets such as BTC. “But I think markets got ahead of themselves, so a lot of that bullishness was already priced in,” Bennett added.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/FkLKVtug/" alt="Bitcoin price chart from TradingView.com" width="3284" height="1646" /></p>

<p class="p2">Since this pullback has pushed the price of BTC dangerously close to the 5-day moving average, it should come as no surprise if the cryptocurrency were to lose another couple of hundred dollars off its value in the coming days.</p>

<p class="p2">However, the bullish trend is expected to continue shortly as trading volume remains high, and investor sentiment reaching 9-month highs, sitting very close to greed on the Crypto Fear &amp; Greed Index.</p>
<p class="p2">BTC is trading at $20,779 at the time of this writing. Its price is down 2.18% in the last 24 hours, but up 14.54% in a 7-day period.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/bitcoin-bear-460x242.jpeg" width="460" height="242" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>If Any Crypto Will Reach $1 Trillion, It&#8217;s Ethereum, Not Bitcoin: Dragonfly Capital</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/ethereum/why-ethereum-will-outperform-bitcoin/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jake Simmons]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 16:20:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dragonfly Capital]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=516719</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Based on the year-to-date performance and their drawdown from their all-time highs (ATHs), Bitcoin (BTC) and Ethereum (ETH) have performed very similarly. While BTC has risen by 25.5% since the beginning of the year, ETH has climbed by about 27%. From its ATH, Bitcoin has declined by 69.9%, while Ether is down by 68.9%. Despite this very comparable performance, the debate persists that Ethereum may replace (&#8220;flip&#8221;) Bitcoin as the largest cryptocurrency by market cap within the next few years or in the next bull cycle. One supporter of this theory is Dragonfly Capital&#8217;s Haseeb Qureshi. In a recent interview, the investment firm&#8217;s managing partner said that if any cryptocurrency is ever going to reach $1 trillion, it will be Ethereum. His reasoning? Institutional investors who need to align buying with their Environmental, Social, and Governance (ESG) agenda: You need institutional buyers to be willing to buy this thing in size and Ethereum is really the only game in town if you are an institutional buyer. Furthermore, the expert expressed that it is becoming increasingly difficult for institutions to justify Bitcoin as an investment. &#8220;I see it a lot because we work a lot with big institutions [&#8230;]. It&#8217;s explicitly something that gets more and more of a concern for them. They want to invest in crypto, but it has to be compliant with their ESG mandate,&#8221; Qureshi said. 2. Ethereum is superior to #Bitcoin in the eyes of institutions, as it&#8217;s more ESG friendly. &#8220;If you want a trillion dollar coin, you&#8217;re not going to get there off the back of retail.&#8221; &#8220;Ethereum is really the only game in town if you want institutional buyers.&#8221; pic.twitter.com/f2H2gg224T — Miles Deutscher (@milesdeutscher) January 18, 2023 Another argument made by proponents of the theory is also that Ethereum is predominantly OFAC (US Office of Foreign Assets Control) compliant, which could make it easier for institutions to enter the market. Related Reading: Will Bitcoin Price Fall If Genesis Files For Bankruptcy? Here’s What We Know On the other hand, Bitcoin supporters are likely to counter that the mining industry is one of the most sustainable industries of all. In its latest report, the Bitcoin Mining Council found that the energy mix in Bitcoin mining is now 58.9% sustainable. Furthermore, estimates suggest that Bitcoin mining can reduce global emissions by up to 8% by 2030, simply by converting the world&#8217;s wasted and dangerous methane emissions into emissions that are 80 times less harmful. Here&#8217;s What Ethereum / Bitcoin Technical Analysis Says A look at the Ethereum / Bitcoin 4-hour chart shows that ETH currently remains in a downtrend compared to BTC. ETH saw a spike above and out of the pennant for the ETH/BTC ratio, followed by a retrace back to support as Bitcoin broke out from $18,000 to $21,000 in a matter of days, as explained by the founder of LedgArt via Twitter. Related Reading: Ethereum Price Dips From $1,600 But ETH Could Start A Fresh Rally According to the analyst, these types of fake-out wicks are breaking out to the downside. He argued: &#8220;Still expecting this level to break lower over the next several weeks as BTC continues to strengthen, absorbing liquidity from alts similar to what happened in the 2019 bear market rally,&#8221; and shared the chart below. BTC is currently changing hands at $18,798, while ETH is sitting just above the $1,500 support level at $1,528. Featured image from Kanchanara / Unsplash, Chart from Twitter/TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Based on the year-to-date performance and their drawdown from their all-time highs (ATHs), Bitcoin (BTC) and Ethereum (ETH) have performed very similarly. While BTC has risen by 25.5% since the beginning of the year, ETH has climbed by about 27%. From its ATH, Bitcoin has declined by 69.9%, while Ether is down by 68.9%.</p>
<p>Despite this very comparable performance, the <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/ethereum/why-ethereum-will-continue-to-outperform-bitcoin-during-september/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">debate</a> persists that Ethereum may replace (&#8220;flip&#8221;) Bitcoin as the largest cryptocurrency by market cap within the next few years or in the next bull cycle.</p>
<p>One supporter of this theory is Dragonfly Capital&#8217;s Haseeb Qureshi. In a recent <a href="https://twitter.com/milesdeutscher/status/1615685114419372035" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">interview</a>, the investment firm&#8217;s managing partner said that if any cryptocurrency is ever going to reach $1 trillion, it will be Ethereum.</p>
<p>His reasoning? Institutional investors who need to align buying with their Environmental, Social, and Governance (ESG) agenda:</p>
<blockquote><p><strong>You need institutional buyers to be willing to buy this thing in size and Ethereum is really the only game in town if you are an institutional buyer.</strong></p></blockquote>
<p>Furthermore, the expert expressed that it is becoming increasingly difficult for institutions to justify Bitcoin as an investment.</p>
<p>&#8220;I see it a lot because we work a lot with big institutions [&#8230;]. It&#8217;s explicitly something that gets more and more of a concern for them. They want to invest in crypto, but it has to be compliant with their ESG mandate,&#8221; Qureshi said.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-conversation="none">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">2. Ethereum is superior to <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Bitcoin?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">#Bitcoin</a> in the eyes of institutions, as it&#8217;s more ESG friendly.</p>
<p>&#8220;If you want a trillion dollar coin, you&#8217;re not going to get there off the back of retail.&#8221;</p>
<p>&#8220;Ethereum is really the only game in town if you want institutional buyers.&#8221; <a href="https://t.co/f2H2gg224T" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/f2H2gg224T</a></p>
<p>— Miles Deutscher (@milesdeutscher) <a href="https://twitter.com/milesdeutscher/status/1615685114419372035?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">January 18, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p>Another argument made by proponents of the theory is also that Ethereum is predominantly OFAC (US Office of Foreign Assets Control) compliant, which could make it easier for institutions to enter the market.</p>

<p>On the other hand, Bitcoin supporters are likely to counter that the mining industry is one of the most sustainable industries of all. In its latest report, the Bitcoin Mining Council found that the energy mix in Bitcoin mining is now 58.9% sustainable.</p>
<p>Furthermore, estimates <a href="https://twitter.com/DSBatten/status/1519902364819685376" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">suggest</a> that Bitcoin mining can reduce global emissions by up to 8% by 2030, simply by converting the world&#8217;s wasted and dangerous methane emissions into emissions that are 80 times less harmful.</p>
<h2>Here&#8217;s What Ethereum / Bitcoin Technical Analysis Says</h2>
<p>A look at the Ethereum / Bitcoin 4-hour chart shows that ETH currently remains in a downtrend compared to BTC. ETH saw a spike above and out of the pennant for the ETH/BTC ratio, followed by a retrace back to support as Bitcoin broke out from $18,000 to $21,000 in a matter of days, as <a href="https://twitter.com/CryptoKaleo/status/1615961654683893760" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">explained</a> by the founder of LedgArt via Twitter.</p>

<p>According to the analyst, these types of fake-out wicks are breaking out to the downside. He argued: &#8220;Still expecting this level to break lower over the next several weeks as BTC continues to strengthen, absorbing liquidity from alts similar to what happened in the 2019 bear market rally,&#8221; and shared the chart below.</p>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-516764 size-full" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ethereum-Bitcoin-.jpg" alt="Ethereum Bitcoin" width="1805" height="830" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ethereum-Bitcoin-.jpg 1805w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ethereum-Bitcoin--460x212.jpg 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ethereum-Bitcoin--860x395.jpg 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ethereum-Bitcoin--768x353.jpg 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ethereum-Bitcoin--1536x706.jpg 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ethereum-Bitcoin--750x345.jpg 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ethereum-Bitcoin--1140x524.jpg 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1805px) 100vw, 1805px" />
<p>BTC is currently changing hands at $18,798, while ETH is sitting just above the $1,500 support level at $1,528.</p>
<p>Featured image from Kanchanara / Unsplash, Chart from Twitter/TradingView.com</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/kanchanara-V9N2JGUx94I-unsplash-460x306.jpg" width="460" height="306" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tezos Approaches The ‘Mumbai Upgrade’, What’s Next For XTZ?</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/tezos/tezos-approaches-mumbai-upgrade/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[anushsamal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 15:30:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Tezos]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mumbai Upgrade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tezos]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XTZ]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xtzusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XTZUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=516721</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Tezos (XTZ) network is readying itself for its latest upgrade, called the &#8216;Mumbai Upgrade.&#8217; On January 17, Nomadic Labs, which is a blockchain developer within the Tezos community, mentioned the Tezos protocol proposal, Mumbai, which is headed toward the implementation process. This will be the 13th upgrade made to the Tezos network. This upgrade will implement various new features. The main features include transfer tickets between accounts and a much shorter block time of 15 seconds. Related Reading: Solana Gleams 30% In Last 7 Days As SOL Bulls Try To Break $21 Barrier Further, this upgrade will add Epoxy, a new technology on Mainnet, which is precisely a validity rollup that can also be referred to as a new layer 2 scaling solution. The Mainnet will gain further strength due to Epoxy, which introduces SNARKs&#8217; proof-of-validity, which will be the reason for quicker transactions. This 13th upgrade, which is called the &#8216;Mumbai Upgrade&#8217; will be implemented after a number of tests are carried out. However, once implemented, the system will get closer to Tezos&#8217; target of achieving one million transactions per second, according to the Nomadic Lab&#8217;s report. The implementation of the upgrade will, as a consequence, increase the value of Tezos&#8217; native token XTZ. The price of the altcoin, XTZ, has reacted positively to this development. XTZ experienced a price reversal, but the altcoin has since resumed its bullish momentum. Tezos Price Analysis: One-Day Chart XTZ was trading at $0.99 at the time of writing. Although the coin started to retrace over the 48 hours, it has regained bullish momentum on the chart. The altcoin has formed a prominent cup-and-handle trading pattern, which is an extension of bullish momentum. This change in price momentum can be attributed to the announcement of the &#8216;Mumbai Upgrade&#8217;. Immediate resistance to XTZ stands at $1.02, but the coin is expected to retrace to $0.97. Once it reaches the $0.97 mark, Tezos can target $1.19, which will mean an 18% appreciation. Over the last week, the coin managed to surge over 8%. The amount of XTZ traded in the last session increased, signifying an increased amount of buying. Technical Analysis XTZ had secured a multi-month high with regard to the buying pressure it witnessed. The Relative Strength Index (RSI) touched the 80 mark a few trading sessions ago, signifying an overvalued tendency. Often, a coin that is overbought experiences a price correction and a fall in demand; Tezos also displayed the same, but at press time, the RSI again noted an uptick. This uptick could mean that the altcoin might head back close to the 80-mark. This unusual uptick can be because of the newest development. On the same note, XTZ rose above the 20-Simple Moving Average (SMA), which indicated that buyers were driving the price momentum. Related Reading: Bitcoin Drops To $20,700 As Miner Outflows Surge The coin was above the 50-SMA (yellow) line too. So with increased accumulation, XTZ can soon breach the 200-SMA (green) line. Overall, Tezos remains quite optimistic on the chart; however, the coin has to remain above its local support line of $0.97 for the uptrend to continue. Featured Image From UnSplash, Charts From TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Tezos (XTZ) network is readying itself for its latest upgrade, called the<a href="https://research-development.nomadic-labs.com/mumbai-announcement.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow"> &#8216;Mumbai Upgrade.&#8217;</a> On January 17, Nomadic Labs, which is a blockchain developer within the Tezos community, mentioned the Tezos protocol proposal, Mumbai, which is headed toward the implementation process.</p>
<p>This will be the 13th upgrade made to the Tezos network. This upgrade will implement various new features. The main features include transfer tickets between accounts and a much shorter block time of 15 seconds.</p>

<p>Further, this upgrade will add Epoxy, a new technology on Mainnet, which is precisely a validity rollup that can also be referred to as a new layer 2 scaling solution.</p>
<p>The Mainnet will gain further strength due to Epoxy, which introduces SNARKs&#8217; proof-of-validity, which will be the reason for quicker transactions.</p>
<p>This 13th upgrade, which is called the &#8216;Mumbai Upgrade&#8217; will be implemented after a number of tests are carried out. However, once implemented, the system will get closer to Tezos&#8217; target of achieving one million transactions per second, according to the Nomadic Lab&#8217;s report.</p>
<p>The implementation of the upgrade will, as a consequence, increase the value of Tezos&#8217; native token XTZ. The price of the altcoin, XTZ, has reacted positively to this development. XTZ experienced a price reversal, but the altcoin has since resumed its bullish momentum.</p>
<h2>Tezos Price Analysis: One-Day Chart</h2>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-516744 size-full" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XTZUSD_2023-01-19_18-14-34.png" alt="Tezos" width="1816" height="830" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XTZUSD_2023-01-19_18-14-34.png 1816w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XTZUSD_2023-01-19_18-14-34-460x210.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XTZUSD_2023-01-19_18-14-34-860x393.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XTZUSD_2023-01-19_18-14-34-768x351.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XTZUSD_2023-01-19_18-14-34-1536x702.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XTZUSD_2023-01-19_18-14-34-750x343.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XTZUSD_2023-01-19_18-14-34-1140x521.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1816px) 100vw, 1816px" />
<p>XTZ was trading at $0.99 at the time of writing. Although the coin started to retrace over the 48 hours, it has regained bullish momentum on the chart. The altcoin has formed a prominent cup-and-handle trading pattern, which is an extension of bullish momentum.</p>
<p>This change in price momentum can be attributed to the announcement of the &#8216;Mumbai Upgrade&#8217;. Immediate resistance to XTZ stands at $1.02, but the coin is expected to retrace to $0.97.</p>
<p>Once it reaches the $0.97 mark, Tezos can target $1.19, which will mean an 18% appreciation. Over the last week, the coin managed to surge over 8%. The amount of XTZ traded in the last session increased, signifying an increased amount of buying.</p>
<h2>Technical Analysis</h2>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-516752 size-full" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XTZUSD_2023-01-19_18-15-23.png" alt="Tezos" width="1816" height="743" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XTZUSD_2023-01-19_18-15-23.png 1816w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XTZUSD_2023-01-19_18-15-23-460x188.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XTZUSD_2023-01-19_18-15-23-860x352.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XTZUSD_2023-01-19_18-15-23-768x314.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XTZUSD_2023-01-19_18-15-23-1536x628.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XTZUSD_2023-01-19_18-15-23-750x307.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XTZUSD_2023-01-19_18-15-23-1140x466.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1816px) 100vw, 1816px" />
<p>XTZ had secured a multi-month high with regard to the buying pressure it witnessed. The Relative Strength Index (RSI) touched the 80 mark a few trading sessions ago, signifying an overvalued tendency.</p>
<p>Often, a coin that is overbought experiences a price correction and a fall in demand; Tezos also displayed the same, but at press time, the RSI again noted an uptick.</p>
<p>This uptick could mean that the altcoin might head back close to the 80-mark. This unusual uptick can be because of the newest development.</p>
<p>On the same note, XTZ rose above the 20-Simple Moving Average (SMA), which indicated that buyers were driving the price momentum.</p>

<p>The coin was above the 50-SMA (yellow) line too. So with increased accumulation, XTZ can soon breach the 200-SMA (green) line.</p>
<p>Overall, Tezos remains quite optimistic on the chart; however, the coin has to remain above its local support line of $0.97 for the uptrend to continue.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/alejo-reinoso-jkBFxwNB98Q-unsplash-460x345.jpg" width="460" height="345" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Bulls Hold The Line At $20,700, But Bigger Losses Are Imminent?</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-holds-line-20700-losses-imminent/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reynaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 15:28:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=516779</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin lost steam the previous day and seems poised to re-test its support levels in the coming days. The cryptocurrency rallied on the back of favorable macroeconomic winds and high upside liquidity from overleveraged short traders.  Related Reading: Solana Gleams 30% In Last 7 Days As SOL Bulls Try To Break $21 Barrier As of this writing, Bitcoin trades at $20,800 with a 3% loss in the last 24 hours. BTC remained positive during the previous seven days and recorded a 16% profit. The number one crypto by market capitalization is the best performer in the top 10.  The Biggest Obstacle For Bitcoin In The Short Term NewsBTC reported that short positions were piling up as Bitcoin trended to the upside. The market took out over half a billion dollars in short positions. As the market trended upside, these positions were liquidated, allowing BTC to continue climbing.  In that sense, Bitcoin might keep trending upwards but at a slower pace. As the market ate off those shorts during the past week, over-confident long positions might become the target. This shift might push BTC back to the critical supports at $19,600 to $19,700.  These levels have confluence with the 200-Day Simple Moving Average (SMA) and 50x leverage longs. Thus, there is a high liquidity pool sitting at those levels, ready to be taken by market movers.  On higher timeframes, a recent report from QCP Capital claims the macroeconomic winds might change and could negatively impact crypto. 2023 kicked off with a positive outlook on critical metrics, such as inflation, and high expectations of a monetary pivot by the U.S. Federal Reserve. The financial institution has been hiking interest rates and unloading its balance sheet to combat inflation. This metric has been at its highest level in the last 40 decades.  Markets Will Take A &#8220;Rude Shock?&#8221; Recent data shows inflation is declining; this trend might support the Fed’s slowdown on its monetary policy and provide room for Bitcoin and risk on assets to rally. However, QCP Capital believes that while Q1, 2023 might be positive for these assets, Q2 could see some hurdles:  While we expect the 1 February FOMC to push back strongly against this pricing, we believe the 22 March FOMC will be the moment of truth, when updated rate forecasts will be released. Should there be no adjustment to the median 2023 dot, then we expect markets will be in for a rude shock. The fact that Bitcoin and some stocks have been rallying is evidence of “how quickly financial conditions have loosened,” the firm believes. The Fed has been fighting against this economic environment, so its return could push the financial institution to tighten its monetary policy.  Related Reading: Bitcoin Drops To $20,700 As Miner Outflows Surge For this time next year, the market is expecting much lower interest rates, as seen in the chart above. It remains to be seen if the Fed will indulge these expectations or if inflation will persist, leading to more pain across the crypto and the legacy financial market.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Bitcoin lost steam the previous day and seems poised to re-test its support levels in the coming days. The cryptocurrency rallied on the back of favorable macroeconomic winds and high upside liquidity from overleveraged short traders. </strong></p>

<p>As of this writing, Bitcoin trades at $20,800 with a 3% loss in the last 24 hours. BTC remained positive during the previous seven days and recorded a 16% profit. The number one crypto by market capitalization is the best performer in the top 10. </p>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-516788 size-large" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-2-860x394.png" alt="Bitcoin BTC BTCUSDT" width="860" height="394" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-2-860x394.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-2-460x211.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-2-768x352.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-2-1536x704.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-2-750x344.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-2-1140x523.png 1140w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-2.png 1813w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" />
<h2>The Biggest Obstacle For Bitcoin In The Short Term</h2>
<p>NewsBTC <a href="https://newsbtc.com/breaking-news-ticker/bitcoin-to-21500-fuel-keep-rising/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">reported</a> that short positions were piling up as Bitcoin trended to the upside. The market took out over half a billion dollars in short positions. As the market trended upside, these positions were liquidated, allowing BTC to continue climbing. </p>
<p>In that sense, Bitcoin might keep trending upwards but at a slower pace. As the market ate off those shorts during the past week, over-confident long positions might become the target. This shift might push BTC back to the critical supports at $19,600 to $19,700. </p>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-516602 size-large" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-3-1-860x413.png" alt="Bitcoin BTC BTCUSDT Chart 3" width="860" height="413" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-3-1-860x413.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-3-1-460x221.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-3-1-768x369.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-3-1-1536x737.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-3-1-750x360.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-3-1-1140x547.png 1140w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-3-1.png 1834w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" />
<p>These levels have confluence with the 200-Day Simple Moving Average (SMA) and 50x leverage longs. Thus, there is a high liquidity pool sitting at those levels, ready to be taken by market movers. </p>
<p>On higher timeframes, a recent <a href="https://qcp.capital/featured-article/the-crypto-circular-9-frightful-fours/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">report</a> from QCP Capital claims the macroeconomic winds might change and could negatively impact crypto. 2023 kicked off with a positive outlook on critical metrics, such as inflation, and high expectations of a monetary pivot by the U.S. Federal Reserve.</p>
<p>The financial institution has been hiking interest rates and unloading its balance sheet to combat inflation. This metric has been at its highest level in the last 40 decades. </p>
Markets Will Take A &#8220;Rude Shock?&#8221;
<p>Recent data shows inflation is declining; this trend might support the Fed’s slowdown on its monetary policy and provide room for Bitcoin and risk on assets to rally. However, QCP Capital believes that while Q1, 2023 might be positive for these assets, Q2 could see some hurdles: </p>
<blockquote><p>While we expect the 1 February FOMC to push back strongly against this pricing, we believe the 22 March FOMC will be the moment of truth, when updated rate forecasts will be released. Should there be no adjustment to the median 2023 dot, then we expect markets will be in for a rude shock.</p></blockquote>
<p>The fact that Bitcoin and some stocks have been rallying is evidence of “how quickly financial conditions have loosened,” the firm believes. The Fed has been fighting against this economic environment, so its return could push the financial institution to tighten its monetary policy. </p>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-516787 size-full" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-IR-Chart-3.jpg" alt="Bitcoin BTC BTCUSDT IR Chart 3" width="846" height="471" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-IR-Chart-3.jpg 846w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-IR-Chart-3-460x256.jpg 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-IR-Chart-3-768x428.jpg 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-IR-Chart-3-750x418.jpg 750w" sizes="(max-width: 846px) 100vw, 846px" />

<p>For this time next year, the market is expecting much lower interest rates, as seen in the chart above. It remains to be seen if the Fed will indulge these expectations or if inflation will persist, leading to more pain across the crypto and the legacy financial market.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Crypto-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Shiba Inu’s BONE Bags New Listing As Token Surges 14% In 7 days</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/shiba-inu-bone-bags-new-listing-and-surges/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samuel Edyme]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 14:50:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Shiba Inu]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BONE]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIB]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shibarium]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=516742</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[As the Shibarium launch draws near, the popularity of the blockchain’s native token, BONE, has been on the rise. In today’s announcement, Singapore-based Exchange BingX announced the listing of BONE trading pairs (BONE/USDT) on the beta version of its BingX Spot platform. The exchange said that the deposit and withdrawal service of the BONE token will be available on the BingX exchange starting from January 18, and trading will commence once the pairs are launched. According to the company’s announcement, the move was taken due to the high demand from customers and members of the Shiba Inu and BONE community. BingX cryptocurrency exchange currently has around five million registered users. The Singapore-based crypto exchange provides users with spot, derivatives, copy and grid trading services to more than 100 countries and regions.  Related Reading: BingX`s New Copy-trading Subsidy Vouchers Will Allow Users To Recover Losses BONE Surges Nearly 15% In 7 Days So far, BONE has gained significant momentum to the upside over the past weeks, especially following the developers&#8217; announcement on making BONE the token to cover gas transactions and compensate validators and delegators on the layer-2 Shibarium blockchain. BONE has advanced and reached higher highs both in price and amount of holders. The BONE holder count has surpassed 60,000, indicating rapid accumulation by various investors. Regarding price, BONE has followed suit with the general crypto market rally. The token has surged 72% in the last 30 days. Meanwhile, at the time of writing, BONE is currently trading at $1.33, down by nearly 11% in the last 24 hours, with a trading volume of $12.1 million over the same period. BONE has also been on an active rally to the upside since the start of this year, with its price reaching a four-month high of $1.59 yesterday, December 18. Currently, CoinMarketCap ranks BONE as the 124th largest cryptocurrency in the world based on market capitalization. The Shiba Inu community believes that BONE has the ability to enter the top 100 cryptocurrencies soon after the launch of the Shibarium Beta. Related Reading: Shibarium Developers Say Each On-Chain Transaction Will Burn SHIB Tokens Shiba Inu’s BONE Anticipated Catalyst Speaking of BONE, the token’s most anticipated catalyst as of this moment is its use case on the Shibarium blockchain. Earlier this month, Shibarium Developers announced BONE would be the only token that would be used for gas fees as well as other blockchain activities, and “No other tokens will be necessary to operate within the protocol.” Featured image from WatcherGuru, chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>As the Shibarium launch draws near, the popularity of the blockchain’s native token, BONE, has been on the rise. In today’s announcement, Singapore-based Exchange BingX announced the listing of BONE trading pairs (BONE/USDT) on the beta version of its BingX Spot platform.</p>
<p>The exchange said that the deposit and withdrawal service of the BONE token will be available on the BingX exchange starting from January 18, and trading will commence once the pairs are launched.</p>
<p>According to the company’s <a href="https://support.bingx.com/hc/es/articles/14590585858201-BingX-a%C3%B1ade-el-par-BONE-a-Spot-Trading" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">announcement</a>, the move was taken due to the high demand from customers and members of the <a href="https://newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/shiba-inu-price-jumps-by-21-here-is-why/">Shiba Inu</a> and BONE community. </p>
<p>BingX cryptocurrency exchange currently has around five million registered users. The Singapore-based crypto exchange provides users with spot, derivatives, copy and grid trading services to more than 100 countries and regions. </p>

<h2>BONE Surges Nearly 15% In 7 Days</h2>
<p>So far, BONE has gained significant momentum to the upside over the past weeks, especially following the developers&#8217; announcement on making <a href="https://newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/why-is-shiba-inus-bone-on-the-rise-and-is-it-time-to-get-in/">BONE</a> the token to cover gas transactions and compensate validators and delegators on the layer-2 Shibarium blockchain.</p>
<p>BONE has advanced and reached higher highs both in price and amount of holders. The BONE holder count has surpassed 60,000, indicating rapid accumulation by various investors. </p>
<p>Regarding price, BONE has followed suit with the general crypto market rally. The token has surged 72% in the last 30 days.</p>
<img loading="lazy" class="size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/HFbzR5AQ/" alt="BONE price chart on TradingView" width="1543" height="800" />
<p>Meanwhile, at the time of writing, BONE is currently trading at $1.33, down by nearly 11% in the last 24 hours, with a trading volume of $12.1 million over the same period. </p>
<p>BONE has also been on an active rally to the upside since the start of this year, with its price reaching a four-month high of $1.59 yesterday, December 18.</p>
<p>Currently, CoinMarketCap ranks BONE as the 124th largest cryptocurrency in the world based on market capitalization. The Shiba Inu community believes that BONE has the ability to enter the top 100 <a href="https://newsbtc.com/press-releases/the-best-cryptocurrency-to-hold-in-2023-experts-flock-to-solana-sol-hedera-hbar-and-orbeon-protocol-orbn/">cryptocurrencies</a> soon after the launch of the Shibarium Beta.</p>

<h2>Shiba Inu’s BONE Anticipated Catalyst</h2>
<p>Speaking of BONE, the token’s most anticipated catalyst as of this moment is its use case on the Shibarium blockchain. </p>
<p>Earlier this month, <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/shibarium-burn-of-shib-tokens/">Shibarium Developers</a> announced BONE would be the only token that would be used for gas fees as well as other blockchain activities, and “No other tokens will be necessary to operate within the protocol.”</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BONE.jpeg" width="350" height="250" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Solana Gleams 30% In Last 7 Days As SOL Bulls Try To Break $21 Barrier</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/solana/solana-up-30-in-last-7-days/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 13:42:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Solana]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[price analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sol]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=516708</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Solana native token SOL has been on a tear since the start of the year. But the token might be on its way to test its support as it faces rejection.  Recent on-chain developments contributed to Solana’s climb. But with the rejection, can SOL regain its bullishness?  Related Reading: LUNC Network Upgrade Backed By Major Exchanges – Will The Crypto Balloon In Price? Solana Keeps Things Aglow The Solana ecosystem is touted as an “Ethereum killer” as it rose in prominence due to its low transaction fees and its capability to go through thousands of transactions per second. Sam Bankman-Fried, former CEO of the now-defunct crypto exchange FTX, called the ecosystem “underrated” last year.  This connection with SBF and FTX led to both the ecosystem and the token to take a plunge, losing nearly half of its value. SOL total market cap at $7.6 billion on the daily chart &#124; Chart: TradingView.com Because of this, the team behind the network made efforts to distance itself from FTX and Bankman-Fried. The Messari overview which was commissioned by the Solana Foundation, detailed how things went down with regards the crypto exchange and its former big boss.  Image: BONK/Twitter But during the turn of the year, SOL and other altcoins started rallying as major cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin and Ether broke through crucial resistances. And with the release of BONK during the rally, the network usage of SOL shot upwards, adding on to the already solid trajectory that SOL has.  Source: Alchemy Despite the fear, uncertainty, and doubt that plagued the ecosystem, Solana is still considered as a fast growing ecosystem, according to a recent report, which shows that the development on the network is increasing compared to its competitors.  1/ A new report by @ElectricCapital shows that Solana is the fastest growing developer ecosystem, surpassing 2,000 total developers in 2022. It&#8217;s second in raw numbers only to Ethereum. Let&#8217;s dig into the numbers.https://t.co/HQvPbQzQD2 pic.twitter.com/xV6pnoT7db — Solana (@solana) January 17, 2023 This certainly had an effect on SOL’s price. At the time of writing, SOL is trading at $20.63, up 30% in the last seven days.  Rejection Line And What It Means Meanwhile, the token was rejected at $25, which could mean that bears will be able to test the two support levels that helped SOL reach its peak price. In the next few days, SOL is seen retesting the $18 and $16 supports.  Chart: TradingView.com Related Reading: XRP Bulls Aim For $1 As Crypto Advances With 12% Weekly Pump SOL’s bullish pace in the weekly timeframe would certainly have an effect on the token’s ability to recover from the rejection. Although it is highly likely that the $18 support will break, investors and traders can rely on $16 as a launching pad to retest $25 in the coming days or weeks.  If $25 is broken, $30 should be the next target as a breakthrough in this area would give SOL bulls legroom for more upward movement. SOL can rely on a solid ecosystem and a bullish community to recover lost ground. Featured image by Sunshine Adult Day Care]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Solana native token SOL has been on a tear since the start of the year. But the token might be on its way to test its support as it faces rejection. </p>
<p>Recent on-chain developments contributed to Solana’s climb. But with the rejection, can SOL regain its bullishness? </p>

<h2><strong>Solana Keeps Things Aglow</strong></h2>
<p>The Solana ecosystem is touted as an <a href="https://phemex.com/academy/solana-vs-ethereum-sol-eth" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">“Ethereum killer”</a> as it rose in prominence due to its low transaction fees and its capability to go through thousands of transactions per second. </p>
<p>Sam Bankman-Fried, former CEO of the now-defunct crypto exchange FTX, <a href="https://news.yahoo.com/billionaire-sam-bankman-fried-thinks-200704759.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">called</a> the ecosystem “underrated” last year. </p>
<p>This connection with SBF and FTX led to both the ecosystem and the token to take a plunge, losing nearly half of its value. </p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/06TcnhHr/" width="2047" height="979" /></p>

<p>Because of this, the team behind the network made efforts to distance itself from FTX and Bankman-Fried.</p>
<p>The <a href="https://messari.io/report/solana-ecosystem-overview" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Messari overview</a> which was commissioned by the Solana Foundation, detailed how things went down with regards the crypto exchange and its former big boss. </p>

<p>But during the turn of the year, SOL and other altcoins started rallying as major cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin and Ether broke through crucial resistances. </p>
<p>And with the release of <a href="https://twitter.com/bonk_inu" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">BONK</a> during the rally, the <a href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2023/01/13/inside-bonk-inu-how-22-developers-put-the-shiba-inu-fun-into-solana-and-away-from-ftx/?outputType=amp" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">network usage</a> of SOL shot upwards, adding on to the already solid trajectory that SOL has. </p>

<p>Despite the fear, uncertainty, and doubt that plagued the ecosystem, Solana is still considered as a <a href="https://twitter.com/solana/status/1615398642717687842?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">fast growing</a> ecosystem, according to a <a href="https://t.co/HQvPbQzQD2" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">recent report</a>, which shows that the development on the network is increasing compared to its competitors. </p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">1/ A new report by <a href="https://twitter.com/ElectricCapital?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">@ElectricCapital</a> shows that Solana is the fastest growing developer ecosystem, surpassing 2,000 total developers in 2022. It&#8217;s second in raw numbers only to Ethereum.</p>
<p>Let&#8217;s dig into the numbers.<a href="https://t.co/HQvPbQzQD2" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">https://t.co/HQvPbQzQD2</a> <a href="https://t.co/xV6pnoT7db" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/xV6pnoT7db</a></p>
<p>— Solana (@solana) <a href="https://twitter.com/solana/status/1615398642717687842?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">January 17, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p>This certainly had an effect on SOL’s price. At the time of writing, SOL is trading at $20.63, up 30% in the last seven days. </p>
<h2><strong>Rejection Line And What It Means</strong></h2>
<p>Meanwhile, the token was rejected at $25, which could mean that bears will be able to test the two support levels that helped SOL reach its peak price. In the next few days, SOL is seen retesting the $18 and $16 supports. </p>
<img loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-516712 size-large" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/sol-chart-860x394.png" alt="" width="860" height="394" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/sol-chart-860x394.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/sol-chart-460x210.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/sol-chart-768x351.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/sol-chart-750x343.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/sol-chart-1140x522.png 1140w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/sol-chart.png 1521w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" />

Chart: TradingView.com

<p>SOL’s bullish pace in the weekly timeframe would certainly have an effect on the token’s ability to recover from the rejection. </p>
<p>Although it is highly likely that the $18 support will break, investors and traders can rely on $16 as a launching pad to retest $25 in the coming days or weeks. </p>
<p>If $25 is broken, $30 should be the next target as a breakthrough in this area would give SOL bulls legroom for more upward movement. </p>
<p>SOL can rely on a solid ecosystem and a <a href="https://twitter.com/rrezi16/status/1615044107780624384?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">bullish</a> community to recover lost ground.</p>
<p><em>Featured image by Sunshine Adult Day Care </em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Solana-6-460x258.png" width="460" height="258" />	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>

<!--
Performance optimized by W3 Total Cache. Learn more: https://www.boldgrid.com/w3-total-cache/

Object Caching 231/234 objects using apc
Page Caching using disk: enhanced (Page is feed) 
Database Caching 31/44 queries in 0.008 seconds using memcached

Served from: newsbtc.com @ 2023-01-19 22:23:39 by W3 Total Cache
-->