<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
>

<channel>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.newsbtc.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<description>Bitcoin &#38; cryptocurrency news today, price &#38; technical analysis</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 22:01:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>China Is Fast Losing Money: Their Bitcoin Stash Just Fell By $388 Million</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/china-is-fast-losing-money-their-bitcoin-stash-just-fell-by-388-million/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dalmas Ngetich]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 22:00:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin trading ban]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[china]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=527865</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[When Bitcoin prices fell from $31,000 to below $29,000, the total value of BTC held by China fell by over $388 million to around $5,4 billion.  China’s Bitcoin Stash Fell By $388 Million Bitcoin is trading below $28,500 and looks likely to edge even lower, considering the formation in the daily chart. With every tick lower, China and other countries, including Ukraine and Georgia, are losing money. The loss could even be bigger for the Chinese considering their big stash of BTC, which translates to around 0.924% of the total fixed supply of 21 million, according to Bitcoin Treasuries data. Related Reading: Bitcoin In Danger Zone: Bulls Must Hold $27,700 For Price Recovery, Expert Suggests Records show that China holds 194,000 BTC, 833,000 ETH, and a variety of other unnamed cryptocurrencies. These digital assets were confiscated from the PlusToken scam in 2019 and were worth over $3 billion. FUN FACT: Government of China🇨🇳 is a crypto whale. Chinese authorities seized 194k BTC, 833k ETH, and others from the PlusToken scam in 2019. They forfeited these $6 billion-worth assets to the national treasury. FWIW, MicroStrategy has 130k $BTC. pic.twitter.com/Ilqp7EnenL &#8212; Ki Young Ju (@ki_young_ju) November 2, 2022 According to reports, these assets were tied to the country’s national treasury. Still, some funds associated with the scam are reportedly being regularly sent to mixers and liquidated at spot rates, impacting prices. However, whether the Chinese government still holds these assets remain unknown. There is no official Bitcoin address to verify the status of these coins. PlusToken Scam was a global Ponzi scheme targeting Chinese and South Korean investors. It started in April 2018, taking advantage of unsuspecting people who thought they could make quick money from an investment opportunity. All users had to pay for registration using cryptocurrencies, mainly BTC, before investing. Perpetrators said they were developing cryptocurrency products.  Six Chinese nationals were arrested in Vanuatu and extradited to China to face the law in June 2019. A year later, the Chinese Ministry of Public Security said they arrested other suspects, recovering over $3 billion of crypto assets. United States Is A Crypto Leader  Cryptocurrency trading and related operations, including mining, are banned in China. Therefore, whether Chinese authorities will “trade” these cryptocurrencies for other assets is unclear for now. Related Reading: Quant Explains Bitcoin Funding Rates Pattern That Precedes Uptrends The country outlawed trading in 2017 and mining in 2021, forcing crypto miners, mainly of Bitcoin, to other jurisdictions. Since the ban, the United States has emerged as the biggest host of crypto mining operations. China accounted for over 50% of all crypto mining operations at peak. According to trackers, the largest public Bitcoin mining companies are in the United States and Canada. Riot Blockchain is the largest publicly listed Bitcoin mining company with a market cap of $1.82 billion. Feature Image From Canva, Chart From TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>When Bitcoin prices fell from $31,000 to below $29,000, the total value of BTC held by China <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://buybitcoinworldwide.com/treasuries/#countries" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">fell</a> by over $388 million to around $5,4 billion. </p>
<h2>China’s Bitcoin Stash Fell By $388 Million</h2>
<p>Bitcoin is trading below $28,500 and looks likely to edge even lower, considering the formation in the daily chart. With every tick lower, China and other countries, including Ukraine and Georgia, are losing money.</p>
<a href="https://www.tradingview.com/x/7FtHM1CE/" rel="nofollow"><img decoding="async" class="size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/7FtHM1CE/" alt="Bitcoin Price On April 20| Source: BTCUSDT On Binance, TradingView" width="1280" height="595" /></a>
<p>The loss could even be bigger for the Chinese considering their big stash of BTC, which translates to around 0.924% of the total fixed supply of 21 million, according to Bitcoin Treasuries data.</p>

<p>Records show that China holds 194,000 BTC, 833,000 ETH, and a variety of other unnamed cryptocurrencies. These digital assets were confiscated from the PlusToken scam in 2019 and were worth over $3 billion.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">FUN FACT: Government of China<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f1e8-1f1f3.png" alt="🇨🇳" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> is a crypto whale.</p>
<p>Chinese authorities seized 194k BTC, 833k ETH, and others from the PlusToken scam in 2019. They forfeited these $6 billion-worth assets to the national treasury.</p>
<p>FWIW, MicroStrategy has 130k <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24BTC&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$BTC</a>. <a href="https://t.co/Ilqp7EnenL" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/Ilqp7EnenL</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Ki Young Ju (@ki_young_ju) <a href="https://twitter.com/ki_young_ju/status/1587917712126144512?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">November 2, 2022</a></p></blockquote>
<p></p>
<p>According to reports, these assets were tied to the country’s national treasury. Still, some funds associated with the scam are reportedly being regularly sent to mixers and liquidated at spot rates, impacting prices.</p>
<p>However, whether the Chinese government still holds these assets remain unknown. There is no official Bitcoin address to verify the status of these coins.</p>
<p>PlusToken Scam was a global Ponzi scheme targeting Chinese and South Korean investors. It started in April 2018, taking advantage of unsuspecting people who thought they could make quick money from an investment opportunity. </p>
<p>All users had to pay for registration using cryptocurrencies, mainly BTC, before investing. Perpetrators said they were developing cryptocurrency products. </p>
<p>Six Chinese nationals were arrested in Vanuatu and extradited to China to face the law in June 2019. A year later, the Chinese Ministry of Public Security said they arrested other suspects, recovering over $3 billion of crypto assets.</p>
<h2>United States Is A Crypto Leader </h2>
<p>Cryptocurrency trading and related operations, including mining, are banned in China. Therefore, whether Chinese authorities will “trade” these cryptocurrencies for other assets is unclear for now.</p>

<p>The country outlawed trading in 2017 and mining in 2021, forcing crypto miners, mainly of Bitcoin, to other jurisdictions. Since the ban, the United States has emerged as the biggest host of crypto mining operations. China accounted for over 50% of all crypto mining operations at peak.</p>
<p>According to <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://companiesmarketcap.com/bitcoin-mining/largest-bitcoin-mining-companies-by-marketcap/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">trackers</a>, the largest public Bitcoin mining companies are in the United States and Canada. Riot Blockchain is the largest publicly listed Bitcoin mining company with a market cap of $1.82 billion.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/China-Bitcoin-460x260.jpg" width="460" height="260" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>XRP Correction Continues: Elliott Waves Theory Predicts Wave 2 At $0.38</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/xrp-correction-continues-elliott-waves-theory-predicts-wave-2-at-0-38/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 21:00:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple (XRP) Price Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrpusdt]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=528032</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Since reaching its yearly high of $0.5842 on March 29th, XRP has experienced a significant price drop. The token has lost its bullish momentum and failed to breach higher levels, disappointing investors who were optimistic about the uptrend of one of the largest cryptocurrencies in the market. It is worth noting that XRP&#8217;s recent price drop is part of a wider market correction affecting the entire cryptocurrency market. Despite this, trader and crypto analyst &#8220;Dark Defender&#8221; believes that there is still further correction ahead for XRP. Related Reading: Is The Final Shakeout Moment Coming For Bitcoin? Expert Weighs In No Signs Of Recovery For XRP? On April 1st, Dark Defender made a bold prediction for the price of XRP based on Elliott Waves theory. According to Dark Defender, the token completed its first wave (W1) at around $0.59 and is expected to enter a second wave (W2) that will find support between $0.48 and $0.38. As of now, there have been no changes to Dark Defender&#8217;s prediction, and XRP remains in correction unless it breaks its resistance level of $0.59 and stays above it for three consecutive days. Dark Defender has provided a list of support levels for XRP, including $0.4812, $0.45544, $0.42044, and $0.38813. The analyst believes that XRP will finish this last correction at one of these levels before targeting the $3 mark.  Furthermore, the analyst has provided a bullish prediction for XRP&#8217;s future, stating that the third wave (W3) of this structure is expected to reach between $2 and $3.47 by the end of this year. However, this wave 3 above $1.33 will be the predecessor of the Grand Wave 3. In scenario 2, Dark Defender predicts that XRP will continue to rise in value. As of this writing, XRP is currently trading at $0.4582, which represents a drop of over 2.6% in the last 24 hours. On wider time frames, the token has recorded significant drops of 11% and 9.2% in the seven and fourteen-day time frames, respectively. This means that if Dark Defender’s prediction is correct, XRP may still have plenty of downtrends to experience, potentially reaching the lower lows of March 21st at $0.380. XRP&#8217;s Wide Adoption Continues To Increase XRP has been gaining traction in recent months, with its unique utility in cross-border payments attracting attention from financial institutions and investors, which has been raising with its continuous innovations to provide a better service to its users.  According to pro-XRP lawyer John Deaton, Uphold, a digital platform that allows users to buy, sell, and hold various cryptocurrencies and traditional currencies, currently holds $1.04 billion in XRP, making XRP the single largest asset holding on the platform. This amount is significantly greater than Uphold’s Bitcoin holdings, which currently stand at $131 million. In addition, the token volume accounted for 28.33% of total transactions on Uphold&#8217;s platform. This indicates a growing demand for XRP among Uphold&#8217;s user base and suggests a positive outlook for the cryptocurrency&#8217;s future growth and adoption. Related Reading: Shiba Inu Whales On Buying Spree, Add 311 Billion Tokens During Price Dip Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com  &#160;]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Since reaching its yearly high of $0.5842 on March 29th, XRP has experienced a significant price drop. The token has lost its bullish momentum and failed to breach higher levels, disappointing investors who were optimistic about the uptrend of one of the largest cryptocurrencies in the market.</p>
<p>It is worth noting that XRP&#8217;s recent price drop is part of a wider market correction affecting the entire cryptocurrency market. Despite this, trader and crypto analyst &#8220;Dark Defender&#8221; <a href="https://twitter.com/DefendDark/status/1649329730624057345?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">believes </a>that there is still further correction ahead for XRP.</p>

<h2><b>No Signs Of Recovery For XRP?</b></h2>
<p>On April 1st, Dark Defender made a bold prediction for the price of XRP based on Elliott Waves theory. According to Dark Defender, the token completed its first wave (W1) at around $0.59 and is expected to enter a second wave (W2) that will find support between $0.48 and $0.38.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large wp-image-528034" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/FuOXb0TWYAc8_qE-860x484.jpg" alt="XRP" width="860" height="484" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/FuOXb0TWYAc8_qE-860x484.jpg 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/FuOXb0TWYAc8_qE-460x259.jpg 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/FuOXb0TWYAc8_qE-768x432.jpg 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/FuOXb0TWYAc8_qE-750x422.jpg 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/FuOXb0TWYAc8_qE-1140x641.jpg 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/FuOXb0TWYAc8_qE.jpg 1366w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" />
<p>As of now, there have been no changes to Dark Defender&#8217;s prediction, and XRP remains in correction unless it breaks its resistance level of $0.59 and stays above it for three consecutive days. Dark Defender has provided a list of support levels for XRP, including $0.4812, $0.45544, $0.42044, and $0.38813. The analyst believes that XRP will finish this last correction at one of these levels before targeting the $3 mark. </p>
<p>Furthermore, the analyst has provided a bullish prediction for XRP&#8217;s future, stating that the third wave (W3) of this structure is expected to reach between $2 and $3.47 by the end of this year. However, this wave 3 above $1.33 will be the predecessor of the Grand Wave 3. In scenario 2, Dark Defender predicts that XRP will continue to rise in value.</p>
<p>As of this writing, XRP is currently trading at $0.4582, which represents a drop of over 2.6% in the last 24 hours. On wider time frames, the token has recorded significant drops of 11% and 9.2% in the seven and fourteen-day time frames, respectively. This means that if Dark Defender’s prediction is correct, XRP may still have plenty of downtrends to experience, potentially reaching the lower lows of March 21st at $0.380.</p>
<b>XRP&#8217;s Wide Adoption Continues To Increase</b>
<p>XRP has been gaining traction in recent months, with its unique utility in cross-border payments attracting attention from financial institutions and investors, which has been raising with its continuous innovations to provide a better service to its users. </p>
<p><a href="https://twitter.com/JohnEDeaton1/status/1647297372613910532?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">According </a>to pro-XRP lawyer John Deaton, Uphold, a digital platform that allows users to buy, sell, and hold various cryptocurrencies and traditional currencies, currently holds $1.04 billion in XRP, making XRP the single largest asset holding on the platform. This amount is significantly greater than Uphold’s Bitcoin holdings, which currently stand at $131 million.</p>
<p>In addition, the token volume accounted for 28.33% of total transactions on Uphold&#8217;s platform. This indicates a growing demand for XRP among Uphold&#8217;s user base and suggests a positive outlook for the cryptocurrency&#8217;s future growth and adoption.</p>

<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large wp-image-528033" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/XRPUSDT_2023-04-21_14-25-42_8d0dd-860x407.png" alt="XRP" width="860" height="407" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/XRPUSDT_2023-04-21_14-25-42_8d0dd-860x407.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/XRPUSDT_2023-04-21_14-25-42_8d0dd-460x218.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/XRPUSDT_2023-04-21_14-25-42_8d0dd-768x363.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/XRPUSDT_2023-04-21_14-25-42_8d0dd-1536x727.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/XRPUSDT_2023-04-21_14-25-42_8d0dd-750x355.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/XRPUSDT_2023-04-21_14-25-42_8d0dd-1140x539.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/XRPUSDT_2023-04-21_14-25-42_8d0dd.png 1814w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" />
<p>Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com </p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/stormseeker-rX12B5uX7QM-unsplash-307x460.jpg" width="307" height="460" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Time To Pay Attention: Bitcoin Reaches &#8220;Logical&#8221; Level</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/time-to-pay-attention-bitcoin-reaches-logical-level/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tony "The Bull"]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 20:04:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bollinger bands]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=528037</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin price is experiencing one of its more significant corrections since the trend began to change directions.  According to the creator of the Bollinger Bands, it’s once again “time to pay attention” — this time because BTCUSD has pulled back to a “logical” level.  Bitcoin Begins Pullback To Logical Level Bitcoin reached almost double from current bear market lows, nearly convincing the crypto community a new bullish trend had begun. With BTCUSD now down more than 10% from local highs, fear is already back on the air in a major way.  Bulls are now all but silent, after just recently declaring the bull market has returned. Bears are already celebrating the correction as continuation of the bearish trend getting underway. Related Reading: Brace Yourself: The Most Explosive Move In Bitcoin In Years Has Begun More tactical technicians, like John Bollinger, simply believe it’s “time to pay attention,” and haven’t yet taken a side. The quote has become a bit of a catchphrase for the creator of the Bollinger Bands. But what exactly is he talking about? The creator of the Bollinger Bands has spoken &#124; BTCUSD on TradingView.com All About The Bollinger Bands The Bollinger Bands are a volatility measuring tool. The tool’s creator recently pointed out an expansion after a lengthy phase or narrowing. This behavior is referred to as a “squeeze” and suggests an uptick in volatility is ahead. Which is precisely what we are witnessing now.  Volatility is the measure of price dispersion across a timeframe, and after very little movement, BTCUSD is like a rollercoaster once again. Ups and downs are par for the course. Related Reading: This “Super” Bitcoin Technical Tool Says Limited Resistance Remains  The Bollinger Bands are made up of a 20-period simple moving average (SMA), to where price pulled back to and has now broken below. The upper and lower bands are set at two standard deviations of the SMA. The next logical level to look for support would be the lower band, located at around $27,000. Once Bitcoin hits the level it could continue downward with strength or snap back to the top of the band.  One thing is for sure, the tool predicting volatility was accurate. Now it’s time to pay attention. As a journalist I often cover the greatest calls by the best in the biz. As a trader, I never forget the corresponding price action, allowing me to learn at every turn. Same vibes. Pay attention. pic.twitter.com/cbpjaK9Ntd &#8212; Tony &#34;The Bull&#34; (@tonythebullBTC) April 20, 2023 Follow @TonyTheBullBTC &#38; @coinchartist_io on Twitter or join the TonyTradesBTC Telegram for exclusive daily market insights and technical analysis education. Please note: Content is educational and should not be considered investment advice. Featured image from iStockPhoto, Charts from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin price is experiencing one of its more significant corrections since the trend began to change directions. </p>
<p>According to the creator of the Bollinger Bands, it’s once again “time to pay attention” — this time because BTCUSD has pulled back to a “logical” level. </p>
<h2>Bitcoin Begins Pullback To Logical Level</h2>
<p>Bitcoin reached almost double from current bear market lows, nearly convincing the crypto community a new bullish trend had begun. With BTCUSD now down more than 10% from local highs, fear is already back on the air in a major way. </p>
<p>Bulls are now all but silent, after just recently declaring the bull market has returned. Bears are already celebrating the correction as continuation of the bearish trend getting underway.</p>

<p>More tactical technicians, like John Bollinger, simply believe it’s “time to pay attention,” and haven’t yet taken a side. The quote has become a bit of a catchphrase for the creator of the Bollinger Bands. But what exactly is he talking about?</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-large wp-image-528039" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/BTCUSD_2023-04-21_15-33-50-860x371.png" alt="BTCUSD_2023-04-21_15-33-50" width="860" height="371" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/BTCUSD_2023-04-21_15-33-50-860x371.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/BTCUSD_2023-04-21_15-33-50-460x198.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/BTCUSD_2023-04-21_15-33-50-768x331.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/BTCUSD_2023-04-21_15-33-50-1536x663.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/BTCUSD_2023-04-21_15-33-50-2048x883.png 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/BTCUSD_2023-04-21_15-33-50-750x323.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/BTCUSD_2023-04-21_15-33-50-1140x492.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" /></p>

<h2>All About The Bollinger Bands</h2>
<p>The <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/topic/bollinger-bands/">Bollinger Bands</a> are a volatility measuring tool. The tool’s creator recently pointed out an expansion after a lengthy phase or narrowing. This behavior is referred to as a “squeeze” and suggests an uptick in volatility is ahead. Which is precisely what we are witnessing now. </p>
<p>Volatility is the measure of price dispersion across a timeframe, and after very little movement, BTCUSD is like a rollercoaster once again. Ups and downs are par for the course.</p>

<p>The Bollinger Bands are made up of a 20-period simple moving average (SMA), to where price pulled back to and has now broken below. The upper and lower bands are set at two standard deviations of the SMA.</p>
<p>The next logical level to look for support would be the lower band, located at around $27,000. Once Bitcoin hits the level it could continue downward with strength or snap back to the top of the band. </p>
<p>One thing is for sure, the tool predicting volatility was accurate. Now it’s time to pay attention.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">As a journalist I often cover the greatest calls by the best in the biz. </p>
<p>As a trader, I never forget the corresponding price action, allowing me to learn at every turn. </p>
<p>Same vibes. Pay attention. <a href="https://t.co/cbpjaK9Ntd" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/cbpjaK9Ntd</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Tony &quot;The Bull&quot; (@tonythebullBTC) <a href="https://twitter.com/tonythebullBTC/status/1649156364860628993?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">April 20, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p></p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/iStock-1294571597-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tornado Cash Suffers 13% Bear Hit, Will Parole Save Price?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/tornado-cash-suffers-bear-hit-parole-save-price/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mudiaga Iritare]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 20:00:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[TORN Token]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tornado Cash]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tornado Cash price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=527955</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Tornado Cash token (TORN) is trading on a negative 13% in today&#8217;s trade session, canceling its previous day&#8217;s gains and rally, which saw the token rise close to the $12 mark. Coinmarketcap data reveals the token to be trading at $8.77 at the time of writing, a significant drop from where it was in price yesterday. The TORN token and its decentralized mixing service platform became controversial when its developer, Alexey Pertev, was arrested mid-last year allegedly for money laundering. However, news about the possible jail release of Alexey circulated the industry yesterday, April 20, and created a rally for the TORN token. Related Reading: FTT Token On a 8% Rockslide Despite FTX Ray Of Hope. Here’s Why Tornado Cash Developer Set To Be Released On This Date According to a recent report, the developer of the TORN token, Alexey Pertev, is expected to be released on April 26, 2023, after spending nine months in detention without trial. The news of his potential release came yesterday when the crypto markets were declining. However, the Tornado Cash token reacted to the news of Alexey&#8217;s release and defied market conditions by displaying bullish price action. While the rally drew investors&#8217; attention, the token could not continue its upward movements today despite positive price speculations by crypto experts and analysts. Alexey Pertev, who is set to be released next Wednesday, will await trial from his home as ruled by a court in the Netherlands. Upon his release, electronic monitoring devices such as an ankle bracelet will be installed on him and other monitoring devices in his home, according to the report. At the time of writing, the TORN token is currently ranked among the top 3 losers in the cryptocurrency market. Alexey Pertev&#8217;s release date is approaching, and we may witness Tornado Cash reacting in price as it did with the news about his release. &#160; TORN token trades in a steep decline after previous day rally &#124; Source: TORNUSD on TradingView &#160; Related Reading: Bitcoin Bears Steal 3%, Time To DCA? Bitcoin Price Impact On TORN Token Bitcoin is on its 3-day bearish candle, failing to break the resistance slightly above the $30,000 price region. BTC price lost momentum after its previous week&#8217;s rally and failed to hold the key support level at $29,200. Today&#8217;s trading session saw Bitcoin falling below $28,000 after it failed to hold $28,600 key support. BTC price fell to a 24-hour low of $27,815 but is now slightly back above the $28,000 price region. Some Altcoins, including the Tornado Cash token, have brutally suffered from the Bitcoin price dump and are still yet to recover. However, a healthy recovery for Bitcoin price will be a good turning point for Tornado Cash as Altcoins are known to react to BTC price movements. BTC price seen trading below support at $28,600 &#124; Souce: BTCUSD on TradingView.com &#160; Featured Image from Istock, Charts from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://ipfs.io/ipns/tornadocash-ipfs.eth/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Tornado Cash</a> token (TORN) is trading on a negative 13% in today&#8217;s trade session, canceling its previous day&#8217;s gains and rally, which saw the token rise close to the $12 mark. Coinmarketcap data reveals the token to be trading at $8.77 at the time of writing, a significant drop from where it was in price yesterday.</p>
<p>The TORN token and its decentralized mixing service platform became controversial when its developer, Alexey Pertev, was arrested mid-last year allegedly for money laundering. However, news about the possible jail release of Alexey circulated the industry yesterday, April 20, and created a rally for the TORN token.
</p>

<h2>Tornado Cash Developer Set To Be Released On This Date</h2>
<p>According to a recent <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tornado-cash-developer-pertsev-freed-110908882.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">report</a>, the developer of the TORN token, Alexey Pertev, is expected to be released on April 26, 2023, after spending nine months in detention without trial.</p>
<p>The news of his potential release came yesterday when the crypto markets were declining. However, the Tornado Cash token reacted to the news of Alexey&#8217;s release and defied market conditions by displaying bullish price action.</p>
<p>While the rally drew investors&#8217; attention, the token could not continue its upward movements today despite positive price speculations by crypto experts and analysts.</p>
<p>Alexey Pertev, who is set to be released next Wednesday, will await trial from his home as ruled by a court in the Netherlands.</p>
<p>Upon his release, electronic monitoring devices such as an ankle bracelet will be installed on him and other monitoring devices in his home, according to the report.</p>
<p>At the time of writing, the TORN token is currently ranked among the top 3 losers in the cryptocurrency market. Alexey Pertev&#8217;s release date is approaching, and we may witness Tornado Cash reacting in price as it did with the news about his release.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/osppCAuG/" alt="Tornado" width="1280" height="595" /></p>

<p>&nbsp;</p>

<h2>Bitcoin Price Impact On TORN Token</h2>
<p>Bitcoin is on its 3-day bearish candle, failing to break the resistance slightly above the $30,000 price region. <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/btc-bears-steal-price-time-to-dca/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BTC</a> price lost momentum after its previous week&#8217;s rally and failed to hold the key support level at $29,200.</p>
<p>Today&#8217;s trading session saw Bitcoin falling below $28,000 after it failed to hold $28,600 key support. BTC price fell to a 24-hour low of $27,815 but is now slightly back above the $28,000 price region.</p>
<p>Some Altcoins, including the Tornado Cash token, have brutally suffered from the Bitcoin price dump and are still yet to recover. However, a healthy recovery for <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-exchange-outflows-spike-bullish-sign/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin price</a> will be a good turning point for Tornado Cash as Altcoins are known to react to BTC price movements.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/IfWR2Kai/" alt="Tornado" width="1280" height="595" /></p>

<p>&nbsp;</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/iStock-1371840452-1-460x248.jpg" width="460" height="248" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Is The Final Shakeout Moment Coming For Bitcoin? Expert Weighs In</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/is-the-final-shakeout-moment-coming-for-bitcoin-expert-weighs-in/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 18:27:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=527977</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[In January of this year, Bitcoin broke above its 200-day MA for the first time since the end of 2021. This was a significant milestone for the cryptocurrency, as it had not seen such a signal in over a year. This breakout was a clear indication of Bitcoin&#8217;s bullish momentum and its potential for further growth in the future. Additionally, Bitcoin retested the 200-day moving average in March and remained well above it, demonstrating its robust behavior. However, the leading cryptocurrency is approaching a lower-level retest at $28,000. Whether Bitcoin will withstand further price decline and continue its bullish trend or if a final shakeout is imminent. Bitcoin&#8217;s Halving Cycle And Potential Dip Below The 200-Day MA Recently, there has been speculation that Bitcoin’s price might be poised for a significant rally as spring arrives. However, the situation is not quite simple as with many things in the crypto world.  According to the expert in the cryptocurrency industry, Mr. Ben Lily, the current halving cycle is an important factor to consider when evaluating Bitcoin’s price movements. When BTC comes off halving cycle lows, it commonly does not immediately clear the 200-day moving average (MA) and stays above it. Instead, it tends to return below the 200-day MA before ultimately moving on to form all-time highs. This pattern can be observed in the chart below, which shows the 200-day MA (represented by the dark red line) and the orange circles, which indicate when the price dipped below the 200-day MA. Furthermore, Lily argues that nothing suggests that the market should expect anything different this time. He believes a catalyst coming this summer will coincide with Bitcoin&#8217;s price dipping below the 200-day MA.  FedNow Rollout And Bitcoin: A Tale Of Two Timing Additionally, Ben Lily has provided further analysis on the potential impact of the upcoming rollout of the Federal Reserve&#8217;s CBDC, FedNow, on Bitcoin’s price movements. According to Lily, if the rollout occurs as scheduled in July, it could benefit BTC’s price trajectory. However, Lily notes that in each of the last three halving cycles, Bitcoin’s price dipped below the 200-day moving average (MA) between 217 and 315 days before the halving itself. If this pattern holds for the current halving cycle, we can expect BTC’s price to dip below the 200-day MA sometime between June and August. With FedNow set to roll out in the middle of that period, Lily suggests we can expect regulator &#8220;war drumming&#8221; to be at a fever pitch. This could lead to a final shakeout moment as Bitcoin drops below the 200-day MA, creating a higher low in the market. At the moment of writing, Bitcoin, the largest cryptocurrency by market capitalization, is being traded at $28,000, indicating a decrease of over 2.5% in the last 24 hours. And, as reported yesterday by NewsBTC, the $27,700 line is key for Bitcoin, as a breakout below this level could signal a shift in the market sentiment and potentially lead to a further decline in price. Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In January of this year, Bitcoin broke above its 200-day MA for the first time since the end of 2021. This was a significant milestone for the cryptocurrency, as it had not seen such a signal in over a year. This breakout was a clear indication of Bitcoin&#8217;s bullish momentum and its potential for further growth in the future.</p>
<p>Additionally, Bitcoin retested the 200-day moving average in March and remained well above it, demonstrating its robust behavior. However, the leading cryptocurrency is approaching a lower-level retest at $28,000. Whether Bitcoin will withstand further price decline and continue its bullish trend or if a final shakeout is imminent.</p>
<h2><b>Bitcoin&#8217;s Halving Cycle And Potential Dip Below The 200-Day MA</b></h2>
<p>Recently, there has been speculation that Bitcoin’s price might be poised for a significant rally as spring arrives. However, the situation is not quite simple as with many things in the crypto world. </p>
<p><a href="https://jarvislabs.substack.com/p/when-to-expect-the-final-shakeout" rel="nofollow">According </a>to the expert in the cryptocurrency industry, Mr. Ben Lily, the current halving cycle is an important factor to consider when evaluating Bitcoin’s price movements. When BTC comes off halving cycle lows, it commonly does not immediately clear the 200-day moving average (MA) and stays above it.</p>
<p>Instead, it tends to return below the 200-day MA before ultimately moving on to form all-time highs. This pattern can be observed in the chart below, which shows the 200-day MA (represented by the dark red line) and the orange circles, which indicate when the price dipped below the 200-day MA.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large wp-image-527978" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/6b9df245-ec9d-4fb4-ae8d-3ff70e9f75b9_1280x606-860x407.jpg" alt="Bitcoin " width="860" height="407" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/6b9df245-ec9d-4fb4-ae8d-3ff70e9f75b9_1280x606-860x407.jpg 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/6b9df245-ec9d-4fb4-ae8d-3ff70e9f75b9_1280x606-460x218.jpg 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/6b9df245-ec9d-4fb4-ae8d-3ff70e9f75b9_1280x606-768x364.jpg 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/6b9df245-ec9d-4fb4-ae8d-3ff70e9f75b9_1280x606-750x355.jpg 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/6b9df245-ec9d-4fb4-ae8d-3ff70e9f75b9_1280x606-1140x540.jpg 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/6b9df245-ec9d-4fb4-ae8d-3ff70e9f75b9_1280x606.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" />
<p>Furthermore, Lily argues that nothing suggests that the market should expect anything different this time. He believes a catalyst coming this summer will coincide with Bitcoin&#8217;s price dipping below the 200-day MA. </p>
<b>FedNow Rollout And Bitcoin: A Tale Of Two Timing</b>
<p>Additionally, Ben Lily has provided further analysis on the potential impact of the upcoming rollout of the Federal Reserve&#8217;s CBDC, FedNow, on Bitcoin’s price movements. According to Lily, if the rollout occurs as scheduled in July, it could benefit BTC’s price trajectory.</p>
<p>However, Lily notes that in each of the last three halving cycles, Bitcoin’s price dipped below the 200-day moving average (MA) between 217 and 315 days before the halving itself. If this pattern holds for the current halving cycle, we can expect BTC’s price to dip below the 200-day MA sometime between June and August.</p>
<p>With FedNow set to roll out in the middle of that period, Lily suggests we can expect regulator &#8220;war drumming&#8221; to be at a fever pitch. This could lead to a final shakeout moment as Bitcoin drops below the 200-day MA, creating a higher low in the market.</p>
<p>At the moment of writing, Bitcoin, the largest cryptocurrency by market capitalization, is being traded at $28,000, indicating a decrease of over 2.5% in the last 24 hours. And, as <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-in-danger-zone-bulls-must-hold-27700-for-price-recovery-expert-suggests/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">reported</a> yesterday by NewsBTC, the $27,700 line is key for Bitcoin, as a breakout below this level could signal a shift in the market sentiment and potentially lead to a further decline in price.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/ywcwTTsu/" alt="Bitcoin " width="1813" height="858" />
<p>Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/kanchanara-9pCV2MB65y8-unsplash-1-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Shiba Inu Whales On Buying Spree, Add 311 Billion Tokens During Price Dip</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/shiba-inu-whales-on-buying-spree-add-311-billion-tokens-during-price-dip/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Eli Dambell]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 16:00:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Shiba Inu]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bull]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIBUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=527958</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Whales have resumed their Shiba Inu buying spree as the meme coin price declined alongside the global crypto market. According to the WhaleStats report, a top ETH whale picked up $3.22 million worth of SHIB tokens over the past 24 hours. The Ethereum whale performed the purchase in two transactions, scooping over 311 billion Siba Inu tokens within minutes. Shiba Inu’s Price Correction Attracts Top ETH Whales Shiba Inu has been on the list of preferred assets among top Ethereum whales over the past few months. The whales actively packed large chunks of SHIB tokens between January and February. However, it appears the whales went on break, waiting for another opportunity to strike. Related Reading: Cardano In Strong Demand Zone, Breaking Through Key Level Crucial A recent alert from the crypto tracking platform, WhaleStats, shows the 254th-biggest Ethereum whale purchased 311,998,734,794 SHIB tokens on April 20. The whale performed the transaction in two consecutive transactions. The whale bought 194,114,774,578 Shiba Inu tokens worth $2,069,263 before initiating another transaction for 117,883,216 SHIB worth $1,256,643. The unexpected token accumulation comes as Shiba Inu&#8217;s price fell from its critical support level at $0.0000107. Shiba Inu Price Outlook Amid Burn Rate Spikes The recent price decline comes after several days of massive SHIB token burn by the Shiba Inu community to boost the meme coin’s price. In the days following the Shibarium PuppyNet launch, large chunks of Shiba Inu coins went into the dead wallets.  On April 20, the Shiba Inu token burn rate spiked by 3,500%, according to the burn tracking website, Shibburn. Following Shibburn’s hourly update, April 20 saw another 5,180% burn rate spike.  Related Reading: Cardano Racks Up Nearly 4% Gain Amid Short-Term Losses – Will Investors Hold Firm? Given Shiba Inu’s massive circulation supply of tokens, the recent burn had little effect on the meme coin&#8217;s price. The token traded bearishly yesterday, with a 7.0% price decline, and has continued in the downtrend today. SHIB is slightly recovering after forming three consecutive red candles on the daily chart. The bears have dominated the market, pushing SHIB close to its support zone. Shiba Inu has dropped below its 50-day and 200-day Simple Moving Averages (SMA), a bearish sentiment for the short and long term.  Also, the Relative Strength Index (RSI) is 41.22, close to the oversold region of 30. The indicator is moving downwards, suggesting further decline for the asset. SHIB&#8217;s support levels are $0.0000085 and $0.0000102, with resistance levels at $0.0000115 and $0.0000112. SHIB is close to the $0.0000102 support level. If the level does not hold, expect further price decline from the asset in the coming days. At press time, Shiba Inu is trading at $0.00001061, and the price is rising after declining by 3.6%. Featured image from Pixabay and chart from Tradingview]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Whales have resumed their Shiba Inu buying spree as the meme coin price declined alongside the global crypto market. According to the WhaleStats <a href="https://twitter.com/WhaleStats/status/1649138216702824449" rel="nofollow">report</a>, a top ETH whale picked up $3.22 million worth of SHIB tokens over the past 24 hours.</p>
<p>The Ethereum whale performed the purchase in two transactions, scooping over 311 billion Siba Inu tokens within minutes.</p>
<h2><b>Shiba Inu’s Price Correction Attracts Top ETH Whales</b></h2>
<p>Shiba Inu has been on the list of preferred assets among top Ethereum whales over the past few months. The whales actively packed large chunks of SHIB tokens between January and February. However, it appears the whales went on break, waiting for another opportunity to strike.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/cardano/cardano-in-strong-demand-zone-breaking-through-key-level-crucial/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Cardano In Strong Demand Zone, Breaking Through Key Level Crucial</a></p>
<p>A recent alert from the crypto tracking platform, WhaleStats, shows the 254th-biggest Ethereum whale purchased 311,998,734,794 SHIB tokens on April 20. The whale performed the transaction in two consecutive transactions.</p>
<p>The whale <a href="https://twitter.com/WhaleStats/status/1649138216702824449" rel="nofollow">bought 194,114,774,578</a> Shiba Inu tokens worth $2,069,263 before initiating <a href="https://twitter.com/WhaleStats/status/1649138225590444036" rel="nofollow">another transaction</a> for 117,883,216 SHIB worth $1,256,643. The unexpected token accumulation comes as Shiba Inu&#8217;s price fell from its critical support level at $0.0000107.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-527961 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/SHIBUSDT_2023-04-21_18-00-00-860x501.png" alt="Shiba Inu Whales On Buying Spree, Add 311 Billion Tokens During Price Dip" width="860" height="501" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/SHIBUSDT_2023-04-21_18-00-00-860x501.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/SHIBUSDT_2023-04-21_18-00-00-460x268.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/SHIBUSDT_2023-04-21_18-00-00-768x447.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/SHIBUSDT_2023-04-21_18-00-00-750x437.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/SHIBUSDT_2023-04-21_18-00-00-1140x664.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/SHIBUSDT_2023-04-21_18-00-00.png 1437w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" />
<h2><b>Shiba Inu Price Outlook Amid Burn Rate Spikes</b></h2>
<p>The recent price decline comes after several days of massive SHIB token burn by the Shiba Inu community to boost the meme coin’s price. In the days following the Shibarium PuppyNet launch, large chunks of Shiba Inu coins went into the dead wallets. </p>
<p>On April 20, the Shiba Inu token <a href="https://twitter.com/shibburn/status/1649050356477984771?" rel="nofollow">burn rate</a> spiked by 3,500%, according to the burn tracking website, Shibburn. Following Shibburn’s <a href="https://twitter.com/shibburn/status/1649095653530779656?" rel="nofollow">hourly update</a>, April 20 saw another 5,180% burn rate spike. </p>

<p>Given Shiba Inu’s massive circulation supply of tokens, the recent burn had little effect on the meme coin&#8217;s price. The token traded bearishly yesterday, with a 7.0% price decline, and has continued in the downtrend today.</p>
<p>SHIB is slightly recovering after forming three consecutive red candles on the daily chart. The bears have dominated the market, pushing SHIB close to its support zone.</p>
<p>Shiba Inu has dropped below its 50-day and 200-day Simple Moving Averages (SMA), a bearish sentiment for the short and long term. </p>
<p>Also, the Relative Strength Index (RSI) is 41.22, close to the oversold region of 30. The indicator is moving downwards, suggesting further decline for the asset. SHIB&#8217;s support levels are $0.0000085 and $0.0000102, with resistance levels at $0.0000115 and $0.0000112.</p>
<p>SHIB is close to the $0.0000102 support level. If the level does not hold, expect further price decline from the asset in the coming days.</p>
<p>At press time, Shiba Inu is trading at $0.00001061, and the price is rising after declining by 3.6%.</p>
<p>Featured image from Pixabay and chart from Tradingview</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/shiba-inu-g800736d0f_1280-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Zilliqa (ZIL) Price Soars As Network Unveils Impressive Performance</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/zilliqa-zil-price-soars-as-network-unveils-impressive-performance/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Eli Dambell]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 15:00:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[smart contract]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ZILUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=527939</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Amid the bearish trend that suppressed several coin prices, including Bitcoin, the Zilliqa token emerged among the gainers. Zilliqa secured first place among top-gaining coins in the bearish cryptocurrency market with a 9% uptrend over the past 24 hours. This price move follows a network performance statistics update shared by a Twitter community member @inna_everstake. According to stats, Zilliqa reached a new milestone in network addresses and daily transactions. Zilliqa Hits Milestone In Network Activity Zilliqa is a permissionless public blockchain that offers high transaction throughput. It aims to improve blockchain scalability and speed using sharding as a layer2 scaling solution.  The Zilliqa network relies on shards to solve scalability issues. Each shard processes transactions independently. The number of transactions increases as the Zilliqa network grows and the number of shards increases. Related Reading: Shiba Inu (SHIB) Price Momentum Screeches To A Halt: What’s The Outlook? The recent network performance statistics suggest the Zilliqa network is rapidly growing and has gained more traction. According to the update, Zilliqa recorded 4,582,116 addresses with 47,937,935 transactions and over 5.5 billion staked ZIL tokens.  The statistics are incredible, given Zilliqa’s position in the cryptocurrency market compared to other Smart Contract platforms like Cardano, Ethereum, and Solana. Another notable fact is that the total addresses recorded participate in active daily transactions. Zilliqa’s improved performance could be due to the increasing number of new developers coming to build on the network. The Zilliqa ecosystem has been active in running innovative programs that attract new Web3 developers, which is why the network addresses and transactions skyrocketed. ZIL Price Outlook Amid The Boost In Network Performance Zilliqa is among the coins with the most dynamic price movement this year. Zilliqa opened in 2023 at $0.01585 but gradually rallied to its current price of $0.0331, a notable increase amid slight pullbacks. Although ZIL is still 87.33% down from its all-time high price of $0.2563, recorded on May 6, 2021, it has improved considerably since 2020.  ZIL&#8217;s price is over 1,210% higher than its all-time low of $0.002477 on March 13, 2020. At press time, ZIL is trading at $0.331, a 9% price increase from the April 20 closing price of $0.03015. Related Reading: OKB Tallies 24% Increase But Active Addresses Fail To Keep Pace – Here’s Why Even ZIL&#8217;s trading volume has increased by over 38% from $116.69 million on April 20 to $190.71 million today, April 21. That could be a further confirmation of increased network activity.  ZIL also recorded a nearly 11% price gain over the past seven days when coins like Bitcoin and Ethereum gave up theirs. The token now has over 12% price increase in the last two weeks. From the technical perspective, ZIL&#8217;s market sentiment is bullish, with the oscillators and moving averages flagging a strong buy signal. Featured image from Pixabay and chart from Tradingview]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Amid the bearish trend that suppressed several coin prices, including Bitcoin, the Zilliqa token emerged among the gainers. <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/zilliqa/" rel="nofollow">Zilliqa</a> secured first place among top-gaining coins in the bearish cryptocurrency market with a 9% uptrend over the past 24 hours.</p>
<p>This price move follows a network performance statistics <a href="https://twitter.com/inna_everstake/status/1649054720928124928?" rel="nofollow">update</a> shared by a Twitter community member @inna_everstake. According to stats, Zilliqa reached a new milestone in network addresses and daily transactions.</p>
<h2><b>Zilliqa Hits Milestone In Network Activity</b></h2>
<p>Zilliqa is a permissionless public blockchain that offers high transaction throughput. It aims to improve blockchain scalability and speed using sharding as a layer2 scaling solution. </p>
<p>The Zilliqa network relies on shards to solve scalability issues. Each shard processes transactions independently. The number of transactions increases as the Zilliqa network grows and the number of shards increases.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/shiba-inue-price-falters/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Shiba Inu (SHIB) Price Momentum Screeches To A Halt: What’s The Outlook?</a></p>
<p>The recent network performance statistics suggest the Zilliqa network is rapidly growing and has gained more traction. According to the update, Zilliqa recorded 4,582,116 addresses with 47,937,935 transactions and over 5.5 billion staked ZIL tokens. </p>
<p>The statistics are incredible, given Zilliqa’s position in the cryptocurrency market compared to other Smart Contract platforms like Cardano, Ethereum, and Solana. Another notable fact is that the total addresses recorded participate in active daily transactions.</p>
<p>Zilliqa’s improved performance could be due to the increasing number of new developers coming to build on the network. The Zilliqa ecosystem has been active in running innovative programs that attract new Web3 developers, which is why the network addresses and transactions skyrocketed.</p>
<h2><b>ZIL Price Outlook Amid The Boost In Network Performance</b></h2>
<p>Zilliqa is among the coins with the most dynamic price movement this year. Zilliqa opened in 2023 at $0.01585 but gradually rallied to its <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/zilliqa/" rel="nofollow">current price of $0.0331</a>, a notable increase amid slight pullbacks.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-527945 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/ZILUSDT_2023-04-21_16-29-25-860x501.png" alt="Zilliqa (ZIL) Price Soars As Network Unveils Impressive Performance" width="860" height="501" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/ZILUSDT_2023-04-21_16-29-25-860x501.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/ZILUSDT_2023-04-21_16-29-25-460x268.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/ZILUSDT_2023-04-21_16-29-25-768x447.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/ZILUSDT_2023-04-21_16-29-25-750x437.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/ZILUSDT_2023-04-21_16-29-25-1140x664.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/ZILUSDT_2023-04-21_16-29-25.png 1437w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" />
<p>Although ZIL is still 87.33% down from its all-time high price of $0.2563, recorded on May 6, 2021, it has improved considerably since 2020. </p>
<p>ZIL&#8217;s price is over 1,210% higher than its all-time low of $0.002477 on March 13, 2020. At press time, ZIL is trading at $0.331, a 9% price increase from the April 20 closing price of $0.03015.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/okb-tallies-24-increase-but-active-addresses-fail-to-keep-pace-heres-why/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener">OKB Tallies 24% Increase But Active Addresses Fail To Keep Pace – Here’s Why</a></p>
<p>Even ZIL&#8217;s trading volume has increased by over 38% from $116.69 million on April 20 to $190.71 million today, April 21. That could be a further confirmation of increased network activity. </p>
<p>ZIL also recorded a nearly <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/zilliqa" rel="nofollow">11% price gain</a> over the past seven days when coins like Bitcoin and Ethereum gave up theirs. The token now has over 12% price increase in the last two weeks.</p>
<p>From the technical perspective, ZIL&#8217;s market sentiment is bullish, with the oscillators and moving averages flagging a strong buy signal.</p>
<p>Featured image from Pixabay and chart from Tradingview</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/zilliqa-evm-460x242.jpg" width="460" height="242" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Casinos not on Gamstop: Find the Best Non-Gamstop UK Casino 2023</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/gambling/casinos-not-on-gamstop-uk/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[NewsBTC]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 14:00:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Gambling]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=527736</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Many gambling sites are registered on Gamstop, but finding secure and reliable casinos not on Gamstop can be a little more challenging. If you&#8217;re at the point where you want to find reputable non-Gamstop casinos, then you&#8217;ve come to the right place. This page looks at the best online casinos without Gamstop available in the UK. We&#8217;ve compiled an updated list of the top sites and what makes them special, from the games available to the bonuses and payment methods accessible. Use this page to help you find the best and most trusted non-Gamstop casinos in the UK for safe online gameplay entertainment in 2023. Non-Gamstop Casinos UK &#124; Top 10 list 2023: Seven.Casino – New Hot UK Casino Betti – Top Casino and Sports Superb.Bet – Best For Payments Not on Gamstop Bloodmoon – High Rated Non-Gamstop Casino NonStop &#8211; Best Non-Gamstop Casino Goldenbet – A Favourite Non-Gamstop Casino Allwins – Best Non-Gamstop Mobile Casino PlayersClubVIP – Best Live-Casino SlotsDreamer – Casino with 400% Bonus Gxmble – Fastest Sign-up Process Top Contenders Games.Bitcoin – Best UK Crypto and Fiat Casino GoldWin – High RTP Casino Not on Gamstop Winner – Top Non-Gamstop Casino For Bonuses Superlines – Premium Non-Gamstop Casino SpicyJackpots – Non-Gamstop Casino with Jackpots 4Crowns – Offers Unique Games Not on Gamstop Gamblii – Offers Crypto Deposits Winstler – Popular Among UK Players Mystake – Established Non-Gamstop Casino Top Non-Gamstop Casino Reviews Each of these casinos without Gamstop has been vetted and reviewed and is considered the best casinos not on gamstop that the UK gaming industry has to offer in 2023. We&#8217;ve written quick reviews of what you can expect to find in each of these casinos without Gamstop to help make the decision-making process easier. Take a look at the different sites and what you can expect. 1. Seven.Casino – Brand New VIP Casino For UK Players Seven Casino is a top-tier online casino that offers a wide range of games and exciting promotions to players from around the world. Launched in 2023, Seven Casino has quickly made a name for itself in the online gambling industry with its exceptional game selection and user-friendly platform. Highlights Quick signup process Generous welcome bonus package 10% Cashback to VIP players Accepts both credit cards and crypto with high limits At Seven Casino, new players can take advantage of a massive welcome package that includes deposit bonuses of up to £7,500; 1st bonus 200% up to £250, 2nd bonus equals 100% up to £1,000, 3rd bonus 50% up to £1,250 and lastly the 4th bonus equals to 100% up to £5,000. You’ll even get 10% cashback on top of that. There are also regular promotions and giveaways that provide players with even more opportunities to win big. The casino&#8217;s game library is extensive and features a diverse selection of titles from top-tier providers such as NetEnt, Microgaming, and Betsoft. Players can enjoy a variety of slots, table games, and live dealer games. The platform also features a sportsbook section where players can bet on a range of sports events. Deposits and withdrawals are processed quickly, with most transactions being completed within 1-3 days. The casino&#8217;s customer support team is available 24/7 to assist with any questions or concerns. Overall, Seven Casino is a great choice for UK players looking for a fun and reliable online casino. With its impressive game selection, attractive promotions, and user-friendly design, Seven Casino is a top destination for both new and experienced players. Welcome Bonus Wagering Requirements Minimum Deposit Payout Time 450% up to £7,500 10x £20 1 – 3 Days 2. Betti.com – Best Overall Casino and Sportsbook Betti Casino is a secure online casino that brings you every type of betting opportunity you can think of. Whether you&#8217;re in the mood for online casino games, sports, or an authentic live gaming experience. Highlights Best for quick Credit Card deposits Biggest selection of slots Evolution live casino Instant “Karma Rewards” program One of the UK online casinos not on Gamstop that we reviewed that truly stands out from the crowd. Betti has over 3,000 games to choose from, a great loyalty program packed with rewards, and a generous welcome bonus for players that are just starting out. There are daily rewards and bonus boosts for players to boost gameplay. With Betti Casino, player safety is a priority, and customer support is available around the clock with trusted payment methods to choose from when it comes to making deposits or withdrawals. Choose from the best games from the industry-leading software providers and start your online gaming experience with Betti Casino. Play online slots, table games, instant win variants, and live tables, and participate in betting. Welcome Bonus Wagering Requirements Minimum Deposit Payout Time Deposit £100 Play With £200 35x £10 1-3 Days &#160; 3. Superb.bet – Highly Popular Sportsbook and Casino Superb.bet is another full-service online casino site. You can find a wide range of games, secure, trusted payments, and great promotional offers, with their sportsbook being the latest in their gaming range. Highlights Exclusive VIP program Low wagering requirements Very fast payouts Credit cards and Crypto payment options If you&#8217;re looking for a sophisticated gaming site where you can enjoy large bonus boosts on over 1000 games, then Superb.bet is a suitable option. This site has a great collection of games with a fun range of promising jackpot games. Playing at this site gives you access to a range of secure payment methods, from traditional fiat to crypto. Then there is the customer support team, who can assist with any questions day or night to make it the most memorable gaming experience for all players. Get started with Superb.bet and experience all the joys of great games and exclusive VIP rewards. Welcome Bonus Wagering Requirements Minimum Deposit Payout Time 200% up to £1000 + 200 Free Spins 50x £20 1-2 Days &#160; &#160; &#160;  4. BloodMoon Casino –  A 5-Star Casino With a 400% Bonus BloodMoon Casino is a reputable online gambling site with the best in bonuses, sports betting options, and entertainment. If you&#8217;re looking for a quality online gaming experience at a non Gamstop casino, then Blood Moon Casino is a great option. Highlights Generous welcome bonus Credit cards and crypto payment options Fun website design Very reputable casino With this secure online gambling, you can enjoy a fantasy-style casino theme with various gaming options, including Casino, Live Casino, Sports, and Live Racing. No matter what type of betting experience you&#8217;re after, you&#8217;re bound to get what you&#8217;re after at Blood Moon. For new players, there is a generous 400% welcome bonus boost to help you get started with casino gameplay, but there is also the option of a sports welcome if you prefer to go that route. Other promotional rewards include crypto bonuses, daily cashback, and more. Blood Moon is one best non gamstop casinos available in the United Kingdom. With a secure site, reliable customer support, and trusted fiat and crypto payment methods available. Enabling you to enjoy a rewarding experience playing the most thrilling games from top software providers. Welcome Bonus Wagering Requirements Minimum Deposit Payout Time 400% up to £800 45x £25 2-5 Days &#160; 5. NonStopCasino &#8211; Best New Casino With 950% Welcome Bonus NonStop Casino is a new online casino that was launched in April 2023. Despite being a newcomer to the industry, it has already garnered a significant following among players due to its wide range of games, attractive bonuses, and convenient payment options. Highlights Huge welcome offer for all new players Premium payment options High limits on cashouts Casino, live casino, sports, and racing NonStop Casino offers an exceptional gaming experience with its diverse game library that includes popular slots, table games, live dealer games, and more. The casino provides a generous welcome package, a 950% bonus up to £7,000. The bonus is available to all new players and is spread over five deposits. The first deposit bonus is a 400% up to £3000 bonus, followed by a 250% up to £1000 bonus for the second deposit, and finally 100% up to £1000 bonus for the third, fourth, and fifth deposits. All bonuses are subject to a 45x wagering requirement. Additionally, the casino offers a lot of value in the form of other exclusive bonuses, such as the daily 5% cashback up to £2,000, and “FreeSpins Bashs” that are offered up to seven times a week, to name a couple. All this is in tandem with the awesome 24/7 customer support and faster withdrawals. NonStop Casino prides itself on its fast and efficient payment processing, with most withdrawals processed within 1-3 business days. Overall, NonStop Casino is a great option for players looking for a reputable and trustworthy online casino not blocked by Gamstop, that offers a broad range of games, excellent bonuses, and easy payment options. Welcome Bonus Wagering Requirements Minimum Deposit Payout Time 950% up to £7,000 45x £25 1 – 3 Days 6. Goldenbet &#8211; Highly Rated Casino and Sportsbook As far as UK online casinos go, Goldenbet is a newcomer to the game. Established in 2022, it has had to move quickly to establish itself. Its gaming library is already impressive, though, and the promotions available have helped it stand out. Highlights Great payment options for UK players High withdrawal limits Unlimited 10% cashback Offers Sports, Racing, Casino, and Live Casino First, as mentioned, the promotions are competitive. The welcome bonus is a little bit lower than some on the market with a 100% deposit match up to £500. However, what really sets it apart is its regular cashback promotion. It is an unlimited-use cashback of 10%. The max cashback amount is £500 but this can be redeemed as many times as the player makes eligible deposits and wagers. Its game catalogue is extensive and includes progressive jackpot slots from some of the leading providers on the markets, as well as table games and live titles. The live selection is a little less full than the other selections but also includes more specialist games like poker. There are also game shows like Monopoly Live for players looking for something different. Perhaps what sets it apart from the crowd most is its commitment to supporting players. There is a 24-hour live chat function open seven days a week. This means that if there are any concerns, an answer will be available whenever necessary. Welcome Bonus Wagering Requirements Minimum Deposit Payout Time 100% up to £500 35x £20 0 &#8211; 24 Hours &#160; 7. AllWins Casino &#8211; Best Mobile Casino in UK AllWins Casino is an online casino that launched in the UK in 2014 and has since become a popular destination for players looking for a diverse selection of games and exciting bonuses. The casino offers a user-friendly platform that is accessible on desktop and mobile devices, making it a convenient option for players on the go. Highlights Popular UK casino launched in 2014 Quick payments with credit cards, e-wallets, and crypto A playful casino great for mobile users Generous welcome bonus of 500% and low wagering requirements AllWins Casino welcomes new players with a generous welcome package that includes deposit bonuses of up to 500% and 150 free spins. The first deposit bonus is equal to a 250% match bonus plus 25 free spins, the second deposit: 100% match bonus + 50 free spins, and lastly, the third deposit: 150% with 75 free spins on top of that! Note: for each deposit, you’ll need to at least deposit £20 to be able to receive the bonus. The casino also offers regular promotions and giveaways, giving players the chance to win big on a variety of games. The casino&#8217;s game library is extensive and features over 700 titles from leading software providers such as NetEnt, Betsoft, and Play&#8217;n GO. Players can enjoy a variety of slots, table games, and video poker, as well as a limited selection of live dealer games. Deposits and withdrawals at AllWins Casino are processed quickly, with most transactions being completed within 24-48 hours. The casino&#8217;s customer support team is available via live chat and email, although they are not available 24/7. Overall, AllWins Casino is a solid choice for players looking for a reliable and exciting gambling experience. With its diverse game selection, attractive promotions, and user-friendly platform, AllWins Casino is a top destination for both new and experienced players. Welcome Bonus Wagering Requirements Minimum Deposit Payout Time Up to 500% + 150 Free Spins 33x £20 1 – 2 Days &#160; 8. PlayersClubVIP – A Classy Casino for Sophisticated Gaming When you&#8217;re looking for a casino without Gamstop that provides a more sophisticated style of gaming experience, then there&#8217;s no place more suitable than the Players Club VIP casino. This sleek style site gives you access to all types of betting options in a high-class gaming environment. Highlights Online casino, live casino, and sportsbook Great promotions and bonuses Daily cashback with low wagering Play with credit cards and Crypto With the Players Club VIP, you can choose between starting your new player journey with a Casino or Sports welcome bonus. From there, you can look forward to an exciting range of daily casino cashback and other rewards, including VIP benefits. The site is packed with the best slots, table games, live casino entertainment, and sports betting options from the industry&#8217;s best software providers. Top security technology is implemented, with professionally trained support agents always on standby to ensure the player experience goes off without a glitch. For a premium betting experience where every player feels like a VIP, this is the non-Gamstop site to be. Welcome Bonus Wagering Requirements Minimum Deposit Payout Time 222% up to £1,000 45x £25 1-2 Days &#160; 9. SlotsDreamer &#8211; 400% Bonus With a Killer Casino Theme SlotsDreamer.co is a great non-Gamstop online casino that provides players with an exciting gaming experience. Established in 2022, this casino offers a wide range of games from top software providers, including NetEnt, Microgaming, and Play&#8217;n GO. The site boasts a sleek and modern design that is easy to navigate, making it a user-friendly experience for players. Highlights Large selection of games from top providers Mobile-friendly site Multiple payment options including cryptocurrencies Established casino with a 400% welcome bonus SlotsDreamer.co welcomes new players with a generous welcome package that includes a 400% match bonus up to £1200 &#38; 10% daily cashback. The casino also runs various promotions that are available to both new and existing players, providing them with an opportunity to win big, including a 10% daily cashback up to £2000. The casino offers a wide variety of games, including slots, table games, video poker, and live casino games. Players can choose from over 2,000 games, with new titles being added regularly. The games are accessible via desktop and mobile devices, ensuring that players can enjoy their favorite games on the go. Overall, SlotsDreamer.co is great for players who enjoy a wide range of games and a user-friendly experience. The site&#8217;s modern design, generous welcome package, and range of payment options make it an excellent choice for UK players looking for a new casino to try. Welcome Bonus Wagering Requirements Minimum Deposit Payout Time 400% up to £1,200 45x £25 1 – 3 Days &#160; 10. Gxmble – Top Casino with Very Low Wagering Requirements Gxmble Casino is one of the latest non-Gamstop casinos to hit the industry. The site debuted at the end of 2022 and quickly caught players&#8217; attention with its attractive design, low wagering requirements on bonuses, and massive game library. Highlights 4000+ casino games Super quick registration Play with Fiat and Cryptocurrencies Mobile-friendly software If you&#8217;re looking for the ultimate gaming experience where great rewards and game variety meet, then Gxmble is the site for you. It starts with a 3-deposit welcome package for new players and rolls over into generous weekly offers to boost gameplay on over 4000 amazing games from industry-leading software providers. The whole experience is smooth and efficient with a sophisticated website design, 1-minute registration, fast deposits and withdrawals, and reliable customer support to assist with any questions and queries. Sign up at Gxmble Casino today to enjoy the thrill of great games and regular rewards. Become a VIP member and enjoy the benefits of 10% cashback. Welcome Bonus Wagering Requirements Minimum Deposit Payout Time 200% up to £500 5x £25 1 – 3 Days Non-Gamstop Casinos That Nearly Made the Top List for 2023 11. Games.Bitcoin – Best UK Casino for Crypto Games.Bitcoin.com is an online crypto casino that offers players a safe and secure gaming experience while allowing them to use cryptocurrency for all their transactions. Whether you are a seasoned player or new to online gambling, this platform has everything you need to enjoy the best gaming experience. Highlights Good selection of slots from a range of providers Deposit with crypto and credit card Multiple bonuses and promotions on offer Instant payouts and high cashout limits Games.Bitcoin.com offers players a fantastic gaming experience with its wide selection of games, including popular slots, table games, video poker, and live dealer games. The platform accepts various cryptocurrencies for easy deposits and withdrawals and provides excellent customer support 24/7. One of the best things about Games.Bitcoin.com is its attractive bonuses and promotions, including a welcome bonus of up to 5 BTC and 300 free spins. The platform updates its promotions regularly, providing players with more opportunities to win and enjoy their gaming experience. Overall, Games.Bitcoin.com is a secure and enjoyable gambling site that provides players with a great gaming experience while allowing them to use cryptocurrency for all their transactions. Welcome Bonus Wagering Requirements Minimum Deposit Payout Time 25% Cashback Bonus 0x 0,0001 BTC Instant &#160; 12. GoldWin Casino – Safe and Secure Non-Gamstop Casino This relatively new UK online casino opened its door in 2020 and focuses on bringing players the best in online slots and wager-free spins. If you&#8217;re an online slot player looking for high-quality slot entertainment and bonus benefits, GoldWin Casino is for you. Highlights Exciting slot tournaments No wagering promotions 24/7 customer support Wide selection of payment options GoldWin has a sleek and sophisticated white and gold website design. It features over 2000 of the best online slots and table games like roulette, blackjack, and more. The live casino section provides an authentic live dealer experience for those looking for that real casino feel. Gameplay gets boosted with daily bonuses and promotional boosts, starting with a generous welcome bonus for new players. And the Tournaments section displays all the hottest tournaments you can participate in, where you can compete in the hottest games for your share in amazing prizes. Funds can be transferred to and from your account via trusted and secure payment methods, with support available daily via multiple channels. Sign up at GoldWin Casino to claim your welcome bonus and get started. &#160; Welcome Bonus Wagering Requirements Minimum Deposit Payout Time 250 Free Spins None £20 1-2 Days 13. Winner – Casino With Generous Promotions When top-notch security, high-quality games, and great daily promotions are what you&#8217;re looking for, then Winner Casino is the place to go. Winner Casino runs smoothly across desktop and mobile devices, allowing you to enjoy a supreme betting experience from home or on the go. Highlights Large range of online slots Mobile-friendly casino 24/7 customer support Generous welcome bonus and promotions At Winner there is a superb collection of casino games, including online slots, table games, jackpot games, and live games. Gameplay is boosted with a giant welcome bonus for new players and daily promotions for the regulars. And then there is a special VIP program that awards exclusive daily promos and rewards to keep the good times rolling. The site utilizes the latest security measures and has great customer support to ensure players have a smooth and carefree betting experience. Start your journey with Winner Casino and explore hundreds of games today. &#160; Welcome Bonus Wagering Requirements Minimum Deposit Payout Time 400% up to £4,000 + 100 Free Spins 50x £20 1-2 Days  14. Superlines &#8211; Top Rated UK Online Casino Highlights Fast and easy deposits and withdrawals Mobile-friendly 24/7 customer support Exciting bonuses and promotions Casino Superlines is a very popular casino that´s been launched recently and has built up a reputation for offering a good number of games. That list includes table games, slots, and live casino titles. The slots are probably the most extensive when it comes to the sheer number of games available. The site stocks titles from a wide range of providers, including Yggdrasil and BetSoft. The former in particular is famous for regularly winning awards for their slots, including the 2021 Slot Provider of the Year. All of these games are RNG (random number generator) verified to ensure transparency and fairness. The live casino section is nearly as impressive as the slots selection. The number of games is high and compares favorably with most other online casinos. There are hundreds of games available, with variants of a number of popular titles, including roulette, blackjack, and baccarat. The welcome bonus is generous with £1,800 available across a player’s first three deposits. That includes 100% up to £600 and 50 spins for each of the first and third deposits, and 150% up to £600 and 75 free spins on the second deposit. Welcome Bonus Wagering Requirements Minimum Deposit Payout Time 100% up to £600 + 50 fs 45x £20 0 &#8211; 24 Hours 15. SpicyJackpots – Premium UK Mobile Casino With 400% Bonus For those interested in a top-rated desktop and mobile casino experience, look no further than SpicyJackpots Casino, founded in 2022. SpicyJackpots is designed specifically for a high-quality gaming experience on any desktop, tablet, or mobile device. Highlights Superb mobile casino Very generous welcome bonus Industry-leading gaming providers 24/7 customer support With this online casino, you can take a bite out of the hottest entertainment, which includes the latest video slot releases, table games, instant win game variants, progressive jackpots, and live dealer games. Leading software providers power the game library. Transferring funds to and from your account is quick and secure, thanks to the most trusted payment methods and the latest security measures the industry offers. On top of that SpicyJackpots Casino comes with a friendly support team that is always ready to assist with any issues should you require help. Start your online gaming journey at the SpicyJackpots casino and feel the heat with great games and daily rewards. Welcome Bonus Wagering Requirements Minimum Deposit Payout Time 400% up to £2000 + 100 Free Spins 50x £20 1-2 Days 16. 4CrownsCasino – Premium Casino With Unique Slots The online gaming industry is packed with quality casinos without Gamstop, and 4 Crowns Casino is another great option. 4Crowns brings you games from an impressive list of software providers with top promotions. Highlights Unique list of game providers 5 deposit welcome bonus Fiat and Crypto payment methods Well-established casino Two things most players tend to look for are the game variety and the boost of bonuses accompanying it. This online gaming platform offers a generous selection of promotions starting with a 5-deposit welcome bonus boost. To claim this offer, you can register your new player account today. The site runs smoothly across desktops, tablets, and mobile devices, making it possible to enjoy online slots, table games, jackpots, instant win variants, and live dealer tables at home or on the go. With trusted payment methods and professional customer support, complete the Royal 4 Crowns Casino experience. Sign up to get your hands on the first of your 5 deposit welcome bonuses today. Welcome Bonus Wagering Requirements Minimum Deposit Payout Time 400%  up to £2000 + 100 Free Spins 50x £20 1-3 Days 17. Gamblii – Crypto-Friendly Casino With Large Welcome Package There are different styles of online casinos on the market, and when you&#8217;re playing at a non Gamstop site, you still have interesting experiences available. At Gamblii.com, the customers get to enjoy all the good stuff online casinos have to offer, like great games, live casino, and sports betting entertainment Highlights Elegant and fun mobile casino Fast, efficient customer support Quick signup feature Rewarding welcome bonus This gambling site is easily accessible on any desktop, tablet, or mobile device, making it possible to enjoy premium gaming entertainment from home or on the go. The site boosts your gameplay right from the get-go with a generous welcome bonus and regular daily promotions. Not to mention the thrilling VIP program with its exclusive range of benefits. Gamblii utilizes the latest safety technology and most trusted payment methods to make deposits and withdrawals quick and hassle-free. Should you run into any issues, a professionally trained support team is ready to assist you. Sign up at Gamblii Casino to claim your welcome bonus and explore the range of slots and other games from industry-leading software providers. Welcome Bonus Wagering Requirements Minimum Deposit Payout Time 200% up to £250 35x £20 1-2 Days 18. Winstler – Best for Big Bonuses High Stakes Highlights Up to £9,500 bonus available on first five deposits Games from leading providers like NetEnt and Microgaming Extensive banking methods Live chat support This is a casino that is new to the scene, having been established in 2022. Despite only recently making its way into the market, it has managed to make a name for itself by establishing exciting offerings for players. The most eye-catching thing about this new casino has to be its welcome bonus for first-time players. For the first five deposits, players can earn up to £9,500 back in bonus credit. The first deposit is matched 300% up to £500, the second 100% up to £1,000, the third 100% up to £2,000, the fourth 50% up to £2,500, and the fifth and final deposit is matched 50% up to £3,500. This is a highly generous potential bonus but the wagering requirements are somewhat restrictive at 45 times the bonus amount. Fully acceptable terms, but a tad bit into the higher end of the scale. The games on offer are also impressive but less numerous than many competing casinos. The slots are numerous and include titles by all of the leading providers. However, the table games are less prominent and not given as much space in the catalog at many other casinos. Its live casino makes up for that slightly, as it includes a good number of games, including gameshows and immersive gaming experiences. Welcome Bonus Wagering Requirements Minimum Deposit Payout Time 300% up to £9,500 45x  £20 0 &#8211; 24 Hours 19. Mystake.com – A Well-Established Favourite UK Casino Mystake Casino is a new and exciting brand that launched in 2021. This casino has quickly gained popularity due to its sleek design, user-friendly interface, and generous welcome bonus. Mystake Casino offers a great selection of casino games from some of the best providers in the industry. Whether you&#8217;re a fan of slots, table games, or live casino games, you&#8217;ll find plenty to enjoy here. Highlights Generous welcome bonus Wide selection of games from top providers Multiple payment options, including cryptocurrencies Mobile-friendly website New players at Mystake Casino can take advantage of a generous welcome bonus that includes a match bonus of 150% up to £200 and 100% from £200 &#8211; £1000 or when depositing using cryptocurrencies 170% up to £600 (equivalent). The bonus is spread over the first three deposits, giving players more chances to win big, note: you’ll need to deposit at least £20 to be able to receive the bonus. The wagering requirements are reasonable, which makes it easier for players to meet the playthrough requirements and withdraw their winnings. The website is easy to navigate, and players can find their favorite games quickly. The site is mobile-friendly, which means that players can access it on their smartphones or tablets. Mystake Casino also accepts a wide range of payment options, including cryptocurrencies, which makes it convenient for players who prefer to use digital currencies. Overall, Mystake Casino is a great choice for players who are looking for a new and exciting online casino experience. With its wide selection of games, generous welcome bonus, and mobile-friendly website, it&#8217;s definitely worth checking out. Welcome Bonus Wagering Requirements Minimum Deposit Payout Time 100% up to £1,000 30x £20 1 – 3 Days Comparing the Best Non Gamstop Online Casinos Here you have a list of great non-Gamstop casinos available in the UK, and each has something different to offer. If you&#8217;re unsure which site may be the best to play at, a quick comparison of what they offer might be the way to go. With this brief comparison, you&#8217;ll easily be able to see which site has the best welcome offer, games, and payment methods accessible to you. Take a look at the different non Gamstop casinos and online gambling sites and what they bring to the table: Non Gamstop Casinos Welcome Offer Game Types Available Payment Methods NonStop Casino Up to 950% up to £7000 Slots Table Games, Live Casino, Sportsbook Visa, MasterCard, MiFinity, Bank Transfer, Bitcoin, Ethereum, Tether Betti Casino 100% up to £100 Slots Table Games, Live Casino, Sportsbook Visa, MasterCard, MiFinity, Bank Transfer, Bitcoin, Ethereum, Tether Blood Moon Casino 400% up to £800 Slots, Table Games, Live Casino, Sportsbook, Live Racing Mastercard, Visa, Bitcoin, Ethereum, Litecoin, Tether, Neteller Gxmble.com 200% up to £500 Slots, Table Games, Live Casino, Sports Betting Neteller, MasterCard, Instant Banking, Bitcoin, Litecoin, Ethereum, Paysafecard, Visa, AstroPay, Skrill Superb.bet 200% up to £1,000 + 200 Free Spins Slots, Table Games, Live Casino, Provably Fair Games Visa, MasterCard, Bitcoin, Litecoin, Ethereum, Tether, Webpayz Winner Casino 400% up to £4,000 + 100 Free Spins Slots, Table Games, Live Casino, Provably Fair Games, Jackpot Games Visa, MasterCard, Bitcoin, Litecoin, Ethereum, Tether, Coinspaid Players Club VIP 222% up to £1,000 Slots, Table Games, Live Casino, Sportsbook, Live Racing, Virtual Games Visa, MasterCard, MiFinity, Bank Transfer, Bitcoin, Ethereum, Tether Gamblii.com 200% up to £250 Slots, Table Games, Sportsbook, Live Casino, Jackpot Games Visa, Mastercard, Maestro, Bitcoin, Ethereum, Litecoin GoldWin Casino 250 Free Spins Slots, Table Games, Sportsbook, Live Casino, Jackpot Games Visa, MasterCard, Sofort, Skrill, Trustly, Paysafecard, Neteller, Zimpler SpicyJackpots 400% up to £2,000 + 100 Free Spins Slots, Table Games, Live Casino, Jackpot Games, Instant Win Games Visa, MasterCard, Bitcoin, Litecoin, Ethereum, Coinspaid, Tether, Webpayz Slotsdreamer.co 400% up to £1,200 Slots, Table Games, Live Casino, Sportsbook, Live Racing, Virtual Games Visa, MasterCard, Bitcoin, Litecoin, Ethereum, Coinspaid, Tether, Webpayz 4 Crowns Casino 400%  up to £2,000 + 100 Free Spins Slots, Table Games, Live Casino, Jackpot Games, Instant Win Games Visa, MasterCard, Bitcoin, Litecoin, Ethereum, Tether, Webpayz, Coinspaid Games.Bitcoin.com 25% Wager Free Cashback Bonus Slots, Table Games, Live Casino, Jackpot Games, Instant Win Games Visa, MasterCard, Bitcoin, Litecoin, Ethereum, Tether, Webpayz, Coinspaid Superlines 100% up to £600 + 50 fs Slots, Table Games, Live Casino, Jackpot Games, Instant Win Games Visa, MasterCard, Bitcoin, Litecoin, Ethereum, Tether, Webpayz, Coinspaid Goldenbet Casino 100% up to £500 Slots, Table Games, Sportsbook, Live Casino, Jackpot Game, Racing Visa, MasterCard, Bitcoin, Litecoin, Ethereum, Tether, Webpayz, Coinspaid Winstler Casino Up to 300% up to £9,500 Slots, Table Games, Live Casino, Jackpot Games, Instant Win Games Visa, MasterCard, Bitcoin, Litecoin, Ethereum, Tether, Webpayz, Coinspaid MyStake 100% up to £1,000 Slots, Table Games, Sportsbook, Live Casino, Jackpot Game, RacingGames, Instant Win Games Visa, MasterCard, Bitcoin, Litecoin, Ethereum, Tether, Webpayz, Coinspaid AllwinsCasino Up to 500% + 150 Free Spins Slots, Table Games, Live Casino, Jackpot Games, Instant Win Games Visa, MasterCard, Bitcoin, Litecoin, Ethereum, Tether, Webpayz, Coinspaid Seven.Casino 450% up to £7,500 Slots, Table Games, Sportsbook, Live Casino, Jackpot Game, Racing Visa, MasterCard, Bitcoin, Litecoin, Ethereum, Tether, Webpayz, Coinspaid &#160; 5 Easy Steps for Signing Up at a Non Gamstop Casino Getting started at casinos not on gamstop is a quick and easy process that is quick to follow. If you&#8217;re new to online gameplay and are unsure how it works, you have come to the right place. We&#8217;ve created a quick 5-step instruction guide on how to get started. Step 1 – Find a Casino: Choose one of our Trusted Casinos not on Gamstop The first step is to find a casino that is suitable for your gaming needs. You can start by browsing our list of top recommended casinos without Gamstop to find the one that has everything you want and require. Step 2 – Register the Account: Get Started by Creating a new Player Account Once you&#8217;ve found the casino most suitable to your gaming requirements, you can visit the no Gamstop casino and click the Join/Sign Up/Register button to create your new player account. You&#8217;ll be required to fill in some personal information, including your name, surname, and email address. Step 3 – Verify the Account: Get Verified Before you Continue One of the last steps before you can start claiming bonuses, funding your account, or taking part in the site&#8217;s activities, is to verify your account. You will receive a link via email or a verification code via text, depending on the casino. Follow the instructions to verify your account. Step 4 – Fund Your Account: Make a deposit and Claim Your Bonus Now it&#8217;s time to add some funds to your bankroll by heading to the cashier. Here you can choose any secure payment method available for that specific non-Gamstop casino to fund your transactions. If you&#8217;re claiming the welcome bonus and a special promotion code is required, entering it during the transaction is important to activate the bonus. Funds will be credited to your account as soon as the transaction is successfully completed. Step 5 – Start Playing: Let the Games Begin With your online casino account successfully registered, verified, and topped up with funds, it&#8217;s time to head over to the game library and choose from the assortment of games available. Take your pick, load a game, and start playing to meet the bonus wagering requirements and strike a couple of wins while you play. With this quick and easy registration process, you&#8217;ll be ready to start playing all your favorite games at any trusted non-Gamstop casino. Always select a secure casino that comes with licensing and prioritizes player safety. Payments at a Casino Not on GamStop Payments at a casino not on GamStop can vary depending on the individual casino. However, most reputable online casinos offer a range of payment methods, including credit cards, e-wallets, bank transfers, and prepaid cards. It&#8217;s important to note that some payment methods may not be available in certain countries or regions. When making a payment at a casino not with GamStop, it&#8217;s crucial to ensure that the website is secure and encrypted to protect your personal and financial information. Look for casinos that use industry-standard security measures, such as SSL encryption, to safeguard your data. It&#8217;s also important to check the deposit and withdrawal limits and processing times for each payment method. Some payment methods may have lower minimum or maximum limits than others, and processing times may vary depending on the payment provider and the casino&#8217;s policies. Overall, when choosing a casino not with GamStop, it&#8217;s important to consider the payment options available and ensure that they meet your needs and preferences. By doing so, you can enjoy a seamless and secure gaming experience without worrying about payment issues. Advantages of Playing at Non Gamstop Casino Sites UK players who choose to play at a non-Gamstop online casino have more control over their gambling experience, as the casinos are not limited by the same restrictions. Here are a couple of benefits that stem from playing at an online casino without Gamstop. Easier KYC Verification When it comes to making your payments at any online casino, there is often a couple of hoops to jump through, especially with Gamstop sites. You may find that non-Gamstop sites do not have the same verification requirements. They are often referred to as no-verification casinos, as the process is much quicker. In contrast, other sites may have a process that takes a couple of days. Less Brand Tax and More Bonus Rewards One of the biggest advantages of these offshore sites is that they often have fewer taxes to pay. While this is an advantage for the site itself, it also comes at an advantage for you as it means that they can expand and increase their range of bonuses and promotions while lowering the deposit requirements. Ideally Situated Many of these online casinos without Gamstop are still located in Europe. While they are non-Gamstop sites, they are still considered safe and accept UK players. They provide a wide range of perks to enhance the gaming experience. Disadvantages of Casinos Not on Gamstop A couple of drawbacks are tied to non-Gamstop online casinos, which also need to be taken into account. We take a look at some of the disadvantages these sites have to give you a clear view of the experience available on any casino site without Gamstop. Counselling on Your Own Dime When it comes to non-Gamstop sites, you don&#8217;t have the option of free counselling. This is something that isn&#8217;t always noticeable, but it can be a big help in cases where it&#8217;s needed. Most non-Gamstop sites don&#8217;t have counselling options. A Withdrawal Flow With most sites, you find set withdrawal limits that are quite strict. At non-Gamstop casino sites, you will notice a free flow in terms of withdrawals, enabling you to withdraw any amount you want at any moment. Not Always Telephone Support Some non gamstop casinos don&#8217;t offer telephone support. However, many of these casinos provide around-the-clock live support via chat, which can be just as efficient. If you prefer telephone support, it&#8217;s important to check whether this option is available before signing up with a particular casino brand. How We Rate the Best Online Casinos Not on Gamstop When reviewing and vetting trusted online casinos without Gamstop, there are different factors we take into consideration. Sites undergo rigorous testing, and only the best sites that meet most of our criteria checklist are added to the list. Take a look at what we consider before adding a site to our list of recommendations: Licensing and Security Before you register at online casinos, you want to know that the site is licensed and regulated to ensure it provides a secure gaming experience for all its players. Commonly non Gamstop casinos are not licensed by the UK Gambling Commission but will carry licensing from other gaming authorities like Curaçao eGaming, Kahnawake Gaming Commission, or Malta Gaming Authority. Licensed sites incorporate the latest security measures like SSL data encryption to provide a secure betting experience. Great Banking Options Once you&#8217;ve confirmed that a site is licensed and utilizes the latest security, reviewing the payment methods to ensure it allows deposits and withdrawals via secure payment methods you&#8217;re comfortable with is best. Most of the casinos not on Gamstop that we review, will offer payments via trusted payment options in fiat and cryptocurrency, giving you a variety of options to choose from. Bonuses at Casinos Not on Gamstop Playing games online often feels even more exciting with the added benefit of promotions and a VIP program where you can climb the tiers to unlock bigger rewards. After checking to see if a site is secure and features secure payment methods, we look for the different types of bonuses and benefits players can access while playing. Along with the terms connected to it, making sure the offers are worthwhile.  We have reviewed more than 30 casinos not on gamstop and carefully selected the highest-quality brands in this article, taking into consideration factors such as bonuses and promotions. We suggest taking a closer look to find a bonus that aligns with your preferred gameplay style. Wide Range of Casino Games There&#8217;s nothing as exciting as a quality range of games from industry-leading providers that run smoothly on all devices. Before recommending online casinos not on gamstop, we ensure that games run smoothly on all platforms in a high-quality format. A big plus is when sites have a large game variety with advanced game filters making it easier to find your favourite games. Helpful Customer Service A priority in the process is testing the customer service available. This means testing whether the support agents are available when they say they are, the quality of support offered, and whether queries are resolved promptly. Support plays a big role in a successful gaming experience, and you want to ensure the support team is always professional and friendly. What we noticed is that there are some concerns from players about casinos not on gamstop. However, our thorough review has shown no significant difference in the quality of customer support between regular UK online casinos and the best non-GamStop casinos listed here in our review. Simple Terms &#38; Conditions Reviewing their terms and conditions are an important factor when sifting through casinos without Gamstop. It&#8217;s important to find sites that provide players with transparent, fair, and simple terms. You want to be able to read and understand the words so you know what you&#8217;re getting yourself into. FAQs about Non Gamstop Casinos in the UK Are My Funds Safe at a Non Gamstop Casino? This depends on the casino. If you are playing at a licensed and regulated non-Gamstop casino, you can enjoy a secure experience where your funds are protected. To ensure you have a safe gaming experience, choose from the top recommended sites listed here on our site. Are non Gamstop Casino Sites Trustworthy? Yes, when you&#8217;re playing at any recommended non Gamstop casinos that are licensed and regulated. You can rest assured that the site is secure and trustworthy, with strict security measures in place, fair gaming practices, and player satisfaction as the number one priority. Can I Cash out Winnings at Casinos, Not on Gamstop in the UK? The non-Gamstop gaming sites within the UK are regulated and licensed and follow strict regulatory measures to provide a safe real, money gaming experience. You can make deposits and cash out your winnings at non Gamstop casinos within the UK. What is the Best Casino not on Gamstop? You can play at plenty of top-rated non Gamstop online casinos. We&#8217;ve compiled a list of safe sites with the best bonuses, games, and features, with Betti Casino and Blood Moon Casino being among the top recommended. Do Casinos not on Gamstop Still use Responsible Gambling Tools? Yes, various non Gamstop casinos still provide players access to responsible gaming tools, including self-exclusion and cool-off options, just not via Gamstop. You can also make use of other tools like setting personal account limits to stay in control of your gaming. Are all UK Casinos on Gamstop? Not necessarily, there are various casinos operating that are not on Gamstop, as seen via this guide. You can still enjoy secure gameplay via a range of non-Gamstop casinos in the UK, including our list of top recommendations. Are There Mobile Casinos Not on Gamstop? There is a great range of secure mobile casinos that are not on Gamstop but provide a secure gameplay experience to players who prefer gameplay on the go. Take a look at our list of top recommendations for the best mobile casinos not on GamStop Can I make Deposits at Casinos That are Not on Gamstop? You can make deposits and withdrawals at non-Gamstop online casinos to enjoy a real money gaming experience with the opportunity to win real money rewards. The sites are regulated and utilise the most secure payment methods for safe deposits and withdrawals. Are non-Gamstop Casino Sites Legit? Yes, these casinos not on Gamstop are legit sites that carry licensing from respected gaming authorities and provide a secure gaming experience to players. The sites are generally not licensed by the UK Gambling Commission but by other respectable gaming authorities within the industry. Will I find All of my Favourite Games at UK Sites not on Gamstop? This depends on the online casino you visit. Not all casinos provide you with the same variety of games to choose from, but at the right casino, you are bound to have access to all your favourite game variants, including the best slots, table games, and live casino games. &#160; &#160;]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Many gambling sites are registered on Gamstop, but finding secure and reliable casinos not on Gamstop can be a little more challenging. If you&#8217;re at the point where you want to find reputable non-Gamstop casinos, then you&#8217;ve come to the right place.</p>
<p>This page looks at the best online casinos without Gamstop available in the UK. We&#8217;ve compiled an updated list of the top sites and what makes them special, from the games available to the bonuses and payment methods accessible. Use this page to help you find the best and most trusted non-Gamstop casinos in the UK for safe online gameplay entertainment in 2023.</p>
<h2>Non-Gamstop Casinos UK | Top 10 list 2023:</h2>
<ul>
<li><a href="https://seven.casino/?affid=10291&amp;campaign=nbtc_ng_top" rel="sponsored nofollow">Seven.Casino</a> – New Hot UK Casino</li>
<li><a href="https://record.bettiaffiliates.com/_1mW-aXseORlhg6WO2I1rgWNd7ZgqdRLk/1/" rel="sponsored nofollow">Betti</a> – Top Casino and Sports</li>
<li><a href="https://go.winnercasino.bet/visit/?bta=35459&amp;nci=5407&amp;afp=click_id&amp;utm_campaign=source_id" rel="sponsored nofollow">Superb.Bet</a> – Best For Payments Not on Gamstop</li>
<li><a href="https://go.lindaspartners.com/visit/?bta=35786&amp;nci=5744&amp;utm_campaign=nbtc_ng_top" rel="sponsored nofollow">Bloodmoon</a> – High Rated Non-Gamstop Casino</li>
<li><a href="https://go.lindaspartners.com/visit/?bta=35786&amp;nci=5760&amp;utm_campaign=nbtc_ng_top" rel="sponsored nofollow">NonStop</a> &#8211; Best Non-Gamstop Casino</li>
<li><a href="https://go.affision.com/visit/?bta=36714&amp;brand=goldenbet&amp;utm_campaign=nbtc_ng_top" rel="sponsored nofollow">Goldenbet</a> – A Favourite Non-Gamstop Casino</li>
<li><a href="https://go.conversionaffiliates.com/visit/?bta=36058&amp;nci=5513&amp;utm_campaign=nbtc_ng_top" rel="sponsored nofollow">Allwins</a> – Best Non-Gamstop Mobile Casino</li>
<li><a href="https://wlharryspartners.adsrv.eacdn.com/C.ashx?btag=a_1073b_276c_&amp;affid=508&amp;siteid=1073&amp;adid=276&amp;c=" rel="sponsored nofollow">PlayersClubVIP</a> – Best Live-Casino</li>
<li><a href="https://www.okptrack.com/C.ashx?btag=a_2017b_402c_&amp;affid=824&amp;siteid=2017&amp;adid=402&amp;c=" rel="sponsored nofollow">SlotsDreamer</a> – Casino with 400% Bonus</li>
<li><a href="https://gxmble.com/?affid=55316&amp;campaign=nbtc_ng_top" rel="sponsored nofollow">Gxmble</a> – Fastest Sign-up Process</li>
</ul>
Top Contenders
<ul>
<li><a href="https://creatives.affiliate.bitcoin.com/redirect.aspx?pid=5681&amp;lpid=17&amp;bid=1816" rel="sponsored nofollow">Games.Bitcoin</a> – Best UK Crypto and Fiat Casino</li>
<li><a href="https://tracker-pm2.west-affiliates.com/link?btag=43670502_251264" rel="sponsored nofollow">GoldWin</a> – High RTP Casino Not on Gamstop</li>
<li><a href="https://go.winnercasino.bet/visit/?bta=35459&amp;nci=5396&amp;afp=click_id&amp;utm_campaign=source_id" rel="sponsored nofollow">Winner</a> – Top Non-Gamstop Casino For Bonuses</li>
<li><a href="https://go.rocksolidaffiliates1.com/visit/?bta=38770&amp;nci=5782&amp;utm_campaign=nbtc_ng_top" rel="sponsored nofollow">Superlines</a> – Premium Non-Gamstop Casino</li>
<li><a href="https://go.partnerbreeze.com/visit/?bta=35466&amp;nci=5391&amp;utm_campaign=nbtc_ng_top" rel="sponsored nofollow">SpicyJackpots</a> – Non-Gamstop Casino with Jackpots</li>
<li><a href="https://go.4crownscasino.com/visit/?bta=35257&amp;nci=5352&amp;utm_campaign=nbtc_ng_top" rel="sponsored nofollow">4Crowns</a> – Offers Unique Games Not on Gamstop</li>
<li><a href="https://gamblii.com/?affid=55316&amp;campaign=nbtc_ng_top" rel="sponsored nofollow">Gamblii</a> – Offers Crypto Deposits</li>
<li><a href="https://winstler.com/?affid=55316&amp;campaign=nbtc_ng_top" rel="sponsored nofollow">Winstler </a>– Popular Among UK Players</li>
<li><a href="https://go.affiliatemystake.com/visit/?bta=3131374&amp;nci=5373&amp;afp1=nbtc_ng_top" rel="sponsored nofollow">Mystake</a> – Established Non-Gamstop Casino</li>
</ul>
<p><strong> <img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-527748 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Featured.png" alt="Non-Gamstop Casinos UK" width="1920" height="1280" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Featured.png 1920w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Featured-460x307.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Featured-860x573.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Featured-768x512.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Featured-1536x1024.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Featured-750x500.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Featured-1140x760.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1920px) 100vw, 1920px" /></strong></p>
<h2>Top Non-Gamstop Casino Reviews</h2>
<p>Each of these casinos without Gamstop has been vetted and reviewed and is considered the best casinos not on gamstop that the UK gaming industry has to offer in 2023. We&#8217;ve written quick reviews of what you can expect to find in each of these casinos without Gamstop to help make the decision-making process easier. Take a look at the different sites and what you can expect.</p>
1. <a href="https://seven.casino/?affid=10291&amp;campaign=nbtc_ng_head" rel="sponsored nofollow">Seven.Casino</a> – Brand New VIP Casino For UK Players
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-527825 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Seven.Casino-casino-uk.png" alt=" Seven New Online Casino" width="1280" height="787" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Seven.Casino-casino-uk.png 1280w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Seven.Casino-casino-uk-460x283.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Seven.Casino-casino-uk-860x529.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Seven.Casino-casino-uk-768x472.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Seven.Casino-casino-uk-750x461.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Seven.Casino-casino-uk-1140x701.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1280px) 100vw, 1280px" />
<p>Seven Casino is a top-tier online casino that offers a wide range of games and exciting promotions to players from around the world. Launched in 2023, Seven Casino has quickly made a name for itself in the online gambling industry with its exceptional game selection and user-friendly platform.</p>
Highlights
<ul>
<li>Quick signup process</li>
<li>Generous welcome bonus package</li>
<li>10% Cashback to VIP players</li>
<li>Accepts both credit cards and crypto with high limits</li>
</ul>
<p>At Seven Casino, new players can take advantage of a massive welcome package that includes deposit bonuses of up to £7,500; 1st bonus 200% up to £250, 2nd bonus equals 100% up to £1,000, 3rd bonus 50% up to £1,250 and lastly the 4th bonus equals to 100% up to £5,000. You’ll even get 10% cashback on top of that.</p>
<p>There are also regular promotions and giveaways that provide players with even more opportunities to win big.</p>
<p>The casino&#8217;s game library is extensive and features a diverse selection of titles from top-tier providers such as NetEnt, Microgaming, and Betsoft. Players can enjoy a variety of slots, table games, and live dealer games. The platform also features a sportsbook section where players can bet on a range of sports events.</p>
<p>Deposits and withdrawals are processed quickly, with most transactions being completed within 1-3 days. The casino&#8217;s customer support team is available 24/7 to assist with any questions or concerns.</p>
<p>Overall, Seven Casino is a great choice for UK players looking for a fun and reliable online casino. With its impressive game selection, attractive promotions, and user-friendly design, Seven Casino is a top destination for both new and experienced players.</p>
<table width="601">
<tbody>
<tr>
<td width="170"><strong>Welcome Bonus</strong></td>
<td width="170"><strong>Wagering Requirements</strong></td>
<td width="132"><strong>Minimum Deposit</strong></td>
<td width="129"><strong>Payout Time</strong></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="170">450% up to £7,500</td>
<td width="170">10x</td>
<td width="132">£20</td>
<td width="129">1 – 3 Days</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
<p><a href="https://seven.casino/?affid=10291&amp;campaign=nbtc_ng_cta" rel="sponsored nofollow"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-527826 size-full aligncenter" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Seven.Casino-casino-uk-1.png" alt="Visit Seven Casino" width="460" height="74" /></a></p>
2. <a href="https://record.bettiaffiliates.com/_1mW-aXseORntk2_LYBq6-mNd7ZgqdRLk/2/" rel="nofollow">Betti.com</a> – Best Overall Casino and Sportsbook
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-527754 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Betti-casino-uk.png" alt="Betti Non Gamstop Casino" width="1280" height="787" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Betti-casino-uk.png 1280w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Betti-casino-uk-460x283.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Betti-casino-uk-860x529.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Betti-casino-uk-768x472.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Betti-casino-uk-750x461.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Betti-casino-uk-1140x701.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1280px) 100vw, 1280px" />
<p>Betti Casino is a secure online casino that brings you every type of betting opportunity you can think of. Whether you&#8217;re in the mood for online casino games, sports, or an authentic live gaming experience.</p>
Highlights
<ul>
<li>Best for quick Credit Card deposits</li>
<li>Biggest selection of slots</li>
<li>Evolution live casino</li>
<li>Instant “Karma Rewards” program</li>
</ul>
<p>One of the UK online casinos not on Gamstop that we reviewed that truly stands out from the crowd. Betti has over 3,000 games to choose from, a great loyalty program packed with rewards, and a generous welcome bonus for players that are just starting out.</p>
<p>There are daily rewards and bonus boosts for players to boost gameplay. With Betti Casino, player safety is a priority, and customer support is available around the clock with trusted payment methods to choose from when it comes to making deposits or withdrawals.</p>
<p>Choose from the best games from the industry-leading software providers and start your online gaming experience with Betti Casino. Play online slots, table games, instant win variants, and live tables, and participate in betting.</p>
<table width="601">
<tbody>
<tr>
<td width="170"><strong>Welcome Bonus</strong></td>
<td width="170"><strong>Wagering Requirements</strong></td>
<td width="132"><strong>Minimum Deposit</strong></td>
<td width="129"><strong>Payout Time</strong></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="170">Deposit £100 Play With £200</td>
<td width="170">35x</td>
<td width="132">£10</td>
<td width="129">1-3 Days</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
<p><a href="https://record.bettiaffiliates.com/_1mW-aXseORnorQZCRpFd_WNd7ZgqdRLk/3/" rel="sponsored nofollow"><strong> <img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-527755 aligncenter" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Betti-casino-uk-1.png" alt="Visit Betti Casino Button" width="460" height="74" /></strong></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
3. <a href="https://go.winnercasino.bet/visit/?bta=35459&amp;nci=5407&amp;afp=click_id&amp;utm_campaign=source_id" rel="sponsored nofollow">Superb.bet</a> – Highly Popular Sportsbook and Casino
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-527756 aligncenter" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Superb.bet-casino-uk.png" alt="Superb.bet Casino" width="1280" height="787" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Superb.bet-casino-uk.png 1280w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Superb.bet-casino-uk-460x283.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Superb.bet-casino-uk-860x529.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Superb.bet-casino-uk-768x472.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Superb.bet-casino-uk-750x461.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Superb.bet-casino-uk-1140x701.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1280px) 100vw, 1280px" />
<p>Superb.bet is another full-service online casino site. You can find a wide range of games, secure, trusted payments, and great promotional offers, with their sportsbook being the latest in their gaming range.</p>
Highlights
<ul>
<li>Exclusive VIP program</li>
<li>Low wagering requirements</li>
<li>Very fast payouts</li>
<li>Credit cards and Crypto payment options</li>
</ul>
<p>If you&#8217;re looking for a sophisticated gaming site where you can enjoy large bonus boosts on over 1000 games, then Superb.bet is a suitable option. This site has a great collection of games with a fun range of promising jackpot games.</p>
<p>Playing at this site gives you access to a range of secure payment methods, from traditional fiat to crypto. Then there is the customer support team, who can assist with any questions day or night to make it the most memorable gaming experience for all players.</p>
<p>Get started with Superb.bet and experience all the joys of great games and exclusive VIP rewards.</p>
<table width="601">
<tbody>
<tr>
<td width="226"><strong>Welcome Bonus</strong></td>
<td width="114"><strong>Wagering Requirements</strong></td>
<td width="132"><strong>Minimum Deposit</strong></td>
<td width="129"><strong>Payout Time</strong></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="226">200% up to £1000 + 200 Free Spins</td>
<td width="114">50x</td>
<td width="132">£20</td>
<td width="129">1-2 Days</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
<p><a href="https://go.winnercasino.bet/visit/?bta=35459&amp;nci=5407&amp;afp=click_id&amp;utm_campaign=source_id" rel="sponsored nofollow"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-527761 aligncenter" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Superb.bet-casino-uk-1.png" alt="SuperbBet Casino Button" width="460" height="74" /></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
 4. <a href="https://go.lindaspartners.com/visit/?bta=35786&amp;nci=5744&amp;utm_campaign=nbtc_ng_head" rel="sponsored nofollow">BloodMoon Casino</a> –  A 5-Star Casino With a 400% Bonus
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-527827 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Bloodmoon-casino-uk.png" alt="BloodMoon Casino Non-gamstop" width="1280" height="787" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Bloodmoon-casino-uk.png 1280w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Bloodmoon-casino-uk-460x283.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Bloodmoon-casino-uk-860x529.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Bloodmoon-casino-uk-768x472.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Bloodmoon-casino-uk-750x461.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Bloodmoon-casino-uk-1140x701.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1280px) 100vw, 1280px" />
<p>BloodMoon Casino is a reputable online gambling site with the best in bonuses, sports betting options, and entertainment. If you&#8217;re looking for a quality online gaming experience at a non Gamstop casino, then Blood Moon Casino is a great option.</p>
<strong>Highlights</strong>
<ul>
<li>Generous welcome bonus</li>
<li>Credit cards and crypto payment options</li>
<li>Fun website design</li>
<li>Very reputable casino</li>
</ul>
<p>With this secure online gambling, you can enjoy a fantasy-style casino theme with various gaming options, including Casino, Live Casino, Sports, and Live Racing. No matter what type of betting experience you&#8217;re after, you&#8217;re bound to get what you&#8217;re after at Blood Moon.</p>
<p>For new players, there is a generous 400% welcome bonus boost to help you get started with casino gameplay, but there is also the option of a sports welcome if you prefer to go that route. Other promotional rewards include crypto bonuses, daily cashback, and more.</p>
<p>Blood Moon is one best non gamstop casinos available in the United Kingdom. With a secure site, reliable customer support, and trusted fiat and crypto payment methods available. Enabling you to enjoy a rewarding experience playing the most thrilling games from top software providers.</p>
<table width="601">
<tbody>
<tr>
<td width="170"><strong>Welcome Bonus</strong></td>
<td width="170"><strong>Wagering Requirements</strong></td>
<td width="132"><strong>Minimum Deposit</strong></td>
<td width="129"><strong>Payout Time</strong></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="170">400% up to £800</td>
<td width="170">45x</td>
<td width="132">£25</td>
<td width="129">2-5 Days</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
<p><a href="https://go.lindaspartners.com/visit/?bta=35786&amp;nci=5744&amp;utm_campaign=nbtc_ng_cta" rel="sponsored nofollow"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-527831 size-full aligncenter" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Bloodmoon-casino-uk-1.png" alt="BloodMoon Casino Button" width="460" height="74" /></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
5.<a href="https://go.lindaspartners.com/visit/?bta=35786&amp;nci=5760&amp;utm_campaign=nbtc_ng_head" rel="sponsored nofollow"> NonStopCasino</a> &#8211; Best New Casino With 950% Welcome Bonus
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-527750 size-full aligncenter" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/NonStopCasino-casino-uk.png" alt="NonStop Online Casino" width="1280" height="787" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/NonStopCasino-casino-uk.png 1280w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/NonStopCasino-casino-uk-460x283.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/NonStopCasino-casino-uk-860x529.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/NonStopCasino-casino-uk-768x472.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/NonStopCasino-casino-uk-750x461.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/NonStopCasino-casino-uk-1140x701.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1280px) 100vw, 1280px" />
<p>NonStop Casino is a new online casino that was launched in April 2023. Despite being a newcomer to the industry, it has already garnered a significant following among players due to its wide range of games, attractive bonuses, and convenient payment options.</p>
Highlights
<ul>
<li>Huge welcome offer for all new players</li>
<li>Premium payment options</li>
<li>High limits on cashouts</li>
<li>Casino, live casino, sports, and racing</li>
</ul>
<p>NonStop Casino offers an exceptional gaming experience with its diverse game library that includes popular slots, table games, live dealer games, and more.</p>
<p>The casino provides a generous welcome package, a 950% bonus up to £7,000. The bonus is available to all new players and is spread over five deposits.</p>
<p>The first deposit bonus is a 400% up to £3000 bonus, followed by a 250% up to £1000 bonus for the second deposit, and finally 100% up to £1000 bonus for the third, fourth, and fifth deposits. All bonuses are subject to a 45x wagering requirement.</p>
<p>Additionally, the casino offers a lot of value in the form of other exclusive bonuses, such as the daily 5% cashback up to £2,000, and “FreeSpins Bashs” that are offered up to seven times a week, to name a couple.</p>
<p>All this is in tandem with the awesome 24/7 customer support and faster withdrawals. NonStop Casino prides itself on its fast and efficient payment processing, with most withdrawals processed within 1-3 business days.</p>
<p>Overall, NonStop Casino is a great option for players looking for a reputable and trustworthy online casino not blocked by Gamstop, that offers a broad range of games, excellent bonuses, and easy payment options.</p>
<table width="601">
<tbody>
<tr>
<td width="170"><strong>Welcome Bonus</strong></td>
<td width="170"><strong>Wagering Requirements</strong></td>
<td width="132"><strong>Minimum Deposit</strong></td>
<td width="129"><strong>Payout Time</strong></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="170">950% up to £7,000</td>
<td width="170">45x</td>
<td width="132">£25</td>
<td width="129">1 – 3 Days</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
<p><a href="https://go.lindaspartners.com/visit/?bta=35786&amp;nci=5760&amp;utm_campaign=nbtc_ng_cta" rel="sponsored nofollow"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-527751 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/NonStopCasino-casino-uk-1.png" alt="NonStop Casino Button" width="460" height="74" /></a></p>

6. <a href="https://go.affision.com/visit/?bta=36714&amp;brand=goldenbet&amp;utm_campaign=nbtc_ng_head" rel="sponsored nofollow">Goldenbet</a> &#8211; Highly Rated Casino and Sportsbook
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-527833 aligncenter" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Goldenbet-casino-uk.png" alt="Goldenbet Online Casino" width="1280" height="787" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Goldenbet-casino-uk.png 1280w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Goldenbet-casino-uk-460x283.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Goldenbet-casino-uk-860x529.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Goldenbet-casino-uk-768x472.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Goldenbet-casino-uk-750x461.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Goldenbet-casino-uk-1140x701.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1280px) 100vw, 1280px" />
<p>As far as UK online casinos go, Goldenbet is a newcomer to the game. Established in 2022, it has had to move quickly to establish itself. Its gaming library is already impressive, though, and the promotions available have helped it stand out.</p>
Highlights
<ul>
<li>Great payment options for UK players</li>
<li>High withdrawal limits</li>
<li>Unlimited 10% cashback</li>
<li>Offers Sports, Racing, Casino, and Live Casino</li>
</ul>
<p>First, as mentioned, the promotions are competitive. The welcome bonus is a little bit lower than some on the market with a 100% deposit match up to £500. However, what really sets it apart is its regular cashback promotion. It is an unlimited-use cashback of 10%. The max cashback amount is £500 but this can be redeemed as many times as the player makes eligible deposits and wagers.</p>
<p>Its game catalogue is extensive and includes progressive jackpot slots from some of the leading providers on the markets, as well as table games and live titles. The live selection is a little less full than the other selections but also includes more specialist games like poker. There are also game shows like Monopoly Live for players looking for something different.</p>
<p>Perhaps what sets it apart from the crowd most is its commitment to supporting players. There is a 24-hour live chat function open seven days a week. This means that if there are any concerns, an answer will be available whenever necessary.</p>
<table width="601">
<tbody>
<tr>
<td width="226"><strong>Welcome Bonus</strong></td>
<td width="114"><strong>Wagering Requirements</strong></td>
<td width="132"><strong>Minimum Deposit</strong></td>
<td width="129"><strong>Payout Time</strong></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="226">100% up to £500</td>
<td width="114">35x</td>
<td width="132">£20</td>
<td width="129">0 &#8211; 24 Hours</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
<p><a href="https://go.affision.com/visit/?bta=36714&amp;brand=goldenbet&amp;utm_campaign=nbtc_ng_cta" rel="sponsored nofollow"> <img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-527837 size-full aligncenter" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Goldenbet-casino-uk-2.png" alt="Visit GoldenBet Casino Button" width="460" height="74" /></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
7. <a href="https://go.conversionaffiliates.com/visit/?bta=36058&amp;nci=5513&amp;utm_campaign=nbtc_ng_head" rel="sponsored nofollow">AllWins Casino</a> &#8211; Best Mobile Casino in UK
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-527838 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/AllwinsCasino-casino-uk.png" alt="AllWins Non-Gamstop Casino" width="1280" height="787" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/AllwinsCasino-casino-uk.png 1280w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/AllwinsCasino-casino-uk-460x283.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/AllwinsCasino-casino-uk-860x529.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/AllwinsCasino-casino-uk-768x472.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/AllwinsCasino-casino-uk-750x461.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/AllwinsCasino-casino-uk-1140x701.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1280px) 100vw, 1280px" />
<p>AllWins Casino is an online casino that launched in the UK in 2014 and has since become a popular destination for players looking for a diverse selection of games and exciting bonuses.</p>
<p>The casino offers a user-friendly platform that is accessible on desktop and mobile devices, making it a convenient option for players on the go.</p>
Highlights
<ul>
<li>Popular UK casino launched in 2014</li>
<li>Quick payments with credit cards, e-wallets, and crypto</li>
<li>A playful casino great for mobile users</li>
<li>Generous welcome bonus of 500% and low wagering requirements</li>
</ul>
<p>AllWins Casino welcomes new players with a generous welcome package that includes deposit bonuses of up to 500% and 150 free spins. The first deposit bonus is equal to a 250% match bonus plus 25 free spins, the second deposit: 100% match bonus + 50 free spins, and lastly, the third deposit: 150% with 75 free spins on top of that!</p>
<p>Note: for each deposit, you’ll need to at least deposit £20 to be able to receive the bonus. The casino also offers regular promotions and giveaways, giving players the chance to win big on a variety of games.</p>
<p>The casino&#8217;s game library is extensive and features over 700 titles from leading software providers such as NetEnt, Betsoft, and Play&#8217;n GO. Players can enjoy a variety of slots, table games, and video poker, as well as a limited selection of live dealer games.</p>
<p>Deposits and withdrawals at AllWins Casino are processed quickly, with most transactions being completed within 24-48 hours. The casino&#8217;s customer support team is available via live chat and email, although they are not available 24/7.</p>
<p>Overall, AllWins Casino is a solid choice for players looking for a reliable and exciting gambling experience. With its diverse game selection, attractive promotions, and user-friendly platform, AllWins Casino is a top destination for both new and experienced players.</p>
<table width="601">
<tbody>
<tr>
<td width="170"><strong>Welcome Bonus</strong></td>
<td width="170"><strong>Wagering Requirements</strong></td>
<td width="132"><strong>Minimum Deposit</strong></td>
<td width="129"><strong>Payout Time</strong></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="170">Up to 500% + 150 Free Spins</td>
<td width="170">33x</td>
<td width="132">£20</td>
<td width="129">1 – 2 Days</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
<p><a href="https://go.conversionaffiliates.com/visit/?bta=36058&amp;nci=5513&amp;utm_campaign=nbtc_ng_top" rel="sponsored nofollow"><strong> <img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-527839 aligncenter" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/AllwinsCasino-casino-uk-1.png" alt="Visit AllWins Online Casino" width="460" height="74" /></strong></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
8.<a href="https://wlharryspartners.adsrv.eacdn.com/C.ashx?btag=a_1074b_276c_&amp;affid=508&amp;siteid=1074&amp;adid=276&amp;c=" rel="sponsored nofollow"> PlayersClubVIP</a> – A Classy Casino for Sophisticated Gaming
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-527840 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/PlayersClubVIP-casino-uk.png" alt="Players Club VIP Casino" width="1280" height="787" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/PlayersClubVIP-casino-uk.png 1280w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/PlayersClubVIP-casino-uk-460x283.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/PlayersClubVIP-casino-uk-860x529.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/PlayersClubVIP-casino-uk-768x472.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/PlayersClubVIP-casino-uk-750x461.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/PlayersClubVIP-casino-uk-1140x701.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1280px) 100vw, 1280px" />
<p>When you&#8217;re looking for a casino without Gamstop that provides a more sophisticated style of gaming experience, then there&#8217;s no place more suitable than the Players Club VIP casino. This sleek style site gives you access to all types of betting options in a high-class gaming environment.</p>
Highlights
<ul>
<li>Online casino, live casino, and sportsbook</li>
<li>Great promotions and bonuses</li>
<li>Daily cashback with low wagering</li>
<li>Play with credit cards and Crypto</li>
</ul>
<p>With the Players Club VIP, you can choose between starting your new player journey with a Casino or Sports welcome bonus. From there, you can look forward to an exciting range of daily casino cashback and other rewards, including VIP benefits. The site is packed with the best slots, table games, live casino entertainment, and sports betting options from the industry&#8217;s best software providers.</p>
<p>Top security technology is implemented, with professionally trained support agents always on standby to ensure the player experience goes off without a glitch. For a premium betting experience where every player feels like a VIP, this is the non-Gamstop site to be.</p>
<table width="601">
<tbody>
<tr>
<td width="170"><strong>Welcome Bonus</strong></td>
<td width="170"><strong>Wagering Requirements</strong></td>
<td width="132"><strong>Minimum Deposit</strong></td>
<td width="129"><strong>Payout Time</strong></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="170">222% up to £1,000</td>
<td width="170">45x</td>
<td width="132">£25</td>
<td width="129">1-2 Days</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
<p><a href="https://wlharryspartners.adsrv.eacdn.com/C.ashx?btag=a_1075b_276c_&amp;affid=508&amp;siteid=1075&amp;adid=276&amp;c=" rel="sponsored nofollow"><strong> <img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-527841 aligncenter" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/PlayersClubVIP-casino-uk-1.png" alt="Visit Players Club Casino" width="460" height="74" /></strong></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
9. <a href="https://www.okptrack.com/C.ashx?btag=a_2018b_402c_&amp;affid=824&amp;siteid=2018&amp;adid=402&amp;c=" rel="sponsored nofollow">SlotsDreamer</a> &#8211; 400% Bonus With a Killer Casino Theme
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-527842 aligncenter" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Slotsdreamer-casino-uk.png" alt="SlotsDreamer Non-Gamstop" width="1280" height="787" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Slotsdreamer-casino-uk.png 1280w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Slotsdreamer-casino-uk-460x283.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Slotsdreamer-casino-uk-860x529.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Slotsdreamer-casino-uk-768x472.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Slotsdreamer-casino-uk-750x461.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Slotsdreamer-casino-uk-1140x701.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1280px) 100vw, 1280px" />
<p>SlotsDreamer.co is a great non-Gamstop online casino that provides players with an exciting gaming experience. Established in 2022, this casino offers a wide range of games from top software providers, including NetEnt, Microgaming, and Play&#8217;n GO. The site boasts a sleek and modern design that is easy to navigate, making it a user-friendly experience for players.</p>
Highlights
<ul>
<li>Large selection of games from top providers</li>
<li>Mobile-friendly site</li>
<li>Multiple payment options including cryptocurrencies</li>
<li>Established casino with a 400% welcome bonus</li>
</ul>
<p>SlotsDreamer.co welcomes new players with a generous welcome package that includes a 400% match bonus up to £1200 &amp; 10% daily cashback. The casino also runs various promotions that are available to both new and existing players, providing them with an opportunity to win big, including a 10% daily cashback up to £2000.</p>
<p>The casino offers a wide variety of games, including slots, table games, video poker, and live casino games. Players can choose from over 2,000 games, with new titles being added regularly. The games are accessible via desktop and mobile devices, ensuring that players can enjoy their favorite games on the go.</p>
<p>Overall, SlotsDreamer.co is great for players who enjoy a wide range of games and a user-friendly experience. The site&#8217;s modern design, generous welcome package, and range of payment options make it an excellent choice for UK players looking for a new casino to try.</p>
<table width="601">
<tbody>
<tr>
<td width="170"><strong>Welcome Bonus</strong></td>
<td width="170"><strong>Wagering Requirements</strong></td>
<td width="132"><strong>Minimum Deposit</strong></td>
<td width="129"><strong>Payout Time</strong></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="170">400% up to £1,200</td>
<td width="170">45x</td>
<td width="132">£25</td>
<td width="129">1 – 3 Days</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
<p><a href="https://www.okptrack.com/C.ashx?btag=a_2019b_402c_&amp;affid=824&amp;siteid=2019&amp;adid=402&amp;c=" rel="sponsored nofollow"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-527881 aligncenter" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Slotsdreamer-casino-uk-1.png" alt="SlotsDreamer Casino Button" width="460" height="74" /></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
10. <a href="https://gxmble.com/?affid=55316&amp;campaign=nbtc_ng_top" rel="sponsored nofollow">Gxmble</a> – Top Casino with Very Low Wagering Requirements
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-527843 aligncenter" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Gxmble-casino-uk.png" alt="Gxmble Online Casino" width="1280" height="787" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Gxmble-casino-uk.png 1280w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Gxmble-casino-uk-460x283.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Gxmble-casino-uk-860x529.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Gxmble-casino-uk-768x472.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Gxmble-casino-uk-750x461.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Gxmble-casino-uk-1140x701.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1280px) 100vw, 1280px" />
<p>Gxmble Casino is one of the latest non-Gamstop casinos to hit the industry. The site debuted at the end of 2022 and quickly caught players&#8217; attention with its attractive design, low wagering requirements on bonuses, and massive game library.</p>
Highlights
<ul>
<li>4000+ casino games</li>
<li>Super quick registration</li>
<li>Play with Fiat and Cryptocurrencies</li>
<li>Mobile-friendly software</li>
</ul>
<p>If you&#8217;re looking for the ultimate gaming experience where great rewards and game variety meet, then Gxmble is the site for you. It starts with a 3-deposit welcome package for new players and rolls over into generous weekly offers to boost gameplay on over 4000 amazing games from industry-leading software providers.</p>
<p>The whole experience is smooth and efficient with a sophisticated website design, 1-minute registration, fast deposits and withdrawals, and reliable customer support to assist with any questions and queries.</p>
<p>Sign up at Gxmble Casino today to enjoy the thrill of great games and regular rewards. Become a VIP member and enjoy the benefits of 10% cashback.</p>
<table width="601">
<tbody>
<tr>
<td width="170"><strong>Welcome Bonus</strong></td>
<td width="170"><strong>Wagering Requirements</strong></td>
<td width="132"><strong>Minimum Deposit</strong></td>
<td width="129"><strong>Payout Time</strong></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="170">200% up to £500</td>
<td width="170">5x</td>
<td width="132">£25</td>
<td width="129">1 – 3 Days</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
<p><a href="https://gxmble.com/?affid=55316&amp;campaign=nbtc_ng_top" rel="sponsored nofollow"><strong> <img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-527882 aligncenter" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Gxmble-casino-uk-1.png" alt="Visit Gxmble Casino" width="460" height="74" /></strong></a></p>
<h2>Non-Gamstop Casinos That Nearly Made the Top List for 2023</h2>
11. <a href="https://creatives.affiliate.bitcoin.com/redirect.aspx?pid=5682&amp;lpid=17&amp;bid=1816" rel="sponsored nofollow">Games.Bitcoin</a> – Best UK Casino for Crypto
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-527844 aligncenter" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Games.Bitcoin.com-casino-uk.png" alt="Games.Bitcoin Non Gamstop Online Casino" width="1280" height="787" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Games.Bitcoin.com-casino-uk.png 1280w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Games.Bitcoin.com-casino-uk-460x283.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Games.Bitcoin.com-casino-uk-860x529.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Games.Bitcoin.com-casino-uk-768x472.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Games.Bitcoin.com-casino-uk-750x461.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Games.Bitcoin.com-casino-uk-1140x701.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1280px) 100vw, 1280px" />
<p>Games.Bitcoin.com is an online crypto casino that offers players a safe and secure gaming experience while allowing them to use cryptocurrency for all their transactions. Whether you are a seasoned player or new to online gambling, this platform has everything you need to enjoy the best gaming experience.</p>
Highlights
<ul>
<li>Good selection of slots from a range of providers</li>
<li>Deposit with crypto and credit card</li>
<li>Multiple bonuses and promotions on offer</li>
<li>Instant payouts and high cashout limits</li>
</ul>
<p>Games.Bitcoin.com offers players a fantastic gaming experience with its wide selection of games, including popular slots, table games, video poker, and live dealer games. The platform accepts various cryptocurrencies for easy deposits and withdrawals and provides excellent customer support 24/7.</p>
<p>One of the best things about Games.Bitcoin.com is its attractive bonuses and promotions, including a welcome bonus of up to 5 BTC and 300 free spins. The platform updates its promotions regularly, providing players with more opportunities to win and enjoy their gaming experience.</p>
<p>Overall, Games.Bitcoin.com is a secure and enjoyable gambling site that provides players with a great gaming experience while allowing them to use cryptocurrency for all their transactions.</p>
<table width="601">
<tbody>
<tr>
<td width="226"><strong>Welcome Bonus</strong></td>
<td width="114"><strong>Wagering Requirements</strong></td>
<td width="132"><strong>Minimum Deposit</strong></td>
<td width="129"><strong>Payout Time</strong></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="226">25% Cashback Bonus</td>
<td width="114">0x</td>
<td width="132">0,0001 BTC</td>
<td width="129">Instant</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
<p><a href="https://creatives.affiliate.bitcoin.com/redirect.aspx?pid=5683&amp;lpid=17&amp;bid=1816" rel="sponsored nofollow"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-527883 aligncenter" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Games.Bitcoin.com-casino-uk-1.png" alt="Games.Bitcoin Button" width="460" height="74" /></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
12. <a href="https://tracker-pm2.west-affiliates.com/link?btag=43670502_251264" rel="nofollow">GoldWin Casino</a> – Safe and Secure Non-Gamstop Casino
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-527845 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Goldwin-casino-uk.png" alt="GoldWin Casino Online" width="1280" height="787" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Goldwin-casino-uk.png 1280w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Goldwin-casino-uk-460x283.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Goldwin-casino-uk-860x529.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Goldwin-casino-uk-768x472.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Goldwin-casino-uk-750x461.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Goldwin-casino-uk-1140x701.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1280px) 100vw, 1280px" />
<p>This relatively new UK online casino opened its door in 2020 and focuses on bringing players the best in online slots and wager-free spins. If you&#8217;re an online slot player looking for high-quality slot entertainment and bonus benefits, GoldWin Casino is for you.</p>
Highlights
<ul>
<li>Exciting slot tournaments</li>
<li>No wagering promotions</li>
<li>24/7 customer support</li>
<li>Wide selection of payment options</li>
</ul>
<p>GoldWin has a sleek and sophisticated white and gold website design. It features over 2000 of the best online slots and table games like roulette, blackjack, and more. The live casino section provides an authentic live dealer experience for those looking for that real casino feel.</p>
<p>Gameplay gets boosted with daily bonuses and promotional boosts, starting with a generous welcome bonus for new players. And the Tournaments section displays all the hottest tournaments you can participate in, where you can compete in the hottest games for your share in amazing prizes.</p>
<p>Funds can be transferred to and from your account via trusted and secure payment methods, with support available daily via multiple channels. Sign up at GoldWin Casino to claim your welcome bonus and get started.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<table width="601">
<tbody>
<tr>
<td width="170"><strong>Welcome Bonus</strong></td>
<td width="170"><strong>Wagering Requirements</strong></td>
<td width="132"><strong>Minimum Deposit</strong></td>
<td width="129"><strong>Payout Time</strong></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="170">250 Free Spins</td>
<td width="170">None</td>
<td width="132">£20</td>
<td width="129">1-2 Days</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
<p><a href="https://tracker-pm2.west-affiliates.com/link?btag=43670502_251264" rel="sponsored nofollow"><strong> <img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-527884 aligncenter" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Goldwin-casino-uk-1.png" alt="GoldWin Online Casino Button" width="460" height="74" /></strong></a></p>
13. <a href="https://go.winnercasino.bet/visit/?bta=35459&amp;nci=5396&amp;afp=click_id&amp;utm_campaign=source_id" rel="nofollow">Winner</a> – Casino With Generous Promotions<strong>
</strong>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-527846 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Winner-casino-uk.png" alt="Winner Online Casino Site" width="1280" height="787" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Winner-casino-uk.png 1280w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Winner-casino-uk-460x283.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Winner-casino-uk-860x529.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Winner-casino-uk-768x472.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Winner-casino-uk-750x461.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Winner-casino-uk-1140x701.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1280px) 100vw, 1280px" /></p>
<p>When top-notch security, high-quality games, and great daily promotions are what you&#8217;re looking for, then Winner Casino is the place to go. Winner Casino runs smoothly across desktop and mobile devices, allowing you to enjoy a supreme betting experience from home or on the go.</p>
Highlights
<ul>
<li>Large range of online slots</li>
<li>Mobile-friendly casino</li>
<li>24/7 customer support</li>
<li>Generous welcome bonus and promotions</li>
</ul>
<p>At Winner there is a superb collection of casino games, including online slots, table games, jackpot games, and live games.</p>
<p>Gameplay is boosted with a giant welcome bonus for new players and daily promotions for the regulars. And then there is a special VIP program that awards exclusive daily promos and rewards to keep the good times rolling.</p>
<p>The site utilizes the latest security measures and has great customer support to ensure players have a smooth and carefree betting experience. Start your journey with Winner Casino and explore hundreds of games today.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<table width="601">
<thead>
<tr>
<td width="170"><strong>Welcome Bonus</strong></td>
<td width="170"><strong>Wagering Requirements</strong></td>
<td width="132"><strong>Minimum Deposit</strong></td>
<td width="129"><strong>Payout Time</strong></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="170">400% up to £4,000 + 100 Free Spins</td>
<td width="170">50x</td>
<td width="132">£20</td>
<td width="129">1-2 Days</td>
</tr>
</thead>
</table>
<p><a href="https://go.winnercasino.bet/visit/?bta=35459&amp;nci=5396&amp;afp=click_id&amp;utm_campaign=source_id" rel="sponsored nofollow"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-527885 size-full aligncenter" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Winner-casino-uk-1.png" alt="Visit Winner Casino" width="460" height="74" /></a></p>
<strong> </strong>14. <a href="https://go.rocksolidaffiliates1.com/visit/?bta=38770&amp;nci=5782&amp;utm_campaign=nbtc_ng_top" rel="nofollow">Superlines</a> &#8211; Top Rated UK Online Casino
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-527848 aligncenter" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/CasinoSuperLines-casino-uk.png" alt="Casino Superlines Non-Gamstop" width="1280" height="787" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/CasinoSuperLines-casino-uk.png 1280w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/CasinoSuperLines-casino-uk-460x283.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/CasinoSuperLines-casino-uk-860x529.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/CasinoSuperLines-casino-uk-768x472.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/CasinoSuperLines-casino-uk-750x461.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/CasinoSuperLines-casino-uk-1140x701.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1280px) 100vw, 1280px" /></p>
Highlights
<ul>
<li>Fast and easy deposits and withdrawals</li>
<li>Mobile-friendly</li>
<li>24/7 customer support</li>
<li>Exciting bonuses and promotions</li>
</ul>
<p>Casino Superlines is a very popular casino that´s been launched recently and has built up a reputation for offering a good number of games. That list includes table games, slots, and live casino titles.</p>
<p>The slots are probably the most extensive when it comes to the sheer number of games available. The site stocks titles from a wide range of providers, including Yggdrasil and BetSoft. The former in particular is famous for regularly winning awards for their slots, including the 2021 Slot Provider of the Year. All of these games are RNG (random number generator) verified to ensure transparency and fairness.</p>
<p>The live casino section is nearly as impressive as the slots selection. The number of games is high and compares favorably with most other online casinos. There are hundreds of games available, with variants of a number of popular titles, including roulette, blackjack, and baccarat.</p>
<p>The welcome bonus is generous with £1,800 available across a player’s first three deposits. That includes 100% up to £600 and 50 spins for each of the first and third deposits, and 150% up to £600 and 75 free spins on the second deposit.</p>
<table width="601">
<tbody>
<tr>
<td width="226"><strong>Welcome Bonus</strong></td>
<td width="114"><strong>Wagering Requirements</strong></td>
<td width="132"><strong>Minimum Deposit</strong></td>
<td width="129"><strong>Payout Time</strong></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="226">100% up to £600 + 50 fs</td>
<td width="114">45x</td>
<td width="132">£20</td>
<td width="129">0 &#8211; 24 Hours</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
<p><a href="https://go.rocksolidaffiliates1.com/visit/?bta=38770&amp;nci=5782&amp;utm_campaign=nbtc_ng_top" rel="sponsored nofollow"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-527886 aligncenter" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/CasinoSuperLines-casino-uk-1.png" alt="Visit Casino Superlines" width="460" height="74" /></a></p>
15. <a href="https://go.partnerbreeze.com/visit/?bta=35466&amp;nci=5391&amp;utm_campaign=nbtc_ng_head" rel="sponsored nofollow">SpicyJackpots</a> – Premium UK Mobile Casino With 400% Bonus
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-527849 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/SpicyJackpots-casino-uk.png" alt="SpicyJackpots Online Casino" width="1280" height="787" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/SpicyJackpots-casino-uk.png 1280w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/SpicyJackpots-casino-uk-460x283.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/SpicyJackpots-casino-uk-860x529.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/SpicyJackpots-casino-uk-768x472.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/SpicyJackpots-casino-uk-750x461.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/SpicyJackpots-casino-uk-1140x701.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1280px) 100vw, 1280px" />
<p>For those interested in a top-rated desktop and mobile casino experience, look no further than SpicyJackpots Casino, founded in 2022. SpicyJackpots is designed specifically for a high-quality gaming experience on any desktop, tablet, or mobile device.</p>
Highlights
<ul>
<li>Superb mobile casino</li>
<li>Very generous welcome bonus</li>
<li>Industry-leading gaming providers</li>
<li>24/7 customer support</li>
</ul>
<p>With this online casino, you can take a bite out of the hottest entertainment, which includes the latest video slot releases, table games, instant win game variants, progressive jackpots, and live dealer games. Leading software providers power the game library.</p>
<p>Transferring funds to and from your account is quick and secure, thanks to the most trusted payment methods and the latest security measures the industry offers. On top of that SpicyJackpots Casino comes with a friendly support team that is always ready to assist with any issues should you require help.</p>
<p>Start your online gaming journey at the SpicyJackpots casino and feel the heat with great games and daily rewards.</p>
<table width="601">
<tbody>
<tr>
<td width="170"><strong>Welcome Bonus</strong></td>
<td width="170"><strong>Wagering Requirements</strong></td>
<td width="132"><strong>Minimum Deposit</strong></td>
<td width="129"><strong>Payout Time</strong></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="170">400% up to £2000 + 100 Free Spins</td>
<td width="170">50x</td>
<td width="132">£20</td>
<td width="129">1-2 Days</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
<p><a href="https://go.partnerbreeze.com/visit/?bta=35466&amp;nci=5391&amp;utm_campaign=nbtc_ng_cta" rel="sponsored nofollow"><strong> <img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-527887 aligncenter" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/SpicyJackpots-casino-uk-2.png" alt="Spicy Jackpots Casino Button" width="460" height="74" /></strong></a></p>
16. <a href="https://go.4crownscasino.com/visit/?bta=35257&amp;nci=5352&amp;utm_campaign=nbtc_ng_head" rel="sponsored nofollow">4CrownsCasino</a> – Premium Casino With Unique Slots
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-527851 aligncenter" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/4Crowns-casino-uk.png" alt="4Crowns Online Casino" width="1280" height="787" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/4Crowns-casino-uk.png 1280w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/4Crowns-casino-uk-460x283.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/4Crowns-casino-uk-860x529.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/4Crowns-casino-uk-768x472.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/4Crowns-casino-uk-750x461.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/4Crowns-casino-uk-1140x701.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1280px) 100vw, 1280px" /></p>
<p>The online gaming industry is packed with quality casinos without Gamstop, and 4 Crowns Casino is another great option. 4Crowns brings you games from an impressive list of software providers with top promotions.</p>
Highlights
<ul>
<li>Unique list of game providers</li>
<li>5 deposit welcome bonus</li>
<li>Fiat and Crypto payment methods</li>
<li>Well-established casino</li>
</ul>
<p>Two things most players tend to look for are the game variety and the boost of bonuses accompanying it. This online gaming platform offers a generous selection of promotions starting with a 5-deposit welcome bonus boost. To claim this offer, you can register your new player account today.</p>
<p>The site runs smoothly across desktops, tablets, and mobile devices, making it possible to enjoy online slots, table games, jackpots, instant win variants, and live dealer tables at home or on the go. With trusted payment methods and professional customer support, complete the Royal 4 Crowns Casino experience. Sign up to get your hands on the first of your 5 deposit welcome bonuses today.</p>
<table width="601">
<tbody>
<tr>
<td width="170"><strong>Welcome Bonus</strong></td>
<td width="170"><strong>Wagering Requirements</strong></td>
<td width="132"><strong>Minimum Deposit</strong></td>
<td width="129"><strong>Payout Time</strong></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="170">400%  up to £2000 + 100 Free Spins</td>
<td width="170">50x</td>
<td width="132">£20</td>
<td width="129">1-3 Days</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
<p><a href="https://go.4crownscasino.com/visit/?bta=35257&amp;nci=5352&amp;utm_campaign=nbtc_ng_cta" rel="sponsored nofollow"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-527888 aligncenter" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/4Crowns-casino-uk-1.png" alt="Visit 4Crowns Casino" width="460" height="74" /></a></p>
17. <a href="https://gamblii.com/?affid=55316&amp;campaign=nbtc_ng_top" rel="sponsored nofollow">Gamblii</a> – Crypto-Friendly Casino With Large Welcome Package
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-527853" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Gamblii-casino-uk.png" alt="Gamblii Non Gamstop Casino" width="1280" height="787" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Gamblii-casino-uk.png 1280w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Gamblii-casino-uk-460x283.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Gamblii-casino-uk-860x529.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Gamblii-casino-uk-768x472.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Gamblii-casino-uk-750x461.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Gamblii-casino-uk-1140x701.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1280px) 100vw, 1280px" /></p>
<p>There are different styles of online casinos on the market, and when you&#8217;re playing at a non Gamstop site, you still have interesting experiences available. At Gamblii.com, the customers get to enjoy all the good stuff online casinos have to offer, like great games, live casino, and sports betting entertainment</p>
Highlights
<ul>
<li>Elegant and fun mobile casino</li>
<li>Fast, efficient customer support</li>
<li>Quick signup feature</li>
<li>Rewarding welcome bonus</li>
</ul>
<p>This gambling site is easily accessible on any desktop, tablet, or mobile device, making it possible to enjoy premium gaming entertainment from home or on the go. The site boosts your gameplay right from the get-go with a generous welcome bonus and regular daily promotions. Not to mention the thrilling VIP program with its exclusive range of benefits.</p>
<p>Gamblii utilizes the latest safety technology and most trusted payment methods to make deposits and withdrawals quick and hassle-free. Should you run into any issues, a professionally trained support team is ready to assist you.</p>
<p>Sign up at Gamblii Casino to claim your welcome bonus and explore the range of slots and other games from industry-leading software providers.</p>
<table width="601">
<tbody>
<tr>
<td width="170"><strong>Welcome Bonus</strong></td>
<td width="170"><strong>Wagering Requirements</strong></td>
<td width="132"><strong>Minimum Deposit</strong></td>
<td width="129"><strong>Payout Time</strong></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="170">200% up to £250</td>
<td width="170">35x</td>
<td width="132">£20</td>
<td width="129">1-2 Days</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
<a href="https://gamblii.com/?affid=55316&amp;campaign=nbtc_ng_top" rel="sponsored nofollow"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-527889 aligncenter" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Gamblii-casino-uk-1.png" alt="Gamblii Casino Visit Button" width="460" height="74" /></a>
18. <a href="https://winstler.com/?affid=55316&amp;campaign=nbtc_ng_top" rel="sponsored nofollow">Winstler</a> – Best for Big Bonuses High Stakes<strong>
</strong>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-527854 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Winstler-casino-uk.png" alt="Winstler Casino Site" width="1280" height="787" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Winstler-casino-uk.png 1280w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Winstler-casino-uk-460x283.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Winstler-casino-uk-860x529.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Winstler-casino-uk-768x472.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Winstler-casino-uk-750x461.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Winstler-casino-uk-1140x701.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1280px) 100vw, 1280px" />
Highlights
<ul>
<li>Up to £9,500 bonus available on first five deposits</li>
<li>Games from leading providers like NetEnt and Microgaming</li>
<li>Extensive banking methods</li>
<li>Live chat support</li>
</ul>
<p>This is a casino that is new to the scene, having been established in 2022. Despite only recently making its way into the market, it has managed to make a name for itself by establishing exciting offerings for players.</p>
<p>The most eye-catching thing about this new casino has to be its welcome bonus for first-time players. For the first five deposits, players can earn up to £9,500 back in bonus credit. The first deposit is matched 300% up to £500, the second 100% up to £1,000, the third 100% up to £2,000, the fourth 50% up to £2,500, and the fifth and final deposit is matched 50% up to £3,500.</p>
<p>This is a highly generous potential bonus but the wagering requirements are somewhat restrictive at 45 times the bonus amount. Fully acceptable terms, but a tad bit into the higher end of the scale.</p>
<p>The games on offer are also impressive but less numerous than many competing casinos. The slots are numerous and include titles by all of the leading providers. However, the table games are less prominent and not given as much space in the catalog at many other casinos. Its live casino makes up for that slightly, as it includes a good number of games, including gameshows and immersive gaming experiences.</p>
<table width="601">
<tbody>
<tr>
<td width="226"><strong>Welcome Bonus</strong></td>
<td width="114"><strong>Wagering Requirements</strong></td>
<td width="132"><strong>Minimum Deposit</strong></td>
<td width="129"><strong>Payout Time</strong></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="226">300% up to £9,500</td>
<td width="114">45x</td>
<td width="132"> £20</td>
<td width="129">0 &#8211; 24 Hours</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
<p><a href="https://winstler.com/?affid=55316&amp;campaign=nbtc_ng_cta" rel="sponsored nofollow"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-527890" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Winstler-casino-uk-1.png" alt="Winstler Casino Button" width="460" height="74" /></a></p>
19. <a href="https://go.affiliatemystake.com/visit/?bta=3131374&amp;nci=5373&amp;afp2=nbtc_ng_head" rel="sponsored nofollow">Mystake.com</a> – A Well-Established Favourite UK Casino
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-527855 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/MyStake-casino-uk.png" alt=" MyStake Online Casino" width="1280" height="787" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/MyStake-casino-uk.png 1280w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/MyStake-casino-uk-460x283.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/MyStake-casino-uk-860x529.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/MyStake-casino-uk-768x472.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/MyStake-casino-uk-750x461.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/MyStake-casino-uk-1140x701.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1280px) 100vw, 1280px" /></p>
<p>Mystake Casino is a new and exciting brand that launched in 2021. This casino has quickly gained popularity due to its sleek design, user-friendly interface, and generous welcome bonus. Mystake Casino offers a great selection of casino games from some of the best providers in the industry. Whether you&#8217;re a fan of slots, table games, or live casino games, you&#8217;ll find plenty to enjoy here.</p>
Highlights
<ul>
<li>Generous welcome bonus</li>
<li>Wide selection of games from top providers</li>
<li>Multiple payment options, including cryptocurrencies</li>
<li>Mobile-friendly website</li>
</ul>
<p>New players at Mystake Casino can take advantage of a generous welcome bonus that includes a match bonus of 150% up to £200 and 100% from £200 &#8211; £1000 or when depositing using cryptocurrencies 170% up to £600 (equivalent).</p>
<p>The bonus is spread over the first three deposits, giving players more chances to win big, note: you’ll need to deposit at least £20 to be able to receive the bonus. The wagering requirements are reasonable, which makes it easier for players to meet the playthrough requirements and withdraw their winnings.</p>
<p>The website is easy to navigate, and players can find their favorite games quickly. The site is mobile-friendly, which means that players can access it on their smartphones or tablets. Mystake Casino also accepts a wide range of payment options, including cryptocurrencies, which makes it convenient for players who prefer to use digital currencies.</p>
<p>Overall, Mystake Casino is a great choice for players who are looking for a new and exciting online casino experience. With its wide selection of games, generous welcome bonus, and mobile-friendly website, it&#8217;s definitely worth checking out.</p>
<table width="601">
<tbody>
<tr>
<td width="170"><strong>Welcome Bonus</strong></td>
<td width="170"><strong>Wagering Requirements</strong></td>
<td width="132"><strong>Minimum Deposit</strong></td>
<td width="129"><strong>Payout Time</strong></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="170">100% up to £1,000</td>
<td width="170">30x</td>
<td width="132">£20</td>
<td width="129">1 – 3 Days</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
<p><a href="https://go.affiliatemystake.com/visit/?bta=3131374&amp;nci=5373&amp;afp3=nbtc_ng_cta" rel="sponsored nofollow"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-527891 size-full aligncenter" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/MyStake-casino-uk-1.png" alt="Visit MyStake Casino" width="460" height="74" /></a></p>
<h2>Comparing the Best Non Gamstop Online Casinos</h2>
<p>Here you have a list of great non-Gamstop casinos available in the UK, and each has something different to offer. If you&#8217;re unsure which site may be the best to play at, a quick comparison of what they offer might be the way to go. With this brief comparison, you&#8217;ll easily be able to see which site has the best welcome offer, games, and payment methods accessible to you.</p>
<p>Take a look at the different non Gamstop casinos and online gambling sites and what they bring to the table:</p>
<table width="601">
<tbody>
<tr>
<td width="150"><strong>Non Gamstop Casinos</strong></td>
<td width="150"><strong>Welcome Offer</strong></td>
<td width="150"><strong>Game Types Available</strong></td>
<td width="150"><strong>Payment Methods</strong></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="150">NonStop Casino</td>
<td width="150">Up to 950% up to £7000</td>
<td width="150">Slots Table Games, Live Casino, Sportsbook</td>
<td width="150">Visa, MasterCard, MiFinity, Bank Transfer, Bitcoin, Ethereum, Tether</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="150">Betti Casino</td>
<td width="150">100% up to £100</td>
<td width="150">Slots Table Games, Live Casino, Sportsbook</td>
<td width="150">Visa, MasterCard, MiFinity, Bank Transfer, Bitcoin, Ethereum, Tether</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="150">Blood Moon Casino</td>
<td width="150">400% up to £800</td>
<td width="150">Slots, Table Games, Live Casino, Sportsbook, Live Racing</td>
<td width="150">Mastercard, Visa, Bitcoin, Ethereum, Litecoin, Tether, Neteller</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="150">Gxmble.com</td>
<td width="150">200% up to £500</td>
<td width="150">Slots, Table Games, Live Casino, Sports Betting</td>
<td width="150">Neteller, MasterCard, Instant Banking, Bitcoin, Litecoin, Ethereum, Paysafecard, Visa, AstroPay, Skrill</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="150">Superb.bet</td>
<td width="150">200% up to £1,000 + 200 Free Spins</td>
<td width="150">Slots, Table Games, Live Casino, Provably Fair Games</td>
<td width="150">Visa, MasterCard, Bitcoin, Litecoin, Ethereum, Tether, Webpayz</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="150">Winner Casino</td>
<td width="150">400% up to £4,000 + 100 Free Spins</td>
<td width="150">Slots, Table Games, Live Casino, Provably Fair Games, Jackpot Games</td>
<td width="150">Visa, MasterCard, Bitcoin, Litecoin, Ethereum, Tether, Coinspaid</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="150">Players Club VIP</td>
<td width="150">222% up to £1,000</td>
<td width="150">Slots, Table Games, Live Casino, Sportsbook, Live Racing, Virtual Games</td>
<td width="150">Visa, MasterCard, MiFinity, Bank Transfer, Bitcoin, Ethereum, Tether</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="150">Gamblii.com</td>
<td width="150">200% up to £250</td>
<td width="150">Slots, Table Games, Sportsbook, Live Casino, Jackpot Games</td>
<td width="150">Visa, Mastercard, Maestro, Bitcoin, Ethereum, Litecoin</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="150">GoldWin Casino</td>
<td width="150">250 Free Spins</td>
<td width="150">Slots, Table Games, Sportsbook, Live Casino, Jackpot Games</td>
<td width="150">Visa, MasterCard, Sofort, Skrill, Trustly, Paysafecard, Neteller, Zimpler</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="150">SpicyJackpots</td>
<td width="150">400% up to £2,000 + 100 Free Spins</td>
<td width="150">Slots, Table Games, Live Casino, Jackpot Games, Instant Win Games</td>
<td width="150">Visa, MasterCard, Bitcoin, Litecoin, Ethereum, Coinspaid, Tether, Webpayz</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="150">Slotsdreamer.co</td>
<td width="150">400% up to £1,200</td>
<td width="150">Slots, Table Games, Live Casino, Sportsbook, Live Racing, Virtual Games</td>
<td width="150">Visa, MasterCard, Bitcoin, Litecoin, Ethereum, Coinspaid, Tether, Webpayz</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="150">4 Crowns Casino</td>
<td width="150">400%  up to £2,000 + 100 Free Spins</td>
<td width="150">Slots, Table Games, Live Casino, Jackpot Games, Instant Win Games</td>
<td width="150">Visa, MasterCard, Bitcoin, Litecoin, Ethereum, Tether, Webpayz, Coinspaid</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="150">Games.Bitcoin.com</td>
<td width="150">25% Wager Free Cashback Bonus</td>
<td width="150">Slots, Table Games, Live Casino, Jackpot Games, Instant Win Games</td>
<td width="150">Visa, MasterCard, Bitcoin, Litecoin, Ethereum, Tether, Webpayz, Coinspaid</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="150">Superlines</td>
<td width="150">100% up to £600 + 50 fs</td>
<td width="150">Slots, Table Games, Live Casino, Jackpot Games, Instant Win Games</td>
<td width="150">Visa, MasterCard, Bitcoin, Litecoin, Ethereum, Tether, Webpayz, Coinspaid</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="150">Goldenbet Casino</td>
<td width="150">100% up to £500</td>
<td width="150">Slots, Table Games, Sportsbook, Live Casino, Jackpot Game, Racing</td>
<td width="150">Visa, MasterCard, Bitcoin, Litecoin, Ethereum, Tether, Webpayz, Coinspaid</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="150">Winstler Casino</td>
<td width="150">Up to 300% up to £9,500</td>
<td width="150">Slots, Table Games, Live Casino, Jackpot Games, Instant Win Games</td>
<td width="150">Visa, MasterCard, Bitcoin, Litecoin, Ethereum, Tether, Webpayz, Coinspaid</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="150">MyStake</td>
<td width="150">100% up to £1,000</td>
<td width="150">Slots, Table Games, Sportsbook, Live Casino, Jackpot Game, RacingGames, Instant Win Games</td>
<td width="150">Visa, MasterCard, Bitcoin, Litecoin, Ethereum, Tether, Webpayz, Coinspaid</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="150">AllwinsCasino</td>
<td width="150">Up to 500% + 150 Free Spins</td>
<td width="150">Slots, Table Games, Live Casino, Jackpot Games, Instant Win Games</td>
<td width="150">Visa, MasterCard, Bitcoin, Litecoin, Ethereum, Tether, Webpayz, Coinspaid</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="150">Seven.Casino</td>
<td width="150">450% up to £7,500</td>
<td width="150">Slots, Table Games, Sportsbook, Live Casino, Jackpot Game, Racing</td>
<td width="150">Visa, MasterCard, Bitcoin, Litecoin, Ethereum, Tether, Webpayz, Coinspaid</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h2>5 Easy Steps for Signing Up at a Non Gamstop Casino</h2>
<p>Getting started at casinos not on gamstop is a quick and easy process that is quick to follow. If you&#8217;re new to online gameplay and are unsure how it works, you have come to the right place. We&#8217;ve created a quick 5-step instruction guide on how to get started.</p>
Step 1 – Find a Casino: Choose one of our Trusted Casinos not on Gamstop
<p>The first step is to find a casino that is suitable for your gaming needs. You can start by browsing our list of top recommended casinos without Gamstop to find the one that has everything you want and require.</p>
Step 2 – Register the Account: Get Started by Creating a new Player Account
<p>Once you&#8217;ve found the casino most suitable to your gaming requirements, you can visit the no Gamstop casino and click the Join/Sign Up/Register button to create your new player account. You&#8217;ll be required to fill in some personal information, including your name, surname, and email address.</p>
Step 3 – Verify the Account: Get Verified Before you Continue
<p>One of the last steps before you can start claiming bonuses, funding your account, or taking part in the site&#8217;s activities, is to verify your account. You will receive a link via email or a verification code via text, depending on the casino. Follow the instructions to verify your account.</p>
Step 4 – Fund Your Account: Make a deposit and Claim Your Bonus
<p>Now it&#8217;s time to add some funds to your bankroll by heading to the cashier. Here you can choose any secure payment method available for that specific non-Gamstop casino to fund your transactions. If you&#8217;re claiming the welcome bonus and a special promotion code is required, entering it during the transaction is important to activate the bonus. Funds will be credited to your account as soon as the transaction is successfully completed.</p>
Step 5 – Start Playing: Let the Games Begin
<p>With your online casino account successfully registered, verified, and topped up with funds, it&#8217;s time to head over to the game library and choose from the assortment of games available. Take your pick, load a game, and start playing to meet the bonus wagering requirements and strike a couple of wins while you play.</p>
<p>With this quick and easy registration process, you&#8217;ll be ready to start playing all your favorite games at any trusted non-Gamstop casino. Always select a secure casino that comes with licensing and prioritizes player safety.</p>
<h2>Payments at a Casino Not on GamStop</h2>
<p>Payments at a casino not on GamStop can vary depending on the individual casino. However, most reputable online casinos offer a range of payment methods, including credit cards, e-wallets, bank transfers, and prepaid cards. It&#8217;s important to note that some payment methods may not be available in certain countries or regions.</p>
<p>When making a payment at a casino not with GamStop, it&#8217;s crucial to ensure that the website is secure and encrypted to protect your personal and financial information. Look for casinos that use industry-standard security measures, such as SSL encryption, to safeguard your data.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-527856 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/casino-room-uk-1.png" alt="Retro Casino Slots UK" width="1344" height="896" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/casino-room-uk-1.png 1344w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/casino-room-uk-1-460x307.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/casino-room-uk-1-860x573.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/casino-room-uk-1-768x512.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/casino-room-uk-1-750x500.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/casino-room-uk-1-1140x760.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1344px) 100vw, 1344px" /></p>
<p>It&#8217;s also important to check the deposit and withdrawal limits and processing times for each payment method. Some payment methods may have lower minimum or maximum limits than others, and processing times may vary depending on the payment provider and the casino&#8217;s policies.</p>
<p>Overall, when choosing a casino not with GamStop, it&#8217;s important to consider the payment options available and ensure that they meet your needs and preferences. By doing so, you can enjoy a seamless and secure gaming experience without worrying about payment issues.</p>
<h2>Advantages of Playing at Non Gamstop Casino Sites</h2>
<p>UK players who choose to play at a non-Gamstop online casino have more control over their gambling experience, as the casinos are not limited by the same restrictions. Here are a couple of benefits that stem from playing at an online casino without Gamstop.</p>
Easier KYC Verification
<p>When it comes to making your payments at any online casino, there is often a couple of hoops to jump through, especially with Gamstop sites. You may find that non-Gamstop sites do not have the same verification requirements. They are often referred to as no-verification casinos, as the process is much quicker. In contrast, other sites may have a process that takes a couple of days.</p>
Less Brand Tax and More Bonus Rewards
<p>One of the biggest advantages of these offshore sites is that they often have fewer taxes to pay. While this is an advantage for the site itself, it also comes at an advantage for you as it means that they can expand and increase their range of bonuses and promotions while lowering the deposit requirements.</p>
Ideally Situated
<p>Many of these online casinos without Gamstop are still located in Europe. While they are non-Gamstop sites, they are still considered safe and accept UK players. They provide a wide range of perks to enhance the gaming experience.</p>
<h2>Disadvantages of Casinos Not on Gamstop</h2>
<p>A couple of drawbacks are tied to non-Gamstop online casinos, which also need to be taken into account. We take a look at some of the disadvantages these sites have to give you a clear view of the experience available on any casino site without Gamstop.</p>
Counselling on Your Own Dime
<p>When it comes to non-Gamstop sites, you don&#8217;t have the option of free counselling. This is something that isn&#8217;t always noticeable, but it can be a big help in cases where it&#8217;s needed. Most non-Gamstop sites don&#8217;t have counselling options.</p>
A Withdrawal Flow
<p>With most sites, you find set withdrawal limits that are quite strict. At non-Gamstop casino sites, you will notice a free flow in terms of withdrawals, enabling you to withdraw any amount you want at any moment.</p>
Not Always Telephone Support
<p>Some non gamstop casinos don&#8217;t offer telephone support. However, many of these casinos provide around-the-clock live support via chat, which can be just as efficient. If you prefer telephone support, it&#8217;s important to check whether this option is available before signing up with a particular casino brand.</p>
<p><a href="https://record.bettiaffiliates.com/_1mW-aXseORkUlyDuv67Mo2Nd7ZgqdRLk/5/" rel="sponsored nofollow"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-527857 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/betti_casino_UK_banner_wb.png" alt="Betti Welcome Bonus Banner" width="728" height="90" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/betti_casino_UK_banner_wb.png 728w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/betti_casino_UK_banner_wb-460x57.png 460w" sizes="(max-width: 728px) 100vw, 728px" /></a></p>
<h2>How We Rate the Best Online Casinos Not on Gamstop</h2>
<p>When reviewing and vetting trusted online casinos without Gamstop, there are different factors we take into consideration. Sites undergo rigorous testing, and only the best sites that meet most of our criteria checklist are added to the list. Take a look at what we consider before adding a site to our list of recommendations:</p>
Licensing and Security
<p>Before you register at online casinos, you want to know that the site is licensed and regulated to ensure it provides a secure gaming experience for all its players. Commonly non Gamstop casinos are not licensed by the UK Gambling Commission but will carry licensing from other gaming authorities like Curaçao eGaming, Kahnawake Gaming Commission, or Malta Gaming Authority. Licensed sites incorporate the latest security measures like SSL data encryption to provide a secure betting experience.</p>
Great Banking Options
<p>Once you&#8217;ve confirmed that a site is licensed and utilizes the latest security, reviewing the payment methods to ensure it allows deposits and withdrawals via secure payment methods you&#8217;re comfortable with is best. Most of the casinos not on Gamstop that we review, will offer payments via trusted payment options in fiat and cryptocurrency, giving you a variety of options to choose from.</p>
Bonuses at Casinos Not on Gamstop
<p>Playing games online often feels even more exciting with the added benefit of promotions and a VIP program where you can climb the tiers to unlock bigger rewards. After checking to see if a site is secure and features secure payment methods, we look for the different types of bonuses and benefits players can access while playing.</p>
<p><a href="https://creatives.affiliate.bitcoin.com/redirect.aspx?pid=5683&amp;lpid=17&amp;bid=1816" rel="sponsored nofollow"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-527858 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/bitcoin.com_Games_Banner_728X90.jpg" alt="Bitcoin.com Games 25% Cashback" width="728" height="90" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/bitcoin.com_Games_Banner_728X90.jpg 728w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/bitcoin.com_Games_Banner_728X90-460x57.jpg 460w" sizes="(max-width: 728px) 100vw, 728px" /></a></p>
<p>Along with the terms connected to it, making sure the offers are worthwhile.  We have reviewed more than 30 casinos not on gamstop and carefully selected the highest-quality brands in this article, taking into consideration factors such as bonuses and promotions. We suggest taking a closer look to find a bonus that aligns with your preferred gameplay style.</p>
Wide Range of Casino Games
<p>There&#8217;s nothing as exciting as a quality range of games from industry-leading providers that run smoothly on all devices. Before recommending online casinos not on gamstop, we ensure that games run smoothly on all platforms in a high-quality format. A big plus is when sites have a large game variety with advanced game filters making it easier to find your favourite games.</p>
Helpful Customer Service
<p>A priority in the process is testing the customer service available. This means testing whether the support agents are available when they say they are, the quality of support offered, and whether queries are resolved promptly. Support plays a big role in a successful gaming experience, and you want to ensure the support team is always professional and friendly.</p>
<p>What we noticed is that there are some concerns from players about casinos not on gamstop. However, our thorough review has shown no significant difference in the quality of customer support between regular UK online casinos and the best non-GamStop casinos listed here in our review.</p>
<a href="https://seven.casino/?affid=10291&amp;campaign=nbtc_ng_cta" rel="sponsored nofollow"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-527863 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/seven_casino_uk_banner_728x90.jpg" alt="Seven Casino Welcome Offer" width="728" height="90" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/seven_casino_uk_banner_728x90.jpg 728w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/seven_casino_uk_banner_728x90-460x57.jpg 460w" sizes="(max-width: 728px) 100vw, 728px" /></a>
Simple Terms &amp; Conditions
<p>Reviewing their terms and conditions are an important factor when sifting through casinos without Gamstop. It&#8217;s important to find sites that provide players with transparent, fair, and simple terms. You want to be able to read and understand the words so you know what you&#8217;re getting yourself into.</p>
<h2>FAQs about Non Gamstop Casinos in the UK</h2>
Are My Funds Safe at a Non Gamstop Casino?
<p>This depends on the casino. If you are playing at a licensed and regulated non-Gamstop casino, you can enjoy a secure experience where your funds are protected. To ensure you have a safe gaming experience, choose from the top recommended sites listed here on our site.</p>
Are non Gamstop Casino Sites Trustworthy?
<p>Yes, when you&#8217;re playing at any recommended non Gamstop casinos that are licensed and regulated. You can rest assured that the site is secure and trustworthy, with strict security measures in place, fair gaming practices, and player satisfaction as the number one priority.</p>
<a href="https://go.affision.com/visit/?bta=36714&amp;brand=goldenbet&amp;utm_campaign=nbtc_ng_cta" rel="nofollow"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-527879 aligncenter" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Goldenbet-banner-UK.png" alt="" width="728" height="60" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Goldenbet-banner-UK.png 728w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Goldenbet-banner-UK-460x38.png 460w" sizes="(max-width: 728px) 100vw, 728px" /></a>
Can I Cash out Winnings at Casinos, Not on Gamstop in the UK?
<p>The non-Gamstop gaming sites within the UK are regulated and licensed and follow strict regulatory measures to provide a safe real, money gaming experience. You can make deposits and cash out your winnings at non Gamstop casinos within the UK.</p>
What is the Best Casino not on Gamstop?
<p>You can play at plenty of top-rated non Gamstop online casinos. We&#8217;ve compiled a list of safe sites with the best bonuses, games, and features, with Betti Casino and Blood Moon Casino being among the top recommended.</p>
Do Casinos not on Gamstop Still use Responsible Gambling Tools?
<p>Yes, various non Gamstop casinos still provide players access to responsible gaming tools, including self-exclusion and cool-off options, just not via Gamstop. You can also make use of other tools like setting personal account limits to stay in control of your gaming.</p>
Are all UK Casinos on Gamstop?
<p>Not necessarily, there are various casinos operating that are not on Gamstop, as seen via this guide. You can still enjoy secure gameplay via a range of non-Gamstop casinos in the UK, including our list of top recommendations.</p>
<p><a href="https://gxmble.com/?affid=55316&amp;campaign=nbtc_ng_top" rel="nofollow"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-527880 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/gxmble_banner_UK_728x90.jpg" alt="Gxmble Casino Welcome Bonus" width="728" height="90" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/gxmble_banner_UK_728x90.jpg 728w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/gxmble_banner_UK_728x90-460x57.jpg 460w" sizes="(max-width: 728px) 100vw, 728px" /></a></p>
Are There Mobile Casinos Not on Gamstop?
<p>There is a great range of secure mobile casinos that are not on Gamstop but provide a secure gameplay experience to players who prefer gameplay on the go. Take a look at our list of top recommendations for the best mobile casinos not on GamStop</p>
Can I make Deposits at Casinos That are Not on Gamstop?
<p>You can make deposits and withdrawals at non-Gamstop online casinos to enjoy a real money gaming experience with the opportunity to win real money rewards. The sites are regulated and utilise the most secure payment methods for safe deposits and withdrawals.</p>
Are non-Gamstop Casino Sites Legit?
<p>Yes, these casinos not on Gamstop are legit sites that carry licensing from respected gaming authorities and provide a secure gaming experience to players. The sites are generally not licensed by the UK Gambling Commission but by other respectable gaming authorities within the industry.</p>
Will I find All of my Favourite Games at UK Sites not on Gamstop?
<p>This depends on the online casino you visit. Not all casinos provide you with the same variety of games to choose from, but at the right casino, you are bound to have access to all your favourite game variants, including the best slots, table games, and live casino games.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/non-gamstop-uk-460x307.png" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin At $25,000 Or $30,000? Crypto Analyst Weighs In</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-at-25000-or-30000-crypto-analyst-weighs-in/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Best Owie]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 14:00:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=527932</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin has experienced a hard couple of days after climbing above $30,000 last week. The coin reaching a new 9-month high triggered euphoria in the market. However, it has begun to wear off as Bitcoin has now returned to $28,000 once more. The question now is where does BTC go from here? Does it continue its uptrend and is further downside more likely for the cryptocurrency? Analyst Shares Expectations For Bitcoin Speaking on where Bitcoin might go from here, analyst Micheal van de Poppe shared his forecasts. The analyst shared a BTC chart that showed unpredictable movement for the cryptocurrency at best, signaling that BTC had entered a region where forecasts are hard to come up with. Related Reading: Arbitrum Defies Bears As ARB Price Breaks Above $1.7 Resistance, But Can It Keep Up? He put the next crucial point for the digital asset at the $27,600 level. Given that Bitcoin had previously ranged support here before its run-up above $30,000, it becomes an important level. Van de Poppe explained that the rally could continue from here but it would need to be fast. “Could take liquidity beneath, but needs a fast recovery,” he explained. #Bitcoin is currently showing weakness. Broke back in the range, lost one of the crucial levels. Final crucial level is at $27,600. Could take liquidity beneath, but needs a fast recovery. If not, and no break of $28,800, then I suspect we&#39;ll see $26,200. pic.twitter.com/TuCaFq8eIk &#8212; Michaël van de Poppe (@CryptoMichNL) April 21, 2023 On the flip side of this is the $28,800 resistance being mounted by the bears. At this point, the analyst explains that it becomes crucial to breach this level. In the event that bulls are unable to retake it, then he puts the price back in the $26,000 territory. BTC Enters A Perilous Position BTC is now at a point where it becomes very important for it to at least see some upside if it is to continue holding its value. This is because its decline to $28,000 has now put it firmly below its 20-day moving average. So while Bitcoin remains bullish for the long term, the short term has turned bearish very quickly. BTC falls to $28,000 &#124; Source: BTCUSD on TradingView.com Right now, there is support at $28,000 but there is no telling if this will hold as BTC is already below $28,100. The mounting resistance at $28,800 is also a deterrent right now for investors, who are choosing to keep their distance. Related Reading: Bears Drag Ethereum Below $2,100 Support As ETH Withdrawals Cross $2 Billion However, such a position also means that the possibility of the upside is just as high as that of the downside. For some, this retracement has presented a unique opportunity to get into the cryptocurrency at cheaper prices and could trigger an accumulation trend. As long as demand remains high, then $25,000 remains speculation for now. Bitcoin’s price is still suffering losses at the time of this writing. It is currently trading at $28,033 with a 2.70% decline in the last 24 hours. On the weekly chart, it is seeing 9.04% losses, but there has been a small uptick of 5.11% in its trading volume in the last day. Follow Best Owie on Twitter for market insights, updates, and the occasional funny tweet… Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="p2">Bitcoin has experienced a hard couple of days after climbing above $30,000 last week. The coin reaching a new 9-month high triggered euphoria in the market. However, it has begun to wear off as Bitcoin has now returned to $28,000 once more. The question now is where does BTC go from here? Does it continue its uptrend and is further downside more likely for the cryptocurrency?</p>
<h2 class="p2">Analyst Shares Expectations For Bitcoin</h2>
<p class="p2">Speaking on where Bitcoin might go from here, analyst Micheal van de Poppe shared his forecasts. The analyst shared a BTC chart that showed unpredictable movement for the cryptocurrency at best, signaling that BTC had entered a region where forecasts are hard to come up with.</p>

<p class="p2">He put the next crucial point for the digital asset at the $27,600 level. Given that Bitcoin had previously ranged support here before its run-up above $30,000, it becomes an important level. Van de Poppe explained that the rally could continue from here but it would need to be fast. “Could take liquidity beneath, but needs a fast recovery,” he explained.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr"><a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Bitcoin?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#Bitcoin</a> is currently showing weakness. </p>
<p>Broke back in the range, lost one of the crucial levels.</p>
<p>Final crucial level is at $27,600. Could take liquidity beneath, but needs a fast recovery. </p>
<p>If not, and no break of $28,800, then I suspect we&#39;ll see $26,200. <a href="https://t.co/TuCaFq8eIk" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/TuCaFq8eIk</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Michaël van de Poppe (@CryptoMichNL) <a href="https://twitter.com/CryptoMichNL/status/1649287357433094146?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">April 21, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p></p>
<p class="p2">On the flip side of this is the $28,800 resistance being mounted by the bears. At this point, the analyst explains that it becomes crucial to breach this level. In the event that bulls are unable to retake it, then he puts the price back in the $26,000 territory.</p>
<h2 class="p2">BTC Enters A Perilous Position</h2>
<p class="p2">BTC is now at a point where it becomes very important for it to at least see some upside if it is to continue holding its value. This is because its decline to $28,000 has now put it firmly below its 20-day moving average. So while Bitcoin remains bullish for the long term, the short term has turned bearish very quickly.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/IcdldzEU/" alt="Bitcoin (BTC) price chart from TradingView.com" width="2854" height="1724" /></p>

<p class="p2">Right now, there is support at $28,000 but there is no telling if this will hold as BTC is already below $28,100. The mounting resistance at $28,800 is also a deterrent right now for investors, who are choosing to keep their distance.</p>

<p class="p2">However, such a position also means that the possibility of the upside is just as high as that of the downside. For some, this retracement has presented a unique opportunity to get into the cryptocurrency at cheaper prices and could trigger an accumulation trend. As long as demand remains high, then $25,000 remains speculation for now.</p>
<p class="p2">Bitcoin’s price is still suffering losses at the time of this writing. It is currently trading at $28,033 with a 2.70% decline in the last 24 hours. On the weekly chart, it is seeing 9.04% losses, but there has been a small uptick of 5.11% in its trading volume in the last day.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/iStock-913653902-1-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Exchange Outflows Spike, Bullish Sign?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-exchange-outflows-spike-bullish-sign/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hououin Kyouma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 13:00:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Bullish]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Exchange Outflows]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=527921</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[On-chain data shows the Bitcoin exchange outflows have seen a significant spike during the past day, a sign that may be bullish for the price. Bitcoin Exchange Outflows Have Observed A Large Spike Today As pointed out by an analyst in a CryptoQuant post, a total of 2,138 BTC has been taken out of exchanges during the last day. The &#8220;exchange outflow&#8221; is an indicator that measures the total amount of Bitcoin that&#8217;s being withdrawn from the wallets of all centralized exchanges. When the value of this metric has an elevated value, it means the investors are transferring out a large number of coins from these platforms. Generally, holders withdraw their BTC from exchanges for holding onto them for extended periods in offsite wallets. Because of this reason, elevated values of this metric can be a sign of accumulation, and hence, can be bullish for the cryptocurrency&#8217;s price. On the other hand, the low values of the indicator imply there aren&#8217;t many withdrawals happening in the market right now. Such a trend can be either bearish or neutral for the asset, depending on how the &#8220;exchange inflow,&#8221; the counterpart indicator, is behaving at the moment. Holders usually deposit to exchanges for selling-related purposes, so when the exchange inflow has high values, it suggests the investors may be participating in a selloff of the asset. Naturally, this can have bearish consequences for the price. Related Reading: Bitcoin Bearish Signal: Supply Older Than 7 Years On The Move Now, here is a chart that shows the trend in the Bitcoin exchange outflow, as well as in the inflow, over the last day: The value of the outflow seems to have been quite high in recent hours &#124; Source: CryptoQuant As displayed in the above graph, the Bitcoin exchange outflow has registered a very sharp spike in the last few hours. In total, the investors have withdrawn 2,138 BTC (about $60.6 million at the current exchange rate) from exchanges with this spike. Since these large withdrawals have come while the price of the cryptocurrency has been in the lower $28,000 values (which are relatively low levels considering the price had been above $30,000 just a few days ago), it&#8217;s possible that these transfers out of exchanges are a sign of fresh buying taking place in the market. From the chart, it&#8217;s also visible that the exchange inflows have remained at low values at the same time, meaning that there aren&#8217;t any deposits happening to counteract these withdrawals. This may imply that there isn&#8217;t any additional appetite for selling at the current levels for now. Related Reading: Quant Explains Bitcoin Funding Rates Pattern That Precedes Uptrends This fresh unimpeded Bitcoin accumulation can be a positive sign for the market, as it means that there are at least some large investors in the sector who view the current prices as a discounted buying opportunity, and not as a sign of more decline to come. BTC Price At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading around $28,000, down 9% in the last week. Looks like the value of the asset has been plunging in the last few days &#124; Source: BTCUSD on TradingView Featured image from Dmitry Demidko on Unsplash.com, charts from TradingView.com, CryptoQuant.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On-chain data shows the Bitcoin exchange outflows have seen a significant spike during the past day, a sign that may be bullish for the price.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Exchange Outflows Have Observed A Large Spike Today</h2>
<p>As pointed out by an analyst in a CryptoQuant <a href="https://cryptoquant.com/insights/quicktake/644223427d475a5166101956-Deciphering-the-Significance-of-a-Noteworthy-Spike-in-Bitcoin-Outflows-from-Exch" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">post</a>, a total of 2,138 BTC has been taken out of exchanges during the last day. The &#8220;<a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/breaking-news-ticker/binance-sees-218-million-in-outflows-following-cftc-lawsuit/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">exchange outflow</a>&#8221; is an indicator that measures the total amount of Bitcoin that&#8217;s being withdrawn from the wallets of all centralized exchanges.</p>
<p>When the value of this metric has an elevated value, it means the investors are transferring out a large number of coins from these platforms. Generally, holders withdraw their BTC from exchanges for holding onto them for extended periods in offsite wallets. Because of this reason, elevated values of this metric can be a sign of accumulation, and hence, can be bullish for the cryptocurrency&#8217;s price.</p>
<p>On the other hand, the low values of the indicator imply there aren&#8217;t many withdrawals happening in the market right now. Such a trend can be either bearish or neutral for the asset, depending on how the &#8220;<a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-largest-inflow-6-sign-profit-taking/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">exchange inflow</a>,&#8221; the counterpart indicator, is behaving at the moment.</p>
<p>Holders usually deposit to exchanges for selling-related purposes, so when the exchange inflow has high values, it suggests the investors may be participating in a selloff of the asset. Naturally, this can have bearish consequences for the price.</p>

<p>Now, here is a chart that shows the trend in the Bitcoin exchange outflow, as well as in the inflow, over the last day:</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone aligncenter" src="https://img.cryptoquant.com/280562/quicktake/dJQnO_cd4b12bacf4f7451dbd9305739683c2da9ffdbb9786942f1966d25d994a6b789.png" alt="Bitcoin Exchange Outflow And Inflow" width="1280" height="705" /></p>

<p>As displayed in the above graph, the Bitcoin exchange outflow has registered a very sharp spike in the last few hours. In total, the investors have withdrawn 2,138 BTC (about $60.6 million at the current exchange rate) from exchanges with this spike.</p>
<p>Since these large withdrawals have come while the price of the cryptocurrency has been in the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/crypto/bitcoin-crypto-drop-in-danger-zone/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">lower $28,000 values</a> (which are relatively low levels considering the price had been above $30,000 just a few days ago), it&#8217;s possible that these transfers out of exchanges are a sign of fresh buying taking place in the market.</p>
<p>From the chart, it&#8217;s also visible that the exchange inflows have remained at low values at the same time, meaning that there aren&#8217;t any deposits happening to counteract these withdrawals. This may imply that there isn&#8217;t any additional appetite for selling at the current levels for now.</p>

<p>This fresh unimpeded Bitcoin accumulation can be a positive sign for the market, as it means that there are at least some large investors in the sector who view the current prices as a discounted buying opportunity, and not as a sign of more decline to come.</p>
<h2>BTC Price</h2>
<p>At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading around $28,000, down 9% in the last week.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium aligncenter" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/Q0fvqGZd/" alt="Bitcoin Price Chart" width="1533" height="911" /></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/dmitry-demidko-eBWzFKahEaU-unsplash-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
