<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
>

<channel>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.newsbtc.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<description>Bitcoin &#38; cryptocurrency news today, price &#38; technical analysis</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 02:17:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Will Bitcoin Prices Limit And Slow Down The Number Of BTC &#8216;Wholecoiners?&#8217;</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/will-bitcoin-prices-limit-and-slow-down-the-number-of-btc-wholecoiners/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dalmas Ngetich]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 02:17:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adam Back]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin whales]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Caitlin Long]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=534321</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[On May 20, Caitlin Long, the founder of Custodia Bank, retweeted and revived an intriguing question posed by Adam Back, CEO of Blockstream, on whether the number of the so-called Bitcoin “wholecoiners” has peaked. Is The Number Of Bitcoin Wholecoiners Peaking? Her question is when the number of wholecoiners, or individuals holding at least 1 BTC, soared above the 1 million mark last week. While the rising number of wholecoiners points to possible adoption and rising BTC demand over time, market forces could end up capping their numbers. Related Reading: Bitcoin Plunges Below $27,000 As Miners Show Signs Of Selling She reckons that as Bitcoin prices increase, it would be more expensive for a would-be wholecoiner to purchase the asset. Therefore, based on these factors, it may be unlikely that there will be 10 million in the coming years. ARE WE AT PEAK WHOLE-COINERS in #bitcoin asks @adam3us? 1M whole-coiners today. Probably couldn’t reach 10M whole-coiners ever tho, bc bitcoin’s price would be bid up too high to reach that given the 21M supply cap… pic.twitter.com/vzRvv2vyAW &#8212; Caitlin Long 🔑⚡️🟠 (@CaitlinLong_) May 20, 2023 On May 13, Glassnode, an on-chain analytics firm, revealed that the number of addresses managing at least 1 BTC had broken above the 1 million mark and continues to steadily grow. This upward trend has remained consistent, weathering the impact of the crypto winter which saw BTC prices crumble from over $69,000 registered in November 2021 to less than $16,000 in Q4 2022. Despite this impressive trend, Long and Adam’s observations may cast doubt on whether this could continue in the long haul, pushing the number of wholecoiners to double digits. By design, Bitcoin is deflationary and there will be 21 million BTC to ever circulate. As inflation also reduces due to BTC halving roughly every four years, coin holders expect BTC prices to gradually increase over the years. Based on historical performance and increasing crypto adoption, market forces could drive BTC prices higher, making it challenging for more users to own 1 BTC currently trading at over $26,900 as on May 21. Less Than 2.5% Of BTC Addresses Are Wholecoiners While the number of wholecoiners has been steadily rising, there is a division between long-term investors and short-term speculators. Long-term Bitcoin holders have demonstrated resilience during market fluctuations, retaining their positions rather than selling. On the other hand, speculators are known more for exiting for USDT and cash during times of heightened volatility. For their actions, short-term holders or speculators have been labeled as “weak hands”. Related Reading: Bitcoin And Ethereum Supply Drops To Record Lows Unseen Since 2015 And 2017 So far, BitInfoCharts data shows that less than 2.5% of all Bitcoin addresses hold at least 1 BTC. As of May 21, addresses with between 1 and 10 BTC stood at 2.1% of the total. Meanwhile, the number of whales, or those holding above 100 BTC represented less than 0.033% of the total addresses. Roughly 93% of all Bitcoin addresses held between 0.00001 and 0.0001 BTC. -Featured Image From Canva, Chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On May 20, Caitlin Long, the founder of Custodia Bank, retweeted and revived an intriguing question posed by Adam Back, CEO of Blockstream, on whether the number of the so-called Bitcoin “wholecoiners” has peaked.</p>
<h2><b>Is The Number Of Bitcoin Wholecoiners Peaking?</b></h2>
<p>Her question is when the number of wholecoiners, or individuals holding at least 1 BTC, soared above the 1 million mark last week.</p>
<p>While the rising number of wholecoiners points to possible adoption and rising BTC demand over time, market forces could end up capping their numbers.</p>

<p>She reckons that as Bitcoin prices increase, it would be more expensive for a would-be wholecoiner to purchase the asset. Therefore, based on these factors, it may be unlikely that there will be 10 million in the coming years.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">ARE WE AT PEAK WHOLE-COINERS in <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/bitcoin?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#bitcoin</a> asks <a href="https://twitter.com/adam3us?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">@adam3us</a>? 1M whole-coiners today. Probably couldn’t reach 10M whole-coiners ever tho, bc bitcoin’s price would be bid up too high to reach that given the 21M supply cap… <a href="https://t.co/vzRvv2vyAW" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/vzRvv2vyAW</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Caitlin Long <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f511.png" alt="🔑" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/26a1.png" alt="⚡" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f7e0.png" alt="🟠" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> (@CaitlinLong_) <a href="https://twitter.com/CaitlinLong_/status/1660025105399906306?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">May 20, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p></p>
<p>On May 13, Glassnode, an on-chain analytics firm, <a href="https://studio.glassnode.com/metrics?a=BTC&amp;category=Addresses&amp;chartStyle=column&amp;m=addresses.Min1Count" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">revealed</a> that the number of addresses managing at least 1 BTC had broken above the 1 million mark and continues to steadily grow.</p>
<p>This upward trend has remained consistent, weathering the impact of the crypto winter which saw BTC prices crumble from over $69,000 registered in November 2021 to less than $16,000 in Q4 2022.</p>
<a href="https://www.tradingview.com/x/IrAlP4JT/" rel="nofollow"><img decoding="async" class="size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/IrAlP4JT/" alt="Bitcoin Price On May 21| Source: BTCUSDT On Binance,TradingView" width="1225" height="595" loading="lazy"/></a>
<p>Despite this impressive trend, Long and Adam’s observations may cast doubt on whether this could continue in the long haul, pushing the number of wholecoiners to double digits.</p>
<p>By design, Bitcoin is deflationary and there will be 21 million BTC to ever circulate. As inflation also reduces due to BTC halving roughly every four years, coin holders expect BTC prices to gradually increase over the years.</p>
<p>Based on historical performance and increasing crypto adoption, market forces could drive BTC prices higher, making it challenging for more users to own 1 BTC currently trading at over $26,900 as on May 21.</p>
<h2><b>Less Than 2.5% Of BTC Addresses Are Wholecoiners</b></h2>
<p>While the number of wholecoiners has been steadily rising, there is a division between long-term investors and short-term speculators.</p>
<p>Long-term Bitcoin holders have demonstrated resilience during market fluctuations, retaining their positions rather than selling. On the other hand, speculators are known more for exiting for USDT and cash during times of heightened volatility. For their actions, short-term holders or speculators have been labeled as “weak hands”.</p>

<p>So far, BitInfoCharts data <a href="https://bitinfocharts.com/top-100-richest-bitcoin-addresses.html" rel="nofollow">shows</a> that less than 2.5% of all Bitcoin addresses hold at least 1 BTC. As of May 21, addresses with between 1 and 10 BTC stood at 2.1% of the total. Meanwhile, the number of whales, or those holding above 100 BTC represented less than 0.033% of the total addresses.</p>
<p>Roughly 93% of all Bitcoin addresses held between 0.00001 and 0.0001 BTC.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-Wholecoiners-460x260.jpg" width="460" height="260" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Expert Predicts Ethereum (ETH) To Reach $457,000 &#8211; Here’s How</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/ethereum/crypto-expert-predicts-ethereum-eth-to-reach/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Edyme]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 14:45:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=534307</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The world of crypto is filled with fascinating possibilities and unexpected growth. In a recent series of tweets, Adam Cochran, a partner at CEHV, sparked a wave of Ethereum discussions by presenting a compelling case for Ethereum&#8217;s token, ETH, to potentially surge to as high as $457,081. Revealing The Analysis Cochran addressed skeptics who questioned the feasibility of ETH experiencing a 20x increase, comparing it to the market capitalizations of tech giants like Apple and Amazon. He emphasized that Ethereum should not be viewed as a traditional company, but rather as a groundbreaking blockchain-based infrastructure that transcends conventional boundaries. Related Reading: Ethereum Price Faces Confluence Of Bearish Factors and At Risk of Another Decline Cochran&#8217;s analysis took inspiration from the sheer magnitude of securities processed through clearing houses, reaching an astounding $2.5 quadrillion last year. Contemplating the possibility of conducting this process on the Ethereum blockchain with a meager 0.05% gas fee, Cochran envisioned an annual burn of $1.25 trillion worth of ETH, equivalent to 5.7 times the current market cap. Building upon this foundation, he extrapolated a forward-looking multiple that projected Ethereum&#8217;s potential value to approach $35 trillion. Cochran&#8217;s projection gained more momentum as he introduced the concept of a compounding burn rate. Assuming an annual compounding burn rate of 2% or more over a 20-year period, the value per ETH could potentially skyrocket to $457,081. Moreover, Cochran acknowledged that achieving a scenario where 100% of global securities settlement occurs on Ethereum within two decades might be unlikely, but settling 10% within a decade appeared feasible. Ethereum Value And Market Reach Beyond the securities market, Cochran proposed that Ethereum could capture additional value-based markets, further propelling its growth. He argued that settling 10% of global securities and tapping into other value markets could realistically lead to a 30x-35x increase in value within the next decade, even accounting for a 33% margin of error. Notably, Cochran&#8217;s analysis sheds light on Ethereum&#8217;s potential to disrupt traditional intermediaries, offering reliable and affordable settlement solutions. With trillions of dollars in annual turnover up for grabs, the prospect of eliminating trusted intermediaries become increasingly enticing for various markets worldwide. Related Reading: Gas Crisis Averted: NFT Marketplaces Witness Dramatic Reduction in Ethereum Fees While Cochran&#8217;s projections may seem audacious, they highlight the boundless possibilities within the crypto space. Ethereum&#8217;s unique position as a blockchain infrastructure opens doors to innovation and disruption, ultimately challenging the status quo of trusted intermediaries. Meanwhile, Ethereum’s price hasn&#8217;t made any significant movement in the past week but a slight upward trend, up by 0.6%. ETH has surged from a low of $1,805 seen last Friday to trade at $1,815, at the time of writing.  Ethereum market capitalization has also recorded little gains in the past seven days. ETH’s market cap has surged nearly 1% from a cap low of $217 billion to a high of $218 billion on Friday. Meanwhile, ETH’s daily trading volume has also plunged throughout the week from a high of $7 billion last Monday to $3.6 billion in the last 24 hours. -Featured image from Shutterstock, Chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The world of crypto is filled with fascinating possibilities and unexpected growth. In a recent series of <a href="https://twitter.com/adamscochran/status/1659976184568872960?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">tweets</a>, Adam Cochran, a partner at CEHV, sparked a wave of Ethereum discussions by presenting a compelling case for Ethereum&#8217;s token, ETH, to potentially surge to as high as $457,081.</p>
<h2>Revealing The Analysis</h2>
<p>Cochran addressed skeptics who questioned the feasibility of <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-bearish-1825/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">ETH experiencing a 20x increase</a>, comparing it to the market capitalizations of tech giants like Apple and Amazon. He emphasized that Ethereum should not be viewed as a traditional company, but rather as a groundbreaking blockchain-based infrastructure that transcends conventional boundaries.</p>

<p>Cochran&#8217;s analysis took inspiration from the sheer magnitude of securities processed through clearing houses, reaching an astounding $2.5 quadrillion last year. Contemplating the possibility of conducting this process on the Ethereum blockchain with a meager 0.05% gas fee, Cochran envisioned an annual burn of $1.25 trillion worth of ETH, equivalent to 5.7 times the current market cap. </p>
<p>Building upon this foundation, he extrapolated a forward-looking multiple that projected Ethereum&#8217;s potential value to approach $35 trillion.</p>
<p>Cochran&#8217;s projection gained more momentum as he introduced the concept of a compounding burn rate. Assuming an annual compounding burn rate of 2% or more over a 20-year period, the value per ETH could potentially skyrocket to $457,081. </p>
<p>Moreover, Cochran acknowledged that achieving a scenario where 100% of global securities settlement occurs on <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/ethereum-whale-resurfaces-after-2-years/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Ethereum</a> within two decades might be unlikely, but settling 10% within a decade appeared feasible.</p>
<h2>Ethereum Value And Market Reach</h2>
<p>Beyond the securities market, Cochran proposed that Ethereum could capture additional value-based markets, further propelling its growth. He argued that settling 10% of global securities and tapping into other value markets could realistically lead to a 30x-35x increase in value within the next decade, even accounting for a 33% margin of error.</p>
<p>Notably, Cochran&#8217;s analysis sheds light on <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/ethereum/gas-crisis-averted-nft-marketplaces-witness-dramatic-reduction-in-ethereum-fees/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Ethereum&#8217;s potential</a> to disrupt traditional intermediaries, offering reliable and affordable settlement solutions. With trillions of dollars in annual turnover up for grabs, the prospect of eliminating trusted intermediaries become increasingly enticing for various markets worldwide.</p>

<p>While Cochran&#8217;s projections may seem audacious, they highlight the boundless possibilities within the crypto space. Ethereum&#8217;s unique position as a blockchain infrastructure opens doors to innovation and disruption, ultimately challenging the status quo of trusted intermediaries.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-bearish-1825/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Ethereum’s price</a> hasn&#8217;t made any significant movement in the past week but a slight upward trend, up by 0.6%. ETH has surged from a low of $1,805 seen last Friday to trade at $1,815, at the time of writing. </p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/Ddfdy4WS/" alt="Ethereum (ETH)’s price chart on TradingView" width="2768" height="1556"/>
<p>Ethereum market capitalization has also recorded little gains in the past seven days. ETH’s market cap has surged nearly 1% from a cap low of $217 billion to a high of $218 billion on Friday. Meanwhile, ETH’s daily trading volume has also plunged throughout the week from a high of $7 billion last Monday to $3.6 billion in the last 24 hours.</p>
<p><em>-Featured image from Shutterstock, Chart from TradingView</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/a-118-460x278.png" width="460" height="278" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Render (RNDR) Price Surges 32% In Single Week &#8211; Here’s Why</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/altcoin/render-rndr-price-surges-32-in-single-week-heres-why/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Opeyemi Sule]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 13:09:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[render]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[RNDR]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=534285</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Render (RNDR) has been on an upward trajectory, recording some of the biggest profits in the crypto market this past week. This show of strength by the metaverse cryptocurrency coincides with a busy week dominated by the bulls.  However, it appears that the RNDR price increase is not a result of general market sentiment. So, what could be driving up the value of Render? Related Reading: Cardano Surpasses 500 Million ADA In TVL – How About Its Impact On Price? RNDR Gains 32% In One Week &#8211; Price Overview After a period of sideways movement, the price of RNDR has chosen to go upward to become one of the biggest gainers this past week. According to CoinGecko data, this coin has ballooned by more than 32% in the last seven days. It is worth noting that most of this price increase happened in two days &#8211; on the 17th and 18th of May. In an almost vertical rise, RNDR surged in value by more than 20% on Wednesday, May 17. This price rise is understood to be a reaction to the news of Apple launching its VR headset. RNDR, the utility token of the Render Network, didn&#8217;t have a great market performance in 2022, sinking as low as $0.325 at some point in the year. However, the cryptocurrency has been on an excellent recovery, gaining nearly 500% since the turn of 2023. As of this writing, the RNDR token changes hands at $2.36, with a 2.8% price increase in the past 24 hours. That said, price data reveals that the coin has not made any significant movement since Thursday, consolidating around the $2.50 price level. RNDRUSD trading at $2.367 &#124; Source: RNDRUSD chart from TradingView How Apple’s VR Headset Will Affect RNDR Price As earlier mentioned, the price surge experienced by RNDR in the past week was primarily due to the rumors of Apple launching its highly-anticipated VR headset next month. In fact, most metaverse tokens, including MANA, ICP, SAND, etc., enjoyed a bullish run as a result of the news. The Render Network offers decentralized GPU-based rendering solutions. Meanwhile, RNDR is the utility token used to pay for motion graphics, animation, and VFX rendering on the network. The RNDR token basically powers all products released by the network’s parent company. And, with the recent release of Render’s OctaneX app on M1 and M2 iPads, there is speculation that the developers of the new VR headset will use the Render network. OctaneX is an app that offers real-time, photo-realistic 3D rendering in M1 and M2 iPads. Considering this potential development, there is rising demand for the RNDR token &#8211; and we are very likely to see a further increase in its price. Related Reading: Decentraland (MANA) Leads Crypto Market Gains, Here’s Why -Featured image from RenderToken.com, chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Render (RNDR) has been on an upward trajectory, recording some of the biggest profits in the crypto market this past week. This show of strength by the metaverse cryptocurrency coincides with a busy week dominated by the bulls. </p>
<p>However, it appears that the RNDR price increase is not a result of general market sentiment. So, what could be driving up the value of Render?</p>

<h2><strong>RNDR Gains 32% In One Week &#8211; Price Overview</strong></h2>
<p>After a period of sideways movement, the price of RNDR has chosen to go upward to become one of the biggest gainers this past week. According to <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/render-token" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">CoinGecko data</a>, this coin has ballooned by more than 32% in the last seven days.</p>
<p>It is worth noting that most of this price increase happened in two days &#8211; on the 17th and 18th of May. In an almost vertical rise, RNDR surged in value by more than 20% on Wednesday, May 17. This price rise is understood to be a reaction to the news of Apple launching its VR headset.</p>
<p>RNDR, the utility token of the Render Network, didn&#8217;t have a great market performance in 2022, sinking as low as $0.325 at some point in the year. However, the cryptocurrency has been on an excellent recovery, gaining nearly 500% since the turn of 2023.</p>
<p>As of this writing, the RNDR token changes hands at $2.36, with a 2.8% price increase in the past 24 hours. That said, price data reveals that the coin has not made any significant movement since Thursday, consolidating around the $2.50 price level.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/5qrEzhuw/" alt="Render" width="1012" height="601"/></p>

<h2><strong>How Apple’s VR Headset Will Affect RNDR Price</strong></h2>
<p>As earlier mentioned, the price surge experienced by RNDR in the past week was primarily due to the rumors of Apple launching its highly-anticipated VR headset next month. In fact, most metaverse tokens, including MANA, ICP, SAND, etc., enjoyed a bullish run as a result of the news.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr"><a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Metaverse?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#Metaverse</a> tokens are on the rise this week amid rumors about Apple&#39;s new AR/VR headset <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f3a7.png" alt="🎧" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /></p>
<p>Got your eyes of any of these coins?<a href="https://t.co/bHqPPKWLk7" rel="nofollow">https://t.co/bHqPPKWLk7</a> <a href="https://t.co/FPl0854ZPa" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/FPl0854ZPa</a></p>
<p>&mdash; CoinGecko (@coingecko) <a href="https://twitter.com/coingecko/status/1659026084195864576?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">May 18, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p></p>
<p>The Render Network offers decentralized GPU-based rendering solutions. Meanwhile, RNDR is the utility token used to pay for motion graphics, animation, and VFX rendering on the network. The RNDR token basically powers all products released by the network’s parent company.</p>
<p>And, with the recent release of Render’s OctaneX app on M1 and M2 iPads, there is speculation that the developers of the new VR headset will use the Render network. OctaneX is an app that offers real-time, photo-realistic 3D rendering in M1 and M2 iPads.</p>
<p>Considering this potential development, there is rising demand for the RNDR token &#8211; and we are very likely to see a further increase in its price.</p>





]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/meta-card-460x227.png" width="460" height="227" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Conflux Token (CFX) Retraces After 39% Gains In Seven Days</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/conflux-token-cfx-retraces-after-39-gains-in-seven-days/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Olowoporoku Adeniyi]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 10:58:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cfx conflux price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conflux]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=534227</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Conflux (CFX), the token powering Conflux&#8217;s high throughput, Tree-Graph powered layer-1 blockchain, experienced a rollercoaster ride in a whirlwind of price fluctuations. Last week, it tumbled to a low of $0.20 per token, leaving observers on edge. However, it managed to climb back up over the course of the week, reaching a level of $0.330. However, the token has faced a downward trajectory in the past four days, resulting in a decrease of over 19% in price. CoinMarketCap data shows that CFX has dipped around 2% in the last 24 hours. Despite this recent dip, optimistic projections for its future price persist. While it may have encountered some setbacks, Conflux has remained one of the top performers in the past seven days, impressively gaining over 30% during this period. Maintaining a position above the key support level of $0.295, which aligns with the previous week&#8217;s high, provides some stability amidst the turbulence. What’s Driving Conflux (CFX) Growth? Conflux (CFX) has been making waves with its remarkable on-the-year gains of approximately 1,700%. Naturally, observers are curious about the role of whales in this upward surge, speculating whether they are driving the buying and pumping of the token. While it&#8217;s a possibility, we can&#8217;t say for certain. The impressive performance of Conflux coincides with the optimism surrounding China&#8217;s renewed interest in cryptocurrencies. As the country seemingly shifts its stance towards the crypto industry, there are hopes that Conflux will reap the benefits. The project has been actively fostering partnerships with various regional enterprises, positioning itself as a potential frontrunner in meeting regulatory requirements. Related Reading: XRP Emerges As Top Performing Crypto With 55% Surge – Messari Report Among its notable partnerships, Conflux has joined forces with Little Red Book, often called China&#8217;s equivalent of Instagram. This collaboration opens up exciting opportunities as Little Red Book&#8217;s massive user base of 180 million individuals can now showcase Conflux-based non-fungible tokens (NFTs) on their profiles. Additionally, Conflux has forged a partnership with China Telecom, further enhancing its presence and potential within the Chinese market. Conflux, China Telecom Introduce Blockchain SIM Card Conflux Network and China Telecom have unveiled the world&#8217;s first Blockchain SIM (BSIM) card, a mobile user identification card based on blockchain technology. The BSIM card, resembling traditional SIM cards, is compatible with Android and iOS systems and offers significantly larger storage space and computing power than traditional SIM cards. The BSIM card goes beyond standard communication functions by generating and storing users&#8217; public and private keys within the card itself. By employing a &#8220;private key never leaves the card&#8221; approach for digital signatures enhances security and reduces the risk of malware or virus attacks on mobile terminals. Additionally, the card provides encrypted storage and key recovery features and integrates traditional U-shield functions, making it a highly secure Web3 user terminal entry solution. Related Reading: Injective (INJ) Surges By 19% Following ‘Surprise’ NFT Announcement This collaboration between Conflux Network and China Telecom showcases their innovation in merging blockchain technology with mobile user identification, introducing a robust and efficient solution for users in the ever-evolving digital landscape. What Next For Conflux (CFX)? As long as renowned cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin and Ethereum continue to thrive in the face of global banking system concerns, Conflux (CFX) might also benefit from these favorable market conditions. Additionally, the prospects of significant financial easing from central banks, including the Federal Reserve, could further bolster CFX&#8217;s performance. Hong Kong&#8217;s recent decision to legalize certain cryptocurrency trades is a noteworthy development to monitor. This move is seen by many as a testing ground for potential crypto legalization on the mainland. Considering Conflux&#8217;s growing popularity and adoption in China, CFX stands to gain as a key beneficiary of this trend. The recent collaboration with a Chinese SIM card company further strengthens the optimism within the crypto community. These factors collectively contribute to the positive outlook for CFX, as it rides the coattails of established cryptocurrencies, anticipates favorable monetary policies, and capitalizes on potential crypto legalization in China. At press time, Conflux was trading at $0.2962. -Featured image from iStock.com, charts from CoinMarketCap and TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Conflux (CFX), the token powering Conflux&#8217;s high throughput, Tree-Graph powered layer-1 blockchain, experienced a rollercoaster ride in a whirlwind of price fluctuations. Last week, it tumbled to a low of $0.20 per token, leaving observers on edge. However, it managed to climb back up over the course of the week, reaching a level of $0.330.</p>
<p>However, the token has faced a downward trajectory in the past four days, resulting in a decrease of over 19% in price. <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/conflux-network/" rel="nofollow">CoinMarketCap data</a> shows that CFX has dipped around 2% in the last 24 hours. Despite this recent dip, optimistic projections for its future price persist.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium wp-image-534228" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image1-2-460x246.png" alt="Conflux price has retraced in the past 24 hours: source @coinmarketcap" width="460" height="246" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image1-2-460x246.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image1-2-860x459.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image1-2-768x410.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image1-2-750x400.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image1-2.png 946w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px"/>
<p>While it may have encountered some setbacks, Conflux has remained one of the top performers in the past seven days, impressively gaining over 30% during this period. Maintaining a position above the key support level of $0.295, which aligns with the previous week&#8217;s high, provides some stability amidst the turbulence.</p>
<h2><strong>What’s Driving Conflux (CFX) Growth?</strong></h2>
<p>Conflux (CFX) has been making waves with its remarkable on-the-year gains of approximately 1,700%. Naturally, observers are curious about the role of whales in this upward surge, speculating whether they are driving the buying and pumping of the token. While it&#8217;s a possibility, we can&#8217;t say for certain.</p>
<p>The impressive performance of Conflux coincides with the optimism surrounding China&#8217;s renewed interest in cryptocurrencies. As the country seemingly shifts its stance towards the crypto industry, there are hopes that Conflux will reap the benefits. The project has been actively fostering partnerships with various regional enterprises, positioning itself as a potential frontrunner in meeting regulatory requirements.</p>
<p><strong>Related Reading</strong>: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/xrp-emerges-as-top-performing-crypto-with-55-surge-messari-report/">XRP Emerges As Top Performing Crypto With 55% Surge – Messari Report</a></p>
<p>Among its notable partnerships, Conflux has joined forces with Little Red Book, often called China&#8217;s equivalent of Instagram. This collaboration opens up exciting opportunities as Little Red Book&#8217;s massive user base of 180 million individuals can now showcase Conflux-based non-fungible tokens (NFTs) on their profiles. Additionally, Conflux has forged a partnership with China Telecom, further enhancing its presence and potential within the Chinese market.</p>
<h2><strong>Conflux, China Telecom Introduce Blockchain SIM Card</strong></h2>
<p>Conflux Network and China Telecom have unveiled the world&#8217;s first Blockchain SIM (BSIM) card, a mobile user identification card based on blockchain technology. The BSIM card, resembling traditional SIM cards, is compatible with Android and iOS systems and offers significantly larger storage space and computing power than traditional SIM cards.</p>
<p>The BSIM card goes beyond standard communication functions by generating and storing users&#8217; public and private keys within the card itself. By employing a &#8220;private key never leaves the card&#8221; approach for digital signatures enhances security and reduces the risk of malware or virus attacks on mobile terminals. Additionally, the card provides encrypted storage and key recovery features and integrates traditional U-shield functions, making it a highly secure Web3 user terminal entry solution.</p>
<p><strong>Related Reading</strong>: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/altcoin/injective-inj-surges-by-19-following-surprise-nft-initiative/">Injective (INJ) Surges By 19% Following ‘Surprise’ NFT Announcement</a></p>
<p>This collaboration between Conflux Network and China Telecom showcases their innovation in merging blockchain technology with mobile user identification, introducing a robust and efficient solution for users in the ever-evolving digital landscape.</p>
<strong>What Next For Conflux (CFX)?</strong>
<p>As long as renowned cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin and Ethereum continue to thrive in the face of global banking system concerns, Conflux (CFX) might also benefit from these favorable market conditions. Additionally, the prospects of significant financial easing from central banks, including the Federal Reserve, could further bolster CFX&#8217;s performance.</p>
<p>Hong Kong&#8217;s recent decision to legalize certain cryptocurrency trades is a noteworthy development to monitor. This move is seen by many as a testing ground for potential crypto legalization on the mainland. Considering Conflux&#8217;s growing popularity and adoption in China, CFX stands to gain as a key beneficiary of this trend. The recent collaboration with a Chinese SIM card company further strengthens the optimism within the crypto community.</p>
<p>These factors collectively contribute to the positive outlook for CFX, as it rides the coattails of established cryptocurrencies, anticipates favorable monetary policies, and capitalizes on potential crypto legalization in China. At press time, Conflux was trading at $0.2962.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium wp-image-534230" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image2-2-460x254.png" alt="Conflux trading below $0.3: source @tradingview" width="460" height="254" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image2-2-460x254.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image2-2-860x474.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image2-2-768x424.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image2-2-750x414.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image2-2.png 1079w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px"/>
<p><em>-Featured image from iStock.com, charts from CoinMarketCap and TradingView.com</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/conflux-cryptoninjas-460x230.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tornado Cash (TORN) Suffers 27% Drop As Hackers Strike</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/crypto/tornado-cash-suffers-27-drop/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Semilore Faleti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 10:05:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[governance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Heist]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[TORN]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tornado Cash]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=534284</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Tornado Cash (TORN) has experienced a sudden fall in its market price over the last few hours following news of the DeFi protocol suffering a crypto exploit late yesterday. According to data from CoinMarketCap, Tornado Cash is down 28.25% in the last 24 hours, albeit this only represents a retraced value. Following news of TORN’s attack, the token initially dropped by over 60% before finding support around the price region of $3.86. Since then, TORN has made some upward movement, however not sufficient to cover up the earlier loss. Related Reading: LUNC Burn Tax Set To Rise To 0.5% As KuCoin Proposal Receives Approval TORN Governance System Breached: $2M Stolen Through a malicious governance proposal, a hacker gained control of Tornado’s Cash Governance, allocating 1,200,000 votes to themselves. According to Chinese reporter Colin Wu, the hacker used their newly gained control to move a total of 483,000 TORN out of the Tornado Cash governance vault worth about $2 million at the present market price of $4.5. The hacker then proceeded to deposit 6,000 TORN on the Bitrue exchange and swapped the remaining 379,300 TORN on-chain for 375ETH. Currently, there has been no official statement from Bitrue on this development. Meanwhile, all TORN investors have been urged to withdraw all their governance-locked funds from the project developers. In addition, the Binance exchange has suspended TORN deposits pending a solution to the governance issue. &#160; For now, it remains unknown how long it may take for TORN developers to regain control of the governance system and perhaps recover the stolen loot. Thus, TORN investors are advised to keep a close watch for any latest development.  At the time of writing, TORN is trading at $4.5, with a 1.5% gain in the last hour. Looking at its broader performance, the DeFi token leaves much to desire, with 30.6% and 48.9% losses in the last 14 and 30 days, respectively. TORN Trading At $4.5837 &#124; Source: TORNUSDT Chart on Tradingview.com Related Reading: Bitcoin And Ethereum Supply Drops To Record Lows Unseen Since 2015 And 2017 Tornado Cash Becomes Target Of Crypto Hacker Interestingly, prior to yesterday’s heist, Tornado Cash had played a different role in crypto heists rather than being the target.  The TORN protocol operates as a decentralized, non-custodial cryptocurrency tumbler that mixes “potentially identifiable or tainted cryptocurrency funds with others” so as to cover the original trail of such funds.  Due to this service, the DeFi project served as a “money laundering” tool in a couple of crypto heists, most notably the $625 million Ronin exploit in 2022. About 2000 ETH &#8211; valued at nearly $2 million then- of the loot were moved to Tornado Cash following the heist. Following this event, TORN was blacklisted by the U.S. Office of Foreign Assets Control (OFAC), banning all U.S. citizens from engaging with the protocol. Other popular heists involving the use of Tornado Cash in moving part of the stolen funds include the recent $200 million theft from Euler Finance and the $28 million Derbit hack in 2022.  -Featured Image: Forbes , Chart from Tradingview &#160;]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Tornado Cash (TORN) has experienced a sudden fall in its market price over the last few hours following news of the DeFi protocol suffering a<a href="https://forum.tornado.ws/t/emergency-withdraw-your-locked-funds-from-governance-now/37" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow"> crypto exploit</a> late yesterday. According to <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/torn/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">data from CoinMarketCap</a>, Tornado Cash is down 28.25% in the last 24 hours, albeit this only represents a retraced value.</p>
<p>Following news of TORN’s attack, the token initially dropped by over 60% before finding support around the price region of $3.86. Since then, TORN has made some upward movement, however not sufficient to cover up the earlier loss.</p>

<h2><strong>TORN Governance System Breached: $2M Stolen</strong></h2>
<p>Through a malicious governance proposal, a hacker gained control of Tornado’s Cash Governance, allocating 1,200,000 votes to themselves.</p>
<p>According to <a href="https://twitter.com/WuBlockchain/status/1660130837504102401?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw%7Ctwcamp%5Etweetembed%7Ctwterm%5E1660130837504102401%7Ctwgr%5Eda2c3d8ba448a480668b99b8d687e03a1be1d37b%7Ctwcon%5Es1_&amp;ref_url=https%3A%2F%2Fcryptonewsland.com%2Ftornado-cash-price-crashes-31-as-platform-gets-hacked%2F" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Chinese reporter Colin Wu</a>, the hacker used their newly gained control to move a total of 483,000 TORN out of the Tornado Cash governance vault worth about $2 million at the present market price of $4.5.</p>
<p>The hacker then proceeded to deposit 6,000 TORN on the Bitrue exchange and swapped the remaining 379,300 TORN on-chain for 375ETH. Currently, there has been no official statement from Bitrue on this development.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">The Tornado Cash attacker obtained a total of 483,000 TORN from the Tornado Cash governance vault, and has deposited 6,000 TORN into Bitrue; sold 379,300 TORN on the chain and exchanged it for 375 ETH (about 680,000 U.S. dollars). The price is US$1.8; there are still 97,700 TORNs…</p>
<p>&mdash; Wu Blockchain (@WuBlockchain) <a href="https://twitter.com/WuBlockchain/status/1660130837504102401?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">May 21, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p></p>
<p>Meanwhile, all TORN investors have been urged to withdraw all their governance-locked funds from the project developers. In addition, the Binance exchange has <a href="https://twitter.com/binance/status/1660127515459895296?s=46&amp;t=JAUmthpFclo8jS4VJkm3DQ" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">suspended</a> TORN deposits pending a solution to the governance issue.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Due to circumstances surrounding the protocol, <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Binance?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#Binance</a> will temporarily pause <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24TORN&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$TORN</a> deposits until further notice.</p>
<p>&mdash; Binance (@binance) <a href="https://twitter.com/binance/status/1660127515459895296?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">May 21, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>For now, it remains unknown how long it may take for TORN developers to regain control of the governance system and perhaps recover the stolen loot. Thus, TORN investors are advised to keep a close watch for any latest development. </p>
<p>At the <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/torn/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">time of writing</a>, TORN is trading at $4.5, with a 1.5% gain in the last hour. Looking at its broader performance, the DeFi token leaves much to desire, with 30.6% and 48.9% losses in the last 14 and 30 days, respectively.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/jm2KpLkb/" alt="Tornado Cash" width="1479" height="913"/></p>


<h2><strong>Tornado Cash Becomes Target Of Crypto Hacker</strong></h2>
<p>Interestingly, prior to yesterday’s heist, Tornado Cash had played a different role in crypto heists rather than being the target. </p>
<p>The TORN protocol operates as a decentralized, non-custodial cryptocurrency tumbler that mixes “potentially identifiable or tainted cryptocurrency funds with others” so as to cover the original trail of such funds. </p>
<p>Due to this service, the DeFi project served as a “money laundering” tool in a couple of crypto heists, most notably the <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2022-04-04/hacker-move-stolen-crypto-funds-from-ronin-breach-to-obfuscator" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">$625 million Ronin exploit in 2022</a>.</p>
<p>About 2000 ETH &#8211; valued at nearly $2 million then- of the loot were moved to Tornado Cash following the heist. Following this event, TORN was <a href="https://www.dotcommagazine.com/2022/08/tornado-cash-becomes-tornado-crash-according-to-us-authorities/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">blacklisted</a> by the U.S. Office of Foreign Assets Control (OFAC), banning all U.S. citizens from engaging with the protocol.</p>
<p>Other popular heists involving the use of Tornado Cash in moving part of the stolen funds include the recent <a href="https://decrypt.co/123751/euler-finance-hacker-sends-1-6m-eth-tornado-cash/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">$200 million theft from Euler Finance</a> and the<a href="https://decrypt.co/112305/bitkeep-hacker-moves-1m-binance-coin-through-tornado-cash/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow"> $28 million Derbit hack in 2022.</a> </p>

<p>&nbsp;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/960x0-1-460x303.jpg" width="460" height="303" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>LUNC Burn Tax Set To Rise To 0.5% As KuCoin Proposal Receives Approval</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/lunc-burn-tax-set-to-rise-to-0-5-as-kucoin-proposal-receives-approval/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Dunn]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 13:50:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[burn]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[KuCoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LUNCUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=534204</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[After garnering the required votes, a major proposal has just passed in the KuCoin network. The proposal aimed at raising Terra Classic LUNC burns tax to 0.5%.  Following the positive results, KuCoin declared increasing the LUNC network burn rate from 0.2% to the proposed 0.5%.  LUNC Network Burn Tax Spikes On KuCoin KuCoin took to Twitter to announce the increase in the burn tax. In its announcement, KuCoin stated that it would facilitate the Terra Classic LUNC and TerraClassicUSD (USTC) increase on its platform following the burn tax activation. Related Reading: Shiba Inu Falls Below Critical Support, Is It Time For You To Buy? Notably, the activation will occur at the designated Terrra Classic block height of 12,902,399 and take effect on May 23.  Once activated, KuCoin will pay users more for transactions involving the two crypto assets, LUNC and USTC. Apart from the increased payments, the burn rate tax will reduce LUNC supply.  But there&#8217;s still a downside to the increased burn rate tax as it will reduce the trading volume. This is why many exchanges rejected such proposals in the past.  Notably, KuCoin has always supported such increases even when other exchanges delay. For instance, the exchange first supported a September 2022 Terra Classic burn tax of 1.2% even before the proposal passed.    Other exchanges, including Crypto.com, MEXC, and Binance, only later declared support for the burn tax.  But after the proposal passed, data implied that the increase reduced the trading volume for LUNC. Many investors stopped trading with the asset due to the spike in fees. Related Reading: NFT Market Takes A Hit: Sales Could Drop Below $1 Billion For The First Time In 2023 Following the outcome, the LUNC community voted to reduce the burn tax to 0.2%, attracting the support of crypto exchanges such as Binance.  After the reduction, the Terra Classic community brought up another proposal to increase the burn tax rate, but it wasn’t implemented.  Latest Burn Tax Increase Proposal, 3 Others Gain Massive Support While other proposals to increase the burn tax after reducing it from 1.2% to 0.2% failed due to several debates and arguments, the latest one received massive support. One of the reasons proposal 11515 passed was the conservative increase, which wouldn&#8217;t spike fees and discourage investors. The proposal focused mainly on reducing the excess supply of LUNC tokens in the market to prevent oversaturation and its associated risks.  But, it is not the only proposal submitted to the LUNC community. An active member raised 3 other proposals, plus the burn tax increase to enhance economic policies on the network.  The three others aimed at augmenting demand by increasing staking rewards, whitelisting smart contracts to enhance chain utility and volume, and increasing community pool funding to bolster developer funding. -Featured image from Pexels, chart from Tradingview]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>After garnering the required votes, a major proposal has just passed in the KuCoin network. The proposal aimed at raising Terra Classic LUNC burns tax to 0.5%. </p>
<p>Following the positive results, KuCoin declared increasing the LUNC network burn rate from 0.2% to the proposed 0.5%. </p>
<h2>LUNC Network Burn Tax Spikes On KuCoin</h2>
<p>KuCoin took to <a href="https://twitter.com/kucoincom/status/1659158748924100610?" rel="nofollow">Twitter</a> to announce the increase in the burn tax. In its announcement, KuCoin stated that it would facilitate the Terra Classic LUNC and TerraClassicUSD (USTC) increase on its platform following the burn tax activation.</p>

<p>Notably, the activation will occur at the designated Terrra Classic block height of 12,902,399 and take effect on May 23. </p>
<p>Once activated, KuCoin will pay users more for transactions involving the two crypto assets, LUNC and USTC. Apart from the increased payments, the burn rate tax will reduce LUNC supply. </p>
<p>But there&#8217;s still a downside to the increased burn rate tax as it will reduce the trading volume. This is why many exchanges rejected such proposals in the past. </p>
<p>Notably, KuCoin has always supported such increases even when other exchanges delay. For instance, <a href="https://www.kucoin.com/news/en-kucoin-will-support-the-tax-burn-proposal-of-the-terra-classic-lunc-community-20220907" rel="nofollow">the exchange first supported</a> a September 2022 Terra Classic burn tax of 1.2% even before the proposal passed.   </p>
<p>Other exchanges, including Crypto.com, MEXC, and Binance, only later declared support for the burn tax. </p>
<p>But after the proposal passed, <a href="https://medium.com/@strathcole/the-1-2-tax-kills-our-volume-does-it-though-a-deeper-analysis-b58163078b79" rel="nofollow">data implied</a> that the increase reduced the trading volume for LUNC. Many investors stopped trading with the asset due to the spike in fees.</p>

<p>Following the outcome, the LUNC community voted to reduce the burn tax to 0.2%, <a href="https://twitter.com/binance/status/1582625797231497217?" rel="nofollow">attracting the support</a> of crypto exchanges such as Binance. </p>
<p>After the reduction, the Terra Classic community brought up another proposal to increase the burn tax rate, <a href="https://twitter.com/ClassyCrypto_/status/1596659582755274752?" rel="nofollow">but it wasn’t implemented</a>. </p>
<h2>Latest Burn Tax Increase Proposal, 3 Others Gain Massive Support</h2>
<p>While other proposals to increase the burn tax after reducing it from 1.2% to 0.2% failed due to several debates and arguments, the latest one received massive support.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-534206 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/LUNCUSDT_2023-05-20_17-08-49-860x370.png" alt="LUNC" width="860" height="370" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/LUNCUSDT_2023-05-20_17-08-49-860x370.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/LUNCUSDT_2023-05-20_17-08-49-460x198.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/LUNCUSDT_2023-05-20_17-08-49-768x331.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/LUNCUSDT_2023-05-20_17-08-49-1536x661.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/LUNCUSDT_2023-05-20_17-08-49-750x323.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/LUNCUSDT_2023-05-20_17-08-49-1140x491.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/LUNCUSDT_2023-05-20_17-08-49.png 1714w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/>
<p>One of the reasons proposal 11515 passed was the conservative increase, which wouldn&#8217;t spike fees and discourage investors.</p>
<p>The proposal focused mainly on reducing the excess supply of LUNC tokens in the market to prevent oversaturation and its associated risks. </p>
<p>But, it is not the only proposal submitted to the LUNC community. An active member <a href="https://classic-agora.terra.money/t/new-economic-policy-for-terra-classic-set-of-4-proposals-to-align-incentives/50415" rel="nofollow">raised</a> 3 other proposals, plus the burn tax increase to enhance economic policies on the network. </p>
<p>The three others aimed at augmenting demand by increasing staking rewards, whitelisting smart contracts to enhance chain utility and volume, and increasing community pool funding to bolster developer funding.</p>
<p><em>-Featured image from Pexels, chart from Tradingview</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/flame-ge8230230f_1280-460x306.jpg" width="460" height="306" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin And Ethereum Supply Drops To Record Lows Unseen Since 2015 And 2017</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/all/bitcoin-and-ethereum-supply-plummet-to-record-lows/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Edyme]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 13:32:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[All]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=534205</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Amid the tussle between the bulls and bears in the crypto market over the past week, the circulating supply of both Bitcoin (BTC) and Ethereum (ETH) has reached record lows, triggering speculation about the potential impact on the cryptocurrency market. Data provided by Santiment reveals a significant decrease in the amount of BTC and ETH held on exchanges, suggesting a shift in investor behavior. Bitcoin And Ethereum Supply Plummets On Exchanges According to Santiment&#8217;s data, the circulating supply of BTC on exchanges currently stands at a mere 5.7%, marking its lowest level since December 2017 when the cryptocurrency surged to an all-time high of $20,000. Related Reading: Ethereum Price Faces Confluence Of Bearish Factors and At Risk of Another Decline Similarly, the supply of ETH on exchanges has dropped to 10.1%, the lowest since its inception in 2015. This trend indicates that crypto investors are actively buying and withdrawing their coins from exchanges, opting for alternative storage methods. Santiment tweeted earlier today: Bitcoin &#38; Ethereum both continue to quietly see more and more of their existing supplies move into self custody. Though not a perfect indicator, declining coins on exchanges generally hint at future bull runs, given enough time playing out. Notably, one key reason behind the declining supply of BTC and ETH on exchanges, particularly in the case of Ethereum, is the increasing popularity of staking. Ethereum 2.0&#8217;s transition to a proof-of-stake (PoS) consensus mechanism has provided ETH holders with the opportunity to stake their coins and participate in securing the network while earning rewards. Stakers lock up their ETH in specialized wallets, ensuring its active involvement in the network&#8217;s operations rather than leaving it idle on exchanges. This shift towards staking is motivated by the desire to earn passive income and contribute to the long-term growth and security of the Ethereum ecosystem. On the other hand, the Bitcoin decrease on exchanges is not so clear, however, the possible reason can be attributed to investors looking to keep their BTC holdings for a long time. This could be due to the feared upcoming global recession which has made many turn to the idea of saving funds for the supposed &#8220;rainy days.&#8221; Implications On The Crypto Market The dwindling supply of Bitcoin and Ethereum on exchanges could have significant implications for the broader cryptocurrency market mostly positively. Firstly, it suggests a decreasing selling pressure as fewer coins are readily available for trading. This &#8220;hints at future bull runs,&#8221; according to Santiment. With a limited supply on exchanges, potential buyers might face greater difficulty acquiring these digital assets, leading to increased demand and potentially driving up the prices of both Bitcoin and Ethereum. Additionally, the reduced presence of BTC and ETH on exchanges may indicate a growing confidence among long-term holders. Investors are likely becoming more inclined to hold their coins in secure wallets or participate in staking, signaling a belief in the future potential and value appreciation of these cryptocurrencies. Related Reading: Whale Alert: 1,750 Bitcoin (BTC) Moved To Exchange, Massive Plunge Incoming? This shift in behavior reflects a maturing market where participants are increasingly focused on the underlying technology and long-term prospects rather than short-term trading. Regardless, both BTC and ETH haven&#8217;t made any significant movement in the past week. BTC&#8217;s price has experienced little upward trend up by 0.3%. BTC has surged from a low of $26,819 seen last Saturday to trading as high as above $27,000 on Thursday. In contrast, ETH&#8217;s price has experienced a slight upward trend up by 0.6% in the past week. ETH has surged from a low of $1,795 last Saturday to trading above $1,800, at the time of writing. -Featured image from Shutterstock, Chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Amid the tussle between the bulls and bears in the crypto market over the past week, the circulating supply of both Bitcoin (BTC) and Ethereum (ETH) has reached record lows, triggering speculation about the potential impact on the cryptocurrency market.</p>
<p><a href="https://twitter.com/santimentfeed/status/1659830319724519425?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Data</a> provided by Santiment reveals a significant decrease in the amount of BTC and ETH held on exchanges, suggesting a shift in investor behavior.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin And Ethereum Supply Plummets On Exchanges</h2>
<p>According to Santiment&#8217;s data, the circulating supply of <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/whale-alert-1750-bitcoin-btc-moved-to-exchange-massive-plunge-incoming/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">BTC on exchanges</a> currently stands at a mere 5.7%, marking its lowest level since December 2017 when the cryptocurrency surged to an all-time high of $20,000. </p>

<p>Similarly, the supply of ETH on exchanges has dropped to 10.1%, the lowest since its inception in 2015. This trend indicates that crypto investors are actively buying and withdrawing their coins from exchanges, opting for alternative storage methods.</p>
<p>Santiment tweeted earlier today:</p>
<blockquote><p>Bitcoin &amp; Ethereum both continue to quietly see more and more of their existing supplies move into self custody. Though not a perfect indicator, declining coins on exchanges generally hint at future bull runs, given enough time playing out.</p></blockquote>
<p>Notably, one key reason behind the declining supply of BTC and ETH on exchanges, particularly in the case of Ethereum, is the increasing popularity of staking. Ethereum 2.0&#8217;s transition to a proof-of-stake (PoS) consensus mechanism has provided ETH holders with the opportunity to <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/ethereum-whale-resurfaces-after-2-years/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">stake their coins</a> and participate in securing the network while earning rewards. </p>
<p>Stakers lock up their ETH in specialized wallets, ensuring its active involvement in the network&#8217;s operations rather than leaving it idle on exchanges. This shift towards staking is motivated by the desire to earn passive income and contribute to the long-term growth and security of the Ethereum ecosystem.</p>
<p>On the other hand, the Bitcoin decrease on exchanges is not so clear, however, the possible reason can be attributed to investors looking to keep their BTC holdings for a long time. This could be due to the feared upcoming global recession which has made many turn to the idea of saving funds for the supposed &#8220;rainy days.&#8221;</p>
<h2>Implications On The Crypto Market</h2>
<p>The dwindling supply of Bitcoin and Ethereum on exchanges could have significant implications for the broader cryptocurrency market mostly positively. Firstly, it suggests a decreasing selling pressure as fewer coins are readily available for trading. This &#8220;hints at future bull runs,&#8221; according to Santiment.</p>
<p>With a limited supply on exchanges, <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-shrimp-accumulation-surge/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">potential buyers</a> might face greater difficulty acquiring these digital assets, leading to increased demand and potentially driving up the prices of both Bitcoin and Ethereum.</p>
<p>Additionally, the reduced presence of BTC and ETH on exchanges may indicate a growing confidence among long-term holders. Investors are likely becoming more inclined to hold their coins in secure wallets or participate in staking, signaling a belief in the future potential and value appreciation of these cryptocurrencies.</p>

<p>This shift in behavior reflects a maturing market where participants are increasingly focused on the underlying technology and long-term prospects rather than short-term trading.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/gNKuk3rC/" alt="Bitcoin (BTC)’s price chart on TradingView" width="2768" height="1556"/>
<p>Regardless, both BTC and ETH haven&#8217;t made any significant movement in the past week. BTC&#8217;s price has experienced little upward trend up by 0.3%. BTC has surged from a low of $26,819 seen last Saturday to trading as high as above $27,000 on Thursday.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/CwItfiWj/" alt="Ethereum (ETH)’s price chart on TradingView" width="2768" height="1556"/>
<p>In contrast, <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-bearish-1825/?swcfpc=1">ETH&#8217;</a>s price has experienced a slight upward trend up by 0.6% in the past week. ETH has surged from a low of $1,795 last Saturday to trading above $1,800, at the time of writing.</p>
<p><em>-Featured image from Shutterstock, Chart from TradingView</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Bitcoin-1-460x333.jpg" width="460" height="333" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cardano Surpasses 500 Million ADA In TVL &#8211; How About Its Impact On Price?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/cardano/cardano-surpasses-500-million-ada-in-tvl-no-significant-impact-on-price/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Opeyemi Sule]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 12:40:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[ADA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=534160</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The total value locked (TVL) on the Cardano blockchain has hit a significant milestone after crossing 500 million ADA. This would come just a month and a few days after TapTools predicted an exponential increase in the network’s TVL. In this prediction, TapTools, a Cardano portfolio tracker, also reported different factors that could be pivotal to Cardano’s explosive growth in the coming months. Related Reading: Bitcoin ‘Shrimp’ Catch Soars To All-Time High Of 1.31 Million Coins – Details Cardano DeFi Ecosystem Hits 500 Million ADA In TVL Data from DeFi TVL aggregator DefiLlama reveals that the total value locked on the Cardano network now stands at 505.114 million ADA. This is equivalent to $186.18 million when converted to U.S. dollars. Source: DefiLlama This new milestone represents a staggering 91.9% increase in total value locked since the turn of the year. Meanwhile, in the last month, Cardano’s TVL has jumped by nearly 8%, indicating a steady adoption of its DeFi ecosystem. On-chain data shows that Minswap is, by a distance, the leading protocol on the network, with a TVL of $55.56 million. In fact, the decentralized exchange boasts a market share dominance of 29.84%. Minswap protocol is followed by Indigo, a collateralized debt protocol, with a total value of $28.5 million locked on it. WingRiders, Liqwid, and Djed Stablecoin are three other notable protocols on the Cardano DeFi ecosystem, with TVLs of $17.51 million, $15.42 million, and $13.71 million, respectively. It is important to note that total value locked is a metric that estimates the amount of cryptocurrency locked in DeFi protocols on a particular blockchain. It is calculated by summing up the value of all the crypto assets locked in various DeFi protocols on a blockchain. TVL can be represented in the native token of a blockchain (as in ADA for Cardano) or in USD. ADA Price Shows No Significant Action A skyrocketing total value locked is often an indicator of increased activity in a DeFi ecosystem. However, Cardano’s impressive TVL growth hasn&#8217;t particularly impacted the price of ADA, the blockchain’s native token. As of this writing, one ADA token trades at $0.3655, losing 1% of its value in the last 24 hours. The price of ADA has been moving sideways recently, dipping by only 0.5% in the last seven days. ADAUSD trading at $$0.3652 &#124; Source: ADAUSD chart from TradingView That said, a broader look at the market reveals that ADA has been on a steady decline, losing more than 13% of its value in the past month. The cryptocurrency boasts a daily trading volume of approximately $129.3 million.  According to data from CoinGecko, ADA ranks as the seventh-largest cryptocurrency, with a total market cap of $12.79 billion. Related Reading: Lido’s ETH Deposits Reach Record High Amid Stagnant stETH Withdrawals -Featured image from Solodev, chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The total value locked (TVL) on the Cardano blockchain has hit a significant milestone after crossing 500 million ADA. This would come just a month and a few days after <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/ada/cardanos-tvl-set-for-exponential-growth/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">TapTools predicted an exponential increase</a> in the network’s TVL.</p>
<p>In this prediction, TapTools, a Cardano portfolio tracker, also reported different factors that could be pivotal to Cardano’s explosive growth in the coming months.</p>

<h2>Cardano DeFi Ecosystem Hits 500 Million ADA In TVL</h2>
<p>Data from DeFi TVL aggregator<a href="https://defillama.com/chain/Cardano" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow"> DefiLlama</a> reveals that the total value locked on the Cardano network now stands at 505.114 million ADA. This is equivalent to $186.18 million when converted to U.S. dollars.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium wp-image-534173 aligncenter" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/photo_2023-05-20_11-29-09-460x227.jpg" alt="Cardano" width="460" height="227" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/photo_2023-05-20_11-29-09-460x227.jpg 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/photo_2023-05-20_11-29-09-860x424.jpg 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/photo_2023-05-20_11-29-09-768x378.jpg 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/photo_2023-05-20_11-29-09-750x370.jpg 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/photo_2023-05-20_11-29-09.jpg 1116w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px"/></p>
<p style="text-align: center">Source: DefiLlama</p>
<p>This new milestone represents a staggering 91.9% increase in total value locked since the turn of the year. Meanwhile, in the last month, Cardano’s TVL has jumped by nearly 8%, indicating a steady adoption of its DeFi ecosystem.</p>
<p>On-chain data shows that Minswap is, by a distance, the leading protocol on the network, with a TVL of $55.56 million. In fact, the decentralized exchange boasts a market share dominance of 29.84%.</p>
<p>Minswap protocol is followed by Indigo, a collateralized debt protocol, with a total value of $28.5 million locked on it. WingRiders, Liqwid, and Djed Stablecoin are three other notable protocols on the Cardano DeFi ecosystem, with TVLs of $17.51 million, $15.42 million, and $13.71 million, respectively.</p>
<p>It is important to note that total value locked is a metric that estimates the amount of cryptocurrency locked in DeFi protocols on a particular blockchain. It is calculated by summing up the value of all the crypto assets locked in various DeFi protocols on a blockchain. TVL can be represented in the native token of a blockchain (as in ADA for Cardano) or in USD.</p>
<h2>ADA Price Shows No Significant Action</h2>
<p>A skyrocketing total value locked is often an indicator of increased activity in a DeFi ecosystem. However, Cardano’s impressive TVL growth hasn&#8217;t particularly impacted the price of ADA, the blockchain’s native token.</p>
<p>As of this writing, one ADA token trades at $0.3655, losing 1% of its value in the last 24 hours. The price of ADA has been moving sideways recently, dipping by only 0.5% in the last seven days.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/K12HyuhT/" alt="Cardano" width="1008" height="591"/></p>

<p>That said, a broader look at the market reveals that ADA has been on a steady decline, losing more than 13% of its value in the past month. The cryptocurrency boasts a daily trading volume of approximately $129.3 million. </p>
<p>According to <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/cardano" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">data from CoinGecko</a>, ADA ranks as the seventh-largest cryptocurrency, with a total market cap of $12.79 billion.</p>




]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Cardano-1536x997-1-460x299.jpg" width="460" height="299" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Injective (INJ) Surges By 19% Following &#8216;Surprise&#8217; NFT Announcement</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/altcoin/injective-inj-surges-by-19-following-surprise-nft-initiative/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Semilore Faleti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 11:58:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[INJ]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Injective]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Santiment]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=534157</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Injective (INJ) is one of the few tokens to have racked up impressive gains in the last week. While most of the assets in the crypto market were marked by insignificant price actions leading to little gains or losses, INJ stood out with an excellent price movement to become one of the biggest weekly gainers.  According to data from CoinMarketCap, Injective’s price gained by 19% in the last seven days boasting of a market performance only beaten by four other tokens &#8211; RNDR, AGIX, MASK, and CFX &#8211; in the entire top 100 crypto ranking.  INJ initially began the week trading around a price region of $6.08 and soon recorded consecutive gains and losses before experiencing a price hike on May 17 to hit a market price of $6.7 Following this price boost, INJ showed signs of consolidation for the next two days before starting its current bullish run. Related Reading: Shiba Inu Falls Below Critical Support, Is It Time For You To Buy? NFT Surprise Announcement Boosts INJ Price  Interestingly, the price rally by INJ in the last week appears to be due to an exciting announcement made by the project developers six days ago. On May 13, the team behind the Injective blockchain tweeted a statement urging the user community to interact more with dApps built on Injective or its L1 chain, stating there could be a chance to receive an “NFT-related surprise.” This announcement sparked much excitement within the Injective community, which has been represented not just in price but also in the network activity.  According to a tweet by @Iryna_Everstake, blockchain manager at network validator service Everstake pool, the Injective blockchain recorded a substantial increase in several network parameters over the last week as follows &#8211; +688K INJ staked, +470 delegators, +130 new wallets, and +295M in cumulative trading volume.  At the time of writing, INJ is trading around $7.0, having gone up 4.73% in the last day. However, it is worth noting that INJ is down by 13.8% from its value as of a month ago. That said, with a circulating supply of 80 million tokens, INJ has a stunning market cap value of $563.7 million. INJ Trading At $7.098 &#124; Source: INJUSD chart on Tradingview.com Related Reading: NFT Market Takes A Hit: Sales Could Drop Below $1 Billion For The First Time In 2023 Altcoins End The Week With Massive Whale Movement Asides from INJ&#8217;s impressive performance this week, another talking point for most investors was the unexpected big altcoin transactions that capped off the work week. According to the on-chain analytics platform Santiment, some mid and low-market cap assets recorded whale activity to the tune of eight-figure transactions. Source: Santiment Of these many assets, MTL, POWR, AERGO, and DIAA recorded the biggest transactions, which were $37.89M, $30.74M, $30.23M, and $18.92M, respectively.  That said, Santiment stated that when small assets such as these record such high transactions, they could be up to something and thus are worth investors’ attention. -Featured Image: injective.com, chart from Tradingview.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Injective (INJ) is one of the few tokens to have racked up impressive gains in the last week. While most of the assets in the crypto market were marked by insignificant price actions leading to little gains or losses, INJ stood out with an excellent price movement to become one of the biggest weekly gainers. </p>
<p>According to <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/injective/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">data from CoinMarketCap</a>, Injective’s price gained by 19% in the last seven days boasting of a market performance only beaten by four other tokens &#8211; RNDR, AGIX, MASK, and CFX &#8211; in the entire top 100 crypto ranking. </p>
<p>INJ initially began the week trading around a price region of $6.08 and soon recorded consecutive gains and losses before experiencing a price hike on May 17 to hit a market price of $6.7</p>
<p>Following this price boost, INJ showed signs of consolidation for the next two days before starting its current bullish run.</p>


<h2><strong>NFT Surprise Announcement Boosts INJ Price </strong></h2>

<p>Interestingly, the price rally by INJ in the last week appears to be due to an exciting announcement made by the project developers six days ago.</p>
<p>On May 13, the team behind the Injective blockchain<a href="https://twitter.com/injective_/status/1657394070996615170?s=46&amp;t=JAUmthpFclo8jS4VJkm3DQ" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow"> tweeted</a> a statement urging the user community to interact more with dApps built on Injective or its L1 chain, stating there could be a chance to receive an “NFT-related surprise.”</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">It might be a good idea to interact with dApps built on Injective or the L1 chain itself.</p>
<p>Make a transfer, trade on a dex built on Injective, bridge assets, stake INJ, etc.</p>
<p>Who knows there might be an NFT related surprise in the works <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f609.png" alt="😉" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /></p>
<p>&mdash; Injective <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f977.png" alt="🥷" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> (@Injective_) <a href="https://twitter.com/Injective_/status/1657394070996615170?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">May 13, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p></p>
<p>This announcement sparked much excitement within the Injective community, which has been represented not just in price but also in the network activity. </p>
<p>According to a <a href="https://twitter.com/iryna_everstake/status/1659466585793331202?s=46&amp;t=JAUmthpFclo8jS4VJkm3DQ" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">tweet</a> by @Iryna_Everstake, blockchain manager at network validator service Everstake pool, the Injective blockchain recorded a substantial increase in several network parameters over the last week as follows &#8211; +688K INJ staked, +470 delegators, +130 new wallets, and +295M in cumulative trading volume. </p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">The Injective community seems to be following the advice to interact w/ dApps or the chain itself to get ready for an upcoming NFT-related surprise<a href="https://twitter.com/Injective_?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">@Injective_</a> stats over the last 5 days: +688K <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24INJ&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$INJ</a> staked, +470 delegators, +130 new wallets, +295M in cumulative trading volume <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f977.png" alt="🥷" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> <a href="https://t.co/N9z9aWw5aQ" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/N9z9aWw5aQ</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Iryna | Everstake <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f977.png" alt="🥷" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> (@iryna_everstake) <a href="https://twitter.com/iryna_everstake/status/1659466585793331202?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">May 19, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p></p>
<p>At the time of writing, INJ is trading around $7.0, having gone up 4.73% in the last day. However, it is worth noting that INJ is down by 13.8% from its value as of a month ago. That said, with a circulating supply of 80 million tokens, INJ has a stunning market cap value of $563.7 million.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/Wmr9Kl4L/" alt="Injective" width="1479" height="913"/></p>




<h2><strong>Altcoins End The Week With Massive Whale Movement</strong></h2>
<p>Asides from INJ&#8217;s impressive performance this week, another talking point for most investors was the unexpected big altcoin transactions that capped off the work week. According to the on-chain analytics platform <a href="https://twitter.com/santimentfeed/status/1659746600888188928?s=46&amp;t=JAUmthpFclo8jS4VJkm3DQ" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Santiment</a>, some mid and low-market cap assets recorded whale activity to the tune of eight-figure transactions.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-large wp-image-534161" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/FwiZsWjagAEKLU1-860x390.jpeg" alt="Injective" width="860" height="390" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/FwiZsWjagAEKLU1-860x390.jpeg 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/FwiZsWjagAEKLU1-460x209.jpeg 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/FwiZsWjagAEKLU1-768x348.jpeg 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/FwiZsWjagAEKLU1-1536x696.jpeg 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/FwiZsWjagAEKLU1-2048x929.jpeg 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/FwiZsWjagAEKLU1-750x340.jpeg 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/FwiZsWjagAEKLU1-1140x517.jpeg 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/></p>

<p>Of these many assets, MTL, POWR, AERGO, and DIAA recorded the biggest transactions, which were $37.89M, $30.74M, $30.23M, and $18.92M, respectively.  That said, Santiment stated that when small assets such as these record such high transactions, they could be up to something and thus are worth investors’ attention.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/og-new-460x242.jpeg" width="460" height="242" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>XRP Emerges As Top Performing Crypto With 55% Surge &#8211; Messari Report</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/xrp-emerges-as-top-performing-crypto-with-55-surge-messari-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Eli Dambel]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 11:50:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[messari]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrpusdt]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=534177</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Amid the prevailing bearish trend in the crypto market, XRP has stayed afloat above other assets with impressive gains. A report from a leading crypto market intelligence product provider, Messari, revealed the Ripple native currency XRP took the lead in the overall crypto market in Q1. XRP Takes The Lead In Overall Crypto Market According to data from Messari, XRP outperformed other crypto assets with a 55% surge on a quarter-on-quarter (QoQ) basis.  From the report, the market cap of XRP grew by a whopping 59.9% in the first quarter of the year. The value increased from $17.4 billion on January 1 to $27.4 billion on March 31. Related Reading: Crypto Assets Flow From Ethereum To BSC, Are Users Escaping High Gas Fees? Notably, the growth rate for XRP’s market cap exceeded the cumulative crypto market cap that witnessed a 46% surge within the same period.  Messari&#8217;s report also showed that XRP kicked off the year with a trading price of $0.35 as of January 1. With the increasing volatility in the crypto market during the beginning of 2023, XRP rallied progressively through the days. As of January 23, XRP&#8217;s price hit $0.43 before retracting due to the influence of the bears. The token closed in January with a 19.71% increase in value. The second month wasn’t quite eventful for XRP as the price gradually dipped to $0.36 amid the downtrend in the overall crypto market. However, XRP ended February with a 7.27% drop as the price hit $0.37. Then XRP’s price rally took a more aggressive look in March. The price of XRP ranged from the beginning of March. But it gained momentum from March 21 as XRP broke the resistance level at $0.400. XRP sustained its volatility and pushed higher with a more bullish stance through the remaining days in March. The token rallied beyond the $0.500 region and progressed higher. Messari noted that XRP hit a 10-month high of $0.5850 on March 29, following a two-week price surge of 56%. This price rally was peculiar to XRP, although most crypto assets posted a decline during the period.  Finally, XRP closed with a price of $0.54 on March 31, a 43% price surge for the month. The feat pushed the token to an overall price gain of 55% in Q1 2023. XRP Performance Analysis In Q1 2023 Besides the XRP’s price performance, the Messari report also highlighted other performance indicators for the token. The data shows an increase in XRP&#8217;s overall network activity metrics in Q1. The total active addresses and average daily transactions surged by 13.9% and 10.7%, respectively, on a QoQ basis. Related Reading: Ethereum Price Faces Confluence Of Bearish Factors and At Risk of Another Decline The total active addresses grew from the receiving addresses, which increased from 47,000 to 55,000 through a 17.1% surge. But XRP sending addresses dropped by 7.2%. -Featured image from Pixabay and chart from Tradingview.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Amid the prevailing bearish trend in the crypto market, XRP has stayed afloat above other assets with impressive gains. A report from a leading crypto market intelligence product provider, Messari, revealed the Ripple native currency XRP took the lead in the overall crypto market in Q1.</p>
<h2>XRP Takes The Lead In Overall Crypto Market</h2>
<p>According to <a href="https://messari.io/report/state-of-xrp-ledger-q1-2023" rel="nofollow">data from Messari</a>, XRP outperformed other crypto assets with a 55% surge on a quarter-on-quarter (QoQ) basis. </p>
<p>From the report, the market cap of XRP grew by a whopping 59.9% in the first quarter of the year. The value increased from $17.4 billion on January 1 to $27.4 billion on March 31.</p>

<p>Notably, the growth rate for XRP’s market cap exceeded the cumulative crypto market cap that witnessed a 46% surge within the same period. </p>
<p>Messari&#8217;s report also showed that XRP kicked off the year with a trading price of $0.35 as of January 1. With the increasing volatility in the crypto market during the beginning of 2023, XRP rallied progressively through the days. As of January 23, XRP&#8217;s price hit $0.43 before retracting due to the influence of the bears. The token closed in January with a 19.71% increase in value.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-534180 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSDT_2023-05-20_15-55-24-860x471.png" alt="XRP Emerges Top Performing Crypto With A 55% Surge QoQ, Messari Report" width="860" height="471" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSDT_2023-05-20_15-55-24-860x471.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSDT_2023-05-20_15-55-24-460x252.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSDT_2023-05-20_15-55-24-768x420.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSDT_2023-05-20_15-55-24-750x411.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSDT_2023-05-20_15-55-24-1140x624.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSDT_2023-05-20_15-55-24.png 1529w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/>
<p>The second month wasn’t quite eventful for XRP as the price gradually dipped to $0.36 amid the downtrend in the overall crypto market. However, XRP ended February with a 7.27% drop as the price hit $0.37.</p>
<p>Then XRP’s price rally took a more aggressive look in March. The price of XRP ranged from the beginning of March. But it gained momentum from March 21 as XRP broke the resistance level at $0.400.</p>
<p>XRP sustained its volatility and pushed higher with a more bullish stance through the remaining days in March. The token rallied beyond the $0.500 region and progressed higher.</p>
<p>Messari noted that XRP hit a 10-month high of $0.5850 on March 29, following a two-week price surge of 56%. This price rally was peculiar to XRP, although most crypto assets posted a decline during the period. </p>
<p>Finally, XRP closed with a price of $0.54 on March 31, a 43% price surge for the month. The feat pushed the token to an overall price gain of 55% in Q1 2023.</p>
<h2>XRP Performance Analysis In Q1 2023</h2>
<p>Besides the XRP’s price performance, the Messari report also highlighted other performance indicators for the token.</p>
<p>The data shows an increase in XRP&#8217;s overall network activity metrics in Q1. The total active addresses and average daily transactions surged by 13.9% and 10.7%, respectively, on a QoQ basis.</p>

<p>The total active addresses grew from the receiving addresses, which increased from 47,000 to 55,000 through a 17.1% surge. But XRP sending addresses dropped by 7.2%.</p>
<p><em>-Featured image from Pixabay and chart from Tradingview.com</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/coin-g7ab8cd001_1280-460x305.jpg" width="460" height="305" />	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
