<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"

	xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
	xmlns:geo="http://www.w3.org/2003/01/geo/wgs84_pos#"
	>

<channel>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.newsbtc.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<description>Bitcoin &#38; Cryptocurrency News Today</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 15:08:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-cropped-favicon.png?fit=32%2C32</url>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
<site xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">221170450</site>	<item>
		<title>This Event Causes Bitcoin Traders&#8217; Sentiment To Rise, Will BTC Surpass $30,000?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/this-event-causes-bitcoin-traders-sentiment-to-rise-will-btc-surpass-30000/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reynaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 18:00:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=547367</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Bitcoin price continues to compress around its current levels, but during today’s trading session, there was an uptick in volatility. The rise in this metric could hint at a shift in the narratives influencing BTC’s price action. Related Reading: Bitcoin Prediction: Crypto Analyst Forecasts New ATH by 2024 – Can It Happen? As of this writing, Bitcoin trades at $29,300 with sideways movement in the last 24 hours. In the previous seven days, the cryptocurrency saw similar action pushing other assets in a similar direction or no direction as the sector flatlines in the short term. Bitcoin ETF Becomes Dominant Narrative In Crypto Market? In a recent market update, crypto analysis firm Blofin pointed to an uptick in market sentiment. Coupled with a rise in volatility, market participants are reacting to the potential announcement from the US Securities Exchange Commission (SEC) around a spot Bitcoin ETF. The Commission is set to rule on asset manager Grayscale’s petition to transform their Grayscale Bitcoin Trust (GBTC) into an ETF. The decision was supposed to come out today, Blofin stated, but it could drag on until this Friday, August 18th. If the SEC postpones the decision for any reason, as it did with Ark’s petition, the market will likely keep moving sideways. In that sense, development around the ETF decision is gaining strength over macroeconomic dynamics. This change in dynamics is more evident in the derivatives sector, with options traders becoming more bullish for the coming months. Blofin noted the following on this dynamic: (…) The news above (on the Bitcoin ETF approval) has promoted the rapid rise of short-term bullish sentiment and uncertainty in the market (…). It appears that investors are waiting for good news related to the spot Bitcoin ETF. And “smart” traders are positioning accordingly. The report notes that the open interest for options contracts is skewed to the call (buy) side. Related Reading: XRP Price at Potentially Significant Turning Point, Key Support Nearby As data from the derivatives platform Deribit shows, traders are betting that the price of Bitcoin will rise above $30,000 by the end of August or September. As seen on the chart below, 57,000 contracts will expire by the end of this month and 90,700 next month. Coupled with the rise in Open Interest skewed to the call side, the chart above shows that traders are betting on a Bitcoin rally above $30,000 to $40,000. The spot BTC ETF decision will move the market, particularly at the end of August and September. Cover image from Unsplash, chart from Tradingview]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>The Bitcoin price continues to compress around its current levels, but during today’s trading session, there was an uptick in volatility. The rise in this metric could hint at a shift in the narratives influencing BTC’s price action. </strong></p>

<p>As of this writing, Bitcoin trades at $29,300 with sideways movement in the last 24 hours. In the previous seven days, the cryptocurrency saw similar action pushing other assets in a similar direction or no direction as the sector flatlines in the short term.</p>
<img decoding="async" fetchpriority="high" class="wp-image-547380 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-price-BTC-BTCUSDT-1.png?w=860&#038;resize=860%2C410" alt="Bitcoin price BTC BTCUSDT" width="860" height="410" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-price-BTC-BTCUSDT-1.png?w=1758 1758w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-price-BTC-BTCUSDT-1.png?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-price-BTC-BTCUSDT-1.png?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-price-BTC-BTCUSDT-1.png?w=860&#038;resize=860%2C410 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-price-BTC-BTCUSDT-1.png?w=1536 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-price-BTC-BTCUSDT-1.png?w=750 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-price-BTC-BTCUSDT-1.png?w=1140 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" loading="lazy" data-recalc-dims="1"/>
<h2>Bitcoin ETF Becomes Dominant Narrative In Crypto Market?</h2>
<p>In a recent market update, crypto analysis firm Blofin pointed to an uptick in market sentiment. Coupled with a rise in volatility, market participants are reacting to the potential announcement from the US Securities Exchange Commission (SEC) around a spot Bitcoin ETF.</p>
<p>The Commission is set to rule on asset manager Grayscale’s petition to transform their Grayscale Bitcoin Trust (GBTC) into an ETF. The decision was supposed to come out today, Blofin stated, but it could drag on until this Friday, August 18th.</p>
<p>If the SEC postpones the decision for any reason, as it did with Ark’s petition, the market will likely keep moving sideways. In that sense, development around the ETF decision is gaining strength over macroeconomic dynamics.</p>
<p>This change in dynamics is more evident in the derivatives sector, with options traders becoming more bullish for the coming months. Blofin noted the following on this dynamic:</p>
<blockquote><p>(…) The news above (on the Bitcoin ETF approval) has promoted the rapid rise of short-term bullish sentiment and uncertainty in the market (…). It appears that investors are waiting for good news related to the spot Bitcoin ETF.</p></blockquote>
<p>And “smart” traders are positioning accordingly. The report notes that the open interest for options contracts is skewed to the call (buy) side.</p>

<p>As data from the derivatives platform Deribit shows, traders are betting that the price of Bitcoin will rise above $30,000 by the end of August or September. As seen on the chart below, 57,000 contracts will expire by the end of this month and 90,700 next month.</p>
<img decoding="async" class="wp-image-547379 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-price-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-OI.jpg?w=860&#038;resize=860%2C227" alt="Bitcoin price BTC BTCUSDT Chart OI" width="860" height="227" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-price-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-OI.jpg?w=1534 1534w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-price-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-OI.jpg?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-price-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-OI.jpg?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-price-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-OI.jpg?w=860&#038;resize=860%2C227 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-price-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-OI.jpg?w=750 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-price-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-OI.jpg?w=1140 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" loading="lazy" data-recalc-dims="1"/>
<p>Coupled with the rise in Open Interest skewed to the call side, the chart above shows that traders are betting on a Bitcoin rally above $30,000 to $40,000. The spot BTC ETF decision will move the market, particularly at the end of August and September.</p>
<p>Cover image from Unsplash, chart from Tradingview</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-Price-BTC-BTCUSDT-4.jpg?fit=460%2C307" width="460" height="307" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">547367</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Subtle Signs A Bullish Bitcoin Trend Is Brewing</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/the-subtle-signs-a-bullish-bitcoin-trend-is-brewing/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tony "The Bull"]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 17:05:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xbt]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xbtusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=547389</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin price remains stagnant for going on months now, with no clear trend developing and volatility in a downward spiral. However, some subtle signs are popping up that could suggest that a bullish Bitcoin trend is beginning to take shape. Make Friends With Strong Trends “The trend is your friend” is one of the most famous trading quotes, highlighting how capturing as much of the prevailing trend as possible can lead to the most profitable results. For this reason, in technical analysis, trend-following tools are among the most successful. But what is an investor or trader to do when there is a clear absence of any discernible trend? The answer is “to wait for the trend to appear” but that’s easier said than done. This is why specific tools have been created to tell when assets like Bitcoin or even stocks are trending or not. One such tool is starting to rise after several weeks of sideways price action, and it suggest that the underlying trend is strengthening. The Average Directional Index &#124; BTCUSD on TradingView.com Bullish Bitcoin Is Building Muscle The Average Directional Index (ADX) is a trend strength measuring tool, created by the father of technical indicators, J. Welles, Wilder, Jr. Other tools Wilder built include the Parabolic SAR, Average True Range, and the Relative Strength Index. A reading above 20 on the ADX means a trend is developing. The more it turns up, the stronger the trend. After weeks of sideways, the trend is starting to strengthen again. The tool also includes two Directional Movement indicators, the DI+ and DI-. The DI+ is currently above the DI-, showing that bulls in control of the underlying price action. All that’s left is for the ADX to strengthen further and Bitcoin could finally break out of this range and begin trending. What Bitcoin bulls ultimately want to see next is for the ADX to grow even steeper, similar to what we can see in late 2020 and into early 2022. The lack of another strong trend at the second 2021 peak was a warning that something was off. Will the bullish trend continue to strengthen, or will bears regain control? #Bitcoin 1W Average Directional Index is turning back up above 20 — this is the signature of a strengthening trend DI+ is above DI- which shows bulls are in control Trend-following tools may soon prove more useful with a trend growing pic.twitter.com/9nAUEVIcL3 &#8212; Tony &#34;The Bull&#34; (@tonythebullBTC) August 14, 2023 Tony is the author of the CoinChartist (VIP) newsletter. Sign up for free. Follow @TonyTheBullBTC &#38; @coinchartist_io on Twitter. Or join the TonyTradesBTC Telegram for daily market insights and technical analysis education. Please note: Content is educational and should not be considered investment advice. Featured image from iStockPhoto, Charts from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin price remains stagnant for going on months now, with no clear trend developing and volatility in a downward spiral. However, some subtle signs are popping up that could suggest that a bullish Bitcoin trend is beginning to take shape.</p>
<h2>Make Friends With Strong Trends</h2>
<p>“The trend is your friend” is one of the most famous trading quotes, highlighting how capturing as much of the prevailing trend as possible can lead to the most profitable results.</p>
<p>For this reason, in technical analysis, trend-following tools are among the most successful. But what is an investor or trader to do when there is a clear absence of any discernible trend?</p>
<p>The answer is “to wait for the trend to appear” but that’s easier said than done. This is why specific tools have been created to tell when assets like Bitcoin or even stocks are trending or not. One such tool is starting to rise after several weeks of sideways price action, and it suggest that the underlying trend is strengthening.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" class="size-large wp-image-547390 aligncenter" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F3gWev9X0AYtIfg.jpeg?w=860&#038;resize=860%2C535" alt="bitcoin adx" width="860" height="535" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F3gWev9X0AYtIfg.jpeg?w=2048 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F3gWev9X0AYtIfg.jpeg?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F3gWev9X0AYtIfg.jpeg?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F3gWev9X0AYtIfg.jpeg?w=860&#038;resize=860%2C535 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F3gWev9X0AYtIfg.jpeg?w=1536 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F3gWev9X0AYtIfg.jpeg?w=750 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F3gWev9X0AYtIfg.jpeg?w=1140 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" loading="lazy" data-recalc-dims="1"/></p>

<h2>Bullish Bitcoin Is Building Muscle</h2>
<p>The Average Directional Index (ADX) is a trend strength measuring tool, created by the father of technical indicators, J. Welles, Wilder, Jr. Other tools Wilder built include the Parabolic SAR, Average True Range, and the Relative Strength Index.</p>
<p>A reading above 20 on the ADX means a trend is developing. The more it turns up, the stronger the trend. After weeks of sideways, the trend is starting to strengthen again.</p>
<p>The tool also includes two Directional Movement indicators, the DI+ and DI-. The DI+ is currently above the DI-, showing that bulls in control of the underlying price action. All that’s left is for the ADX to strengthen further and Bitcoin could finally break out of this range and begin trending.</p>
<p>What Bitcoin bulls ultimately want to see next is for the ADX to grow even steeper, similar to what we can see in late 2020 and into early 2022. The lack of another strong trend at the second 2021 peak was a warning that something was off. Will the bullish trend continue to strengthen, or will bears regain control?</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr"><a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Bitcoin?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#Bitcoin</a> 1W Average Directional Index is turning back up above 20 — this is the signature of a strengthening trend</p>
<p>DI+ is above DI- which shows bulls are in control</p>
<p>Trend-following tools may soon prove more useful with a trend growing <a href="https://t.co/9nAUEVIcL3" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/9nAUEVIcL3</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Tony &quot;The Bull&quot; (@tonythebullBTC) <a href="https://twitter.com/tonythebullBTC/status/1691126381005135872?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">August 14, 2023</a></p></blockquote>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/istock-teagkhdgkd.jpeg?fit=460%2C230" width="460" height="230" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">547389</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Chiliz (CHZ) Empowers Smart Contracts With Upgrades &#8211; Positive Impact On Price?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/chiliz-chz-empowers-smart-contracts-with-upgrades-positive-impact-on-price/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 17:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[chiliZ]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CHZ Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price action]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=547328</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Chiliz, the pioneering sports blockchain platform, is set to make waves once again as it teases forthcoming upgrades to its smart contracts. In a recent tweet, Chiliz unveiled its plans to enhance the functionality of its smart contracts, showcasing the company&#8217;s ongoing commitment to providing a seamless and efficient experience for its users.  Chiliz has been a trailblazer in the sports and entertainment industry, utilizing blockchain technology to bridge the gap between sports fans and their favorite teams. Related Reading: Dogecoin Vs. Bitcoin: Co-Founder Labels BTC Maximalists As ‘Insecure Losers’ The platform&#8217;s innovative approach allows fans to engage with their chosen teams through fan tokens, gaining access to exclusive content, rewards, and even influencing certain team decisions through token-based voting systems.  🗳️ Upcoming Proposals: Upgrading the Smart contracts Upgrade 1: Upgrading the contracts to allow factory contracts to deploy without being whitelisted as deployers. The factory contract will still need to be deployed by a whitelisted deployer.#ChilizGovernance ⚡ $CHZ pic.twitter.com/zyBTqzAhTJ — Chiliz ($CHZ) &#8211; Powering Socios.com ⚡ (@Chiliz) August 14, 2023 As the platform gears up for these improvements, the question on everyone&#8217;s mind is whether these upgrades will play a role in boosting the price of CHZ, Chiliz&#8217;s native cryptocurrency. Chiliz Upgrades On The Horizon The first of the upcoming upgrades focuses on streamlining the deployment of factory contracts. In a bid to improve efficiency, Chiliz plans to enable such contracts to be deployed without the need for whitelisting as deployers.  This move is expected to simplify the process while maintaining a level of security by ensuring that the factory contract is still initiated by a whitelisted deployer. By reducing friction in the contract deployment process, Chiliz aims to enhance user experience and attract a wider range of participants. The second upgrade revolves around staking pool contract enhancements. Chiliz aims to address issues related to the accuracy of voting power displayed for validators and the calculation of delegated amounts.  Chiliz is currently trading at $0.0748. Chart by TradingView.com To rectify this, the Chiliz team has indicated that a temporary downtime for the delegated and undelegated features will be necessary during the upgrade. While this may temporarily inconvenience users, the improvements are anticipated to provide a more accurate and transparent staking experience. Impact On CHZ Price As Chiliz enthusiasts eagerly await these upgrades, the impact on the price of CHZ remains a topic of interest. At the time of writing, CHZ is in the red in all timeframes, and priced at $0.074903 according to CoinGecko. The past 24 hours have seen a decline of 1.2% in its value, while the past seven days have witnessed a decline of 1.5%. These fluctuations underscore the inherent volatility of the cryptocurrency market. CHZ price action today. Source: Coingecko Related Reading: FDIC Warns Of Crypto’s Legal And Fraud Risks For US Banks – Here’s Why While the direct correlation between upgrades and price movements can be complex and multifaceted, the anticipated improvements in Chiliz&#8217;s smart contracts could bolster investor confidence in the platform&#8217;s future prospects.  (This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk). Featured image from Dr Trouble Hot Sauce]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Chiliz, the pioneering sports blockchain platform, is set to make waves once again as it teases forthcoming upgrades to its smart contracts. </p>
<p>In a recent tweet, Chiliz unveiled its plans to enhance the functionality of its smart contracts, showcasing the company&#8217;s ongoing commitment to providing a seamless and efficient experience for its users. </p>
<p>Chiliz has been a trailblazer in the sports and entertainment industry, utilizing blockchain technology to bridge the gap between sports fans and their favorite teams. </p>

<p>The platform&#8217;s innovative approach allows fans to engage with their chosen teams through fan tokens, gaining access to exclusive content, rewards, and even influencing certain team decisions through token-based voting systems. </p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en"><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f5f3.png" alt="🗳" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> Upcoming Proposals: Upgrading the Smart contracts</p>
<p>Upgrade 1: Upgrading the contracts to allow factory contracts to deploy without being whitelisted as deployers. The factory contract will still need to be deployed by a whitelisted deployer.<a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/ChilizGovernance?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#ChilizGovernance</a> <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/26a1.png" alt="⚡" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24CHZ&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$CHZ</a> <a href="https://t.co/zyBTqzAhTJ" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/zyBTqzAhTJ</a></p>
<p>— Chiliz ($CHZ) &#8211; Powering Socios.com <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/26a1.png" alt="⚡" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> (@Chiliz) <a href="https://twitter.com/Chiliz/status/1691037068963590146?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">August 14, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p>As the platform gears up for these improvements, the question on everyone&#8217;s mind is whether these upgrades will play a role in boosting <a href="https://u.today/chiliz-chz-unveils-game-changing-upgrades-for-smart-contracts" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">the price of CHZ</a>, Chiliz&#8217;s native cryptocurrency.</p>
<h2><strong>Chiliz Upgrades On The Horizon</strong></h2>
<p>The first of the <a href="https://twitter.com/Chiliz/status/1691037068963590146" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">upcoming upgrades</a> focuses on streamlining the deployment of factory contracts. In a bid to improve efficiency, Chiliz plans to enable such contracts to be deployed without the need for whitelisting as deployers. </p>
<p>This move is expected to simplify the process while maintaining a level of security by ensuring that the factory contract is still initiated by a whitelisted deployer. By reducing friction in the contract deployment process, Chiliz aims to enhance user experience and attract a wider range of participants.</p>
<p>The second upgrade revolves around staking pool contract enhancements. Chiliz aims to address issues related to the accuracy of voting power displayed for validators and the calculation of delegated amounts. </p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/IPJnrKlj/" width="1835" height="893"/></p>

<p>To rectify this, the Chiliz team has indicated that a temporary downtime for the delegated and undelegated features will be necessary during the upgrade. While this may temporarily inconvenience users, the improvements are anticipated to provide a more accurate and transparent staking experience.</p>
<h2><strong>Impact On CHZ Price</strong></h2>
<p>As Chiliz enthusiasts eagerly await these upgrades, the impact on the price of CHZ remains a topic of interest. At the time of writing, CHZ is in the red in all timeframes, and priced at $0.074903 according to <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/chiliz" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">CoinGecko</a>. </p>
<p>The past 24 hours have seen a decline of 1.2% in its value, while the past seven days have witnessed a decline of 1.5%. These fluctuations underscore the inherent volatility of the cryptocurrency market.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-547363" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-85.png?resize=1024%2C53" alt="" width="1024" height="53" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-85.png?resize=1024%2C53?w=1137 1137w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-85.png?resize=1024%2C53?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-85.png?resize=1024%2C53?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-85.png?resize=1024%2C53?w=860 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-85.png?resize=1024%2C53?w=750 750w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" data-recalc-dims="1"/></p>


<p>While the direct correlation between upgrades and price movements can be complex and multifaceted, the anticipated improvements in Chiliz&#8217;s smart contracts could bolster investor confidence in the platform&#8217;s future prospects. </p>
<p><em>(This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk).</em></p>
<p><em>Featured image from Dr Trouble Hot Sauce</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-84.png?fit=460%2C310" width="460" height="310" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">547328</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>DeFiance Capital Gains Upper Hand In Jurisdiction Battle Against 3AC: Singapore Courts To Preside</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/crypto/defiance-capital-gains-upper-hand-jurisdiction-against-3ac/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samuel Edyme]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 16:00:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3AC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DeFiance Capital]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[law]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[singapore]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=547334</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The crypto finance world has witnessed numerous disputes, but few have been similar to that of the ongoing feud between DeFiance Capital and Three Arrows Capital Limited (3AC). Particularly, this dispute underscores the intricate interplay between traditional financial frameworks and the evolving dynamics of digital assets. In a tweet posted earlier today, DeFiance Capital CEO shed new light on their ongoing legal tussle with 3AC, suggesting a turn in the tide. Statement and Update on Dispute with Three Arrows Capital Limited (3AC) We are very pleased to share a positive development on our end with the public. It is well-known that for the past year, we have been locked in a dispute with the 3AC estate who are claiming that the assets… — Arthur (@Arthur_0x) August 15, 2023 DeFiance Capital: A Year-long Struggle Almost a year ago, the disagreement between DeFiance Capital and the 3AC estate took center stage when the estate contended that the assets held by DeFiance Capital should be used to square off the debts of 3AC. Related Reading: 3AC NFTs Sale To Commence Soon Due to Liquidation Countering this claim, DeFiance maintained that they had complete authority and rightful ownership of their assets. This stance, they assert, aligns with common industry perceptions and is supported by available evidence. The debate took a geographical turn when the liquidators insisted on settling the dispute in the British Virgin Islands (BVI). DeFiance Capital, which was managed from Singapore alongside 3AC, found this choice of jurisdiction puzzling. They argued that the primary evidence and witnesses were based in Singapore, making it a more apt location for the hearing. Their persistence bore fruit last week when the High Court of Singapore agreed to their jurisdiction preference, subtly undermining the liquidators&#8217; earlier narrative that DeFiance&#8217;s stance held no ground. The Road Ahead: Seeking Effective Resolutions Despite these disagreements, DeFiance has shown a willingness to collaborate. They have extended assistance to 3AC&#8217;s liquidators in understanding the position of DeFiance and even offered help in identifying 3AC&#8217;s assets. The intention, as expressed by the CEO &#38; CIO of DeFiance, was to minimize the resources spent on deciding the hearing location and instead concentrate on the core issues at hand. However, the journey hasn&#8217;t been without its hitches. The liquidators faced setbacks in the US while trying to hold Three Arrows Capital Co-Founder  Kyle Davies accountable in a US court. This effort was thwarted when it came to light that Davies was no longer a US citizen, an information oversight that resulted in unnecessary legal expenses. Blossom Hing, representing DeFiance, highlighted the significance of the recent jurisdiction decision. Emphasizing that the Singapore International Commercial Court could address issues pertaining to BVI law, she expressed optimism about an efficient resolution that benefits all parties. Related Reading: Crypto Hedge Fund 3 Arrows Capital (3AC) Files For Bankruptcy Hing noted: We welcome the decision by the Singapore Court as it will ensure that important evidence located in Singapore would be available for the purposes of resolving the dispute in a just and efficient manner. Coupled with the fact that the Singapore International Commercial Court can hear arguments on and decide on BVI law issues, we believe that having the dispute heard in Singapore will result in considerable savings of costs and time for all parties. Featured image from Unsplash, Chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The crypto finance world has witnessed numerous disputes, but few have been similar to that of the ongoing feud between DeFiance Capital and <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/crypto-hedge-fund-3-arrows-capital-3ac-files-for-bankruptcy/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Three Arrows Capital Limited (3AC)</a>. Particularly, this dispute underscores the intricate interplay between traditional financial frameworks and the evolving dynamics of digital assets.</p>
<p>In a tweet posted earlier today, DeFiance Capital CEO shed new light on their ongoing legal tussle with 3AC, suggesting a turn in the tide.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Statement and Update on Dispute with Three Arrows Capital Limited (3AC)</p>
<p>We are very pleased to share a positive development on our end with the public.</p>
<p>It is well-known that for the past year, we have been locked in a dispute with the 3AC estate who are claiming that the assets…</p>
<p>— Arthur (@Arthur_0x) <a href="https://twitter.com/Arthur_0x/status/1691400992645087232?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">August 15, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<h2>DeFiance Capital: A Year-long Struggle</h2>
<p>Almost a year ago, the disagreement between DeFiance Capital and the 3AC estate took center stage when the estate contended that the assets held by DeFiance Capital should be used to square off the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/nft/3ac-nfts-sale-to-commence-soon-due-to-liquidation/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">debts of 3AC</a>.</p>

<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w g0rxnol2" dir="ltr">Countering this claim, DeFiance maintained that they had complete authority and rightful ownership of their assets. This stance, they assert, aligns with common industry perceptions and is supported by available evidence.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The debate took a geographical turn when the liquidators insisted on settling the dispute in the British Virgin Islands (BVI). DeFiance Capital, which was managed from Singapore alongside 3AC, found this choice of jurisdiction puzzling. </p>
<p dir="ltr">They argued that the primary evidence and witnesses were <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/crypto/singapore-red-cross-to-accept-crypto/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">based in Singapore</a>, making it a more apt location for the hearing. Their persistence bore fruit last week when the High Court of Singapore agreed to their jurisdiction preference, subtly undermining the liquidators&#8217; earlier narrative that DeFiance&#8217;s stance held no ground.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">The Road Ahead: Seeking Effective Resolutions</h2>
<p>Despite these disagreements, DeFiance has shown a willingness to collaborate. They have extended assistance to 3AC&#8217;s liquidators in understanding the position of DeFiance and even offered help in identifying 3AC&#8217;s assets.</p>
<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w g0rxnol2" dir="ltr">The intention, as expressed by the CEO &amp; CIO of DeFiance, was to minimize the resources spent on deciding the hearing location and instead concentrate on the core issues at hand.</p>
<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w g0rxnol2" dir="ltr">However, the journey hasn&#8217;t been without its hitches. The liquidators faced setbacks in the US while trying to hold Three Arrows Capital Co-Founder  Kyle Davies accountable in a US court. This effort was thwarted when it came to light that Davies was no longer a US citizen, an <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/crypto/judge-declares-crypto-is-personal-property/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">information oversight</a> that resulted in unnecessary legal expenses.</p>
<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w g0rxnol2" dir="ltr">Blossom Hing, representing DeFiance, highlighted the significance of the recent jurisdiction decision. Emphasizing that the Singapore International Commercial Court could address issues pertaining to BVI law, she expressed optimism about an efficient resolution that benefits all parties.</p>

<p dir="ltr">Hing noted:</p>
<blockquote>
<p dir="ltr">We welcome the decision by the Singapore Court as it will ensure that important evidence located in Singapore would be available for the purposes of resolving the dispute in a just and efficient manner. Coupled with the fact that the Singapore International Commercial Court can hear arguments on and decide on BVI law issues, we believe that having the dispute heard in Singapore will result in considerable savings of costs and time for all parties.</p>
</blockquote>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/ufLoPCNB/" alt="The global crypto market cap value on TradingView" width="2770" height="1408"/>
<p dir="ltr">Featured image from Unsplash, Chart from TradingView</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/DeFiance-Capital-Gains-Upper-Hand-In-Jurisdiction-Battle-Against-3AC.jpg?fit=460%2C307" width="460" height="307" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">547334</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>PEPE Shines With 20% Gains As Market Sees Correction, What&#8217;s Next?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/pepe/pepe-shines-with-20-gains-as-market-sees-correction-whats-next/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Kent Glory]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 15:00:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[PEPE]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PEPE analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PEPE price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PEPE Rally]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[pepeusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=547333</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[PEPE surged remarkably in the past week posting gains of approximately 20%. The $0.0000011079 support level on the daily chart acted as a price pivot for the gains in the last few days, indicating an attempt to enter the buy zone.  PEPE&#8217;s previous attempts to break above the $0.0000015440 resistance zone between July 19-24 were unsuccessful. However, the bulls are in control, driving PEPE to attempt another break above the $0.0000015440 resistance.  Related Reading: US Prosecutors Accuse FTX’s Sam Bankman-Fried Of Using $100M To Curry Political Favors The rally in the past 7-days indicates a momentum shift for PEPE to a more positive outlook as the bulls attempt to seize control again.  PEPE Bulls Forcing Another Rally, But Bears Still Active Price volatility is evident when comparing price data for PEPE on the daily, weekly, and monthly timeframes. It trades at $0.000001348 on August 15 with a 6.03% price drop in 24 hours, while it has dropped 17% on the monthly time frame.   However, PEPE shows a more positive outlook on the weekly timeframe, although traders must tread cautiously as a price drop remains a possibility due to volatility.  The Relative Strength Index (RSI) value is 55.71 in the neutral zone reflecting traders&#8217; indecision in the market. Also, the Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD) is rising above the signal line, confirming the return of the bulls.  However, the size of the candles indicates low trading activity despite the gains making the price action moving forward quite tricky. The close of the August 15 candle will bring confirmation of the next price direction.  PEPE Shows Resilient Above $0.00000120 As Whale Comes Onboard In recent days, there has been a resurgence in PEPE&#8217;s performance. This trend is attributable to substantial investments from prominent investors and a rise in social engagement. According to Lookonchain data, there is a significant surge in whale attention to the PEPE token. The data shows a whale spent $ 1 million to acquire 807 billion PEPE tokens at $0.000001239. This whale involvement will likely have positive impacts on the price of PEPE. Another instance of this type of Whale involvement occurred on August 7. A holder of PEPE tokens sold a substantial amount of 2.26 trillion tokens at the price of $0.000001121 per token. Unfortunately, this action resulted in a significant decrease of $707,000 in the token&#8217;s overall market capitalization. Such contrasting maneuvers taking place in a short period might carry potential consequences for individual investors over an extended duration. Related Reading: Bitcoin Prediction: Crypto Analyst Forecasts New ATH by 2024 – Can It Happen? Meanwhile, the asset has been experiencing a notable resurgence, attracting investors&#8217; attention. The steady upward trajectory has pushed it from $0.000001185 to approximately $0.000001356, with a trading volume of over $100 million. Featured image from Pixabay and chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>PEPE surged remarkably in the past week posting gains of approximately 20%. The $0.0000011079 support level on the daily chart acted as a price pivot for the gains in the last few days, indicating an attempt to enter the buy zone. </p>
<p>PEPE&#8217;s previous attempts to break above the $0.0000015440 resistance zone between July 19-24 were unsuccessful. However, the bulls are in control, driving PEPE to attempt another break above the $0.0000015440 resistance. </p>

<p>The rally in the past 7-days indicates a momentum shift for PEPE to a more positive outlook as the bulls attempt to seize control again. </p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/TE4tsk3Y/" alt="PEPEUSD price chart" width="980" height="589"/>
<h2>PEPE Bulls Forcing Another Rally, But Bears Still Active</h2>
<p>Price volatility is evident when comparing price data for PEPE on the daily, weekly, and monthly timeframes. It trades at $0.000001348 on August 15 with a 6.03% price drop in 24 hours, while it has dropped 17% on the monthly time frame.  </p>
<p>However, PEPE shows a more positive outlook on the weekly timeframe, although traders must tread cautiously as a price drop remains a possibility due to volatility. </p>
<p>The Relative Strength Index (RSI) value is 55.71 in the neutral zone reflecting traders&#8217; indecision in the market. Also, the Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD) is rising above the signal line, confirming the return of the bulls. </p>
<p>However, the size of the candles indicates low trading activity despite the gains making the price action moving forward quite tricky. The close of the August 15 candle will bring confirmation of the next price direction. </p>
<h2>PEPE Shows Resilient Above $0.00000120 As Whale Comes Onboard</h2>
<p>In recent days, there has been a resurgence in PEPE&#8217;s performance. This trend is attributable to substantial investments from prominent investors and a rise in social engagement. According to <a href="https://twitter.com/lookonchain/status/1689098811057315840?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw%7Ctwcamp%5Etweetembed%7Ctwterm%5E1689098811057315840%7Ctwgr%5E258a528bb00d37a60bd05f067271f7af09c2a05c%7Ctwcon%5Es1_&amp;ref_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.analyticsinsight.net%2Fpepe-price-prediction-pepe-displays-strength-above-0-00000121-is-a-rebound-on-the-radar%2F" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Lookonchain</a> data, there is a significant surge in whale attention to the PEPE token.</p>
<p>The data shows a whale spent $ 1 million to acquire 807 billion PEPE tokens at $0.000001239. This whale involvement will likely have positive impacts on the price of PEPE.</p>
<p>Another instance of this type of Whale involvement occurred on August 7. A holder of PEPE tokens sold a substantial amount of <a href="https://walletinvestor.com/magazine/solana-whale-buys-into-new-into-the-pomerdoge-presale-which-chatgpt-predicts-a-winner-over-pepe#:~:text=The%20whale%20sold%20about%202.26,of%20Pepe%20(PEPE)%20tokens." rel="nofollow">2.26 trillion tokens</a> at the price of $0.000001121 per token.</p>
<p>Unfortunately, this action resulted in a significant decrease of $707,000 in the token&#8217;s overall market capitalization. Such contrasting maneuvers taking place in a short period might carry potential consequences for individual investors over an extended duration.</p>

<p>Meanwhile, the asset has been experiencing a notable resurgence, attracting investors&#8217; attention. The steady upward trajectory has pushed it from $0.000001185 to approximately $0.000001356, with a <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/pepe" rel="nofollow">trading volume</a> of over $100 million.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">547333</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hedera (HBAR) Blooms 21% &#8211; Uncloaking The Factors Behind The Rise</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/hedera-hbar-soars-17-uncloaking-the-catch-behind-the-rise/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 14:01:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[HBAR Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hedera]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price action]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=547310</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Hedera (HBAR) has stolen the limelight by becoming the highest-gaining cryptocurrency in the past 24 hours. As investors eagerly accumulate, the token&#8217;s price exhibits a roller-coaster ride of volatility. While optimism fuels the anticipation of a price rally, caution is advised as HBAR&#8217;s Bollinger Bands cast a shadow of uncertainty over its immediate future. At the time of writing, HBAR&#8217;s price is recorded at $0.071 according to CoinGecko, reflecting an 8.1% rally over the past 24 hours. Impressively, the token has experienced a seven-day surge of 21.3%, underlining its significance in the market&#8217;s recent performance. Hedera price action today. Source: Coingecko Hedera Price Roller-Coaster And Its Indicators The token&#8217;s recent performance showcases its resilience amidst market dynamics, but investors should be prepared for its volatile nature. Bollinger Bands, a widely-used technical analysis tool, serve as a flashing signal of HBAR&#8217;s ongoing turbulence.  A price analysis notes that token is currently trading above the upper band of the indicator, implying a potential overbought situation. Moreover, the notable disparity between the upper and lower bands accentuates the prevailing high volatility. This discrepancy warns of an imminent correction, underscoring the capricious nature of HBAR&#8217;s market behavior. Today, @droppcc, the micropayments solution built on @Hedera and fuelled by #HBAR, was showcased as a service provider for FedNow, the instant payment service developed by the @federalreserve 🇺🇸 Catch up with @SushilDropp (CEO, Dropp) as he explains the #Hedera integration: pic.twitter.com/4HbZqlwghl — HBAR Foundation (@HBAR_foundation) August 14, 2023 Related Reading: XRP Volume Jolt: How Did The $3 Billion Surge Impact Price Action? The surge in HBAR&#8217;s value can be attributed to a significant development in the coin&#8217;s ecosystem. News of the United States Federal Reserve&#8217;s endorsement of the FedNow payment system, which integrates support for Dropp—a micropayment platform built on the Hedera Network—has undoubtedly propelled the value of HBAR.  This latest endorsement follows a series of positive strides for Hedera. In the preceding week, the network cemented its commitment to a &#8220;blockchain-powered future&#8221; by becoming a part of Blockchain for Europe.  HBAR market cap currently at $2.3 billion. Chart: TradingView.com Hedera Transactions, User Base Climb Amidst the market&#8217;s tumult, Hedera&#8217;s accomplishments continue to underscore its prowess. The recent celebration of processing 17 billion transactions on its blockchain stands as a testament to its efficiency and scalability.  Related Reading: Toncoin Solid Climb: Price Spikes By 21% In Surprise Burst Source: Arkhia Metrics Data sourced from Arkhia reveals that the total transactions now stand at an impressive 17.5 billion. Additionally, the network boasts an expanding user base, with 3.1 million accounts created as of press time. These milestones not only reflect the network&#8217;s growth but also highlight its potential as a significant player in the blockchain space. (This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk). Featured image from The Daily Hodl]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Hedera (HBAR) has stolen the limelight by becoming the highest-gaining cryptocurrency in the past 24 hours. As investors eagerly accumulate, the token&#8217;s price exhibits a roller-coaster ride of volatility. While optimism fuels the anticipation of a price rally, caution is advised as HBAR&#8217;s Bollinger Bands cast a shadow of uncertainty over its immediate future.</p>
<p>At the time of writing, HBAR&#8217;s price is recorded at $0.071 according to <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/hedera" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">CoinGecko</a>, reflecting an 8.1% rally over the past 24 hours. Impressively, the token has experienced a seven-day surge of 21.3%, underlining its significance in the market&#8217;s recent performance.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-547311" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-81.png?resize=1024%2C56" alt="" width="1024" height="56" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-81.png?resize=1024%2C56?w=1130 1130w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-81.png?resize=1024%2C56?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-81.png?resize=1024%2C56?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-81.png?resize=1024%2C56?w=860 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-81.png?resize=1024%2C56?w=750 750w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" data-recalc-dims="1"/></p>

<h2><strong>Hedera Price Roller-Coaster And Its Indicators</strong></h2>
<p>The token&#8217;s recent performance showcases its resilience amidst market dynamics, but investors should be prepared for its volatile nature. Bollinger Bands, a widely-used technical analysis tool, serve as a flashing signal of HBAR&#8217;s ongoing turbulence. </p>
<p>A <a href="https://ambcrypto.com/hederas-accumulation-pressure-mounts-but-there-is-a-catch/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">price analysis</a> notes that token is currently trading above the upper band of the indicator, implying a potential overbought situation. Moreover, the notable disparity between the upper and lower bands accentuates the prevailing high volatility. This discrepancy warns of an imminent correction, underscoring the capricious nature of HBAR&#8217;s market behavior.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Today, <a href="https://twitter.com/droppcc?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">@droppcc</a>, the micropayments solution built on <a href="https://twitter.com/hedera?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">@Hedera</a> and fuelled by <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/HBAR?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#HBAR</a>, was showcased as a service provider for FedNow, the instant payment service developed by the <a href="https://twitter.com/federalreserve?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">@federalreserve</a> <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f1fa-1f1f8.png" alt="🇺🇸" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /></p>
<p>Catch up with <a href="https://twitter.com/SushilDropp?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">@SushilDropp</a> (CEO, Dropp) as he explains the <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Hedera?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#Hedera</a> integration: <a href="https://t.co/4HbZqlwghl" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/4HbZqlwghl</a></p>
<p>— HBAR Foundation (@HBAR_foundation) <a href="https://twitter.com/HBAR_foundation/status/1691178015420452865?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">August 14, 2023</a></p></blockquote>

<p>The surge in HBAR&#8217;s value can be attributed to a significant development in the coin&#8217;s ecosystem. News of the United States Federal Reserve&#8217;s endorsement of the FedNow payment system, which <a href="https://twitter.com/HBAR_foundation/status/1691178015420452865" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">integrates support for Dropp</a>—a micropayment platform built on the Hedera Network—has undoubtedly propelled the value of HBAR. </p>
<p>This latest endorsement follows a series of positive strides for Hedera. In the preceding week, the network cemented its commitment to a &#8220;blockchain-powered future&#8221; by <a href="https://twitter.com/BlockchainforEU/status/1690008209308737539" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">becoming a part of Blockchain for Europe</a>. </p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/rqek3Zye/" width="2475" height="1179"/></p>

<h2><strong>Hedera Transactions, User Base Climb</strong></h2>
<p>Amidst the market&#8217;s tumult, Hedera&#8217;s accomplishments continue to underscore its prowess. The recent celebration of processing 17 billion transactions on its blockchain stands as a testament to its efficiency and scalability. </p>

<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-547349 size-medium" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-82.png?w=460&#038;resize=460%2C343" alt="" width="460" height="343" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-82.png?w=908 908w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-82.png?w=460&#038;resize=460%2C343 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-82.png?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-82.png?w=860 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-82.png?w=750 750w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px" data-recalc-dims="1"/></p>

<p><a href="http://metrics.arkhia.io/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Data sourced from Arkhia</a> reveals that the total transactions now stand at an impressive 17.5 billion. Additionally, the network boasts an expanding user base, with 3.1 million accounts created as of press time. These milestones not only reflect the network&#8217;s growth but also highlight its potential as a significant player in the blockchain space.</p>
<p><em>(This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk).</em></p>
<p><em>Featured image from The Daily Hodl</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-83.png?fit=460%2C243" width="460" height="243" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">547310</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Singapore Wraps Up Stablecoin Framework: Pathway to Global Adoption?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/stablecoin/singapore-stablecoin-framework-pathway-to-global-adoption/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Opeyemi Sule]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 13:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Stablecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PayPal stablecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[singapore]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[stablecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[united states]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=547324</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Monetary Authority of Singapore (MAS) has unveiled the features of a new regulatory framework aimed at ensuring a high degree of stability for stablecoins in the country. This is the outcome of the central bank’s public consultation, which commenced in October 2022. Feedback from this public consultation was considered during the design of this new set of stablecoin rules in Singapore. According to MAS, these rules will apply to single-currency stablecoins (SCS) pegged to the Singapore dollar or any G10 currency &#8211; including the US dollar. MAS Releases “Key Requirements” For Stablecoin Issuers In Singapore In a media release published on Tuesday, August 15, the Monetary Authority of Singapore outlined key requirements for issuers of single-currency stablecoins in the country. The new regulatory framework for stablecoins consists of various provisions relating to value stability, base capital, redemption timeframes, and disclosure. Related Reading: US Congresswoman Raises Concerns About Paypal Stablecoin In The Absence Of Regulation The central bank stated that reserve assets &#8211; of a stablecoin &#8211; will be subject to requirements relating to their composition, valuation, custody, and audit, to give a high level of assurance on value stability.  Meanwhile, issuers are required to maintain minimum base capital and liquid assets to lower the risk of bankruptcy. This is to also facilitate an “orderly wind-down” of business &#8211; if the need arises. Additionally, SCS issuers in Singapore must refund the equivalent value of the stablecoins to holders within five business days after a redemption request is submitted.  Finally, the Monetary Authority of Singapore has mandated all stablecoin companies to provide appropriate disclosures to their users. Some of the information they are expected to disclose to their customers include SCS’ value stabilizing mechanism, the rights of SCS holders, and the audit results of reserve assets. The MAS noted that only issuers that fulfill all requirements under this new regulatory framework can apply for their stablecoins to be recognized as “MAS-regulated stablecoins.”  However, the financial regulator also warned issuers against misrepresenting their tokens as MAS-regulated stablecoins, as it may result in penalties under the revised stablecoin regulatory framework. MAS&#8217; Stablecoin Regulatory Framework &#8211; A Positive Sign For Global Adoption? In the press release, the MAS defined stablecoins as digital payment tokens designed to maintain a constant value against one of more specified fiat currencies. “When well-regulated to preserve such value stability, stablecoins can serve as a trusted medium of exchange to support innovation, including the “on-chain” purchase and sale of digital assets,” it added. Meanwhile, Ms. Ho Hern Shin, MAS’ deputy managing director, reacted to this development in a statement:  MAS’ stablecoin regulatory framework aims to facilitate the use of stablecoins as a credible digital medium of exchange and as a bridge between the fiat and digital asset ecosystems. We encourage SCS issuers who would like their stablecoins recognized as “MAS-regulated stablecoins” to make early preparations for compliance. Taking these statements into account, this new regulatory framework represents a positive attitude by the Singaporean authorities towards the use of stablecoin as a trusted means of payment. Moreover, it is expected to provide the needed clarity for stablecoin companies to operate in the country. It is worth mentioning that Singapore is not the only country making positive strides in terms of stablecoin regulation. There have also been discussions on regulating these digital payment tokens in the United States. Related Reading: Can PayPal’s PYUSD Be Frozen In Your Wallet Like Tether’s USDT? In what was dubbed a &#8220;momentous move&#8221;, the US House Financial Services Committee recently advanced a bill titled “Clarity for Payments Stablecoin.” This proposed bill, if passed, will regulate the issuance and use of payment stablecoins in the United States. Crypto Total Market Cap at $1.15 trillion &#124; Source: daily TOTAL chart from TradingView &#160; Featured image from Shutterstock, chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Monetary Authority of Singapore (MAS) has unveiled the features of a new regulatory framework aimed at ensuring a high degree of stability for stablecoins in the country. This is the outcome of the central bank’s public consultation, which commenced in October 2022.</p>
<p>Feedback from this public consultation was considered during the design of this new set of stablecoin rules in Singapore. According to MAS, these rules will apply to single-currency stablecoins (SCS) pegged to the Singapore dollar or any G10 currency &#8211; including the US dollar.</p>
<h2>MAS Releases “Key Requirements” For Stablecoin Issuers In Singapore</h2>
<p>In a <a href="https://www.mas.gov.sg/news/media-releases/2023/mas-finalises-stablecoin-regulatory-framework" rel="nofollow">media release</a> published on Tuesday, August 15, the Monetary Authority of Singapore outlined key requirements for issuers of single-currency stablecoins in the country. The new regulatory framework for stablecoins consists of various provisions relating to value stability, base capital, redemption timeframes, and disclosure.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/stablecoin/us-congresswoman-raises-concerns-about-paypal-pyusd-stablecoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">US Congresswoman Raises Concerns About Paypal Stablecoin In The Absence Of Regulation</a></p>
<p>The central bank stated that reserve assets &#8211; of a stablecoin &#8211; will be subject to requirements relating to their composition, valuation, custody, and audit, to give a high level of assurance on value stability. </p>
<p>Meanwhile, issuers are required to maintain minimum base capital and liquid assets to lower the risk of bankruptcy. This is to also facilitate an “orderly wind-down” of business &#8211; if the need arises.</p>
<p>Additionally, SCS issuers in Singapore must refund the equivalent value of the stablecoins to holders within five business days after a redemption request is submitted. </p>
<p>Finally, the Monetary Authority of Singapore has mandated all stablecoin companies to provide appropriate disclosures to their users. Some of the information they are expected to disclose to their customers include SCS’ value stabilizing mechanism, the rights of SCS holders, and the audit results of reserve assets.</p>
<p>The MAS noted that only issuers that fulfill all requirements under this new regulatory framework can apply for their stablecoins to be recognized as “MAS-regulated stablecoins.” </p>
<p>However, the financial regulator also warned issuers against misrepresenting their tokens as MAS-regulated stablecoins, as it may result in penalties under the revised stablecoin regulatory framework.</p>
<h2>MAS&#8217; Stablecoin Regulatory Framework &#8211; A Positive Sign For Global Adoption?</h2>
<p>In the press release, the MAS defined stablecoins as digital payment tokens designed to maintain a constant value against one of more specified fiat currencies. “When well-regulated to preserve such value stability, stablecoins can serve as a trusted medium of exchange to support innovation, including the “on-chain” purchase and sale of digital assets,” it added.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, Ms. Ho Hern Shin, MAS’ deputy managing director, reacted to this development in a statement: </p>
<blockquote><p>MAS’ stablecoin regulatory framework aims to facilitate the use of stablecoins as a credible digital medium of exchange and as a bridge between the fiat and digital asset ecosystems. We encourage SCS issuers who would like their stablecoins recognized as “MAS-regulated stablecoins” to make early preparations for compliance.</p></blockquote>
<p>Taking these statements into account, this new regulatory framework represents a positive attitude by the Singaporean authorities towards the use of stablecoin as a trusted means of payment. Moreover, it is expected to provide the needed clarity for stablecoin companies to operate in the country.</p>
<p>It is worth mentioning that Singapore is not the only country making positive strides in terms of stablecoin regulation. There have also been discussions on regulating these digital payment tokens in the United States.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/stablecoin/can-pyusd-be-frozen-in-your-wallet/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Can PayPal’s PYUSD Be Frozen In Your Wallet Like Tether’s USDT?</a></p>
<p>In what was dubbed a &#8220;momentous move&#8221;, the US House Financial Services Committee<a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/stablecoin/paypal-pyusd-launch-triggers-calls-for-stablecoin-bill/amp/"> recently advanced a bill titled “Clarity for Payments Stablecoin.”</a> This proposed bill, if passed, will regulate the issuance and use of payment stablecoins in the United States.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/q2u3ktnA/" alt="Singapore" width="1013" height="595"/></p>

<p>&nbsp;</p>



]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/270318-Singapore-MAS-Monetary-Authority-Of-Singapore.jpg?fit=460%2C307" width="460" height="307" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">547324</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Low Bitcoin Volatility Mirrors 2016: A Bullish Breakout On The Horizon?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/low-bitcoin-volatility-mirrors-2016-bullish-breakout/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jake Simmons]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 11:50:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Capriole Investments]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Charles Edwards]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=547314</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[In today’s micro update from Capriole, founder Charles Edwards presented a compelling analysis that draws parallels between the current low volatility of Bitcoin and its historical behavior in 2016. With Bitcoin&#8217;s price stagnating around the $29,000 mark, experts are closely watching for signs of a potential bullish breakout. &#8220;Bitcoin’s price remains at $29K, in a sideways consolidation that has created one of the absolute lowest volatility periods in Bitcoin’s 14 year history,&#8221; Edwards states. This prolonged period of low volatility is reminiscent of 2016, suggesting that a significant price movement could be imminent. Bitcoin Breakout Imminent? While the technicals indicate a bearish breakdown from the $30,000 mark, the absence of a downward momentum offers a glimmer of hope for bullish investors. &#8220;If price was going to collapse, we would usually have seen that follow through by now,&#8221; the report notes. However, for a more concrete bullish sentiment, &#8220;a close back above $30K on the daily timeframe is required at the minimum as a technical confirmation of a failed breakdown.&#8221; Related Reading: Bernstein Predicts Spot ETFs Could Claim 10% Of Bitcoin’s Market If Greenlit On the fundamental front, Bitcoin&#8217;s on-chain data continues to contract, albeit at a decelerating rate. The imminent decisions on several Bitcoin ETF approvals could potentially disrupt the current low volatility phase. &#8220;An approval could cause a break from the current low volatility range. Best not to pre-empt this though, as these decisions often get pushed. Confirmations are key to mitigate risk,&#8221; Edwards cautions. Diving deeper into the technicals, the report highlighted two key observations: Since 2010, Bitcoin’s historic volatility has only been lower than today in 2016. Suggesting a big price move is on the horizon when volatility expansion (reversion to the mean) occurs. Bitcoin’s $30K breakdown has (so far) failed to follow through&#8230; A close back into the Wyckoff structure at $30K would signify a failed breakdown and therefore be a very positive technical signal. BTC On-Chain Indicators Are Neutral Capriole&#8217;s Bitcoin Macro Index, a comprehensive tool that amalgamates over 40 Bitcoin on-chain, macro market, and equities metrics into a machine learning model, currently scores at -0.36, indicating &#8220;Contraction&#8221;. This suggests that while the short-term outlook remains neutral, the long-term perspective appears bullish. Remarkably, this strategy takes long-only positions in Bitcoin. In slowdowns and contractions, cash is held. &#8220;The Macro Index today remains in a period of relative value (below zero), suggesting decent long-term value for multi-year horizon investors,&#8221; the report elucidated. Related Reading: Bitcoin Price Supported By Thin $40 Million Bid Pool, But For How Long? A noteworthy addition to Capriole&#8217;s analysis toolkit is the &#8220;Bitcoin Production Cost&#8221; model, which evaluates the cost of mining a Bitcoin based on global average electrical consumption. Currently, this model indicates that Bitcoin is trading within a long-term value region, with the report speculating, &#8220;I would be surprised if this holds into 2024.&#8221; In conclusion, the analysis from Capriole paints a picture of potential long-term value amidst the current bearish technicals. Drawing parallels with 2016, the report suggests that Bitcoin&#8217;s current low volatility phase could be a precursor to a bullish breakout. &#8220;All else equal, Bitcoin is like a beach ball submerged underwater. Nonetheless, we remain in a technical breakdown. We don’t know how long that hand will hold the ball underwater for. Prudent risk-management will await a technical confirmation before acting.&#8221; With the cyclical nature of Bitcoin&#8217;s expansion and contraction cycles, only time will tell if history will indeed repeat itself; especially with the backdrop of a totally different macro environment. At press time, the BTC price remained stagnant, trading at $29,445. Featured image from André François McKenzie / Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In today’s micro <a href="https://capriole.com/the-capriole-macro-index/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">update</a> from Capriole, founder Charles Edwards presented a compelling analysis that draws parallels between the current low volatility of Bitcoin and its historical behavior in 2016. With Bitcoin&#8217;s price stagnating around the $29,000 mark, experts are closely watching for signs of a potential bullish breakout.</p>
<p>&#8220;Bitcoin’s price remains at $29K, in a sideways consolidation that has created one of the absolute lowest volatility periods in Bitcoin’s 14 year history,&#8221; Edwards states. This prolonged period of low volatility is reminiscent of 2016, suggesting that a significant price movement could be imminent.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Breakout Imminent?</h2>
<p>While the technicals indicate a bearish breakdown from the $30,000 mark, the absence of a downward momentum offers a glimmer of hope for bullish investors. &#8220;If price was going to collapse, we would usually have seen that follow through by now,&#8221; the report notes. However, for a more concrete bullish sentiment, &#8220;a close back above $30K on the daily timeframe is required at the minimum as a technical confirmation of a failed breakdown.&#8221;</p>

<p>On the fundamental front, Bitcoin&#8217;s on-chain data continues to contract, albeit at a decelerating rate. The imminent decisions on <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/blackrock-first-spot-bitcoin-etf/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">several</a> Bitcoin ETF approvals could potentially disrupt the current low volatility phase. &#8220;An approval could cause a break from the current low volatility range. Best not to pre-empt this though, as these decisions often get pushed. Confirmations are key to mitigate risk,&#8221; Edwards cautions.</p>
<p>Diving deeper into the technicals, the report highlighted two key observations:</p>
<blockquote><p><strong>Since 2010, Bitcoin’s historic volatility has only been lower than today in 2016. Suggesting a big price move is on the horizon when volatility expansion (reversion to the mean) occurs. </strong></p>
<p><strong>Bitcoin’s $30K breakdown has (so far) failed to follow through&#8230; A close back into the Wyckoff structure at $30K would signify a failed breakdown and therefore be a very positive technical signal.</strong></p></blockquote>
<h2>BTC On-Chain Indicators Are Neutral</h2>
<p>Capriole&#8217;s Bitcoin Macro Index, a comprehensive tool that amalgamates over 40 Bitcoin on-chain, macro market, and equities metrics into a machine learning model, currently scores at -0.36, indicating &#8220;Contraction&#8221;. This suggests that while the short-term outlook remains neutral, the long-term perspective appears bullish. Remarkably, this strategy takes long-only positions in Bitcoin. In slowdowns and contractions, cash is held.</p>
<p>&#8220;The Macro Index today remains in a period of relative value (below zero), suggesting decent long-term value for multi-year horizon investors,&#8221; the report elucidated.</p>

<p>A noteworthy addition to Capriole&#8217;s analysis toolkit is the &#8220;Bitcoin Production Cost&#8221; model, which evaluates the cost of mining a Bitcoin based on global average electrical consumption. Currently, this model indicates that Bitcoin is trading within a long-term value region, with the report speculating, &#8220;I would be surprised if this holds into 2024.&#8221;</p>
<p>In conclusion, the analysis from Capriole paints a picture of potential long-term value amidst the current bearish technicals. Drawing parallels with 2016, the report suggests that Bitcoin&#8217;s current low volatility phase could be a precursor to a bullish breakout.</p>
<p>&#8220;All else equal, Bitcoin is like a beach ball submerged underwater. Nonetheless, we remain in a technical breakdown. We don’t know how long that hand will hold the ball underwater for. Prudent risk-management will await a technical confirmation before acting.&#8221;</p>
<p>With the cyclical nature of Bitcoin&#8217;s expansion and contraction cycles, only time will tell if history will indeed repeat itself; especially with the backdrop of a totally different macro environment. At press time, the BTC price remained stagnant, trading at $29,445.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-547322 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD_2023-08-15_11-34-58.png?resize=3628%2C1672" alt="Bitcoin price" width="3628" height="1672" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD_2023-08-15_11-34-58.png?resize=3628%2C1672?w=3628 3628w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD_2023-08-15_11-34-58.png?resize=3628%2C1672?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD_2023-08-15_11-34-58.png?resize=3628%2C1672?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD_2023-08-15_11-34-58.png?resize=3628%2C1672?w=860 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD_2023-08-15_11-34-58.png?resize=3628%2C1672?w=1536 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD_2023-08-15_11-34-58.png?resize=3628%2C1672?w=2048 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD_2023-08-15_11-34-58.png?resize=3628%2C1672?w=750 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD_2023-08-15_11-34-58.png?resize=3628%2C1672?w=1140 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD_2023-08-15_11-34-58.png?resize=3628%2C1672?w=3000 3000w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" data-recalc-dims="1"/>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/andre-francois-mckenzie-uw3VwkDHiMI-unsplash.jpg?fit=460%2C307" width="460" height="307" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">547314</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>US Prosecutors Accuse FTX’s Sam Bankman-Fried Of Using $100M To Curry Political Favors</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/ftx/sam-bankman-fried-100m-political-favors/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 10:50:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX bankruptcy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SBF]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=547307</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The drama surrounding FTX and founder Sam Bankman-Fried (SBF) continues to unfold almost a year after the crypto exchange collapsed. This time around, prosecutors are coming after the former CEO for allegedly using customer funds to buy the favor of politicians. SBF Used Customer Funds For Campaign Contributions The latest indictment filed by the United States Department of Justice (DOJ) details how Bankman-Fried embezzled customer deposits and used these stolen funds towards various ventures, including funding the political campaigns of several politicians in the Democratic and Republican parties.  Related Reading: BALD Deployer Moves Proceeds Of The Rug From Base To Ethereum According to the filing, SBF did this to lobby for crypto regulations that could favor him and his company. His plan was to get Congress and regulators to make laws and regulations that make it easier for FTX to accept customers’ deposits, consequently allowing his embezzlement to continue without getting noticed.  SBF also apparently broke several campaign finance rules to maximize his influence on politicians by using straw donors as some of these political contributions were allegedly made in the names of FTX executives. The founder also made to conceal the fact that the source of these donations was customer funds, as he directed that the customer deposits be paid into the executives’ bank accounts, who then made the donations in their names.  SBF had been publicly known to make contributions to the Democratic party while secretly funneling funds to the GOP. He previously admitted that he made “significant” donations to both parties before the midterm elections last year.  At the time, the funds he reportedly donated totaled over $40 million, making him the seventh-highest political donor between 2021 and 2022. However, the latest indictment filing reveals that he could have well been the second-highest political donor with over $100 million in political contributions.  While SBF made these donations and portrayed himself as the “savior of the cryptocurrency industry” (in reference to SBF bailing out crypto firms that were struggling financially), there were gaps in FTX’s finances resulting from his alleged misappropriation.  FTT Token struggles as SBF case intensifies &#124; Source: FTTBUSD on Tradingview.com Sam Bankman-Fried Faces Seven Counts Of Fraud Despite this latest revelation, prosecutors will no longer be charging SBF with violation of campaign finance rules. This decision was made to protect the US government&#8217;s extradition agreement with the Bahamas as the latter “did not intend to extradite the defendant on the campaign contributions count.” Related Reading: Here’s Why This Former SEC Lawyer Thinks A Spot Bitcoin ETF Isn’t Coming According to the latest indictment filing, SBF now faces seven counts of financial fraud. These charges cut across his misappropriation of funds that belonged to FTX customers and Alameda Research Creditors. He is also charged with money laundering.  Last week, a US Judge ruled that SBF be remanded in the infamous Brooklyn Metropolitan Detention Center (MDC), known for its unfavorable living conditions. This ruling came after SBF was found to have tampered with evidence, and he is expected to remain in custody until his trial set for October 2.  Featured image from Sky News, chart from Tradingview.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The drama surrounding FTX and founder Sam Bankman-Fried (SBF) continues to unfold almost a year after the crypto exchange collapsed. This time around, prosecutors are coming after the former CEO for allegedly using customer funds to buy the favor of politicians.</p>
<h2>SBF Used Customer Funds For Campaign Contributions</h2>
<p>The latest <a href="https://storage.courtlistener.com/recap/gov.uscourts.nysd.590940/gov.uscourts.nysd.590940.202.0.pdf" rel="nofollow">indictment</a> filed by the United States Department of Justice (DOJ) details how Bankman-Fried embezzled customer deposits and used these stolen funds towards various ventures, including funding the political campaigns of several politicians in the Democratic and Republican parties. </p>

<p>According to the filing, SBF did this to lobby for crypto regulations that could favor him and his company. His plan was to get Congress and regulators to make laws and regulations that make it easier for FTX to accept customers’ deposits, consequently allowing his embezzlement to continue without getting noticed. </p>
<p>SBF also apparently broke several campaign finance rules to maximize his influence on politicians by using straw donors as some of these political contributions were allegedly made in the names of FTX executives. The founder also made to conceal the fact that the source of these donations was customer funds, as he directed that the customer deposits be paid into the executives’ bank accounts, who then made the donations in their names. </p>
<p>SBF had been publicly known to make <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/breaking-news-ticker/ftxs-sbf-hit-with-fresh-batch-of-bank-fraud-charges/">contributions</a> to the Democratic party while secretly funneling funds to the GOP. He previously <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/ftx-sbf-bernie-madoff-of-crypto-democrats-ukraine/" rel="nofollow">admitted</a> that he made “significant” donations to both parties before the midterm elections last year. </p>
<p>At the time, the funds he reportedly <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/ftx-to-politicos-return-donations/" rel="nofollow">donated</a> totaled over $40 million, making him the seventh-highest political donor between 2021 and 2022. However, the latest indictment filing reveals that he could have well been the second-highest political donor with over $100 million in political contributions. </p>
<p>While SBF made these donations and portrayed himself as the “savior of the cryptocurrency industry” (in reference to SBF bailing out crypto firms that were struggling financially), there were gaps in FTX’s finances resulting from his alleged misappropriation. </p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/QIGWmXVe/" alt="FTX FTT Token price chart from Tradingview.com (Sam Bankman-Fried)" width="2884" height="1746"/></p>

<h2>Sam Bankman-Fried Faces Seven Counts Of Fraud</h2>
<p>Despite this latest revelation, prosecutors will no longer be charging SBF with violation of campaign finance rules. This decision was made to protect the US government&#8217;s extradition agreement with the Bahamas as the latter “did not intend to extradite the defendant on the campaign contributions count.”</p>

<p>According to the latest indictment filing, SBF now faces seven counts of financial fraud. These charges cut across his misappropriation of funds that belonged to FTX customers and Alameda Research Creditors. He is also charged with money laundering. </p>
<p>Last week, a US Judge <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/ftx-founder-faces-brooklyns-notorious-hellhole/#:~:text=In%20a%20U.S.%20District%20Judge,Metropolitan%20Detention%20Center%20(MDC)." rel="nofollow">ruled</a> that SBF be remanded in the infamous Brooklyn Metropolitan Detention Center (MDC), known for its unfavorable living conditions. This ruling came after SBF was found to have tampered with evidence, and he is expected to remain in custody until his trial set for October 2. </p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/FTX-Sam-Bankman-Fried.jpeg?fit=460%2C259" width="460" height="259" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">547307</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Prediction: Crypto Analyst Forecasts New ATH by 2024 &#8211; Can It Happen?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-prediction-crypto-analyst-forecasts-new-ath-by-2024-can-it-happen/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Semilore Faleti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 09:40:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ath]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto cycle]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Kevin Kelly]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=547291</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[On August 14, Kevin Kelly, Co-founder of prominent crypto research firm Delphi Digital provided some interesting insights on Bitcoin and the crypto market in general. According to Kelly, the crypto market moves in consistent cycles, and we are currently in the initial stages of a new cycle based on market evidence. Using the premier cryptocurrency as a benchmark, Kelly states a crypto cycle usually begins with Bitcoin attaining a new all-time high (ATH) value, followed by an 80% loss in the next year. Thereafter, BTC would experience a market recovery over two years before embarking on a bullish run to attain a new ATH.  The Interplay Between The Crypto Cycle And Macroeconomic Signals Based on Kelly’s analysis, a typical crypto cycle occurs within four years, and its events are triggered by some factors in the bigger macro business cycle.  Related Reading: Bitcoin Price Relatively Muted – What Could Trigger A Sharp Decline? The analyst noted that, for example, Bitcoin usually attains new price peaks at the same period as the Institute of Supply Management (ISM) Index &#8211;  an economic indicator that tracks the manufacturing sector’s health in the United States. He said: BTC price peaks occur around the same time the ISM shows signs of topping out. Active addresses, total transaction volumes, total fees – they all peaked alongside tops in the ISM too. As the business cycle shows signs of recovery, so too does network activity levels… Due to this similarity in market movement, Kevin notes that turning moments in a typical business cycle have proven to be a favorable period to increase one’s exposure to risk assets such as Bitcoin.  Source: Delphi Digital Bitcoin Poised To Attain New ATH By Q4 2024, Kelly Says Interestingly, Kevin Kelly stated in his analysis that the ISM is currently heading toward the end of a two-year downtrend, indicating that BTC’s prices may soon start surging in the coming months. To back his long-term bullish price prediction, Kelly highlights several other factors, including the Bitcoin Halving event coming up in April 2024.  The Delphi Digital Co-founder stated that the last two Bitcoin halvings had occurred 18 months after BTC’s price tanked and 7 months before rallying to a new ATH. Related Reading: Bernstein Predicts Spot ETFs Could Claim 10% Of Bitcoin’s Market If Greenlit Based on this historical data, BTC could well attain a new ATH by Q4 2024. However, as with all predictions, Kelly stated that are certain risk factors involved.  Firstly, he predicted that the BTC market is likely to soon witness a modest selling pressure or price consolidation, especially following the market&#8217;s strong recovery in the last 9 months. In addition, he also highlighted the possibility of the business cycle presenting a false bearish end &#8211; as seen in March 2020 &#8211;  or not reaching its bearish end as soon as predicted.  According to data from CoinMarketCap, Bitcoin is trading around $29,333.89, with a 0.12% decline on the last day. However, the token’s daily trading volume is up by 26.38% and is valued at $12.2 billion BTC trading at $29,322 on the daily chart &#124; Source: BTCUSD chart on Tradingview.com Featured image from LinkedIn, chart from Tradingview]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On August 14, Kevin Kelly, Co-founder of prominent <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/crypto/michael-egorovs-100-million-position-a-risk-to-curve-finance-and-defi/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">crypto research firm Delphi Digital</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/Kevin_Kelly_II/status/1691200100922724353?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">provided</a> some interesting insights on Bitcoin and the crypto market in general. According to Kelly, the crypto market moves in <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-price-prediction-2024-25-4-year-cycle-elliot-wave/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">consistent cycles</a>, and we are currently in the initial stages of a new cycle based on market evidence.</p>
<p>Using the premier cryptocurrency as a benchmark, Kelly states a crypto cycle usually begins with Bitcoin attaining a new all-time high (ATH) value, followed by an 80% loss in the next year. Thereafter, BTC would experience a market recovery over two years before embarking on a bullish run to attain a new ATH. </p>
<h2>The Interplay Between The Crypto Cycle And Macroeconomic Signals</h2>
<p>Based on Kelly’s analysis, a typical crypto cycle occurs within four years, and its events are triggered by some factors in the bigger macro business cycle. </p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-muted-29650/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Bitcoin Price Relatively Muted – What Could Trigger A Sharp Decline?</a></p>
<p>The analyst noted that, for example, Bitcoin usually attains new price peaks at the same period as the Institute of Supply Management (ISM) Index &#8211;  an economic indicator that tracks the manufacturing sector’s health in the United States.</p>
<p>He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>BTC price peaks occur around the same time the ISM shows signs of topping out. Active addresses, total transaction volumes, total fees – they all peaked alongside tops in the ISM too. As the business cycle shows signs of recovery, so too does network activity levels…</p></blockquote>
<p>Due to this similarity in market movement, Kevin notes that turning moments in a typical business cycle have proven to be a favorable period to increase one’s exposure to risk assets such as Bitcoin. </p>

<h2>Bitcoin Poised To Attain New ATH By Q4 2024, Kelly Says</h2>
<p>Interestingly, Kevin Kelly stated in his analysis that the ISM is currently heading toward the end of a two-year downtrend, indicating that BTC’s prices may soon start surging in the coming months.</p>
<p>To back his long-term bullish price prediction, Kelly highlights several other factors, including the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/all/bitcoin-bull-run-beckons-unleashing-the-potential-of-2024-halving-on-prices/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Bitcoin Halving event</a> coming up in April 2024. </p>
<p>The Delphi Digital Co-founder stated that the last two Bitcoin halvings had occurred 18 months after BTC’s price tanked and 7 months before rallying to a new ATH.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bernstein-predicts-spot-etfs-bitcoin-market-if-greenlit/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Bernstein Predicts Spot ETFs Could Claim 10% Of Bitcoin’s Market If Greenlit</a></p>
<p>Based on this historical data, BTC could well attain a new ATH by Q4 2024. However, as with all predictions, Kelly stated that are certain risk factors involved. </p>
<p>Firstly, he predicted that the BTC market is likely to soon witness a modest selling pressure or price consolidation, especially following the market&#8217;s strong recovery in the last 9 months.</p>
<p>In addition, he also highlighted the possibility of the business cycle presenting a false bearish end &#8211; as seen in March 2020 &#8211;  or not reaching its bearish end as soon as predicted. </p>
<p>According to data from CoinMarketCap, Bitcoin is trading around $29,333.89, with a 0.12% decline on the last day. However, the token’s daily trading volume is up by 26.38% and is valued at $12.2 billion
</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/4VQEOrnG/" alt="Bitcoin" width="1480" height="906"/></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/1634821037107.png?fit=460%2C259" width="460" height="259" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">547291</post-id>	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
