<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
>

<channel>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.newsbtc.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<description>Bitcoin &#38; Cryptocurrency News Today</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 11:01:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Dogecoin Leaps 13% Following Elon Musk&#8217;s Cryptic Tweet &#8211; Details</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/dogecoin-up-13-after-musk-tweet/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 11:01:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=545053</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[This time around, Elon Musk, the CEO of SpaceX and the world&#8217;s largest manufacturer of electric vehicles, Tesla, is creating a flurry of excitement around cryptocurrencies, maybe with a particular focus on Dogecoin, the well-known parody cryptocurrency. The crypto community has taken note of Musk&#8217;s recent acts since they continue to demonstrate his influence in altering the market dynamics of digital currency. The billionaire Musk, who is also the owner of the X app (formerly known as Twitter), posted on Sunday that &#8220;something special is coming soon.&#8221; Related Reading: CryptoPunks Toughness Tested As NFT Succumbs To 60% Drop In 1 Week Elon Musk Tweet Does It Again This tweet received a lot of positive feedback from the cryptocurrency community, especially from accounts with a Dogecoin theme. Something special coming soon — Elon Musk (@elonmusk) July 29, 2023 Based on Musk&#8217;s repeated references to this development in the past, many people, including the influencer David Gokhstein, anticipate that X will add DOGE &#8211; the largest meme coin &#8211; as a payment option. This anticipation arises from the fact that Elon Musk has previously made a number of very quiet signals that a similar action may be planned. Dogecoin (DOGE) saw a stunning price increase on Friday, garnering a lot of attention in the cryptocurrency community. On that particular day, DOGE&#8217;s price noticedably increased by over 10%, breaking past the $0.07 barrier mark. Dogecoin Rising At $0.08 When this article was being written, DOGE was trading at $0.08, up 2.7% over the previous day. However, the meme coin really proved its worth on a weekly basis, rising in value by about 13% in response to Musk&#8217;s post. Source: Coingecko This positive momentum-driven upward rise in value led to a sizable increase in the market capitalisation of the asset. The cryptocurrency&#8217;s market cap increased as a result, rising by an estimated $1 billion to a new high of $10.66 billion from its previous value of $9.67 billion. Related Reading: Traders’ Interest In XRP Remains Solid Despite Price Retreat, Data Shows The reasons for this remarkable rise have been the subject of heated speculation among many members of the crypto community. One of the more intriguing current theories is on the potential integration of DOGE, the disputed cryptocurrency, into the source code of Tesla&#8217;s website&#8217;s payment page. DOGE market cap currently at $11.8 billion on the weekly chart: TradingView.com Price Boom Soon? As enthusiasts and investors alike anticipate the potential effects of such a development, this notion has been spreading. The mere possibility of DOGE becoming a payment option for Tesla has sparked curiosity and led to upbeat predictions for the cryptocurrency&#8217;s future. If Elon Musk does truly integrate DOGE payments into his X app, Dogecoin will experience a solid increase in utility and acceptance, as well as a significant price boom. (This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk). Featured image from Getty Images]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This time around, Elon Musk, the CEO of SpaceX and the world&#8217;s largest manufacturer of electric vehicles, Tesla, is creating a flurry of excitement around cryptocurrencies, maybe with a particular focus on Dogecoin, the well-known parody cryptocurrency.</p>
<p>The crypto community has taken note of Musk&#8217;s recent acts since they continue to demonstrate his influence in altering the market dynamics of digital currency.</p>
<p>The billionaire Musk, who is also the owner of the X app (formerly known as Twitter), posted on Sunday that &#8220;something special is coming soon.&#8221;</p>

<h2><strong>Elon Musk Tweet Does It Again</strong></h2>
<p>This tweet received a lot of positive feedback from the cryptocurrency community, especially from accounts with a Dogecoin theme.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Something special coming soon</p>
<p>— Elon Musk (@elonmusk) <a href="https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1685363794090819584?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">July 29, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p>Based on Musk&#8217;s repeated references to this development in the past, many people, including the influencer David Gokhstein, anticipate that X will add DOGE &#8211; the largest meme coin &#8211; as a payment option.</p>
<p>This anticipation arises from the fact that Elon Musk has previously made a number of very quiet signals that a similar action may be planned.</p>
<p>Dogecoin (DOGE) saw a stunning price increase on Friday, garnering a lot of attention in the cryptocurrency community. On that particular day, DOGE&#8217;s price noticedably increased by over 10%, breaking past the $0.07 barrier mark.</p>
<h2><strong>Dogecoin Rising At $0.08</strong></h2>
<p>When this article was being written, DOGE was <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">trading at $0.08</a>, up 2.7% over the previous day. However, the meme coin really proved its worth on a weekly basis, rising in value by about 13% in response to Musk&#8217;s post.<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-545057" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/doge.png" alt="" width="1262" height="66" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/doge.png 1262w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/doge-460x24.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/doge-860x45.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/doge-768x40.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/doge-750x39.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/doge-1140x60.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1262px) 100vw, 1262px"/></p>
<p style="text-align: center">Source: <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Coingecko</a></p>
<p>This positive momentum-driven upward rise in value led to a sizable increase in the market capitalisation of the asset. The cryptocurrency&#8217;s market cap increased as a result, rising by an estimated $1 billion to a new high of $10.66 billion from its previous value of $9.67 billion.</p>

<p>The reasons for this remarkable rise have been the subject of heated speculation among many members of the crypto community.</p>
<p>One of the more intriguing current theories is on the potential integration of DOGE, the disputed cryptocurrency, into the source code of Tesla&#8217;s website&#8217;s payment page.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/NrQnwRzl/" width="2475" height="1187"/></p>

<strong>Price Boom Soon?</strong>
<p>As enthusiasts and investors alike anticipate the potential effects of such a development, this notion has been spreading. The mere possibility of DOGE becoming a payment option for Tesla has sparked curiosity and led to upbeat predictions for the cryptocurrency&#8217;s future.</p>
<p>If Elon Musk does truly integrate DOGE payments into his X app, Dogecoin will experience a solid increase in utility and acceptance, as well as a significant price boom.</p>
<p><em>(This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk).</em></p>
<p><em>Featured image from Getty Images</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-187-460x258.png" width="460" height="258" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Court Filing Suggests FTX’s $2 Billion Lawsuit Against Genesis Is Coming To An End</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/crypto/ftx-2-billion-lawsuit-against-genesis/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 20:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DCG]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX lawsuit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[genesis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=545005</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The legal tussle between bankrupt crypto exchange FTX and crypto lender Genesis seems to be coming to a resolution, a recent court filing reveals. According to the letter filed yesterday at the US bankruptcy court for the Southern District of New York, both firms &#8211; who happened to have filed for bankruptcy &#8211; have agreed to settle their ongoing billion-dollar dispute.  How The Feud Began FTX filed a motion in May this year to recover its funds from Genesis and “non-debtor affiliates” so the company could pay back its creditors. The motion went as far as describing Genesis (who attributed its solvency issues to FTX’s collapse) as “one of the main feeder funds and instrumental to its [FTX and Sister company Alameda Research] fraudulent business model.” Related Reading: Shiba Inu Reclaims 14th Spot In Market After 5% Jump FTX further claimed that Genesis received “avoidable transfers” from FTX’s debtors totaling almost $3.9 billion. In response, Genesis denied owing FTX and filed a motion asking the bankruptcy judge to rule its debt to FTX as zero. However, a subsequent letter from FTX to the bankruptcy judge showed that the company had reduced its claim from $3.9 billion to $2 billion. FTT token trades at $1.3 amid exchange's woes &#124; Source: FTTUSD on Tradingview.com FTX’s claim could have delayed a creditor payout and slowed Genesis’ bankruptcy proceedings. However, with settlement in sight, things are likely to move along quickly, as according to the letter, FTX, its associated debtors, and debtors in its Chapter 11 bankruptcy case have reached a preliminary agreement. The court filing reads: The parties have reached an agreement in principle, subject to documentation, regarding a settlement that would resolve, among other things, the claims asserted by the FTX debtors against the debtors in these Chapter 11 Cases and the claims asserted by the Genesis debtors against the FTX debtors in the FTX Chapter 11 cases. Genesis Still Not In The Clear Despite reaching a settlement with FTX, crypto lending platform Genesis still has other lawsuits to deal with, including one filed by Gemini against its parent company, Digital Currency Group (DCG), and its CEO, Barry Silbert. Gemini’s co-founder Cameron Winklevoss called out Barry Silbert on Twitter in an open letter, claiming that Silbert and DCG had engaged in “Fraudulent Behavior.”  Related Reading: This Machine Learning Tool Was Asked To Predict XRP Price, Here’s What It Said He warned that Silbert’s failure to reply and come to the negotiation table by Friday would result in a lawsuit. In a follow-up tweet, Winklevoss also tabled a “best and final offer” involving a repayment plan. Still, Silbert and DCG failed to reply, and true to his words, Winklevoss and Gemini filed a lawsuit against DCG and Silbert for fraud on July 7. Featured image from SlashGear, chart from Tradingview.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The legal tussle between bankrupt crypto exchange FTX and crypto lender Genesis seems to be coming to a resolution, a recent court <a href="https://restructuring.ra.kroll.com/genesis/Home-DownloadPDF?id1=MjEyNDc4Nw==&amp;id2=-1" rel="nofollow">filing</a> reveals. According to the letter filed yesterday at the US bankruptcy court for the Southern District of New York, both firms &#8211; who happened to have filed for bankruptcy &#8211; have agreed to settle their ongoing billion-dollar dispute. </p>
<h2>How The Feud Began</h2>
<p>FTX <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/crypto-firms-fight-over-crumbs-ftx-genesis-battle/" rel="nofollow">filed a motion</a> in May this year to recover its funds from Genesis and “non-debtor affiliates” so the company could pay back its creditors. The <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/ftx-vs-genesis-the-3-9-billion-crypto-showdown/" rel="nofollow">motion</a> went as far as describing Genesis (who attributed its solvency issues to FTX’s collapse) as “one of the main feeder funds and instrumental to its [FTX and Sister company Alameda Research] fraudulent business model.”</p>

<p>FTX further claimed that Genesis received “avoidable transfers” from FTX’s debtors totaling almost $3.9 billion. In response, Genesis denied owing FTX and <a href="https://restructuring.ra.kroll.com/genesis/Home-DownloadPDF?id1=MTUxNTA4NQ==&amp;id2=-1" rel="nofollow">filed</a> a motion asking the bankruptcy judge to rule its debt to FTX as zero. However, a subsequent letter from FTX to the bankruptcy judge showed that the company had reduced its claim from $3.9 billion to $2 billion.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/Gc0j5evR/" alt="FTX FTT Token price chart from Tradingview.com" width="2884" height="1746"/></p>

<p>FTX’s claim could have delayed a creditor payout and slowed Genesis’ bankruptcy proceedings. However, with settlement in sight, things are likely to move along quickly, as according to the letter, FTX, its associated debtors, and debtors in its Chapter 11 bankruptcy case have reached a preliminary agreement.</p>
<p>The court filing reads:</p>
<blockquote><p>The parties have reached an agreement in principle, subject to documentation, regarding a settlement that would resolve, among other things, the claims asserted by the FTX debtors against the debtors in these Chapter 11 Cases and the claims asserted by the Genesis debtors against the FTX debtors in the FTX Chapter 11 cases.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Genesis Still Not In The Clear</h2>
<p>Despite reaching a settlement with FTX, crypto lending platform Genesis still has other lawsuits to deal with, including one filed by <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/sponsored/gemini-earn-users-want-justice-exchange-ignores-them-to-buy-ledgerx/">Gemini against its parent company, Digital Currency Group (DCG), and its CEO, Barry Silbert</a>. Gemini’s co-founder Cameron Winklevoss called out Barry Silbert on <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/gemini-vs-dcg-winklevoss-lawsuit-within-72-hours/" rel="nofollow">Twitter</a> in an open letter, claiming that Silbert and DCG had engaged in “Fraudulent Behavior.” </p>

<p>He warned that Silbert’s failure to reply and come to the negotiation table by Friday would result in a lawsuit. In a follow-up <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/gemini-vs-dcg-winklevoss-lawsuit-within-72-hours/" rel="nofollow">tweet</a>, Winklevoss also tabled a “best and final offer” involving a repayment plan.</p>
<p>Still, Silbert and DCG failed to reply, and true to his words, Winklevoss and Gemini filed a lawsuit against DCG and Silbert for fraud on July 7.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/FTX-and-Genesis-crypto-460x258.jpeg" width="460" height="258" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Shiba Inu Reclaims 14th Spot In Market After 5% Jump</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/shiba-inu-reclaims-14th-spot/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 16:00:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Shiba Inu]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIB]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIB market cap]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIB price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shibarium]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIBUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIBUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=544991</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[After a rough few months of slipping down the ranks, Shiba Inu is back in the top 15 cryptocurrencies by market cap. In the last 24 hours, the price of Shiba Inu has spiked in excess of 5%, allowing it to overtake cryptocurrencies like Wrapped Bitcoin and Bitcoin Cash to reach the 14th spot with a market cap of $4.8 billion. Shiba Inu Jumps 5% In 24 Hours, Reclaiming 14th Spot The price of the majority of cryptocurrencies seems to be plateauing in the past week, with some even losing some of their market cap. However, meme coins like Shiba Inu and Dogecoin seem to be doing slightly well, with DOGE leading the pack with a 7.02% gain in the past seven days.  Related Reading: VC Firm Sequoia Capital Slashes Crypto Fund By 65% Amid Bear Market In the case of Shiba Inu (SHIB), the altcoin has found a bit of momentum, amassing an increase of 293.16% in trading volume in the past 24 hours.  As usual with volatile meme coins, it’s hard to pin down an exact catalyst of the spike. However, the price jump seems to have come after Shiba Inu&#8217;s developers announced the release of a testnet bridge between Shibarium and Ethereum. Shibarium to Ethereum Testnet Bridge Pushes SHIB&#8217;s Price by 5% Shiba Inu has come a long way since its creation as a meme coin made just to challenge the popular Dogecoin (DOGE). However, the Shiba Inu ecosystem now has a lot of following, investors, developers, and an active community.  Shiba Inu developers are now working on a Layer-2 upgrade with the aim of developing the ecosystem and becoming a serious blockchain contender. The network, which will operate on top of Ethereum, is called Shibarium and was announced earlier in March. When Shibarium is launched, it is expected to help minimize costs and increase transaction speeds. 🔥 Shibarium Beta Bridge has gone live for public testing! 🎉 Be among the first to try out this revolutionary cross-chain solution. Remember, always exercise caution and verify authenticity before connecting your wallet to any website. PLEASE DO NOT USE YOUR REAL ASSETS!… pic.twitter.com/7yfhX8gQc6 — 𝐋𝐔𝐂𝐈𝐄 (@LucieSHIB) July 26, 2023 On July 28, SHIB devs began testing a bridge that allows tokens to be easily transferred between the Shibarium and Ethereum. The testnet release is an important step toward making Shibarium a reality. This cross-chain solution seems to have sparked the interest of SHIB investors, as the price of the token spiked in the hours after.  Related Reading: Ripple Attorney Withdraws From SEC Lawsuit, Will It Affect XRP? How High Can The Price Go? Shiba Inu is the second-largest meme coin in terms of market cap. Although the price is now nearly 80% from its all-time high in October 2021, current upgrades show momentum seems to be turning positive. The coming months and the progress of the Shibarium Layer-2 will be crucial in determining whether Shiba Inu can build on this momentum to retest previous highs or whether it continues to plateau.  At the time of writing, SHIB is trading at $0.000008191. SHIB price recovers above $0.000008 &#124; Source: SHIBUSD on Tradingview.com Featured image from iStock, chart from Tradingview.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>After a rough few months of slipping down the ranks, Shiba Inu is back in the top 15 cryptocurrencies by market cap. In the last 24 hours, the price of Shiba Inu has spiked in excess of 5%, allowing it to overtake cryptocurrencies like Wrapped Bitcoin and Bitcoin Cash to reach the 14th spot with a market cap of $4.8 billion.</p>
<h2>Shiba Inu Jumps 5% In 24 Hours, Reclaiming 14th Spot</h2>
<p>The price of the majority of cryptocurrencies seems to be plateauing in the past week, with some even losing some of their market cap. However, meme coins like Shiba Inu and Dogecoin seem to be doing slightly well, with DOGE leading the pack with a 7.02% gain in the past seven days. </p>

<p>In the case of Shiba Inu (SHIB), the altcoin has found a bit of momentum, amassing an increase of 293.16% in trading volume in the past 24 hours. </p>
<p>As usual with volatile meme coins, it’s hard to pin down an exact catalyst of the spike. However, the price jump seems to have come after Shiba Inu&#8217;s developers announced the release of a testnet bridge between Shibarium and Ethereum.</p>
<h2>Shibarium to Ethereum Testnet Bridge Pushes SHIB&#8217;s Price by 5%</h2>
<p>Shiba Inu has come a long way since its creation as a meme coin made just to challenge the popular Dogecoin (DOGE). However, the Shiba Inu ecosystem now has a lot of following, investors, developers, and an active community. </p>
<p>Shiba Inu developers are now working on a Layer-2 upgrade with the aim of developing the ecosystem and becoming a serious blockchain contender. The network, which will operate on top of Ethereum, is called <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/shibarium-bridge-goes-live-in-beta-but-theres-a-catch/?swcfpc=1">Shibarium</a> and was announced earlier in March. When Shibarium is launched, it is expected to help minimize costs and increase transaction speeds.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en"><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f525.png" alt="🔥" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> Shibarium Beta Bridge has gone live for public testing! <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f389.png" alt="🎉" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /></p>
<p>Be among the first to try out this revolutionary cross-chain solution.</p>
<p>Remember, always exercise caution and verify authenticity before connecting your wallet to any website.</p>
<p>PLEASE DO NOT USE YOUR REAL ASSETS!… <a href="https://t.co/7yfhX8gQc6" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/7yfhX8gQc6</a></p>
<p>— 𝐋𝐔𝐂𝐈𝐄 (@LucieSHIB) <a href="https://twitter.com/LucieSHIB/status/1684252125704880131?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">July 26, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p>On July 28, SHIB devs began testing a bridge that allows tokens to be easily transferred between the Shibarium and Ethereum. The testnet release is an important step toward making Shibarium a reality. This cross-chain solution seems to have sparked the interest of SHIB investors, as the price of the token spiked in the hours after. </p>

How High Can The Price Go?
<p>Shiba Inu is the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/shiba-inu-will-this-bullish-formation-lead-to-a-25-upsurge/?swcfpc=1">second-largest meme coin in terms of market cap</a>. Although the price is now nearly 80% from its all-time high in October 2021, current upgrades show momentum seems to be turning positive. </p>
<p>The coming months and the progress of the Shibarium Layer-2 will be crucial in determining whether Shiba Inu can build on this momentum to retest previous highs or whether it continues to plateau. </p>
<p>At the time of writing, SHIB is trading at $0.000008191.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/erjzVWBN/" alt="Shiba Inu (SHIB) price chart from Tradingview.com" width="2884" height="1746"/></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/iStock-1353098980-1-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>This Machine Learning Tool Was Asked To Predict XRP Price, Here’s What It Said</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/ai-tool-was-asked-to-predict-xrp-price/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 13:00:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrp]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrpusdt]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=544992</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[XRP has been one of the trending tokens following the summary judgment which ruled that the token was not a security, giving its parent company, Ripple, a ‘partial victory’ over the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). That event saw XRP’s price soar to about $0.93.  However, XRP’s price seems to have cooled off, settling at the $0.7 price mark. Despite this, there still seems to be bullish sentiment around XRP’s future price, which is why this Machine Learning tool was consulted to predict XRP’s price.  Here’s What It Said PricePredictions.com, a site powered by an advanced machine learning algorithm that provides current and futuristic trends about several tokens, was consulted in a bid to get an insight into XRP’s future price and to better position themselves in case of a rally by the token. Related Reading: Ripple Attorney Withdraws From SEC Lawsuit, Will It Affect XRP? According to XRP’s futuristic price action, the AI tool forecasts that there will be an upward trend that will see XRP gain about 1.5% in value from its current price of $0.7. It has also been projected that XRP will hit the price mark of $0.71 by August 26, 2023. For insight into how the machine learning tool works, the algorithm analyzes current technical analysis (TA) indicators, like moving average convergence divergence (MACD), average true range (ATR), relative strength index (RSI), and Bollinger Bands (BB) to come up with a logical price forecast. XRP price trending at $0.7 &#124; Source: XRPUSD on Tradingview.com XRP Has Come A Long Way Ripple Lab’s aforementioned victory over the SEC undoubtedly sparked significant interest in XRP, especially from institutional investors, seeing the token rise above Circle’s USDC and Binance’s BNB to become the fourth-largest cryptocurrency by market cap. This took XRP&#8217;s market capitalization to a yearly high of $46.1 billion at the time of the ruling that it wasn’t a security (XRP’s market currently stands at around $37 billion according to data from CoinMarketCap). Related Reading: Bitcoin Whales Make Alarming Deposits To Exchanges Amid Falling Prices XRP also became the most actively traded altcoin in 2023. The token accumulated over $1 billion in trading volume, outperforming other altcoins like BNB, SOL, MATIC, and DOGE. Although XRP is still far below its all-time high of $3.84 in 2018, it has undoubtedly had an impressive market trend lately, and it is projected that many more users will continue to pick an interest in the token and ultimately promote wider adoption. Featured image from iStock, chart from Tradingview.com  ]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>XRP has been one of the trending tokens following the summary judgment which ruled that the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/ripple-attorney-withdraws-from-sec-lawsuit/?swcfpc=1">token was not a security</a>, giving its parent company, Ripple, a ‘partial victory’ over the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). That event saw XRP’s price soar to about $0.93. </p>
<p>However, XRP’s price seems to have cooled off, settling at the $0.7 price mark. Despite this, there still seems to be bullish sentiment around XRP’s future price, which is why this Machine Learning tool was consulted to predict XRP’s price. </p>
<h2>Here’s What It Said</h2>
<p>PricePredictions.com, a site powered by an advanced machine learning algorithm that provides current and futuristic trends about several tokens, was consulted in a bid to get an insight into XRP’s future price and to better position themselves in case of a rally by the token.</p>

<p>According to XRP’s futuristic price action, the AI tool <a href="https://pricepredictions.com/forecast/xrp" rel="nofollow">forecasts</a> that there will be an upward trend that will see XRP gain about 1.5% in value from its current price of $0.7. It has also been projected that XRP will hit the price mark of $0.71 by August 26, 2023.</p>
<p>For insight into how the machine learning tool works, the algorithm analyzes current technical analysis (TA) indicators, like moving average convergence divergence (MACD), average true range (ATR), relative strength index (RSI), and Bollinger Bands (BB) to come up with a logical price forecast.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/bgLGi3Yf/" alt="Ripple (XRP) price chart from Tradingview.com" width="2884" height="1746"/></p>

<h2>XRP Has Come A Long Way</h2>
<p>Ripple Lab’s aforementioned victory over the SEC undoubtedly sparked significant interest in XRP, especially from institutional investors, seeing the token rise above Circle’s USDC and Binance’s BNB to become the fourth-largest cryptocurrency by market cap. </p>
<p>This took XRP&#8217;s market capitalization to a yearly high of $46.1 billion at the time of the ruling that it wasn’t a security (XRP’s market currently stands at around $37 billion according to data from <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/xrp/" rel="nofollow">CoinMarketCap</a>).</p>

<p>XRP also became the most actively traded altcoin in 2023. The token accumulated over $1 billion in trading volume, outperforming other altcoins like BNB, SOL, MATIC, and DOGE.</p>
<p>Although XRP is still far below its all-time high of $3.84 in 2018, it has undoubtedly had an impressive market trend lately, and it is projected that many more users will continue to pick an interest in the token and ultimately promote wider adoption.</p>

<p> </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/iStock-1363462648-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tether (USDT) Market Cap Reaches New Peak, Edges Toward $84 Billion Mark</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/stablecoin/tether-usdt-market-cap-reaches-new-peak-edges-toward-84-billion-mark/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Semilore Faleti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 09:40:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Stablecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DeFi Stablecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[stablecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=544967</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Tether USDT has seen its market cap value reach new highs in the month of July. According to a report by on-chain analytics company Into The Block, the world’s largest stablecoin is steadily approaching the key $84 billion mark. Based on data from DeFiLlama, USDT’s market cap is up by over $480 million since the beginning of July, indicating an increasing level of adoption. Generally, the stablecoin’s total market share value has been on the rise for the majority of 2023, moving from $66.23 billion on January 1 to its current value of $83.80 billion. In tandem with USDT’s market cap growth, Into The Block also noted the token’s circulating supply is up by almost 30% year to date. Interestingly, USDT’s market growth has also been reflected in its operator&#8217;s development.  Back in May, Tether Holdings Ltd published its quarterly assurance report announcing a net profit of $1.48 billion for Q1 2023, bringing its excess reserve to an all-time high of $2.44 billion.  Into The Block noted that currently, Tether is well on course to surpass those profit levels in Q2 and Q3 as there is an increase in the amount of USDT being issued. Related Reading: Stablecoins Volume Down Despite Crypto Market Recovery, Ratings Agency Finds Tether (USDT) Increasing Stablecoin Dominance In 2023 The general stablecoin market has recorded a major decline in 2023, losing over $12.17 billion since the start of the year. However, during this period,  USDT has been waxing strong, accumulating over about $17 billion in market cap. According to data from DeFiILama, Tether’s market dominance has grown by about 19% in 2023, as the token now accounts for two-thirds of the stablecoin market.  While this development is mainly driven by USDT’s impressive performance, there has also been a notable decline in the market shares of some other prominent stablecoins. &#160; Source: DeFilLama For example, Circle’s USD Coin (USDC), which ranks as the second-largest stablecoin, has seen its market cap fall by a staggering 40% in 2023, with the current value now set at $26.26 billion. Meanwhile, Binance USD (BUSD), with a market cap of $3.71 billion, has shed over 77% of its market shares following an embargo on its issuance earlier this year.  At the time of writing, Tether&#8217;s value remains pegged at $1. With a market cap of 83.80 billion, the stablecoin ranks as the third biggest cryptocurrency falling Bitcoin (BTC) and Ethereum (ETH) Tether (USDT) rising market cap in 2023 &#124; Source: USDT Market Cap Daily Chart On Tradingview.com Related Reading: Tether CTO Paulo Adoino Explains 1 Billion USDT Issuance DeFi Stablecoins Gearing Up To Match Centralized Counterparts In other news, DeFi stablecoins have been rolling out some impressive upgrades as they attempt to close the gap between them and their centralized competitors. In a tweet on Friday, Into The Block highlighted some of these developments. Firstly, the MakerDAO recently hiked the DAI Savings Rate (DSR) to 3.49%, and there is the possibility of an increase to 8% in the coming weeks. Furthermore, the Frax protocol will be launching FRAX v3 in August as they look to make FRAX a fully algorithmic token, delinking its minting process from the USDC token. In addition, there is Lybra Finance which lends its stablecoin eUSD to users at an interest rate of 0%. Other DeFi stablecoins with impressive features or upgrades include Curve Finance’s crvUSD and Aave’s GHO.  Featured Image From Barron, Chart From Tradingview]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Tether USDT has seen its market cap value reach new highs in the month of July. According to a <a href="https://twitter.com/intotheblock/status/1684941911067357186?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">report</a> by on-chain analytics company Into The Block, the world’s largest stablecoin is steadily approaching the key $84 billion mark.</p>
<p>Based on <a href="https://defillama.com/stablecoin/tether" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">data from DeFiLlama,</a> USDT’s market cap is up by over $480 million since the beginning of July, indicating an increasing level of adoption. Generally, the stablecoin’s total market share value has been on the rise for the majority of 2023, moving from $66.23 billion on January 1 to its current value of $83.80 billion.</p>
<p>In tandem with USDT’s market cap growth, Into The Block also noted the token’s circulating supply is up by almost 30% year to date. Interestingly, USDT’s market growth has also been reflected in its operator&#8217;s development. </p>
<p>Back in May, Tether Holdings Ltd<a href="https://tether.to/en/tethers-latest-q1-2023-assurance-report-shows-reserves-surplus-at-all-time-high-of-244b-up-148b-in-net-profit-new-categories-for-additional-transparency-reveals-bitcoin-and-gold-allocations/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow"> published</a> its quarterly assurance report announcing a net profit of $1.48 billion for Q1 2023, bringing its excess reserve to an all-time high of $2.44 billion. </p>
<p>Into The Block <a href="https://twitter.com/intotheblock/status/1684911713370451968?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">noted</a> that currently, Tether is well on course to surpass those profit levels in Q2 and Q3 as there is an increase in the amount of USDT being issued.</p>

<h2><strong>Tether (USDT) Increasing Stablecoin Dominance In 2023</strong></h2>
<p>The general stablecoin market has recorded a major decline in 2023, losing over $12.17 billion since the start of the year. However, during this period,  USDT has been waxing strong, accumulating over about $17 billion in market cap.</p>
<p>According to <a href="https://defillama.com/stablecoins" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">data from DeFiILama,</a> Tether’s market dominance has grown by about 19% in 2023, as the token now accounts for two-thirds of the stablecoin market. </p>
<p style="text-align: left">While this development is mainly driven by USDT’s impressive performance, there has also been a notable decline in the market shares of some other prominent stablecoins.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>

<p>For example, Circle’s USD Coin (USDC), which ranks as the second-largest stablecoin, has seen its market cap fall by a staggering 40% in 2023, with the current value now set at $26.26 billion. </p>
<p>Meanwhile, Binance USD (BUSD), with a market cap of $3.71 billion, has shed over 77% of its market shares following an embargo on its issuance earlier this year. </p>
<p>At the time of writing, Tether&#8217;s value remains pegged at $1. With a market cap of 83.80 billion, the stablecoin ranks as the third biggest cryptocurrency falling Bitcoin (BTC) and Ethereum (ETH)</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/aoM9O5eq/" alt="Tether" width="1480" height="913"/></p>


<h2><strong>DeFi Stablecoins Gearing Up To Match Centralized Counterparts</strong></h2>
<p>In other news, DeFi stablecoins have been rolling out some impressive upgrades as they attempt to close the gap between them and their centralized competitors. In a <a href="https://twitter.com/intotheblock/status/1684987225560231937?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">tweet</a> on Friday, Into The Block highlighted some of these developments.</p>
<p>Firstly, the MakerDAO recently hiked the DAI Savings Rate (DSR) to 3.49%, and there is the possibility of an increase to 8% in the coming weeks. Furthermore, the Frax protocol will be launching FRAX v3 in August as they look to make FRAX a fully algorithmic token, delinking its minting process from the USDC token.</p>
<p>In addition, there is Lybra Finance which lends its stablecoin eUSD to users at an interest rate of 0%. Other DeFi stablecoins with impressive features or upgrades include Curve Finance’s crvUSD and Aave’s GHO. </p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/im-403756-460x345.jpeg" width="460" height="345" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>AI Tokens Record Lowest Weekly Volume Since January &#8211; A Sign Of Waning Interest?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/altcoin/ai-tokens-record-lowest-weekly-trading-volume-since-january-a-sign-of-waning-interest/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Opeyemi Sule]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 09:09:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AI crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AI Tokens]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[GRT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[OpenAI]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[WorldCoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=544965</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[AI (artificial intelligence) tokens were one of the most promising assets in the cryptocurrency market at the beginning of 2023. One of the major drivers of this was the launch of ChatGPT &#8211; an AI-based chatbot &#8211; in late 2022, which propelled some AI-related cryptocurrencies to substantial gains. However, the interest in this set of cryptocurrencies appears to be cooling, with data research firm Kaiko revealing a significant decline in trading activity for the AI-related tokens. Related Reading: Traders’ Interest In XRP Remains Solid Despite Price Retreat, Data Shows Lowest Weekly Trading Volume For AI Tokens AI-related tokens registered their lowest weekly trading volume since January 2023, according to a recent data report from Kaiko. In this report, the research platform looked at the trading volume of six of the top seven AI tokens, including FET, INJ, ROSE, AGIX, RNDR, and GRT. Source: Kaiko/Twitter This notable decrease in trading activity suggests a decline in attention from investors since the AI token frenzy peaked in January. And this appears to be reflected in the price performances of many AI-related cryptocurrencies. The Graph (GRT), the largest AI token in the market, was one of the top gainers at the start of 2023, surging by roughly 122% to reach a yearly high of $0.2323 on February 7. However, the price of the GRT token has since plummeted, with a 51% decline from the 2023 peak. Can ChatGPT &#38; OpenAI Do It Again? As mentioned earlier, the surge of interest in AI tokens was partly driven by the launch of ChatGPT. However, there has not been a similar effect on the AI and big-data crypto economy following the launch of Sam Altman’s Worldcoin project and WLD token. On July 24, 2023, Altman, the CEO of OpenAI &#8211; the artificial intelligence company behind ChatGPT &#8211; rolled out his crypto product, releasing the World ID development kit and the WLD token.  The WLD token soared more than 85% to reach an all-time high of $3.3 on the day of launch, according to CoinGecko data. However, the cryptocurrency’s price has declined by over 31% since hitting this peak. Related Reading: Why Worldcoin (WLD) And PEPE Dominate The Crypto Market Trends This Week Although there has been enthusiasm around the launch of Worldcoin, the project &#8211; especially its technology &#8211; has also been met with some skepticism. Notably, Ethereum co-founder Vitalik Buterin voiced his concern over the project’s iris-scanning hardware and biometric data collection practices. Meanwhile, Worldcoin looks set to face some regulatory scrutiny, with the UK’s data regulator Information Commissioner Office (ICO) already making inquiries. France’s privacy regulator CNIL has also questioned the legality of the project’s biometric data collection. While the Worldcoin project and the WLD token seem to be gaining some traction at the moment, it remains to be seen how they will impact the AI and big-data crypto economy. As of this writing, the WLD token changes hand at $2.27, with a 6.8% price increase in the past day. WLDUSD trading at $2.262 &#124; Source: daily WLDUSD chart from TradingView &#160; Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>AI (artificial intelligence) tokens were one of the most promising assets in the cryptocurrency market at the beginning of 2023. One of the major drivers of this was the launch of ChatGPT &#8211; an AI-based chatbot &#8211; in late 2022, which propelled some AI-related cryptocurrencies to substantial gains.</p>
<p>However, the interest in this set of cryptocurrencies appears to be cooling, with data research firm Kaiko revealing a significant decline in trading activity for the AI-related tokens.</p>

<h2><strong>Lowest Weekly Trading Volume For AI Tokens</strong></h2>
<p>AI-related tokens registered their lowest weekly trading volume since January 2023, according to a recent <a href="https://twitter.com/kaikodata/status/1684528478295654402?s=46&amp;t=A3BHEABYQUOwmN2Zphb4ng" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">data report from Kaiko</a>. In this report, the research platform looked at the trading volume of six of the top seven AI tokens, including FET, INJ, ROSE, AGIX, RNDR, and GRT.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-544968 size-medium" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/photo_2023-07-29_08-39-51-460x262.jpg" alt="AI Tokens" width="460" height="262" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/photo_2023-07-29_08-39-51-460x262.jpg 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/photo_2023-07-29_08-39-51-860x489.jpg 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/photo_2023-07-29_08-39-51-768x437.jpg 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/photo_2023-07-29_08-39-51-750x427.jpg 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/photo_2023-07-29_08-39-51-1140x648.jpg 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/photo_2023-07-29_08-39-51.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px"/></p>

<p>This notable decrease in trading activity suggests a decline in attention from investors since the AI token frenzy peaked in January. And this appears to be reflected in the price performances of many AI-related cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p>The Graph (GRT), the largest AI token in the market, was one of the top gainers at the start of 2023, surging by roughly 122% to reach a yearly high of $0.2323 on February 7. However, the price of the GRT token has since plummeted, with a 51% decline from the 2023 peak.</p>
<h2><strong>Can ChatGPT &amp; OpenAI Do It Again?</strong></h2>
<p>As mentioned earlier, the surge of interest in AI tokens was partly driven by the launch of ChatGPT. However, there has not been a similar effect on the AI and big-data crypto economy following the launch of Sam Altman’s Worldcoin project and WLD token.</p>
<p>On July 24, 2023, Altman, the CEO of OpenAI &#8211; the artificial intelligence company behind ChatGPT &#8211; rolled out his crypto product, releasing the World ID development kit and the WLD token. </p>
<p>The WLD token soared more than 85% to reach an all-time high of $3.3 on the day of launch, according to <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/worldcoin" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">CoinGecko data</a>. However, the cryptocurrency’s price has declined by over 31% since hitting this peak.</p>

<p>Although there has been enthusiasm around the launch of Worldcoin, the project &#8211; especially its technology &#8211; has also been met with some skepticism. Notably, Ethereum co-founder Vitalik Buterin voiced his concern over the project’s iris-scanning hardware and biometric data collection practices.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, Worldcoin looks set to face some regulatory scrutiny, with the UK’s data regulator Information Commissioner Office (ICO) already making inquiries. France’s privacy regulator CNIL has also <a href="https://www.reuters.com/technology/frances-privacy-watchdog-says-worldcoin-legality-seems-questionable-2023-07-28/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">questioned the legality</a> of the project’s biometric data collection.</p>
<p>While the Worldcoin project and the WLD token seem to be gaining some traction at the moment, it remains to be seen how they will impact the AI and big-data crypto economy. As of this writing, the WLD token changes hand at $2.27, with a 6.8% price increase in the past day.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/wDEXED74/" alt="AI Tokens" width="997" height="586"/></p>

<p>&nbsp;</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/istockphoto-1344769416-612x612-1-460x376.jpg" width="460" height="376" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>CryptoPunks Toughness Tested As NFT Succumbs To 60% Drop In 1 Week</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/cryptopunks-toughness-tested-as-nft-succumbs-to-60-drop-in-1-week/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 08:32:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=544962</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Non-fungible tokens continue to play a significant role in developing the Web3 ecosystem, despite the enthusiasm around them having subsided since its peak in 2021. Unquestionably, these distinctive digital assets have been a significant force behind the NFT transformations that have taken place. Despite the wide variety of NFT collections and their accomplishments, it is crucial to recognize that some particular ones have recently been severely affected by market pressures and are now beginning to fall from their lofty positions. Consider the situation with CryptoPunks. CoinGecko discovered that of the top 11 &#8220;blue chip&#8221; NFT projects studied, CryptoPunks suffered the worst losses. Non-fungible tokens known as &#8220;blue chip NFTs&#8221; are regarded as highly precious and prestigious in digital assets. These NFTs are frequently linked to well-known and recognized producers or organizations, such as renowned artists, enduring businesses, or essential historical items. Source: CoinGecko Collectors and investors widely seek after them due to scarcity, historical relevance, and the artist&#8217;s reputation that determine their value. Alarming statistics currently facing CryptoPunks are raising questions among NFT enthusiasts. These formerly well-liked digital assets have recently encountered a worrying situation, sparking disputes and disagreements among investors and fans. Related Reading: Traders’ Interest In XRP Remains Solid Despite Price Retreat, Data Shows Source: NFT Floor Price At the time of writing, the floor price for these NFT collections was set at 47.69 ETH. Data from NFT Floor Price shows that the collection&#8217;s value declined after reaching a high of 11,000ETH during the 2021 NFT bull market. The volume and sales of CryptoPunks have significantly decreased during the past seven days, claims OpenSea. Sales were down 60%, while volume dropped sharply by 64%. Bitcoin slightly above the  $29K level. Chart: TradingView.com Due to their distinctiveness and variable rarity, CryptoPunks, developed by Larva Labs in 2017 and helped increase generative PFP collections, are still incredibly sought-after NFTs. CryptoPunks, regarded as art and collectibles, have generated respectable profits for their owners. CryptoPunk #5822, which sold for $23 million in February last year, was the most expensive ever. Related Reading: Dogecoin Ascendance: How It Captured PEPE Investors’ Attention Now, in terms of the number of unique active wallets, CryptoPunks has seen a depressing reduction of about 20%, and transactions have also suffered, losing more than 32% of their values. Meanwhile, CryptoPunks&#8217; monthly sales volume is also feeling the heat, declining precipitously since March. The NFT initiative reported sales of $30.43 million for the month, but by the end of June, those figures had substantially dropped to less than $10 million. (This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk). Featured image from Reuters]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Non-fungible tokens continue to play a significant role in developing the Web3 ecosystem, despite the enthusiasm around them having subsided since its peak in 2021.</p>
<p>Unquestionably, these distinctive digital assets have been a significant force behind the NFT transformations that have taken place. Despite the wide variety of NFT collections and their accomplishments, it is crucial to recognize that some particular ones have recently been severely affected by market pressures and are now beginning to fall from their lofty positions.</p>
<p>Consider the situation with <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">CryptoPunks</a>. CoinGecko discovered that of the top 11 &#8220;blue chip&#8221; NFT projects studied, CryptoPunks suffered the worst losses.</p>
<p>Non-fungible tokens known as &#8220;blue chip NFTs&#8221; are regarded as highly precious and prestigious in digital assets. These NFTs are frequently linked to well-known and recognized producers or organizations, such as renowned artists, enduring businesses, or essential historical items.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-544971" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-183.png" alt="" width="619" height="738" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-183.png 619w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-183-386x460.png 386w" sizes="(max-width: 619px) 100vw, 619px"/></p>

<p>Collectors and investors widely seek after them due to scarcity, historical relevance, and the artist&#8217;s reputation that determine their value.</p>
<p>Alarming statistics currently facing CryptoPunks are raising questions among NFT enthusiasts. These formerly well-liked digital assets have recently encountered a worrying situation, sparking disputes and disagreements among investors and fans.</p>

<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-544984 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-185-860x439.png" alt="" width="860" height="439" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-185-860x439.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-185-460x235.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-185-768x392.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-185-750x383.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-185.png 975w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/></p>

<p>At the time of writing, the floor price for these NFT collections was set at 47.69 ETH. Data from NFT Floor Price shows that the collection&#8217;s value declined after reaching a high of 11,000ETH during the 2021 NFT bull market.</p>
<p>The volume and sales of CryptoPunks have significantly decreased during the past seven days, claims OpenSea. Sales were down 60%, while volume dropped sharply by 64%.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/WglRFUV3/" width="2475" height="1187"/></p>

<p>Due to their distinctiveness and variable rarity, CryptoPunks, developed by Larva Labs in 2017 and helped increase generative PFP collections, are still incredibly sought-after NFTs.</p>
<p>CryptoPunks, regarded as art and collectibles, have generated respectable profits for their owners. CryptoPunk #5822, which sold for $23 million in February last year, was the most expensive ever.</p>

<p>Now, in terms of the number of unique active wallets, CryptoPunks has seen a depressing reduction of about 20%, and transactions have also suffered, losing more than 32% of their values.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, CryptoPunks&#8217; monthly sales volume is also feeling the heat, declining precipitously since March. The NFT initiative reported sales of $30.43 million for the month, but by the end of June, those figures had substantially dropped to less than $10 million.</p>
<p><em>(This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk).</em></p>
<p><em>Featured image from Reuters</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-184-460x306.png" width="460" height="306" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Traders’ Interest In XRP Remains Solid Despite Price Retreat, Data Shows</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/interest-in-xrp-remains-solid/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 06:05:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC VS Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrp]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=544943</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The enduring allure of XRP, despite market volatility, may be evidence of its continued relevance, as it has continued to attract the interest of traders and investors equally. Even as the dust settles after Ripple&#8217;s recent victory jubilation, the cryptocurrency market remains keen on XRP. Kaiko, a provider of market data on digital assets, reports that the open interest ratio on XRP futures trades on prominent exchanges remains quite impressive. Recently, the crypto market has experienced a pervasive price reversal. Despite the pullbacks, traders&#8217; interest in the Ripple cryptocurrency remained remarkably high, according to Kaiko. At the time of writing, XRP was in the red in all timeframes, trading at $$0.712, down a measly 0.02% in the last 24 hours, and a considerable 8.4% in the last seven days, data from crypto market tracker Coingecko shows. Given these numbers, XRP is still able to shine in another key department. XRP in crimson in all timeframes during the weekend. Source: Coingecko XRP Community Remains Upbeat About The Crypto Kaiko shows that across numerous markets, XRP&#8217;s volume-to-open interest ratio is consistently higher than the median value. This reliability suggests that the XRP coin is actively traded in a healthy market. This percentage is significantly greater than the market average, indicating strong liquidity and sustained interest from traders and investors. On prominent exchanges, the volume-to-open-interest ratio is also used to measure trading activity. When the interest metric is high, it indicates that more purchasers and sellers are willing to trade the token, which indicates speculative interest. A favorable volume-to-open interest ratio could be a signal for market participants to trade in such a token. Related Reading: Dogecoin Ascendance: How It Captured PEPE Investors’ Attention Ripple&#8217;s popularity on social media, as assessed by Santiment, has increased dramatically over the previous two months, reflecting the excitement surrounding the cryptocurrency. Its social dominance increased dramatically in late May and early June, peaking at over 4%. Source: Santiment Ripple had just roughly 2% of the social market share at the time this story was published. Despite the fact that this number may appear tiny, it demonstrates that the cryptocurrency has a significant presence and impact in the crypto community as a whole. Despite the fact that Ripple appears to be a minor topic of discussion, it has managed to stand out as a formidable contender, attracting the attention of enthusiasts and experts alike and causing them to discuss it. XRP market cap currently at $37 billion. Chart: TradingView.com In the ever-evolving world of cryptocurrencies, where numerous digital assets vie for attention and recognition, Ripple carved out a useful niche for itself, influencing discussions about blockchain technology and financial innovation. Strong Social Footprint Even though Ripple must contend with other well-known cryptocurrencies, the fact that it has maintained a strong social presence indicates that it has a large number of supporters and investors. Related Reading: Is Arbitrum Promise Fading? Downtime, Metrics Decline Raise ARB Price Alarms Meanwhile, the loss of nearly 10% of XRP&#8217;s value over the past week appeared insignificant to some speculators. Based on figures from Santiment, the funding rate for cryptocurrencies was 0.1%. A positive reading of the funding rate indicated favorable sentiment on average. (This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk). Featured image from Times Tabloid]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The enduring allure of XRP, despite market volatility, may be evidence of its continued relevance, as it has continued to attract the interest of traders and investors equally.</p>
<p>Even as the dust settles after Ripple&#8217;s recent victory jubilation, the cryptocurrency market remains keen on XRP. Kaiko, a provider of market data on digital assets, reports that the open interest ratio on XRP futures trades on prominent exchanges remains quite impressive.</p>
<p>Recently, the crypto market has experienced a pervasive price reversal. Despite the pullbacks, traders&#8217; interest in the Ripple cryptocurrency remained remarkably high, according to Kaiko.</p>
<p>At the time of writing, XRP was in the red in all timeframes, <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">trading at $$0.712</a>, down a measly 0.02% in the last 24 hours, and a considerable 8.4% in the last seven days, data from crypto market tracker Coingecko shows. Given these numbers, XRP is still able to shine in another key department.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-544946" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRP-3.png" alt="" width="989" height="65" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRP-3.png 989w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRP-3-460x30.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRP-3-860x57.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRP-3-768x50.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRP-3-750x49.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 989px) 100vw, 989px"/></p>

<h2><strong>XRP Community Remains Upbeat About The Crypto</strong></h2>
<p>Kaiko shows that across numerous markets, XRP&#8217;s <a href="https://twitter.com/KaikoData/status/1684529048754573313/photo/1" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">volume-to-open interest ratio</a> is consistently higher than the median value. This reliability suggests that the XRP coin is actively traded in a healthy market. This percentage is significantly greater than the market average, indicating strong liquidity and sustained interest from traders and investors.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-544948 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-178-860x449.png" alt="" width="860" height="449" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-178-860x449.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-178-460x240.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-178-768x401.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-178-1536x802.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-178-750x392.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-178-1140x596.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-178.png 1587w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/>On prominent exchanges, the volume-to-open-interest ratio is also used to measure trading activity. When the interest metric is high, it indicates that more purchasers and sellers are willing to trade the token, which indicates speculative interest. A favorable volume-to-open interest ratio could be a signal for market participants to trade in such a token.</p>

<p>Ripple&#8217;s <a href="https://statics.ambcrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRP-XRP-10.38.38-26-Jul-2023.png" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">popularity on social media,</a> as assessed by Santiment, has increased dramatically over the previous two months, reflecting the excitement surrounding the cryptocurrency. Its social dominance increased dramatically in late May and early June, peaking at over 4%.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-544950 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-179-860x294.png" alt="" width="860" height="294" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-179-860x294.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-179-460x157.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-179-768x262.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-179-1536x525.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-179-750x256.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-179-1140x390.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-179.png 1542w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/></p>

<p>Ripple had just roughly 2% of the social market share at the time this story was published. Despite the fact that this number may appear tiny, it demonstrates that the cryptocurrency has a significant presence and impact in the crypto community as a whole.</p>
<p>Despite the fact that Ripple appears to be a minor topic of discussion, it has managed to stand out as a formidable contender, attracting the attention of enthusiasts and experts alike and causing them to discuss it.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/QPFRGlWM/" width="2475" height="1187"/></p>

<p>In the ever-evolving world of cryptocurrencies, where numerous digital assets vie for attention and recognition, Ripple carved out a useful niche for itself, influencing discussions about blockchain technology and financial innovation.</p>
<h2><strong>Strong Social Footprint</strong></h2>
<p>Even though Ripple must contend with other well-known cryptocurrencies, the fact that it has maintained a strong social presence indicates that it has a large number of supporters and investors.</p>

<p>Meanwhile, the loss of nearly 10% of XRP&#8217;s value over the past week appeared insignificant to some speculators. Based on figures from Santiment, the funding rate for cryptocurrencies was 0.1%. A positive reading of the funding rate indicated favorable sentiment on average.</p>
<p><em>(This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk).</em></p>
<p><em>Featured image from Times Tabloid</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-182-460x303.png" width="460" height="303" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Casper (CSPR) Spikes 15% Following Key Partnership &#8211; What&#8217;s Next?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/casper-cspr-spikes-15-following-key-partnership-whats-next/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Olowoporoku Adeniyi]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 03:26:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Casper]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Casper Network]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CSPR Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=544936</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Casper (CSPR) has been making significant strides in the cryptocurrency market, attracting attention with its aim to accelerate enterprise and developer adoption of blockchain technology. As a live proof-of-stake blockchain built off the Casper CBC specification, Casper offers unique features and growth potential, drawing interest from investors and enthusiasts alike. In the past week, there has been a significant upturn in its on-chain volume. Casper has experienced a substantial price surge in the past 24 hours, with its value increasing by 4.62%. This surge has created excitement among investors, especially as the cryptocurrency has displayed steady growth over the past 7 days, gaining an impressive 14.58%. The positive price movement has generated enthusiasm and optimism among Casper investors, who are pleased with their returns during this period. As of the latest data, Casper (CSPR) is ranked 84th among all cryptocurrencies, with a current price of $0.04035. The circulating supply of Casper stands at 11,202,499,993, contributing to a total market capitalization of $456,309,769. The cryptocurrency&#8217;s recent performance has been particularly noteworthy, showcasing impressive short- and long-term growth. Collaboration With INX Boosts Market Sentiment A contributing factor to Casper&#8217;s recent growth can be attributed to its strategic partnership with INX, a United States-regulated broker-dealer. Casper&#8217;s equity was tokenized and listed through this collaboration, enhancing investor confidence and further supporting the cryptocurrency&#8217;s upward trajectory. This strategic move has enabled Casper to tap into new markets and expand its reach to a broader audience. Related Reading: Cardano (ADA) Price Remains Muted Despite Significant Milestones, Why? Casper&#8217;s price surge aligns with the optimistic market sentiment toward cryptocurrencies. The growing interest from institutional investors and the increasing mainstream adoption of digital assets has instilled confidence in crypto. Additionally, influential figures within the blockchain industry have shared positive views on cryptocurrencies, including Casper, contributing to the overall positive outlook. Casper (CSPR) Price Analysis Casper has experienced a consistent upward trend in July after it bottomed at $0.0365. Since then, its price has increased by 30% and has hit heights of $0.0405. This positive trend is likely to continue in the coming weeks with more developments expected to be deployed on Casper. From a technical analysis standpoint, Casper exhibits promising signals. The daily chart reveals the formation of a bullish falling wedge pattern, indicating a potential trend reversal. CSPR has also surpassed the 25-day exponential moving average and is currently testing the 50-day MA. If the bullish trend continues the next resistance point is $0.40 while a bearish downturn will see the support at $0.0397. Related Reading: Why Worldcoin (WLD) And PEPE Dominate The Crypto Market Trends This Week As Casper continues to gain visibility and traction in the market, its future growth potential remains promising. The cryptocurrency&#8217;s underlying technology, including its proof-of-stake consensus mechanism, offers scalability, security, and energy efficiency. These features position Casper as an attractive enterprise adoption and long-term development candidate.  (This site’s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk). Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Casper (CSPR) has been making significant strides in the cryptocurrency market, attracting attention with its aim to accelerate enterprise and developer adoption of blockchain technology. As a live <a href="https://www.investopedia.com/terms/p/proof-stake-pos.asp" rel="nofollow">proof-of-stake</a> blockchain built off the Casper CBC specification, Casper offers unique features and growth potential, drawing interest from investors and enthusiasts alike. </p>
<p>In the past week, there has been a significant upturn in its on-chain volume. Casper has experienced a substantial price surge in the past 24 hours, with its value increasing by 4.62%. This surge has created excitement among investors, especially as the cryptocurrency has displayed steady growth over the past 7 days, gaining an impressive 14.58%. The positive price movement has generated enthusiasm and optimism among Casper investors, who are pleased with their returns during this period.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-544937 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/CSPRUSDT_2023-07-29_02-30-27-860x406.png" alt="Casper (CSPR) price has spiked in the past few days: Source @Tradingview" width="860" height="406" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/CSPRUSDT_2023-07-29_02-30-27-860x406.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/CSPRUSDT_2023-07-29_02-30-27-460x217.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/CSPRUSDT_2023-07-29_02-30-27-768x363.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/CSPRUSDT_2023-07-29_02-30-27-1536x726.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/CSPRUSDT_2023-07-29_02-30-27-750x354.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/CSPRUSDT_2023-07-29_02-30-27-1140x539.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/CSPRUSDT_2023-07-29_02-30-27.png 1835w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/>
<p>As of the latest data, Casper (CSPR) is ranked 84th among all cryptocurrencies, with a current price of $0.04035. The circulating supply of Casper stands at 11,202,499,993, contributing to a total market capitalization of $456,309,769. The cryptocurrency&#8217;s recent performance has been particularly noteworthy, showcasing impressive short- and long-term growth.</p>
<h2><strong>Collaboration With INX Boosts Market Sentiment</strong></h2>
<p>A contributing factor to Casper&#8217;s recent growth can be attributed to its strategic partnership with <a href="https://www.inx.co/" rel="nofollow">INX</a>, a United States-regulated broker-dealer. Casper&#8217;s equity was tokenized and listed through this collaboration, enhancing investor confidence and further supporting the cryptocurrency&#8217;s upward trajectory. This strategic move has enabled Casper to tap into new markets and expand its reach to a broader audience.</p>
<p><strong>Related Reading</strong>: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/cardano/cardano-ada-price-remains-muted-despite-significant-milestones-why/?swcfpc=1">Cardano (ADA) Price Remains Muted Despite Significant Milestones, Why?</a></p>
<p>Casper&#8217;s price surge aligns with the optimistic market sentiment toward cryptocurrencies. The growing interest from institutional investors and the increasing mainstream adoption of digital assets has instilled confidence in crypto. Additionally, influential figures within the blockchain industry have shared positive views on cryptocurrencies, including Casper, contributing to the overall positive outlook.</p>
<h2><strong>Casper (CSPR) Price Analysis</strong> </h2>
<p>Casper has experienced a consistent upward trend in July after it bottomed at $0.0365. Since then, its price has increased by 30% and has hit heights of $0.0405. This positive trend is likely to continue in the coming weeks with more developments expected to be deployed on Casper.</p>
<p>From a technical analysis standpoint, Casper exhibits promising signals. The daily chart reveals the formation of a bullish falling wedge pattern, indicating a potential trend reversal.
CSPR has also surpassed the 25-day exponential moving average and is currently testing the 50-day MA. If the bullish trend continues the next resistance point is $0.40 while a bearish downturn will see the support at $0.0397.</p>
<p><b>Related Reading</b>: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/why-worldcoin-wld-and-pepe-dominate-the-crypto-market-trends-this-week/?swcfpc=1">Why Worldcoin (WLD) And PEPE Dominate The Crypto Market Trends This Week</a></p>
<p>As Casper continues to gain visibility and traction in the market, its future growth potential remains promising. The cryptocurrency&#8217;s underlying technology, including its proof-of-stake consensus mechanism, offers scalability, security, and energy efficiency. These features position Casper as an attractive enterprise adoption and long-term development candidate. </p>
<p><i>(This site’s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk).</i></p>
<p><i>Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView</i></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/iStock-1370952479-1-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cup And Handle Pattern Emerges In XRP Chart: What Does It Mean?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/cup-and-handle-pattern-emerges-in-xrp-chart-what-does-it-mean/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[anushsamal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 00:00:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrp]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrpusdt]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=544927</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Despite a favorable ruling as a non-security token, XRP had experienced a correction for over a week and a half, losing bullish momentum after reaching a yearly high of $0.94. It is trading above the $0.70 mark, with the $0.66 level acting as a support. Related Reading: Stanford MBA Explains Why Next Bitcoin Cycle Could Be “Bigger” Over the past 24 hours, XRP has exhibited sideways trading yet shows potential signs of price appreciation. The technical analysis indicates a leaning toward bullish sentiment, with positive buying strength, demand, and accumulation. Even though the emergence of a pattern suggesting further bullishness is possible, it remains critical for XRP to maintain support at $0.66 and $0.56 levels. Additionally, breaking through critical resistance levels is essential for the bulls to retain market control. Encouragingly, the altcoin&#8217;s market capitalization has increased, signaling a positive development for the altcoin. XRP Price Analysis: One-Day Chart When writing, the altcoin XRP was trading at $0.71. The XRP price chart shows the formation of a bullish reversal pattern known as a cup and handle. Despite this positive pattern, the coin&#8217;s true bullish potential will be determined by its ability to surpass two significant resistance levels at $0.76 and $0.84, respectively. It&#8217;s worth noting that after reaching a yearly high of $0.94, XRP encountered resistance at $0.84 twice. On the downside, if there is a decline from the current price level, XRP may find support at $0.66 and then at $0.56. Technical Analysis In recent trading sessions, the buying strength of the altcoin has shown consistency. The Relative Strength Index (RSI) has held steady around the 60-mark over the past few weeks, indicating buyers have maintained control of the price action. This positive signal suggests that the coin will attract more buyers if the price remains above the $0.66 level. Moreover, the price of XRP has remained above the 20-Simple Moving Average (SMA) line, indicating buoyant demand and confirming that buyers are actively driving the price momentum in the market. With the surge in purchasing power, the altcoin exhibits a decline in sell signals. The Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD) reflects changes in price momentum. Related Reading: Here’s How Crypto Offers A Lifeline For This Bahamian Payment Company Red signal bars appear below the half-line, indicating decreased sell signals. Meanwhile, the Bollinger Bands suggest a likelihood of price volatility and fluctuations in the upcoming trading sessions. The considerable widening of the bands indicates the potential for significant price fluctuation shortly. Featured image from UnSplash, charts from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Despite a favorable ruling as a non-security token, XRP had experienced a correction for over a week and a half, losing bullish momentum after reaching a yearly high of $0.94. It is trading above the $0.70 mark, with the $0.66 level acting as a support.</p>

<p>Over the past 24 hours, XRP has exhibited sideways trading yet shows potential signs of price appreciation. The technical analysis indicates a leaning toward bullish sentiment, with positive buying strength, demand, and accumulation.</p>
<p>Even though the emergence of a pattern suggesting further bullishness is possible, it remains critical for XRP to maintain support at $0.66 and $0.56 levels.</p>
<p>Additionally, breaking through critical resistance levels is essential for the bulls to retain market control. Encouragingly, the altcoin&#8217;s market capitalization has increased, signaling a positive development for the altcoin.</p>
<h2>XRP Price Analysis: One-Day Chart</h2>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-544929 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRPUSDT_2023-07-29_00-10-17.png" alt="XRP" width="1817" height="735" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRPUSDT_2023-07-29_00-10-17.png 1817w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRPUSDT_2023-07-29_00-10-17-460x186.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRPUSDT_2023-07-29_00-10-17-860x348.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRPUSDT_2023-07-29_00-10-17-768x311.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRPUSDT_2023-07-29_00-10-17-1536x621.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRPUSDT_2023-07-29_00-10-17-750x303.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRPUSDT_2023-07-29_00-10-17-1140x461.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1817px) 100vw, 1817px"/>
<p>When writing, the altcoin XRP was trading at $0.71. The XRP price chart shows the formation of a bullish reversal pattern known as a cup and handle.</p>
<p>Despite this positive pattern, the coin&#8217;s true bullish potential will be determined by its ability to surpass two significant resistance levels at $0.76 and $0.84, respectively.</p>
<p>It&#8217;s worth noting that after reaching a yearly high of $0.94, XRP encountered resistance at $0.84 twice. On the downside, if there is a decline from the current price level, XRP may find support at $0.66 and then at $0.56.</p>
<h2>Technical Analysis</h2>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-544930 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRPUSDT_2023-07-29_00-20-24.png" alt="XRP" width="1817" height="735" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRPUSDT_2023-07-29_00-20-24.png 1817w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRPUSDT_2023-07-29_00-20-24-460x186.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRPUSDT_2023-07-29_00-20-24-860x348.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRPUSDT_2023-07-29_00-20-24-768x311.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRPUSDT_2023-07-29_00-20-24-1536x621.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRPUSDT_2023-07-29_00-20-24-750x303.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRPUSDT_2023-07-29_00-20-24-1140x461.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1817px) 100vw, 1817px"/>
<p>In recent trading sessions, the buying strength of the altcoin has shown consistency. The Relative Strength Index (RSI) has held steady around the 60-mark over the past few weeks, indicating buyers have maintained control of the price action.</p>
<p>This positive signal suggests that the coin will attract more buyers if the price remains above the $0.66 level. Moreover, the price of XRP has remained above the 20-Simple Moving Average (SMA) line, indicating buoyant demand and confirming that buyers are actively driving the price momentum in the market.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-544931 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRPUSDT_2023-07-29_00-20-48.png" alt="XRP" width="1817" height="735" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRPUSDT_2023-07-29_00-20-48.png 1817w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRPUSDT_2023-07-29_00-20-48-460x186.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRPUSDT_2023-07-29_00-20-48-860x348.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRPUSDT_2023-07-29_00-20-48-768x311.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRPUSDT_2023-07-29_00-20-48-1536x621.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRPUSDT_2023-07-29_00-20-48-750x303.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRPUSDT_2023-07-29_00-20-48-1140x461.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1817px) 100vw, 1817px"/>
<p>With the surge in purchasing power, the altcoin exhibits a decline in sell signals. The Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD) reflects changes in price momentum.</p>

<p>Red signal bars appear below the half-line, indicating decreased sell signals. Meanwhile, the Bollinger Bands suggest a likelihood of price volatility and fluctuations in the upcoming trading sessions. The considerable widening of the bands indicates the potential for significant price fluctuation shortly.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/fabio-spano-2lHhfn7KXTw-unsplash-460x259.jpg" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
