<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	 xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" >

<channel>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://newsbtc.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://newsbtc.com</link>
	<description>Bitcoin &#38; cryptocurrency news today, price &#38; technical analysis</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 03:42:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<link>https://newsbtc.com</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Price Resumes Increase as The Bulls Aim Larger Rally To $25K</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-resumes-increase-25k/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 03:42:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xbtusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=517548</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin price started a fresh increase from the $22,400 support zone. BTC climbed to a new yearly high and now aims more upsides above $24,000. Bitcoin started a fresh increase after forming a base near the $22,400 support zone. The price is trading above $23,000 and the 100 hourly simple moving average. There was a break above a major bearish trend line with resistance near $23,000 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Kraken). The pair could start a fresh increase if it stays above the $23,000 support zone. Bitcoin Price Restarts Increase Bitcoin price saw a downside correction below the $23,000 level. However, BTC remained well bid near the $22,400 support zone. A low was formed near $22,341 and the price started a fresh increase. There was a clear move above the $23,000 resistance zone. Besides, there was a break above a major bearish trend line with resistance near $23,000 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair. The pair surged to a new yearly high at $23,829 and is currently correcting gains. There was a move below the 50% Fib retracement level of the recent increase from the $22,341 swing low to $23,829 high. However, the bulls appeared near the $23,200 support zone. Bitcoin price is now trading above $23,000 and the 100 hourly simple moving average. It is also above the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the recent increase from the $22,341 swing low to $23,829 high. An immediate resistance is near the $23,400 level. Source: BTCUSD on TradingView.com The next major resistance is near the $23,850 zone, above which the price might gain bullish momentum. In the stated case, the price may perhaps rise towards the $24,200 level. The next resistance could be near the $24,500 level. Any more gains might send btc price towards the $25,000 level. Dips Supported in BTC? If bitcoin price fails to clear the $23,400 resistance, it could continue to move down. An immediate support on the downside is near the $23,000 zone. The next major support is near the $22,850 zone. A downside break below the $22,850 level might send the price towards the $22,500 level. Any more losses might send the price to $22,350 in the near term. Technical indicators: Hourly MACD – The MACD is now losing pace in the bullish zone. Hourly RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BTC/USD is now above the 50 level. Major Support Levels – $23,000, followed by $22,850. Major Resistance Levels – $23,400, $23,850 and $24,200.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>Bitcoin price started a fresh increase from the $22,400 support zone. BTC climbed to a new yearly high and now aims more upsides above $24,000.</em></p>
<ul>
<li>Bitcoin started a fresh increase after forming a base near the $22,400 support zone.</li>
<li>The price is trading above $23,000 and the 100 hourly simple moving average.</li>
<li>There was a break above a major bearish trend line with resistance near $23,000 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could start a fresh increase if it stays above the $23,000 support zone.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Bitcoin Price Restarts Increase</h2>
<p>Bitcoin price saw a downside correction below the $23,000 level. However, BTC remained well bid near the $22,400 support zone. A low was formed near $22,341 and the <a href="https://newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-correction-22k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">price started a fresh increase</a>.</p>
<p>There was a clear move above the $23,000 resistance zone. Besides, there was a break above a major bearish trend line with resistance near $23,000 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair. The pair surged to a new yearly high at $23,829 and is currently correcting gains.</p>
<p>There was a move below the 50% Fib retracement level of the recent increase from the $22,341 swing low to $23,829 high. However, the bulls appeared near the $23,200 support zone.</p>
<p>Bitcoin price is now trading above $23,000 and the 100 hourly simple moving average. It is also above the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the recent increase from the $22,341 swing low to $23,829 high. An immediate resistance is near the $23,400 level.</p>
<p><a href="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-22.png"><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-517549" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-22.png" alt="Bitcoin Price" width="1834" height="845" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-22.png 1834w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-22-460x212.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-22-860x396.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-22-768x354.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-22-1536x708.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-22-750x346.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-22-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1834px) 100vw, 1834px" /></a></p>
<p>Source: <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BTCUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">BTCUSD on TradingView.com</a></p>
<p>The next major resistance is near the $23,850 zone, above which the price might gain bullish momentum. In the stated case, the price may perhaps rise towards the $24,200 level. The next resistance could be near the $24,500 level. Any more gains might send <a href="https://newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-surge-to-25k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">btc price towards the $25,000 level</a>.</p>
<h2>Dips Supported in BTC?</h2>
<p>If bitcoin price fails to clear the $23,400 resistance, it could continue to move down. An immediate support on the downside is near the $23,000 zone.</p>
<p>The next major support is near the $22,850 zone. A downside break below the $22,850 level might send the price towards the $22,500 level. Any more losses might send the price to $22,350 in the near term.</p>
<p>Technical indicators:</p>
<p>Hourly MACD – The MACD is now losing pace in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>Hourly RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BTC/USD is now above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Levels – $23,000, followed by $22,850.</p>
<p>Major Resistance Levels – $23,400, $23,850 and $24,200.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/crypto_market_altcoins_rise-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Banking Giant Goldman Sachs Ranks Bitcoin As World Best Performing Asset</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/goldman-bitcoin-is-world-best-performing/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ronaldomarquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 22:25:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=517536</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Ahead of Gold, US Treasury, the S&#38;P 500, and others, banking giant Goldman Sachs ranks Bitcoin (BTC) in the top 1 best-performing asset year-to-date, per a Twitter user. Related Reading: MakerDAO Passes Proposal To Deploy $100 Million USDC In Yearn Finance Vault According to Goldman Sachs, Bitcoin has outperformed its cryptocurrency pairs and those major financial institutions of the traditional market with a risk-adjusted return (Sharpe ratio) of 3.1. The Sharpe Ratio is used to measure market volatility-adjusted performance; the higher the ratio, the better the investment, currency, or stock in terms of risk-adjusted returns. Bitcoin Takes The Lead In Broad Market Recovery On smaller timeframes, Bitcoin continues its quest to regain lost territory. Slowly but steadily, Bitcoin is attempting to break above the resistance level of $23,800. Bitcoin appears to have a healthy pullback below the resistance line in search of bullish momentum. Despite the recent crisis of not only the cryptocurrency market with the collapse of FTX and the world economy in free fall, bringing consequences for investors and institutions, the market has also noted the comeback of market makers on cryptocurrency exchanges.  In contrast with Goldman Sachs&#8217; report, according to an annual report by CoinGecko, Bitcoin is the worst-performing asset among the major currencies, with a significant decline of 64%. CoinGecko also noted that since January 2022, the trading volume in the spot market has decreased by 67%.  The new year for Bitcoin and the market started positively, with $200 billion bulking the volume and volatility sheets, according to CoinMarketCap data. Bitcoin&#8217;s year-to-date solid rally has shifted market sentiment. Analysts seem bullish in the short term, expecting the cryptocurrency to increase to as much as $30,000. However, in the long term, economist Lyn Alden said that Bitcoin could be in &#8220;considerable danger&#8221; in the second quarter of 2023 as liquidity risks increase.  As the price of Bitcoin consolidates below the resistance zone, the cryptocurrency is looking for a trendline break to position itself above the $24,500 level, representing its next obstacle.  The rising 20-day moving average at $20,700 and the Relative Strength Index (RSI) in the overbought zone near 80 suggest that BTC&#8217;s bullish trend line can continue and conquer new regions. Conversely, bears are ready to stall the Bitcoin price action to the upside and turn the momentum and direction of the market, but bulls seem unwilling to surrender. Speculation is on the rise with no certainties in the market and the upcoming Federal Open Market Committee (FOMC) meetings.  Related Reading: Cardano’s Aggressive Development Activity Will Withstand Bear Assault At $0.3? As of this writing, Bitcoin has gained nearly 8% in the last seven days. It has traded at $22,889 with sideways movement in the last 24 hours. The currency&#8217;s current capitalization stands at $440 billion, outperforming all its market pairs.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ahead of Gold, US Treasury, the S&amp;P 500, and others, banking giant Goldman Sachs ranks Bitcoin (BTC) in the top 1 best-performing asset year-to-date, <a href="https://twitter.com/DocumentingBTC/status/1617594072280989698/photo/1" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">per a Twitter user</a>.</p>

<p>According to Goldman Sachs, Bitcoin has outperformed its cryptocurrency pairs and those major financial institutions of the traditional market with a risk-adjusted return (Sharpe ratio) of 3.1. The Sharpe Ratio is used to measure market volatility-adjusted performance; the higher the ratio, the better the investment, currency, or stock in terms of risk-adjusted returns.</p>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-517540 size-large" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-860x635.jpeg" alt="Bitcoin BTC BTCUSDT" width="860" height="635" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-860x635.jpeg 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-460x340.jpeg 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-768x567.jpeg 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-750x554.jpeg 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-1140x842.jpeg 1140w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT.jpeg 1285w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" />
<h2><b>Bitcoin Takes The Lead In Broad Market Recovery</b></h2>
<p>On smaller timeframes, Bitcoin continues its quest to regain lost territory. Slowly but steadily, Bitcoin is attempting to break above the resistance level of $23,800. Bitcoin appears to have a healthy pullback below the resistance line in search of bullish momentum.</p>
<p>Despite the recent crisis of not only the cryptocurrency market with the collapse of FTX and the world economy in free fall, bringing consequences for investors and institutions, the market has also noted the comeback of market makers on cryptocurrency exchanges. </p>
<p>In contrast with Goldman Sachs&#8217; report, according to an annual <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/research/publications/2022-annual-crypto-report" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">report</a> by CoinGecko, Bitcoin is the worst-performing asset among the major currencies, with a significant decline of 64%. CoinGecko also noted that since January 2022, the trading volume in the spot market has decreased by 67%. </p>
<p>The new year for Bitcoin and the market started positively, with $200 billion bulking the volume and volatility sheets, according to CoinMarketCap data.</p>
<p>Bitcoin&#8217;s year-to-date solid rally has shifted market sentiment. Analysts seem bullish in the short term, expecting the cryptocurrency to increase to as much as $30,000. However, in the long term, economist Lyn Alden said that Bitcoin could be in &#8220;considerable danger&#8221; in the second quarter of 2023 as liquidity risks increase. </p>
<p>As the price of Bitcoin consolidates below the resistance zone, the cryptocurrency is looking for a trendline break to position itself above the $24,500 level, representing its next obstacle. </p>
<p>The rising 20-day moving average at $20,700 and the Relative Strength Index (RSI) in the overbought zone near 80 suggest that BTC&#8217;s bullish trend line can continue and conquer new regions.</p>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-517543 size-full" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-2-1.jpg" alt="Bitcoin BTC BTCUSDT Chart 2" width="602" height="365" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-2-1.jpg 602w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-2-1-460x279.jpg 460w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" />
<p>Conversely, bears are ready to stall the Bitcoin price action to the upside and turn the momentum and direction of the market, but bulls seem unwilling to surrender. Speculation is on the rise with no certainties in the market and the upcoming Federal Open Market Committee (FOMC) meetings. </p>

<p>As of this writing, Bitcoin has gained nearly 8% in the last seven days. It has traded at $22,889 with sideways movement in the last 24 hours. The currency&#8217;s current capitalization stands at $440 billion, outperforming all its market pairs.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-price-performance-460x259.jpg" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>MakerDAO Passes Proposal To Deploy $100 Million USDC In Yearn Finance Vault</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/defi/makerdao-passes-proposal-deploy-usdc/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samuel Edyme]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 19:00:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[DeFi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[circle]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dai]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MakerDAO]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MKR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[stablecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USDC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=517517</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[In the hopes of generating yield while offering users what its best known for, MakerDAO, the issuer of the Ethereum-based stablecoin, DAI, has approved a proposal to deploy $100 million of Circle’s USD Coin (USDC) in a Yearn Finance yield-generating account called a “vault.” The proposal, submitted on January 9, aims to look for a way MakerDAO could split its treasury allocations and earn yield. MakerDAO To Generate Yields From Yearn Finance Vault Following the approval of the MIP92 (Maker Improvement Proposal 92), MakerDAO plans to begin depositing $100 million USDC to the Yearn finance vault to earn a 2% yield annually, approximately $2 million every year on its YearnFi investment.  Related Reading: MakerDAO Could Replace Governance Token, Will It Provide Enhanced Incentives? Founded by prominent DeFi developer Andre Cronje, Yearn finance is a yield aggregator built on the Ethereum blockchain, allowing users to deposit crypto assets in the service in exchange for yield or interest over some time.  With a total of 95,666.284 of Maker’s native token, MKR cast in the vote, approximately 68,462 MKR, which accounts for 71.56%, voted in favor of deploying USDC in Yearn Finance, while 27,204 MKR, which accounts for 28.44% voted out the whole idea and 0.0% voted “abstain.” Though the MIP92 has been passed, the proposal still has to go through an executive vote for the concept to be implemented. MakerDAO Attraction To USDC Before the MIP92 submission, MakerDAO had already demonstrated interest in Circle’s dollar-backed token, USDC. Late last year, the DAI stablecoin operator invested a hefty amount alongside collaboration with Coinbase to become the largest stakeholder in USDC. As reported by NewsBTC, MakerDAO and Coinbase Prime have a total of USD 1.6 billion in custody, allowing both partners to earn 1.5% returns from the deposited assets. Notably, stablecoins have seen rapid growth in recognition in recent years. As a result, investors now rely on these assets to protect the value of their investments. Related Reading: MakerDAO Invests Hefty Amount Becoming The Largest Stake Holder In USDC Unlike traditional cryptocurrencies, which fluctuate now and then, stablecoins are tied to the value of an underlying asset, like the U.S. dollar. Due to the nature of stablecoins, many investors have found them enticing, especially as a vital part of future finance. With the USDC still lagging behind USDT in adoption, the goal has always been to surpass the latter and become number one in the market cap. Veering back to MakerDAO, the protocol&#8217;s native token, MKR, has also been thriving to cover the gaps between its current price and its all-time high. Over the past 30 days, MKR has surged more than 20% and currently trades above $650 with a 24-hour trading volume of $22.3 million. Featured image from BlockchainReporter, Chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In the hopes of generating yield while offering users what its best known for, MakerDAO, the issuer of the Ethereum-based stablecoin, DAI, has approved a <a href="https://vote.makerdao.com/polling/Qma4jEPY#vote-breakdown" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">proposal</a> to deploy $100 million of Circle’s USD Coin (USDC) in a Yearn Finance yield-generating account called a “<a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/polygon-vault-makerdao-matic-tokens/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">vault</a>.”</p>
<p>The proposal, submitted on January 9, aims to look for a way MakerDAO could split its treasury allocations and earn yield.</p>
<h2>MakerDAO To Generate Yields From Yearn Finance Vault</h2>
<p>Following the approval of the MIP92 (Maker Improvement Proposal 92), <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/defi/makerdao-revenue-experiences-a-major-drop-heres-why/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">MakerDAO</a> plans to begin depositing $100 million USDC to the Yearn finance vault to earn a 2% yield annually, approximately $2 million every year on its YearnFi investment. </p>

<p>Founded by prominent DeFi developer Andre Cronje, Yearn finance is a yield aggregator built on the Ethereum blockchain, allowing users to deposit crypto assets in the service in exchange for yield or interest over some time. </p>
<p>With a total of 95,666.284 of Maker’s native token, MKR cast in the vote, approximately 68,462 MKR, which accounts for 71.56%, voted in favor of deploying USDC in Yearn Finance, while 27,204 MKR, which accounts for 28.44% voted out the whole idea and 0.0% voted “abstain.” </p>
<p>Though the MIP92 has been passed, the proposal still has to go through an executive vote for the concept to be implemented.</p>
<h2>MakerDAO Attraction To USDC</h2>
<p>Before the MIP92 submission, MakerDAO had already demonstrated interest in Circle’s dollar-backed token, USDC. Late last year, the DAI stablecoin operator <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/makerdao-invests-hefty-amount-becoming-the-largest-stake-holder-in-usdc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">invested a hefty amount</a> alongside collaboration with Coinbase to become the largest stakeholder in USDC.</p>
<p>As reported by NewsBTC, <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/defi/makerdao-could-replace-governance-token-will-it-provide-enhanced-incentives/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">MakerDAO</a> and Coinbase Prime have a total of USD 1.6 billion in custody, allowing both partners to earn 1.5% returns from the deposited assets. Notably, stablecoins have seen rapid growth in recognition in recent years. As a result, investors now rely on these assets to protect the value of their investments.</p>

<p>Unlike traditional cryptocurrencies, which fluctuate now and then, stablecoins are tied to the value of an underlying asset, like the U.S. dollar. Due to the nature of<a href="https://newsbtc.com/press-releases/stablecoin-decentralization-demeter-expected-to-be-makerdao-on-heco-network/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"> stablecoins</a>, many investors have found them enticing, especially as a vital part of future finance. </p>
<p>With the USDC still lagging behind USDT in adoption, the goal has always been to surpass the latter and become number one in the market cap.</p>
<img loading="lazy" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/1S1FrlVf/" alt="MKRUSDT price chart on TradingView" width="1562" height="826" />
<p>Veering back to MakerDAO, the protocol&#8217;s native token, MKR, has also been thriving to cover the gaps between its current price and its all-time high. Over the past 30 days, MKR has surged more than 20% and currently trades above $650 with a 24-hour trading volume of $22.3 million.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/MakerDAO-460x230.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cardano&#8217;s Aggressive Development Activity Will Withstand Bear Assault At $0.3?</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/cardano/cardanos-activity-withstand-bear-assault/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reynaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 18:00:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cardano]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADAUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=517507</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The crypto market’s rally is losing strength, forcing significant cryptocurrencies, such as Bitcoin, Ethereum, and Cardano, back to their support regions. The latter has been deploying products and development that hint at a longer bullish trend. Related Reading: Bitcoin Short-Term Holder Profit-Taking Spikes, Will BTC Price Recover? As of this writing, Cardano (ADA) trades at $0.35 with a 5% loss in the last 24 hours. Over the past week, ADA’s price still recorded some profits as the bulls made their stand against a spike in selling pressure. Cardano In The Olympus Of Development Activity Data from research firm Santiment indicates that the Cardano ecosystem is vibrating with development activity. Currently, this blockchain ranks number 3 in the metric, according to the number of commits on the software development platform GitHub. As seen in the chart below, Cardano’s development activity over the past 30 days records over 330 GitHub commits for the different projects on this blockchain. Only Polkadot and its experimental environment Kusama have seen more development activity, with 441 commits. As the chart above shows, the price of Cardano (ADA) has been moving in tandem with its developments and the general market sentiment. As more developers onboard the blockchain, the ecosystem is more appealing to investors. ADA records a 38% rally over the past 30 days. In the coming weeks, this blockchain will deploy a new upgrade for its smart contract programming language, Plutus. This update will enable support for the Elliptic Curve Digital Signature Algorithm (ECDSA) and Schnorr. These new components will allow developers to provide more security and build cross-chain capabilities. Plutus was designed to operate as an easy-to-use and accessible programming language. Thus, people might feel even more incentive to build on this blockchain. Related Reading: Here’s What Might Have Triggered Ethereum’s Decline Below $1,600 It remains to be seen if ADA’s price will extend its recent trend and follow its spike in development activity. According to Input Output Global, Cardano’s lead developer company: This upgrade will bring greater interoperability and secure cross-chain #DApp development to #Cardano, making it easier for developers to work with other blockchains. Developers would otherwise need to spend extra time, effort, and funds to implement ECDSA and Schnorr over the SECP elliptic curves in #Plutus, increasing potential security risks and using an unrealistic amount of resources.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>The crypto market’s rally is losing strength, forcing significant cryptocurrencies, such as Bitcoin, Ethereum, and Cardano, back to their support regions. The latter has been deploying products and development that hint at a longer bullish trend. </strong></p>

<p>As of this writing, Cardano (ADA) trades at $0.35 with a 5% loss in the last 24 hours. Over the past week, ADA’s price still recorded some profits as the bulls made their stand against a spike in selling pressure.</p>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-517524 size-large" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Cardano-ADA-ADAUSDT-2-860x394.png" alt="Cardano ADA ADAUSDT" width="860" height="394" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Cardano-ADA-ADAUSDT-2-860x394.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Cardano-ADA-ADAUSDT-2-460x211.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Cardano-ADA-ADAUSDT-2-768x352.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Cardano-ADA-ADAUSDT-2-1536x704.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Cardano-ADA-ADAUSDT-2-750x344.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Cardano-ADA-ADAUSDT-2-1140x522.png 1140w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Cardano-ADA-ADAUSDT-2.png 1814w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" />
<h2>Cardano In The Olympus Of Development Activity</h2>
<p>Data from research firm Santiment <a href="https://twitter.com/santimentfeed/status/1617932609602088960" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">indicates</a> that the Cardano ecosystem is vibrating with development activity. Currently, this blockchain ranks number 3 in the metric, according to the number of commits on the software development platform GitHub.</p>
<p>As seen in the chart below, Cardano’s development activity over the past 30 days records over 330 GitHub commits for the different projects on this blockchain. Only Polkadot and its experimental environment Kusama have seen more development activity, with 441 commits.</p>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-517513 size-large" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Cardano-ADA-ADAUSDT-Chart-2-860x595.jpeg" alt="Cardano ADA ADAUSDT Chart 2" width="860" height="595" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Cardano-ADA-ADAUSDT-Chart-2-860x595.jpeg 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Cardano-ADA-ADAUSDT-Chart-2-460x319.jpeg 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Cardano-ADA-ADAUSDT-Chart-2-768x532.jpeg 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Cardano-ADA-ADAUSDT-Chart-2-1536x1064.jpeg 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Cardano-ADA-ADAUSDT-Chart-2-2048x1418.jpeg 2048w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Cardano-ADA-ADAUSDT-Chart-2-750x519.jpeg 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Cardano-ADA-ADAUSDT-Chart-2-1140x789.jpeg 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" />
<p>As the chart above shows, the price of Cardano (ADA) has been moving in tandem with its developments and the general market sentiment. As more developers onboard the blockchain, the ecosystem is more appealing to investors. ADA records a 38% rally over the past 30 days.</p>
<p>In the coming weeks, this blockchain will deploy a new upgrade for its smart contract programming language, Plutus. This update will enable support for the Elliptic Curve Digital Signature Algorithm (ECDSA) and Schnorr.</p>
<p>These new components will allow developers to provide more security and build cross-chain capabilities. Plutus was designed to operate as an easy-to-use and accessible programming language. Thus, people might feel even more incentive to build on this blockchain.</p>

<p>It remains to be seen if ADA’s price will extend its recent trend and follow its spike in development activity. According to Input Output Global, Cardano’s lead developer company:</p>
<blockquote><p>This upgrade will bring greater interoperability and secure cross-chain #DApp development to #Cardano, making it easier for developers to work with other blockchains. Developers would otherwise need to spend extra time, effort, and funds to implement ECDSA and Schnorr over the SECP elliptic curves in #Plutus, increasing potential security risks and using an unrealistic amount of resources.</p></blockquote>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/Cryptocurrecny_cardano_1642474364856_1642474365013-460x259.jpg" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Here’s What Might Have Triggered Ethereum’s Decline Below $1,600</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/ethereum/what-triggered-ethereum-decline/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Best Owie]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 17:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eth price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=517428</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[After what has been two weeks of an incredible rally for the price of Ethereum, the digital asset seems to be running out of steam. ETH’s price has now declined once more below $1,600 after a sharp downturn on Tuesday. The culprit for this seems to be growing FUD across the community. FUD Could Have Been The Trigger According to Santiment, the social dominance of Ethereum grew rapidly in the last couple of days. While this can sometimes be a good thing, it tells a negative story this time around. Ethereum is now dominating 21% of cryptocurrency discussion on social media and the on-chain data aggregator says this might be evidence that FUD might be behind the dip. However, this may not be the only reason. Related Reading: Money Leaves ADA, SOL To Small Cap Altcoins, Here’s Where It’s Headed A report from Bitcoinist had previously shown that profit-taking in large assets such as Bitcoin and Ethereum had been ramping up with the increase in price. Santiment also highlights this in its post, pointing to the spike in the profit-taking ratio on January 20. Taking this in concert with the growing FUD, it presents a recipe for disaster for the digital asset. ETH social dominance indicates FUD &#124; Source: Santiment Another prominent event was the Wormhole attacker started moving the stolen funds around. On Monday, the attacker moved over $155 million in ETH to OpenOcean which they proceeded to exchange for staked ETH tokens such as stETH and wstETH. The dumping of these coins on the open market saw sell pressure mount on ETH during this time. It contributed to the already declining momentum, resulting in the current dip in the price. Can Ethereum Recover From Here? Despite the recent decline, the overall sentiment for Ethereum is still skewing largely toward buy. This is because the cryptocurrency is still trading well above its 50-day and 100-day moving averages. And even with the decline, it continues to trend around its 200-day moving average. Related Reading: Crypto Analyst Says Bitcoin Price Could See Another 30% Rally What this shows is that, at least in the short to mid-term, there is still a lot of bullish sentiment surrounding the digital asset. Add in the ample support that has built up around $1,500 over the last couple of days and Ethereum is still presenting as a formidable choice of investment. ETH price falls below $1,600 &#124; Source: ETHUSD on TradingView.com Investors are also seeing good profits during this time with 57% of all holders in profit. Figures like these also help to push a bullish narrative for the digital asset as more investors try to take advantage of the dip and move into the green. Overall, as long as ETH maintains its momentum and trading volume continues rising, it’ll retest the $1,600 resistance once more.  ETH’s price is changing hands at $1,555 at the time of this writing. Its price is down 5.27% in the last 24 hours but trading volume is up 11.91% over the same time period to be sitting at $9.32 billion. Follow Best Owie on Twitter for market insights, updates, and the occasional funny tweet… Featured image from Bitcoinist, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="p2">After what has been two weeks of an incredible rally for the price of Ethereum, the digital asset seems to be running out of steam. ETH’s price has now declined once more below $1,600 after a sharp downturn on Tuesday. The culprit for this seems to be growing FUD across the community.</p>
<h2 class="p2">FUD Could Have Been The Trigger</h2>
<p class="p2">According to <a href="https://twitter.com/santimentfeed/status/1618081583629766657?s=20&amp;t=vRj0IWqW88LQllu28S7emg" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">Santiment</a>, the social dominance of Ethereum grew rapidly in the last couple of days. While this can sometimes be a good thing, it tells a negative story this time around. Ethereum is now dominating 21% of cryptocurrency discussion on social media and the on-chain data aggregator says this might be evidence that FUD might be behind the dip. However, this may not be the only reason.</p>

<p class="p2">A report from <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-ethereum-profit-taking-2021-levels/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">Bitcoinist</a> had previously shown that profit-taking in large assets such as Bitcoin and Ethereum had been ramping up with the increase in price. Santiment also highlights this in its post, pointing to the spike in the profit-taking ratio on January 20. Taking this in concert with the growing FUD, it presents a recipe for disaster for the digital asset.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-517429 aligncenter" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ethereum-dominance-460x293.jpeg" alt="Ethereum dominance" width="460" height="293" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ethereum-dominance-460x293.jpeg 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ethereum-dominance-860x547.jpeg 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ethereum-dominance-768x489.jpeg 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ethereum-dominance-1536x977.jpeg 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ethereum-dominance-2048x1303.jpeg 2048w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ethereum-dominance-750x477.jpeg 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ethereum-dominance-1140x725.jpeg 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px" /></p>

<p class="p2">Another prominent event was the Wormhole attacker started moving the stolen funds around. On Monday, the attacker moved over $155 million in ETH to OpenOcean which they proceeded to exchange for staked ETH tokens such as stETH and wstETH.</p>
<p class="p2">The dumping of these coins on the open market saw sell pressure mount on ETH during this time. It contributed to the already declining momentum, resulting in the current dip in the price.</p>
<h2 class="p2">Can Ethereum Recover From Here?</h2>
<p class="p2">Despite the recent decline, the overall sentiment for Ethereum is still skewing largely toward buy. This is because the cryptocurrency is still trading well above its 50-day and 100-day moving averages. And even with the decline, it continues to trend around its 200-day moving average.</p>

<p class="p2">What this shows is that, at least in the short to mid-term, there is still a lot of bullish sentiment surrounding the digital asset. Add in the ample support that has built up around $1,500 over the last couple of days and Ethereum is still presenting as a formidable choice of investment.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/AZOt79zL/" alt="Ethereum price chart from TradingView.com" width="2882" height="1724" /></p>

<p class="p2">Investors are also seeing good profits during this time with 57% of all holders in profit. Figures like these also help to push a bullish narrative for the digital asset as more investors try to take advantage of the dip and move into the green. Overall, as long as ETH maintains its momentum and trading volume continues rising, it’ll retest the $1,600 resistance once more. </p>
<p class="p2">ETH’s price is changing hands at $1,555 at the time of this writing. Its price is down 5.27% in the last 24 hours but trading volume is up 11.91% over the same time period to be sitting at $9.32 billion.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Grayscale-Bitcoin-Trust-1-460x276.jpeg" width="460" height="276" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Short-Term Holder Profit-Taking Spikes, Will BTC Price Recover?</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-short-term-holder-profit-correct/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hououin Kyouma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 16:20:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin bearish]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin short-term holders]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin SOPR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin STH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin STH SOPR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=517484</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[On-chain data shows Bitcoin short-term holder profit-taking has spiked, will this lead to a correction in the price of the crypto? Bitcoin Short-Term Holder SOPR Has Surged Recently As pointed out by an analyst in a CryptoQuant post, instances of the current trend have led to declines in the crypto&#8217;s price in the past. The relevant indicator here is the &#8220;Spent Output Profit Ratio&#8221; (SOPR), which tells us whether the average Bitcoin investor is selling their coins at a profit or at a loss right now. When the value of this metric is greater than 1, it means the holders as a whole are realizing some profits on their selling currently. On the other hand, values below the threshold suggest the overall market is leaning towards loss realization at the moment. Naturally, the indicator being exactly equal to 1 implies the average holder is just breaking even on their distribution right now. One of the two main segments of the BTC market is made up of the &#8220;short-term holders&#8221; (STHs), which is a cohort that includes all investors who acquired their coins within the last 155 days. The holders who have been sitting on their coins for more than this threshold amount are called &#8220;long-term holders&#8221; (LTHs). Now, here is a chart that shows the trend in the Bitcoin SOPR specifically for the STHs: The value of the metric seems to have risen in recent days &#124; Source: CryptoQuant As displayed in the above graph, the Bitcoin STH SOPR (as well as its 7-day moving average) has surged and broken above 1 recently. This means that as the BTC rally has taken place, the STHs have come into profits and they are now selling to harvest these gains. Related Reading: Shiba Inu Declines 6%, Gets Flipped By Litecoin In Market Cap Again The chart also includes data for the 7-day triple exponential average (TRIX) of the STH SOPR. The TRIX is a momentum oscillator that shows the percentage change in a metric&#8217;s moving average after smoothening it exponentially three times (hence the name). From the chart, it&#8217;s visible that during this bear market, whenever the STH SOPR 7-day TRIX has hit a positive top, the price of Bitcoin has noticed a local top formation as well and has subsequently gone down. It looks like most recently, the 7-day TRIX of the STH SOPR has shot up again, and the metric seems to be curving inside now, potentially moving toward a top formation. This pattern looks similar to the instances seen earlier in the bear market, which could suggest this Bitcoin rally may be heading toward the same fate as those previous ones. Though that would be only if the pattern does complete and the indicator makes the top. Related Reading: Here’s Why The Bitcoin Price Rally Stalled For Now The analyst has also posted the chart for the 2018-2019 bear market, to see how the current rally compares with that of April 2019. The trend in the STH SOPR 7-day TRIX in the 2018-2019 bear market &#124; Source: CryptoQuant Interestingly, the rally of April 2019 only felt a short-term pullback from the first big spike in the indicator; it was only with the second spike that the price topped out. There have been some similarities between the current rally and that of April 2019 already, which may mean that the current one could also shrug off this first spike in the indicator and continue its momentum, just like the past rally. BTC Price At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading around $22,900, up 5% in the last week. BTC consolidates &#124; Source: BTCUSD on TradingView Featured image from Thought Catalog on Unsplash.com, charts from TradingView.com, CryptoQuant.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On-chain data shows Bitcoin short-term holder profit-taking has spiked, will this lead to a correction in the price of the crypto?</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Short-Term Holder SOPR Has Surged Recently</h2>
<p>As pointed out by an analyst in a CryptoQuant <a href="https://cryptoquant.com/quicktake/63d10d294a71fb5ea520e4b6-STH-SOPR-shows-a-bearish-alert" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">post</a>, instances of the current trend have led to declines in the crypto&#8217;s price in the past. The relevant indicator here is the &#8220;<a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-asopr-bull-bear-resistance-break/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Spent Output Profit Ratio</a>&#8221; (SOPR), which tells us whether the average Bitcoin investor is selling their coins at a profit or at a loss right now.</p>
<p>When the value of this metric is greater than 1, it means the holders as a whole are realizing some profits on their selling currently. On the other hand, values below the threshold suggest the overall market is leaning towards loss realization at the moment. Naturally, the indicator being exactly equal to 1 implies the average holder is just breaking even on their distribution right now.</p>
<p>One of the two main segments of the BTC market is made up of the &#8220;<a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-declines-short-term-holders-take-profits/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">short-term holders</a>&#8221; (STHs), which is a cohort that includes all investors who acquired their coins within the last 155 days. The holders who have been sitting on their coins for more than this threshold amount are called &#8220;long-term holders&#8221; (LTHs).</p>
<p>Now, here is a chart that shows the trend in the Bitcoin SOPR specifically for the STHs:</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone aligncenter" src="https://img.cryptoquant.com/352589/quicktake/IQiAY_5f6505e4ce8c655506f873a04a59e06015c98fd0a6bb0997bd18d0df1d7a2171.png" alt="Bitcoin Short-Term Holder SOPR" width="1280" height="694" /></p>

<p>As displayed in the above graph, the Bitcoin STH SOPR (as well as its 7-day moving average) has surged and broken above 1 recently. This means that as the BTC rally has taken place, the STHs have come into profits and they are now selling to harvest these gains.</p>

<p>The chart also includes data for the 7-day triple exponential average (TRIX) of the STH SOPR. The TRIX is a momentum oscillator that shows the percentage change in a metric&#8217;s moving average after smoothening it exponentially three times (hence the name).</p>
<p>From the chart, it&#8217;s visible that during this bear market, whenever the STH SOPR 7-day TRIX has hit a positive top, the price of Bitcoin has noticed a local top formation as well and has subsequently gone down.</p>
<p>It looks like most recently, the 7-day TRIX of the STH SOPR has shot up again, and the metric seems to be curving inside now, potentially moving toward a top formation.</p>
<p>This pattern looks similar to the instances seen earlier in the bear market, which could suggest this Bitcoin rally may be heading toward the same fate as those previous ones. Though that would be only if the pattern does complete and the indicator makes the top.</p>

<p>The analyst has also posted the chart for the 2018-2019 bear market, to see how the current rally compares with that of April 2019.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone aligncenter" src="https://img.cryptoquant.com/352589/quicktake/comment/dRdVV_859b6e2b11cd0e30cd00ffa80cae3bdfd54af6a99119236fd9aea1478b98d9d9.png" alt="Bitcoin 2018-2019 bear market" width="1280" height="694" /></p>

<p>Interestingly, the rally of April 2019 only felt a short-term pullback from the first big spike in the indicator; it was only with the second spike that the price topped out. There have been <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/repeat-april-2019-bitcoin-rally-levels/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">some similarities</a> between the current rally and that of April 2019 already, which may mean that the current one could also shrug off this first spike in the indicator and continue its momentum, just like the past rally.</p>
<h2>BTC Price</h2>
<p>At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading around $22,900, up 5% in the last week.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone wp-image-517501 size-large aligncenter" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/chart-39-860x308.png" alt="Bitcoin Price Chart" width="860" height="308" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/chart-39-860x308.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/chart-39-460x165.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/chart-39-768x275.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/chart-39-750x269.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/chart-39.png 990w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" /></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/thought-catalog-I0TDRP0fj6Y-unsplash-1-1-460x345.jpg" width="460" height="345" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Why This Analyst Thinks Traders Should Not Be Bearish On Solana</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/solana/traders-should-not-bearish-solana/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samuel Edyme]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 15:30:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Solana]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto market]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sol]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trader]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=517492</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[For traders thinking Solana is controlled by the bears, a popular crypto market analyst, Chris Burniske, is giving a fresh perspective of hope for the major altcoin.    According to the former lead of Ark Invest&#8217;s crypto department, those who think that SOL is generally bedridden in a bearish mood are mistaken. SOL Sets To Make a Breakthrough Burniske said that the Ethereum killer still has a breakthrough opportunity to rally its price despite its reverse down at a resistance level. The prominent analyst urged traders not to be extremely bearish on SOL as the coin would eventually retrace its value. He expects the crypto&#8217;s retracement to occur within the next few months.  Related Reading: Solana Keeps Positive Radiance But Bears Could Dampen The Mood At This Level Burniske, however, cautioned that investors might experience price decline due to the market volatility, which might heighten and cause massive losses for traders who have opened long positions in their leverages. Since the start of the year, Solana has been in a bullish mood and showing signs of resilience and bravery, actually benefiting from the recent market bullishness. Based on the daily and weekly trading movement since the beginning of the year, the current bearish action of SOL can be regarded as a mere retracement, something which is generally seen in other risky assets. Most Ethereum killers, including Solana, are witnessing a similar kind of price reversal, which signals no major panic on the part of the SOL price. Solana Price Analysis Shows Buy Signal Burniske’s projection seems to be right based on technical price analysis. Over the past three months, Solana moved in a sideways trajectory trend at an average price of around the $14 mark. But within the last two weeks, Solana has surged its value by over 68% to trade at an average price of $23.59. At the time of writing, Solana is currently trading at $23.18, down 5.50%, with a trading volume of $801,611,149 in the last 24 hours. The altcoin’s market cap stands at $8.6 billion, which puts it the 10th largest cryptocurrency, according to Coinmarketcap. Related Reading: Solana (SOL) Outperforms Top Coins With 28% Gains On Weekly Chart As per the TradingView chart below, the presence of a bullish hammer in the candlesticks signals the buyers are taking back control and pushing the price back above. The green indicator shows the sellers’ inability to drive the price of an asset further down. The 50-day and 200-day moving average settings on the 4-hour price chart further support this bullish trend. The presence of the golden cross, as it is indicated by an asset’s short-term moving average crossing above its long-term moving average, signals a switch from a bear trend to a bull trend. Based on price analysis, the current sentiment is bullish, as this can also be seen in the RSI stands at 64.22, showing that Solana is in the bull territory. Generally, the technical analysis shows that Solana has the potential to regain its value, though it may experience some corrections triggered by macro events.   Featured image from Unsplash, Chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>For traders thinking Solana is controlled by the bears, a popular crypto market analyst, Chris Burniske, is giving a<a href="https://twitter.com/cburniske/status/1618107956922580992" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"> fresh perspective</a> of hope for the major altcoin.   </p>
<p>According to the former lead of Ark Invest&#8217;s crypto department, those who think that SOL is generally bedridden in a bearish mood are mistaken.</p>
<h2>SOL Sets To Make a Breakthrough</h2>
<p>Burniske<a href="https://u.today/you-shouldnt-be-bearish-on-solana-sol-says-analyst" rel="nofollow" target="_blank"> said</a> that the Ethereum killer still has a breakthrough opportunity to rally its price despite its reverse down at a resistance level.</p>
<p>The prominent analyst urged traders not to be extremely bearish on SOL as the coin would eventually retrace its value. He expects the crypto&#8217;s retracement to occur within the next few months. </p>

<p>Burniske, however, cautioned that investors might experience price decline due to the market volatility, which might heighten and cause massive losses for traders who have opened long positions in their leverages.</p>
<p>Since the start of the year, Solana has been in a<a href="https://u.today/solana-sol-down-by-63-healthy-correction-or-cause-for-alarm" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow"> bullish mood</a> and showing signs of resilience and bravery, actually benefiting from the recent market bullishness.</p>
<p>Based on the daily and weekly trading movement since the beginning of the year, the current bearish action of <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/solana/solana-sol-outperforms-top-coins/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SOL</a> can be regarded as a mere retracement, something which is generally seen in other risky assets.</p>
<p>Most Ethereum killers, including Solana, are witnessing a similar kind of price reversal, which signals no major panic on the part of the <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/solana-jumps-by-23-will-a-correction-impact-the-recent-rise/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SOL price</a>.</p>
<h2>Solana Price Analysis Shows Buy Signal</h2>
<p>Burniske’s projection seems to be right based on technical price analysis. Over the past three months, Solana moved in a sideways trajectory trend at an average price of around the $14 mark. But within the last two weeks, Solana has<a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/solana-price-prediction-as-sol-jumps-up-68-just-two-weeks-how-high-can-sol-go-2023.htm" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow"> surged</a> its value by over 68% to trade at an average price of $23.59.</p>
<p>At the time of writing, <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/solana/solana-positive-but-bears-dampen-mood/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Solana</a> is currently trading at $23.18, down 5.50%, with a trading volume of $801,611,149 in the last 24 hours. The altcoin’s market cap stands at $8.6 billion, which puts it the 10th largest cryptocurrency, according to<a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/solana/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow"> Coinmarketcap</a>.</p>

<p>As per the TradingView chart below, the presence of a bullish hammer in the candlesticks signals the buyers are taking back control and pushing the price back above. The green indicator shows the sellers’ inability to drive the price of an asset further down.</p>
<img loading="lazy" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/NYFf5EVL/" alt="SOL price chart on TradingView" width="1575" height="880" />
<p>The 50-day and 200-day moving average settings on the 4-hour price chart further support this bullish trend. The presence of the golden cross, as it is indicated by an asset’s short-term moving average crossing above its long-term moving average, signals a switch from a bear trend to a <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/solana/solana-up-30-in-last-7-days/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">bull trend</a>.</p>
<p>Based on price analysis, the current sentiment is bullish, as this can also be seen in the RSI stands at 64.22, showing that <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/solana-network-on-hyperdrive/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Solana</a> is in the bull territory. Generally, the technical analysis shows that Solana has the potential to regain its value, though it may experience some corrections triggered by macro events.  </p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Solana-2.jpg" width="350" height="250" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>TRON As Currency: Kingdom Of The Netherlands To Adopt TRON As Legal Tender</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/tron-as-currency-in-the-netherlands/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 14:39:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Justin Sun]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[St. Maarten]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[TRON]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tron price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[TRX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[TRX Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=517488</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[On January 24, Justin Sun, TRON Founder, announced that St. Maarten has expressed his wishes to adopt TRON which is alongside TRON’s goals of massive adoption on a global scale. St. Maarten bares plans of adopting TRON TRX price down by 3.31% Price to peak by Q2 of 2023; could potentially shoot to $0.0973 St. Maarten, also spelled Saint Martin, is a country located in the Kingdom of the Netherlands in the Lesser Antilles, northeastern Caribbean Sea. Related Reading: Solana (SOL) Network On Hyperdrive As TVL And NFT Trade Volume Soars Image: Zipmex Decentralization, The Name Of The Game TRON (TRX) refers to the decentralized open-source blockchain network that allows users to seamlessly connect with each other while also providing them access to a myriad of entertainment applications including graphics, videos, and games. Essentially, decentralization remains the focus of the TRON project which facilitates the smooth transfer of money between users without any interference from financial companies or middlemen. Another milestone for #TRON! St Maarten to adopt TRON as legal tender marks another achievement for our push on worldwide blockchain adoption.https://t.co/HXEnouj0Le — H.E. Justin Sun🌞🇬🇩🇩🇲🔥₮ (@justinsuntron) January 23, 2023 The contrasting factor lies mainly in TRX unique architecture, as it is dispersed into three categories or layers: the Storage Layer which has a distributed block storage the Application Layer which is mobilized by developers for creating dApps that are used for issuing tokens the Core Layer which consists of varied modules and smart contracts These different layers are interconnected using a protocol that is compatible with multiple programming languages. More so, the network also has built its community which is fostered towards the goal of speeding up the internet’s decentralizations with the use of blockchain and dApps. On December 27, the TRX community merged with the Enterprise Ethereum Alliance (EEA) bandwagon, which is geared towards promoting best practices with the use of Ethereum blockchain technology, enabling real-world applications and processes. TRON As Legal Tender; Social Volume Up With St. Maarten’s announcement declaring the adoption of TRON as legal tender, its native token responded accordingly with metrics looking positive. TRX&#8217;s social volume spiked which hints at its booming popularity. More so, TRX also exhibited an increased demand in the futures market with its Binance Funding Rate extremely high. Related Reading: Aptos Climbs 75% – What Keeps APT In The Green In Last 7 Days TRX total market cap at $5.5 billion on the daily chart &#124; Chart: TradingView.com However, the network&#8217;s development activity has plunged as seen in the past couple of days which could pose problems for the network. According to CoinMarketCap, TRX price is seen to retreat by 3.31%. The token is trading at $0.06068 as of this writing. Evidently, investors have so much to rejoice about with TRX looking to spike in the next couple of days as seen in the recent market indicators, with the crypto peaking in the Q2 of 2023 or reaching as much as $0.0973. With St. Maarten’s collaboration with TRON, the latter taps into the inclusive and expansive global network which can further boost the island nation&#8217;s economy. Featured image by World Atlas]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On January 24, Justin Sun, TRON Founder, announced that <a href="https://smn-news.com/index.php/st-maarten-st-martin-news/42233-brison-to-adopt-tron-legal-tender-legislation-to-parliament-of-st-maarten-by-initiative-law.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">St. Maarten</a> has expressed his wishes to adopt TRON which is alongside TRON’s goals of massive adoption on a global scale.</p>
<ul>
<li>St. Maarten bares plans of adopting TRON</li>
<li>TRX price down by 3.31%</li>
<li>Price to peak by Q2 of 2023; could potentially shoot to $0.0973</li>
</ul>
<p>St. Maarten, also spelled Saint Martin, is a <a class="md-crosslink autoxref" href="https://www.britannica.com/topic/nation-state" target="_blank" data-show-preview="true" rel="noopener nofollow">country</a> located in the Kingdom of the <a class="md-crosslink" href="https://www.britannica.com/place/Netherlands" target="_blank" data-show-preview="true" rel="noopener nofollow">Netherlands</a> in the Lesser Antilles, northeastern Caribbean Sea.</p>


<h2><b>Decentralization, The Name Of The Game</b></h2>
<p>TRON (TRX) refers to the decentralized open-source blockchain network that allows users to seamlessly connect with each other while also providing them access to a myriad of entertainment applications including graphics, videos, and games.</p>
<p>Essentially, decentralization remains the focus of the TRON project which facilitates the smooth transfer of money between users without any interference from financial companies or middlemen.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Another milestone for <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/TRON?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">#TRON</a>! St Maarten to adopt TRON as legal tender marks another achievement for our push on worldwide blockchain adoption.<a href="https://t.co/HXEnouj0Le" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">https://t.co/HXEnouj0Le</a></p>
<p>— H.E. Justin Sun<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f31e.png" alt="🌞" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f1ec-1f1e9.png" alt="🇬🇩" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f1e9-1f1f2.png" alt="🇩🇲" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f525.png" alt="🔥" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />₮ (@justinsuntron) <a href="https://twitter.com/justinsuntron/status/1617612092642844672?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">January 23, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p>The contrasting factor lies mainly in TRX unique architecture, as it is dispersed into three categories or layers:</p>
<ul>
<li>the Storage Layer which has a distributed block storage</li>
<li>the Application Layer which is mobilized by developers for creating dApps that are used for issuing tokens</li>
<li>the Core Layer which consists of varied modules and smart contracts</li>
</ul>
<p>These different layers are interconnected using a protocol that is compatible with multiple programming languages.</p>
<p>More so, the network also has built its community which is fostered towards the goal of speeding up the internet’s decentralizations with the use of blockchain and dApps.</p>
<p>On December 27, the TRX community merged with the Enterprise Ethereum Alliance (EEA) bandwagon, which is geared towards promoting best practices with the use of Ethereum blockchain technology, enabling real-world applications and processes.</p>
<h2><b>TRON As Legal Tender; Social Volume Up</b></h2>
<p>With St. Maarten’s announcement declaring the adoption of TRON as legal tender, its native token responded accordingly with metrics looking positive. </p>
<p>TRX&#8217;s social volume spiked which hints at its booming popularity. More so, TRX also exhibited an increased demand in the futures market with its Binance Funding Rate extremely high.</p>

<p><img loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/jBpZYQgt/" width="2047" height="979" /></p>

<p>However, the network&#8217;s development activity has plunged as seen in the past couple of days which could pose problems for the network. According to<a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/tron/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow"> CoinMarketCap</a>, TRX price is seen to retreat by 3.31%. The token is trading at $0.06068 as of this writing.</p>
<p>Evidently, investors have so much to rejoice about with TRX looking to spike in the next couple of days as seen in the recent market indicators, with the crypto peaking in the Q2 of 2023 or reaching as much as $0.0973.</p>
<p>With St. Maarten’s collaboration with TRON, the latter taps into the inclusive and expansive global network which can further boost the island nation&#8217;s economy.</p>
<p><em>Featured image by World Atlas</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/a-76-460x308.png" width="460" height="308" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Shiba Inu Declines 6%, Gets Flipped By Litecoin In Market Cap Again</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/shiba-inu-declines-6-litecoin-market-cap/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hououin Kyouma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 14:30:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Shiba Inu]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Litecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Litecoin Market Cap]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ltc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIB]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shiba Inu Market Cap]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIBUSD]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=517419</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Shiba Inu has once again been flipped by Litecoin in terms of market cap as the meme coin has recorded losses of 6% in the past 24 hours. Shiba Inu Is Down More Than 6% Today The year 2023 so far has overall been a pleasant time for SHIB holders as the coin is up around 40% year-to-date. But in the past day, the market hasn&#8217;t been so kind on the meme coin as its price has observed some significant decline. At the time of writing, Shiba Inu is trading around $0.00001132, down 6% in the last 24 hours. Here is a chart that shows the trend in the price of the asset over the past month: The value of the crypto seems to have sharply risen during this period &#124; Source: SHIBUSD on TradingView As can be seen in the above graph, Shiba Inu caught an upwards momentum in the first week of this month and continued to rapidly rise until forming a local top above the $0.00001270 level around a week ago. In the days that followed, however, the coin mostly displayed a sideways movement, until today came around and the asset plunged. Related Reading: Bitcoin Price Just Saw Technical Correction But Key Uptrend Support Intact Over the last seven days, SHIB is now down around over 8%. For comparison, rival coin Dogecoin has only seen a decline of less than 2% in this period, while Bitcoin has observed decent profits of almost 7%. One question arises here: why did Shiba Inu see such a drop? According to crypto whale tracker service WhaleStats, the DOGE-cousin coin has been the most traded token among the top 100 Ethereum whales today: 📰 JUST IN: $SHIB @Shibtoken flipped $NMR for MOST TRADED token among top 100 #ETH whales Check the top 100 whales here: https://t.co/N5qqsCAH8j (and hodl $BBW to see data for the top 5000!)#SHIB #NMR #whalestats #babywhale #BBW pic.twitter.com/WnD70M3mVj &#8212; WhaleStats (tracking crypto whales) (@WhaleStats) January 25, 2023 While high trading activity from whales can sometimes have a bullish effect on the price, as it may be a sign of accumulation from them, today&#8217;s movements from this cohort may actually have been done with the purpose of selling instead, which would provide an explanation behind the decline in the crypto&#8217;s price. Related Reading: Repeat Of April 2019? Bitcoin Rally Shows Similar Break Above These Key Levels Nonetheless, the 500 largest ETH whales were still holding onto more than $600 million worth of SHIB as of yesterday, so even with some short-term selling today, this cohort might have some large long-term positions still set up. 🐳 The top 500 #ETH whales are hodling $606,186,035 $SHIB$149,861,656 $BEST$87,204,580 $LOCUS$82,520,983 $MATIC$70,925,015 $BIT$68,961,547 $LINK$64,312,686 $QNT$62,585,574 $UNI Whale leaderboard 👇https://t.co/tgYTpOm5ws pic.twitter.com/5EWZ77PN4k &#8212; WhaleStats (tracking crypto whales) (@WhaleStats) January 24, 2023 Litecoin Has Flipped SHIB In Market Cap Again Litecoin and Shiba Inu have been fierce rivals on the list of the top cryptocurrencies by market cap in recent weeks, with both coins getting a chance to take the lead at a few different points. With SHIB&#8217;s most recent drawdown, LTC has once more overtaken the meme coin as its decline hasn&#8217;t been as sharp. The below table shows where the two coins stand in the wider crypto sector right now. Looks like SHIB has a market cap of $6.2 billion now &#124; Source: CoinMarketCap From the table, it&#8217;s visible that Shiba Inu has now dropped to being the 14th largest crypto in terms of market cap, while Litecoin has moved up to the 13th position. The coin just below SHIB is the stablecoin Dai, and it&#8217;s not too far off from the meme coin&#8217;s market cap. This means that if SHIB continues to decline, it may quickly fall down to the 15th spot. Featured image from Ferhat Deniz Fors on Unsplash.com, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Shiba Inu has once again been flipped by Litecoin in terms of market cap as the meme coin has recorded losses of 6% in the past 24 hours.</p>
<h2>Shiba Inu Is Down More Than 6% Today</h2>
<p>The year 2023 so far has overall been a pleasant time for SHIB holders as the coin is up around 40% year-to-date. But in the past day, the market hasn&#8217;t been so kind on the meme coin as its price has observed some significant decline.</p>
<p>At the time of writing, Shiba Inu is trading around $0.00001132, down 6% in the last 24 hours. Here is a chart that shows the trend in the price of the asset over the past month:</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone wp-image-517426 size-large aligncenter" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/chart-37-860x319.png" alt="Bitcoin Price Chart" width="860" height="319" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/chart-37-860x319.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/chart-37-460x170.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/chart-37-768x285.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/chart-37-750x278.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/chart-37.png 969w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" /></p>

<p>As can be seen in the above graph, Shiba Inu caught an upwards momentum in the first week of this month and continued to rapidly rise until forming a local top above the $0.00001270 level around a week ago. In the days that followed, however, the coin mostly displayed a sideways movement, until today came around and the asset plunged.</p>

<p>Over the last seven days, SHIB is now down around over 8%. For comparison, rival coin <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/dogecoin/dogecoin-whale-5m-doge-coinbase-bearish/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Dogecoin</a> has only seen a decline of less than 2% in this period, while Bitcoin has observed decent profits of almost 7%.</p>
<p>One question arises here: why did Shiba Inu see such a drop? According to crypto whale tracker service WhaleStats, the DOGE-cousin coin has been the most traded token among the top 100 <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/ethereum/ethereum-surges-whales-elevated-activity/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ethereum whales</a> today:</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr"><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f4f0.png" alt="📰" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> JUST IN: <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24SHIB&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">$SHIB</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/Shibtoken?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">@Shibtoken</a> flipped <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24NMR&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">$NMR</a> for MOST TRADED token among top 100 <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/ETH?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">#ETH</a> whales</p>
<p>Check the top 100 whales here: <a href="https://t.co/N5qqsCAH8j" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">https://t.co/N5qqsCAH8j</a></p>
<p>(and hodl <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24BBW&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">$BBW</a> to see data for the top 5000!)<a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/SHIB?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">#SHIB</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/NMR?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">#NMR</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/whalestats?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">#whalestats</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/babywhale?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">#babywhale</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/BBW?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">#BBW</a> <a href="https://t.co/WnD70M3mVj" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/WnD70M3mVj</a></p>
<p>&mdash; WhaleStats (tracking crypto whales) (@WhaleStats) <a href="https://twitter.com/WhaleStats/status/1618104750750273536?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">January 25, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p></p>
<p>While high trading activity from whales can sometimes have a bullish effect on the price, as it may be a sign of accumulation from them, today&#8217;s movements from this cohort may actually have been done with the purpose of selling instead, which would provide an explanation behind the decline in the crypto&#8217;s price.</p>

<p>Nonetheless, the 500 largest ETH whales were still holding onto more than $600 million worth of SHIB as of yesterday, so even with some short-term selling today, this cohort might have some large long-term positions still set up.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr"><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f433.png" alt="🐳" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> The top 500 <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/ETH?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">#ETH</a> whales are hodling</p>
<p>$606,186,035 <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24SHIB&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">$SHIB</a>$149,861,656 <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24BEST&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">$BEST</a>$87,204,580 <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24LOCUS&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">$LOCUS</a>$82,520,983 <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24MATIC&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">$MATIC</a>$70,925,015 <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24BIT&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">$BIT</a>$68,961,547 <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24LINK&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">$LINK</a>$64,312,686 <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24QNT&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">$QNT</a>$62,585,574 <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24UNI&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">$UNI</a></p>
<p>Whale leaderboard <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f447.png" alt="👇" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><a href="https://t.co/tgYTpOm5ws" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">https://t.co/tgYTpOm5ws</a> <a href="https://t.co/5EWZ77PN4k" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/5EWZ77PN4k</a></p>
<p>&mdash; WhaleStats (tracking crypto whales) (@WhaleStats) <a href="https://twitter.com/WhaleStats/status/1617956444560625673?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">January 24, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p></p>
<h2>Litecoin Has Flipped SHIB In Market Cap Again</h2>
<p><a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/litecoin/litecoin-expecting-a-pullback/">Litecoin</a> and Shiba Inu have been fierce rivals on the list of the top cryptocurrencies by market cap in recent weeks, with both coins getting a chance to take the lead at a few different points.</p>
<p>With SHIB&#8217;s most recent drawdown, LTC has once more overtaken the meme coin as its decline hasn&#8217;t been as sharp. The below table shows where the two coins stand in the wider crypto sector right now.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone wp-image-517432 size-large aligncenter" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/data-1-860x451.png" alt="Shiba Inu Vs Litecoin Market Cap" width="860" height="451" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/data-1-860x451.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/data-1-460x241.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/data-1-768x402.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/data-1-750x393.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/data-1.png 895w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" /></p>

<p>From the table, it&#8217;s visible that Shiba Inu has now dropped to being the 14th largest crypto in terms of market cap, while Litecoin has moved up to the 13th position.</p>
<p>The coin just below SHIB is the stablecoin Dai, and it&#8217;s not too far off from the meme coin&#8217;s market cap. This means that if SHIB continues to decline, it may quickly fall down to the 15th spot.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ferhat-deniz-fors-YOCDD-D4oOM-unsplash-1-460x259.jpg" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>1inch Foundation Allocates 10 Million Tokens To The Delegation Incentive Program</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/defi/1inch-foundation-allocates-10-million-tokens/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dalmas Ngetich]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 13:30:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[DeFi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[1INCH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[1inch Network]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fusion Mode]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Resolvers]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=517454</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[1inch Network, a DEX aggregating platform, has allocated 10 million INCH tokens to its Delegation Incentive Program, a press release on January 24 shows. The goal is to incentivize more 1INCH stakers to delegate their Unicorn Power to resolvers. Incentivize 1inch Stakers&#8217; Delegation To Resolvers 1inch Network wants to increase the number of resolvers within its platform. Accordingly, it launched the 1inch Resolver Incentive Program in December 2022. The program&#8217;s goal was to compensate resolvers for the cost of gas they pay when they fill in user orders.  As part of this arrangement, the aggregator encourages its users to stake 1INCH, their native governance token. Any user who stakes the governance token receives Unicorn Power in place of delegation rewards.  Related Reading: MEV Crypto Bot Gains $1M But Loses Same To Hack Same Day Unicorn Power can either be delegated to resolvers or be used when voting on crucial network decisions. The aggregator has stated that the number of Unicorn Power received directly depends on the lockup period. Stakers who lock their assets for longer will receive more Unicorn Power. Following this announcement, 1inch Network will now distribute 250,000 1INCH to resolvers weekly. The program will run until all 10 million 1INCH are distributed. Funds from the foundation will, in turn, be used to reward 1INCH stakers who choose to delegate their Unicorn Power. However, the 1inch Foundation has stated that the number of 1INCH received will vary between resolvers depending on their network share. Program Follows Launch Of Fusion In late December 2022, 1inch Network launched the Fusion Mode. With Fusion, users can swap transactions without paying network fees.  Depending on the underlying platform, network fees can vary from near-zero, cents, to double digits, in USD terms, in some blockchains, mainly Ethereum. Gas fees tend to spike when the Ethereum network is congested. Subsequently, this can increase the cost of swapping transactions in top decentralized exchanges like Uniswap, a platform whose price feeds are aggregated by the 1inch Network. Related Reading: 1Inch Exchange Co-Founder Disputes Claims bZx Attackers Stole $8m in DeFi Exploit In Fusion Mode, resolvers play a critical role in enabling users to swap without paying transaction fees. In this setup, resolvers fill pending orders. These resolvers are professional market makers who will pay underlying gas fees on behalf of the user. As a result of their participation, they profit from arbitrage trading.  The launch of Fusion was described as a huge step forward for the entire DeFi space by Sergej Kunz, the co-founder of 1Inch Network. He added that swapping on the platform using Fusion will be much more cost-efficient and safer. “This is a huge step forward for the entire DeFi space. Fusion makes swaps on 1inch dramatically more cost-efficient, as users won’t have to pay network fees, plus, an extra layer of security is added, protecting users from sandwich attacks.” 1INCH is trading at $0.514 as of writing on January 25. Feature image from Canva, Chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>1inch Network, a DEX aggregating platform, has allocated 10 million INCH tokens to its Delegation Incentive Program, a press release on January 24 <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://blog.1inch.io/1inch-incentivizes-unicorn-power-delegation-ee381551f78" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">shows</a>. The goal is to incentivize more 1INCH stakers to delegate their Unicorn Power to resolvers.
</p>
<h2>Incentivize 1inch Stakers&#8217; Delegation To Resolvers</h2>
<p>1inch Network wants to increase the number of resolvers within its platform. Accordingly, it launched the 1inch Resolver Incentive Program in December 2022. The program&#8217;s goal was to compensate resolvers for the cost of gas they pay when they fill in user orders. </p>
<p>As part of this arrangement, the aggregator encourages its users to stake 1INCH, their native governance token. Any user who stakes the governance token receives Unicorn Power in place of delegation rewards. </p>

<p>Unicorn Power can either be delegated to resolvers or be used when voting on crucial network decisions. The aggregator has stated that the number of Unicorn Power received directly depends on the lockup period. Stakers who lock their assets for longer will receive more Unicorn Power.</p>
<p>Following this announcement, 1inch Network will now distribute 250,000 1INCH to resolvers weekly. The program will run until all 10 million 1INCH are distributed. Funds from the foundation will, in turn, be used to reward 1INCH stakers who choose to delegate their Unicorn Power. However, the 1inch Foundation has stated that the number of 1INCH received will vary between resolvers depending on their network share.</p>
<h2>Program Follows Launch Of Fusion</h2>
<p>In late December 2022, 1inch Network launched the Fusion Mode. With Fusion, users can swap transactions without paying network fees. </p>
<p>Depending on the underlying platform, network fees can vary from near-zero, cents, to double digits, in USD terms, in some blockchains, mainly <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/ethereum/number-of-new-ethereum-validators-remains-flat-ahead-of-shanghai-upgrade/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ethereum</a>. Gas fees tend to spike when the Ethereum network is congested. Subsequently, this can increase the cost of swapping transactions in top decentralized exchanges like Uniswap, a platform whose price feeds are aggregated by the 1inch Network.</p>

<p>In Fusion Mode, resolvers play a critical role in enabling users to swap without paying transaction fees. In this setup, resolvers fill pending orders. These resolvers are professional market makers who will pay underlying gas fees on behalf of the user. As a result of their participation, they profit from arbitrage trading. </p>
<p>The launch of Fusion was <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://blog.1inch.io/the-1inch-network-releases-a-major-upgrade-fusion-96184d8141d3" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">described</a> as a huge step forward for the entire DeFi space by Sergej Kunz, the co-founder of 1Inch Network. He added that swapping on the platform using Fusion will be much more cost-efficient and safer.</p>
<blockquote><p>“This is a huge step forward for the entire DeFi space. Fusion makes swaps on 1inch dramatically more cost-efficient, as users won’t have to pay network fees, plus, an extra layer of security is added, protecting users from sandwich attacks.”</p></blockquote>
<p>1INCH is trading at $0.514 as of writing on January 25.</p>
<img loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-517457" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/1INCH-Prices-on-January-25.png" alt="1INCH Prices on January 25" width="1270" height="529" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/1INCH-Prices-on-January-25.png 1270w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/1INCH-Prices-on-January-25-460x192.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/1INCH-Prices-on-January-25-860x358.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/1INCH-Prices-on-January-25-768x320.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/1INCH-Prices-on-January-25-750x312.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/1INCH-Prices-on-January-25-1140x475.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1270px) 100vw, 1270px" />
<p>Feature image from Canva, Chart from TradingView</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/1INCH-Incentives-460x260.jpg" width="460" height="260" />	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>

<!--
Performance optimized by W3 Total Cache. Learn more: https://www.boldgrid.com/w3-total-cache/

Object Caching 230/233 objects using apc
Page Caching using disk: enhanced (Page is feed) 
Database Caching 34/43 queries in 0.009 seconds using memcached

Served from: newsbtc.com @ 2023-01-25 23:06:52 by W3 Total Cache
-->