<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
>

<channel>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.newsbtc.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<description>Bitcoin &#38; cryptocurrency news today, price &#38; technical analysis</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2023 02:43:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Polkadot (DOT) Price Slumps Below $6 &#8211; Any Chances For Reversal?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/dot/polkadot-dot-price-slumps-below-6-any-chances-for-reversal/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Eli Dambell]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2023 02:43:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[DOT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bear]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bull]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DOTUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[polkadot]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=528119</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The price of Polkadot (DOT) has been gradually moving south over the past few days. The price decline cuts across the entire crypto market, with strong signs of bears. The cumulative market cap has dropped by 2.58% to sit at $1.25 trillion in 24 hours. Related Reading: OKB Token Shines With 23% Gains On Weekly Chart, What’s Pushing It? DOT has finally lost its grip on the $6 region as the bears became aggressive on the token over the past 24 hours. The market is wondering if Polkadot still has a chance to reverse the downtrend. Polkadot Price Drops Drastically With Prevailing Bearish Trend   The past few days seem to be turning out more negatively for DOT. The asset hovered between $6.1 and $6.9 last week except on April 21, when it dipped.  Currently, the 60-day and 90-day price action for Polkadot shows negative values of 4.45% and 5.36%, respectively. Also, DOT dipped by 12.46% over the past 7 days. Related Reading: These Top 5 Cryptos Are Thriving Despite A Slippery Market After losing its hold on the price level of $7 in February, DOT has maintained a trading price within the $6 region. As of April 21, the price of DOT dropped to its resistance point of $5.8 before correcting.  However, the price analysis of DOT for the past 24 hours shows the token is gradually going down again within the past few hours.  At the time of writing, DOT is trading at $5.921, indicating a slight reversal after plunging. The bearish push on DOT from the past few days has spilled over to the weekend. The crypto market is undergoing a bearish trend, with most crypto assets battling for price stability. Polkadot is included in the market performance. Hence, the selling pressure for the token has exceeded its buying pressure, forcing the price of DOT below the $6 region. Bears Push DOT Below $6 After three consecutive red days, DOT has formed a green candle on the price chart. However, the bears are still in control as they struggle to reclaim past price levels.  DOT has dropped below its 50-day and 200-day Simple Moving Averages (SMA), indicating a bearish sentiment in the short and long term. DOT&#8217;s support levels are $5.15 and $5.75. A decline below its support will bring further price fall. Also, the resistance levels are $6.71 and $7.89. However, the $6 price level has transformed into a psychological resistance level. The Relative Strength Index (RSI) indicator is 39.74, close to the oversold region of 30. However, the indicator points upwards, suggesting a bullish reversal in the short term. DOT&#8217;s indicators are mostly bearish. Its next price action depends on traders&#8217; decisions in the coming weeks. Further drop into the oversold region will likely lead to a trend reversal at the $5.75 support level. Featured image from Pixabay and chart from Tradingview]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The price of Polkadot (DOT) has been gradually moving south over the past few days. The price decline cuts across the entire crypto market, with strong signs of bears. The cumulative market cap has dropped by 2.58% to sit at $1.25 trillion in 24 hours.</p>

<p>DOT has finally lost its grip on the $6 region as the bears became aggressive on the token over the past 24 hours. The market is wondering if Polkadot still has a chance to reverse the downtrend.</p>
<h2><b>Polkadot Price Drops Drastically With Prevailing Bearish Trend  </b></h2>
<p>The past few days seem to be turning out more negatively for DOT. The asset hovered between $6.1 and $6.9 last week except on April 21, when it dipped. </p>
<p>Currently, the 60-day and 90-day price action for Polkadot shows negative values of 4.45% and 5.36%, respectively. Also, DOT dipped by 12.46% over the past 7 days.</p>

<p>After losing its hold on the <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/polkadot-new/historical-data/" rel="nofollow">price level of $7</a> in February, DOT has maintained a trading price within the $6 region. As of April 21, the price of DOT dropped to its resistance point of $5.8 before correcting. </p>
<p>However, the price analysis of DOT for the past 24 hours shows the token is gradually going down again within the past few hours. </p>
<p>At the time of writing, DOT is trading at $5.921, indicating a slight reversal after plunging. The bearish push on DOT from the past few days has spilled over to the weekend.</p>
<img decoding="async" class="wp-image-528122 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/DOTUSDT_2023-04-22_18-19-47-860x501.png" alt="Polkadot (DOT) Price Slumps Below $6 Mark, Any Chances For Reversal?" width="860" height="501" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/DOTUSDT_2023-04-22_18-19-47-860x501.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/DOTUSDT_2023-04-22_18-19-47-460x268.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/DOTUSDT_2023-04-22_18-19-47-768x447.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/DOTUSDT_2023-04-22_18-19-47-750x437.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/DOTUSDT_2023-04-22_18-19-47-1140x664.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/DOTUSDT_2023-04-22_18-19-47.png 1437w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" />
<p>The crypto market is undergoing a bearish trend, with most crypto assets battling for price stability. Polkadot is included in the market performance. Hence, the selling pressure for the token has exceeded its buying pressure, forcing the price of DOT below the $6 region.</p>
<h2><b>Bears Push DOT Below $6</b></h2>
<p>After three consecutive red days, DOT has formed a green candle on the price chart. However, the bears are still in control as they struggle to reclaim past price levels. </p>
<p>DOT has dropped below its 50-day and 200-day Simple Moving Averages (SMA), indicating a bearish sentiment in the short and long term.</p>
<p>DOT&#8217;s support levels are $5.15 and $5.75. A decline below its support will bring further price fall. Also, the resistance levels are $6.71 and $7.89. However, the $6 price level has transformed into a psychological resistance level.</p>
<p>The Relative Strength Index (RSI) indicator is 39.74, close to the oversold region of 30. However, the indicator points upwards, suggesting a bullish reversal in the short term. </p>
<p>DOT&#8217;s indicators are mostly bearish. Its next price action depends on traders&#8217; decisions in the coming weeks. Further drop into the oversold region will likely lead to a trend reversal at the $5.75 support level.</p>
<p><em>Featured image from Pixabay and chart from Tradingview</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/E9BA970008A02E915453DF0723FE059549F9495C7045D0A8251D78248CD865CA-460x242.jpg" width="460" height="242" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>BONE Surges 8.3% As OKX Amasses 1.71 Million BONE Tokens In Single Day</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/altcoin/bone-surges-as-okx-amasses-tokens-in-1-day/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Opeyemi Sule]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2023 10:30:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BONE]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bone Shibaswap]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[OKX]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=528081</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[While the crypto market appears to be in decline, Bone Shibaswap (BONE), the Shibaswap ecosystem&#8217;s governance token, has been on the rise. As of this writing, the price of Bone Shibaswap has ballooned to an impressive 8.3% in the past 24 hours, according to CoinGecko data. However, a broader look at BONE’s market performance indicates an underwhelming run in the past month. The meme token has experienced a 16.8% price drop in the last 30 days. Related Reading: OKB Token Shines With 23% Gains On Weekly Chart, What’s Pushing It? OKX Becomes 13th Biggest BONE Holder Without a doubt, the price rise of Bone Shibaswap is reflective of recent market activity. On-chain data from Etherscan.io reveals that OKX, a prominent cryptocurrency exchange, has acquired a staggering 1,900,736.16586897 BONE tokens (equivalent to $1,788,547.11 ) in the past 24 hours. This acquisition, executed via multiple transactions, pushed OKX to 12th place on the list of largest BONE holders. OKX is not the only exchange on this list, as Singapore-based firms Crypto.com and MEXC Global are also members of the exclusive club. The buying spree kicked off after OKX launched a voting event on Friday, April 21st, inviting users to vote for the meme project they would like to see listed on the exchange. The voting event features five of the most popular meme tokens, including AIDOGE, BONE, BONK, OPTI, and PEPE.  OKX also declared its intention to list the three tokens with the highest number of votes. The voting event will end at exactly 06:00 am UTC on April 24th, 2023. Results are to be announced on the same day at 10:00 am UTC. If OKX does list BONE on its exchange, it will be the coin’s biggest exchange listing ever. Of course, as has been exhibited in the past 24 hours, this would have an impact on the value of Bone Shibaswap. Other prominent exchanges to have listed the token include Crypto.com, Gate.io, Bitget, Bing, and BTCEX. Time To Buy The Dip? Going by the coin’s movement in the past, BONE surged to new heights when listed by a crypto exchange. However, it is worth noting that these price increases were short-lived, as is often the case in the market these days. For example, after the cryptocurrency was listed on Crypto.com in early March, it rallied a 14.8% increase in a few days. By the end of March, the token price had plummeted by a disappointing 30.9%. According to CoinCodex price prediction, the current sentiment for Bone Shibaswap is bearish, with the token expected to lose 6.99% of its current value in five days. Meanwhile, the coin is projected to lose an additional 40% over the next month. That said, this information should not be relied upon as investment advice. BONE is currently priced at $0.945, with a daily trading volume of $4,888,630. Related Reading: These Top 5 Cryptos Are Thriving Despite A Slippery Market BONE trading at $0.9404 &#124; Source: BONE/USD chart from TradingView Featured image from CoinGecko, chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>While the crypto market appears to be in decline, Bone Shibaswap (BONE), the Shibaswap ecosystem&#8217;s governance token, has been on the rise. As of this writing, the price of Bone Shibaswap has ballooned to an impressive 8.3% in the past 24 hours, according to CoinGecko data.</p>
<p>However, a broader look at BONE’s market performance indicates an underwhelming run in the past month. The meme token has experienced a 16.8% price drop in the last 30 days.</p>

<h2>OKX Becomes 13th Biggest BONE Holder</h2>
<p>Without a doubt, the price rise of Bone Shibaswap is reflective of recent market activity. On-chain data from <a href="https://etherscan.io/token/0x9813037ee2218799597d83d4a5b6f3b6778218d9?a=0x6cc5f688a315f3dc28a7781717a9a798a59fda7b" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Etherscan.io</a> reveals that OKX, a prominent cryptocurrency exchange, has acquired a staggering 1,900,736.16586897 BONE tokens (equivalent to $1,788,547.11 ) in the past 24 hours.</p>
<p style="text-align: left">This acquisition, executed via multiple transactions, pushed OKX to 12th place on the list of largest BONE holders. OKX is not the only exchange on this list, as Singapore-based firms Crypto.com and MEXC Global are also members of the exclusive club.</p>
<p>The buying spree kicked off after OKX launched a <a href="https://www.okx.com/help-center/okx-launches-voting-for-popular-meme-token-projects-aidoge-bone-bonk-opti" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">voting event</a> on Friday, April 21st, inviting users to vote for the meme project they would like to see listed on the exchange. The voting event features five of the most popular meme tokens, including AIDOGE, BONE, BONK, OPTI, and PEPE. </p>
<p>OKX also declared its intention to list the three tokens with the highest number of votes. The voting event will end at exactly 06:00 am UTC on April 24th, 2023. Results are to be announced on the same day at 10:00 am UTC.</p>
<p>If OKX does list BONE on its exchange, it will be the coin’s biggest exchange listing ever. Of course, as has been exhibited in the past 24 hours, this would have an impact on the value of Bone Shibaswap. Other prominent exchanges to have listed the token include Crypto.com, Gate.io, Bitget, Bing, and BTCEX.</p>
<h2>Time To Buy The Dip?</h2>
<p>Going by the coin’s movement in the past, BONE surged to new heights when listed by a crypto exchange. However, it is worth noting that these price increases were short-lived, as is often the case in the market these days.</p>
<p>For example, after the cryptocurrency was listed on Crypto.com in early March, it rallied a 14.8% increase in a few days. By the end of March, the token price had plummeted by a disappointing 30.9%.</p>
<p>According to <a href="https://coincodex.com/crypto/bone-shibaswap/price-prediction/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">CoinCodex price prediction</a>, the current sentiment for Bone Shibaswap is bearish, with the token expected to lose 6.99% of its current value in five days. Meanwhile, the coin is projected to lose an additional 40% over the next month. That said, this information should not be relied upon as investment advice.</p>
<p>BONE is currently priced at $0.945, with a daily trading volume of $4,888,630.</p>

<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/FBZJNeYI/" alt="BONE" width="1012" height="601" /></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/1_rnWZgp7LSD8_9Vl_fgMrCg-460x250.png" width="460" height="250" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Celer Network (CELR) Soars 11% Amidst General Bearish Trend</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/altcoin/celer-network-celr-soars-11-amidst-general-bearish-trend/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Semilore Faleti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2023 10:02:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cBridge]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Celer Network]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Celr]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Polygon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[zkSync]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=528079</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Celer Network (CELR) is currently experiencing a market pump amidst a general crypto fall. In a week in which several assets have bled with significant losses, CELR has repaid investors&#8217; confidence gaining 10.8% in the last seven days. According to more data from Coingecko, CELR has gained by 26.3% in the last two weeks representing a far better market performance than market giants Bitcoin (BTC), and Ethereum (ETH), within the same period. However, it must be said that CELR is a long way from its market price as of this time last year, with a staggering 44.4% decline from its year-to-date value.  That said, much of CELR’s price growth in the past week has been driven by a series of announcements by the project, sparking excitement among the user community and increasing traction on the network.  At press time, CELR is trading around $0.0264, having gone up by 3.2% in the last 24 hours. Based on more data from Coingecko, the ERC-20 token has a daily trading volume of $60.67 million and a total market cap of $149.65 million. CELR trading at $0.026 &#124; Source: CELRUSD chart from Tradingview.com Related Reading: China Is Fast Losing Money: Their Bitcoin Stash Just Fell By $388 Million Celer Announces Expansion of zkSync Coverage  For most investors, it is little to no surprise that Celer has managed to stay above the waters during this crypto storm, as the blockchain network has recorded various exciting developments in the last few weeks.  On April 19, Celer Network announced the expansion of its support for the zkSync Network. According to Celer’s Twitter post, users can now utilize the cBridge, the network’s multi-chain cross-layer asset bridge, to bridge ETH and USDC between the zkSync Era network and over 10 other blockchains, including Ethereum, BNB Chain, Avalanche, Polygon, etc.  The zkSync project is a layer-two scaling solution designed to scale operations on the Ethereum network using zero-knowledge (zk) technology. It is currently one of the nascent and most exciting technologies in the crypto space following the launch of its Alpha Mainnet last month. Related Reading: XRP Correction Continues: Elliott Waves Theory Predicts Wave 2 At $0.38 Other Developments On The Celer Network In addition to the expansion of its zkSync coverage, Celer Network also unveiled its collaboration with Polygon as one of the initial launch partners of the project’s zkEVM upgrade. The developer&#8217;s team stated that the cBridge would provide support for bridging ETH between Polygon zkEVM and other networks, including Ethereum, Fantom, Optimism, Arbitrum, BNB Chain, Avalanche, and the Polygon Mainnet.  Meanwhile, BitGo, one of the most popular names in the crypto space, also announced support for CELR this week. BitGo is a leading digital asset security and custody company with over 1,500 institutional clients in 50 countries, including top cryptocurrency exchanges, trading platforms, regulated entities, etc. Featured Image: Celer Network, Chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Celer Network (CELR) is currently experiencing a market pump amidst a general crypto fall. In a week in which several assets have bled with significant losses, CELR has repaid investors&#8217; confidence gaining 10.8% in the last seven days.</p>
<p>According to more <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/celer-network" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">data from Coingecko</a>, CELR has gained by 26.3% in the last two weeks representing a far better market performance than market giants Bitcoin (BTC), and Ethereum (ETH), within the same period.</p>
<p>However, it must be said that CELR is a long way from its market price as of this time last year, with a staggering 44.4% decline from its year-to-date value. </p>
<p>That said, much of CELR’s price growth in the past week has been driven by a series of announcements by the project, sparking excitement among the user community and increasing traction on the network. </p>
<p>At press time, CELR is trading around $0.0264, having gone up by 3.2% in the last 24 hours. Based on more<a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/celer-network" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow"> data from Coingecko</a>, the ERC-20 token has a daily trading volume of $60.67 million and a total market cap of $149.65 million.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/xBW8DMGR/" alt="Celer Network" width="1256" height="875" /></p>


<h2>Celer Announces Expansion of zkSync Coverage </h2>
<p>For most investors, it is little to no surprise that Celer has managed to stay above the waters during this crypto storm, as the blockchain network has recorded various exciting developments in the last few weeks. </p>
<p>On April 19, Celer Network <a href="https://twitter.com/CelerNetwork/status/1648733575015956482?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">announced</a> the expansion of its support for the zkSync Network. According to Celer’s Twitter post, users can now utilize the cBridge, the network’s multi-chain cross-layer asset bridge, to bridge ETH and USDC between the zkSync Era network and over 10 other blockchains, including Ethereum, BNB Chain, Avalanche, Polygon, etc. </p>
<p>The zkSync project is a layer-two scaling solution designed to scale operations on the Ethereum network using zero-knowledge (zk) technology. It is currently one of the nascent and most exciting technologies in the crypto space following the launch of its Alpha Mainnet last month.</p>

<h2>Other Developments On The Celer Network</h2>
<p>In addition to the expansion of its zkSync coverage, Celer Network also <a href="https://twitter.com/CelerNetwork/status/1648778676899643393?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">unveiled</a> its collaboration with Polygon as one of the initial launch partners of the project’s zkEVM upgrade.</p>
<p>The developer&#8217;s team stated that the cBridge would provide support for bridging ETH between Polygon zkEVM and other networks, including Ethereum, Fantom, Optimism, Arbitrum, BNB Chain, Avalanche, and the Polygon Mainnet. </p>
<p>Meanwhile, BitGo, one of the most popular names in the crypto space, also <a href="https://twitter.com/BitGo/status/1649081238333059073?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">announced</a> support for CELR this week. BitGo is a leading digital asset security and custody company with over 1,500 institutional clients in 50 countries, including top cryptocurrency exchanges, trading platforms, regulated entities, etc.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/previewImg-a12c9307b4ea40b2db223a22854fb52a-460x240.png" width="460" height="240" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Price Analysis: Is A Retracement To $25,000 Likely?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-price-analysis-is-a-retracement-to-25000-likely/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Olowoporoku Adeniyi]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2023 09:24:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin price analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=528072</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Despite the relative performance of altcoins in 2023, Bitcoin has seen a significant 75% bullish rally since the beginning of the year. However, Bitcoin&#8217;s price has been unable to surpass the resistance level of $30,000 for a week, and this has stirred a technical belief that there is a possibility of a retracement streak toward the medium-term support level of $25,000. Is Bitcoin&#8217;s Rally Losing Steam At $30,000?  The annual upward movement in the price of Bitcoin, fueled by the banking crisis in March, may be hitting a roadblock at the $30,000 resistance level. To assess the underlying dynamics of BTC, we need to look at an extended chart, which provides a longer-term perspective spanning several weeks. Historically, the bullish reversals in this time frame have shown a well-defined chart structure, with phases of bullish impulses followed by periods of sideways transitions. Related Reading: Ethereum (ETH) Drops 11%, Sheds All Gains From Shanghai Rally The recent bullish reversal in the last quarter of 2022, followed by the rebound from $20,000 that kickstarted the current rally, was preceded by a notable bullish momentum divergence (as indicated by the RSI technical indicator) from the oversold zone. Bitcoin Could Hit The $25,000 Support Level In Coming Days The RSI indicator has entered the technical overbought zone as BTC approached the $30,000 resistance level. The overall chart pattern resembles that of August 2020, which saw a retracement from $12,000 to $9,500 before the subsequent bull run starting in October 2020. Considering chartist probabilities, the scenario of a retracement towards the major support at $25,000 has gained in probability. Therefore, preserving the $25,000 support level would be a key factor in invalidating the bullish trend in 2023. This retracement scenario could be triggered by a break of the short-term support at $28,800; the upper part of the bearish gap opened on Monday, June 13, 2022. Related Reading: China Is Fast Losing Money: Their Bitcoin Stash Just Fell By $388 Million The market is on a precarious edge following a significant session of long position liquidations. To avoid a potential return to $25,000, the market would need to bounce convincingly off the $28,800 level and break above the intermediate resistance at $29,500 to signal renewed bullish momentum. The situation remains fluid, and further price action will provide more insights into the direction of BTC&#8217;s price movement. The Impact Of Interest Rates And US Dollar On Bitcoin&#8217;s Technical Analysis  Bitcoin is currently at a crucial chart juncture, and the market is expected to decide in the coming hours. This decision is likely to be influenced by two key factors from the inter-asset class dynamics: the trend of market interest rates and the behavior of the US dollar on the Forex, which has returned to its annual low and is acting as a support level.  If there is a continuation of the rebound in rates and a breakout of support on the US dollar, it may negatively impact Bitcoin&#8217;s price and increase the likelihood of a decline toward $25,000. On the other hand, if there is a cessation of the rebound in rates and the US dollar support level holds, it may counter the scenario of a decline toward $25,000. The market will ultimately determine which direction Bitcoin takes. (This is not financial advice and is the observation of the author. Featured Image from iStock, charts from TradingView.com)]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Despite the relative performance of altcoins in 2023, Bitcoin has seen a significant 75% bullish rally since the beginning of the year. However, Bitcoin&#8217;s price has been unable to surpass the resistance level of $30,000 for a week, and this has stirred a technical belief that there is a possibility of a retracement streak toward the medium-term support level of $25,000.</p>
<h2><strong>Is Bitcoin&#8217;s Rally Losing Steam At $30,000? </strong></h2>
<p>The annual upward movement in the price of Bitcoin, fueled by the banking crisis in March, may be hitting a roadblock at the $30,000 resistance level. To assess the underlying dynamics of BTC, we need to look at an extended chart, which provides a longer-term perspective spanning several weeks.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium wp-image-528077" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/BTCUSD_2023-04-22_09-51-32-460x231.png" alt="Bitcoin weekly chart shows a steep decline from $30.000 to $27,000: source @TradingView" width="460" height="231" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/BTCUSD_2023-04-22_09-51-32-460x231.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/BTCUSD_2023-04-22_09-51-32-860x432.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/BTCUSD_2023-04-22_09-51-32-768x386.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/BTCUSD_2023-04-22_09-51-32-360x180.png 360w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/BTCUSD_2023-04-22_09-51-32-750x377.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/BTCUSD_2023-04-22_09-51-32-1140x573.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/BTCUSD_2023-04-22_09-51-32.png 1478w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px" />
<p>Historically, the bullish reversals in this time frame have shown a well-defined chart structure, with phases of bullish impulses followed by periods of sideways transitions.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/ethereum-eth-drops-11/">Ethereum (ETH) Drops 11%, Sheds All Gains From Shanghai Rally</a></p>
<p>The recent bullish reversal in the last quarter of 2022, followed by the rebound from $20,000 that kickstarted the current rally, was preceded by a notable bullish momentum divergence (as indicated by the RSI technical indicator) from the oversold zone.</p>
<h2><strong>Bitcoin Could Hit The $25,000 Support Level In Coming Days</strong></h2>
<p>The RSI indicator has entered the technical overbought zone as BTC approached the $30,000 resistance level. The overall chart pattern resembles that of August 2020, which saw a retracement from $12,000 to $9,500 before the subsequent bull run starting in October 2020.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium wp-image-528082" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/BTCUSD_2023-04-22_10-12-31-460x231.png" alt="Bitcoin price appears to be heading for a major price correction: source @tradingview" width="460" height="231" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/BTCUSD_2023-04-22_10-12-31-460x231.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/BTCUSD_2023-04-22_10-12-31-860x432.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/BTCUSD_2023-04-22_10-12-31-768x386.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/BTCUSD_2023-04-22_10-12-31-360x180.png 360w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/BTCUSD_2023-04-22_10-12-31-750x377.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/BTCUSD_2023-04-22_10-12-31-1140x573.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/BTCUSD_2023-04-22_10-12-31.png 1478w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px" />
<p>Considering chartist probabilities, the scenario of a retracement towards the major support at $25,000 has gained in probability. Therefore, preserving the $25,000 support level would be a key factor in invalidating the bullish trend in 2023. This retracement scenario could be triggered by a break of the short-term support at $28,800; the upper part of the bearish gap opened on Monday, June 13, 2022.</p>
<p><strong>Related Reading: </strong><a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/china-is-fast-losing-money-their-bitcoin-stash-just-fell-by-388-million/">China Is Fast Losing Money: Their Bitcoin Stash Just Fell By $388 Million</a></p>
<p>The market is on a precarious edge following a significant session of long position liquidations. To avoid a potential return to $25,000, the market would need to bounce convincingly off the $28,800 level and break above the intermediate resistance at $29,500 to signal renewed bullish momentum. The situation remains fluid, and further price action will provide more insights into the direction of BTC&#8217;s price movement.</p>
<strong>The Impact Of Interest Rates And US Dollar On Bitcoin&#8217;s Technical Analysis </strong>
<p>Bitcoin is currently at a crucial chart juncture, and the market is expected to decide in the coming hours. This decision is likely to be influenced by two key factors from the inter-asset class dynamics: the trend of market interest rates and the behavior of the US dollar on the Forex, which has returned to its annual low and is acting as a support level. </p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-528078 size-medium" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/DXY_2023-04-22_10-02-34-460x231.png" alt="US Dollar Index is currently hovering around a yearly low price: source @TradingView" width="460" height="231" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/DXY_2023-04-22_10-02-34-460x231.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/DXY_2023-04-22_10-02-34-860x432.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/DXY_2023-04-22_10-02-34-768x386.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/DXY_2023-04-22_10-02-34-360x180.png 360w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/DXY_2023-04-22_10-02-34-750x377.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/DXY_2023-04-22_10-02-34-1140x573.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/DXY_2023-04-22_10-02-34.png 1479w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px" />
<p>If there is a continuation of the rebound in rates and a breakout of support on the US dollar, it may negatively impact Bitcoin&#8217;s price and increase the likelihood of a decline toward $25,000. On the other hand, if there is a cessation of the rebound in rates and the US dollar support level holds, it may counter the scenario of a decline toward $25,000. The market will ultimately determine which direction Bitcoin takes.</p>
<p><em>(This is not financial advice and is the observation of the author. Featured Image from iStock, charts from TradingView.com)</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/iStock-1344135727-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum (ETH) Drops 11%, Sheds All Gains From Shanghai Rally</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/ethereum-eth-drops-11/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2023 06:49:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eth price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price action]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shanghai Upgrade]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=528055</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Ethereum, the world&#8217;s second-largest cryptocurrency, has seen its recent rally come to a screeching halt as Ethereum (ETH) has erased all of its gains in the wake of the highly anticipated Shanghai upgrade.  While many had high hopes for this upgrade, which promised to improve the network&#8217;s speed and scalability, the market seems to have reacted negatively to the news.  This sudden drop in price has left investors wondering what the future holds for Ethereum, and whether or not it can recover from this setback. Crypto Market Downturn Drags Ethereum Lower At the time of writing, the price of Ethereum stands at $1,860.72 according to CoinMarketCap, but the past 24 hours have not been kind to the cryptocurrency, as it has seen a slump of 4.05%.  The past week has been even more unforgiving, with Ethereum experiencing a significant drop of 11.02%. The once high-flying cryptocurrency is now left to wonder what caused this downturn and whether it can regain its vigor in the days and weeks ahead. In recent days, the cryptocurrency markets have been displaying signs of fragility, largely due to anxieties about persistently high inflation, fluctuations in the stock market, and the looming threat of an economic recession, which have all contributed to dragging prices downward.  Against this backdrop, Ethereum has been experiencing a steady decline since Tuesday, a trend that has been mirrored in the wider cryptocurrency market.  Bitcoin, for instance, has suffered a drop of over 3% in the past 24 hours alone and has fallen by more than 10% from its recent peak above $30,000, currently trading at just around $27,346. ETH False Breakout Of Local Support Level: Potential Bounce-Back? Despite a recent fall, the price of ETH experienced a false breakout of the local support level at $1,896. However, a daily closure far from the $1,900 mark may trigger a bounce back toward the $1,920-$1,930 zone tomorrow. Related Reading: Shiba Inu Gets Stuck In Price Range – Will SHIB Break Free? Ethereum (ETH) market cap at $223 billion on the daily chart at TradingView.com Related Reading: OKB Unfazed By Crypto Market Bloodshed, Rallies 22% Today On a larger time frame, the situation for Ethereum remains bearish, with the bar on the verge of closing below yesterday&#8217;s low at $1,913.60. If this happens, there is a high likelihood of further decline towards the next significant support level at $1,846, a scenario that may play out until the end of the week. Looking ahead from a midterm perspective, Ethereum&#8217;s price has retreated to the middle of a wide channel, with sellers taking control as the price remains below the crucial $2,000 mark.  This indicates that the cryptocurrency may face continued pressure and struggle to regain its bullish momentum. -Featured image from Zohr]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ethereum, the world&#8217;s second-largest cryptocurrency, has seen its recent rally come to a screeching halt as Ethereum (ETH) has erased all of its gains in the wake of the highly anticipated Shanghai upgrade. </p>
<p>While many had high hopes for this upgrade, which promised to improve the network&#8217;s speed and scalability, the market seems to have reacted negatively to the news. </p>
<p>This sudden drop in price has left investors wondering what the future holds for Ethereum, and whether or not it can recover from this setback.</p>
<h2><strong>Crypto Market Downturn Drags Ethereum Lower</strong></h2>
<p>At the time of writing, the price of Ethereum stands at $1,860.72 according to <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">CoinMarketCap</a>, but the past 24 hours have not been kind to the cryptocurrency, as it has seen a slump of 4.05%. </p>
<p>The past week has been even more unforgiving, with Ethereum experiencing a significant drop of 11.02%. The once high-flying cryptocurrency is now left to wonder what caused this downturn and whether it can regain its vigor in the days and weeks ahead.</p>
<p>In recent days, the cryptocurrency markets have been displaying <a href="https://www.heraldscotland.com/business_hq/23470224.banking-crisis-eased-volatility-persists/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">signs of fragility</a>, largely due to anxieties about persistently high inflation, fluctuations in the stock market, and the looming threat of an economic recession, which have all contributed to dragging prices downward. </p>
<p>Against this backdrop, Ethereum has been experiencing a steady decline since Tuesday, a trend that has been mirrored in the wider cryptocurrency market. </p>
<p>Bitcoin, for instance, has suffered a drop of over 3% in the past 24 hours alone and has fallen by more than 10% from its recent peak above $30,000, currently trading at just around $27,346.</p>
<h2><strong>ETH False Breakout Of Local Support Level: Potential Bounce-Back?</strong></h2>
<p>Despite a recent fall, the price of ETH experienced a <a href="https://u.today/ethereum-eth-price-analysis-for-april-21" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">false breakout</a> of the local support level at $1,896. However, a daily closure far from the $1,900 mark may trigger a bounce back toward the $1,920-$1,930 zone tomorrow.</p>

<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/G2fx2PkW/" width="2047" height="979" /></p>


<p>On a larger time frame, the situation for Ethereum remains bearish, with the bar on the verge of closing below yesterday&#8217;s low at $1,913.60. If this happens, there is a high likelihood of further decline towards the next significant support level at $1,846, a scenario that may play out until the end of the week.</p>
<p>Looking ahead from a midterm perspective, Ethereum&#8217;s price has retreated to the middle of a wide channel, with sellers taking control as the price remains below the crucial $2,000 mark. </p>
<p>This indicates that the cryptocurrency may face continued pressure and struggle to regain its bullish momentum.</p>
<p><em>-Featured image from Zohr</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/a-62-460x306.png" width="460" height="306" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>China Is Fast Losing Money: Their Bitcoin Stash Just Fell By $388 Million</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/china-is-fast-losing-money-their-bitcoin-stash-just-fell-by-388-million/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dalmas Ngetich]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 22:00:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin trading ban]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[china]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=527865</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[When Bitcoin prices fell from $31,000 to below $29,000, the total value of BTC held by China fell by over $388 million to around $5,4 billion.  China’s Bitcoin Stash Fell By $388 Million Bitcoin is trading below $28,500 and looks likely to edge even lower, considering the formation in the daily chart. With every tick lower, China and other countries, including Ukraine and Georgia, are losing money. The loss could even be bigger for the Chinese considering their big stash of BTC, which translates to around 0.924% of the total fixed supply of 21 million, according to Bitcoin Treasuries data. Related Reading: Bitcoin In Danger Zone: Bulls Must Hold $27,700 For Price Recovery, Expert Suggests Records show that China holds 194,000 BTC, 833,000 ETH, and a variety of other unnamed cryptocurrencies. These digital assets were confiscated from the PlusToken scam in 2019 and were worth over $3 billion. FUN FACT: Government of China🇨🇳 is a crypto whale. Chinese authorities seized 194k BTC, 833k ETH, and others from the PlusToken scam in 2019. They forfeited these $6 billion-worth assets to the national treasury. FWIW, MicroStrategy has 130k $BTC. pic.twitter.com/Ilqp7EnenL &#8212; Ki Young Ju (@ki_young_ju) November 2, 2022 According to reports, these assets were tied to the country’s national treasury. Still, some funds associated with the scam are reportedly being regularly sent to mixers and liquidated at spot rates, impacting prices. However, whether the Chinese government still holds these assets remain unknown. There is no official Bitcoin address to verify the status of these coins. PlusToken Scam was a global Ponzi scheme targeting Chinese and South Korean investors. It started in April 2018, taking advantage of unsuspecting people who thought they could make quick money from an investment opportunity. All users had to pay for registration using cryptocurrencies, mainly BTC, before investing. Perpetrators said they were developing cryptocurrency products.  Six Chinese nationals were arrested in Vanuatu and extradited to China to face the law in June 2019. A year later, the Chinese Ministry of Public Security said they arrested other suspects, recovering over $3 billion of crypto assets. United States Is A Crypto Leader  Cryptocurrency trading and related operations, including mining, are banned in China. Therefore, whether Chinese authorities will “trade” these cryptocurrencies for other assets is unclear for now. Related Reading: Quant Explains Bitcoin Funding Rates Pattern That Precedes Uptrends The country outlawed trading in 2017 and mining in 2021, forcing crypto miners, mainly of Bitcoin, to other jurisdictions. Since the ban, the United States has emerged as the biggest host of crypto mining operations. China accounted for over 50% of all crypto mining operations at peak. According to trackers, the largest public Bitcoin mining companies are in the United States and Canada. Riot Blockchain is the largest publicly listed Bitcoin mining company with a market cap of $1.82 billion. Feature Image From Canva, Chart From TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>When Bitcoin prices fell from $31,000 to below $29,000, the total value of BTC held by China <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://buybitcoinworldwide.com/treasuries/#countries" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">fell</a> by over $388 million to around $5,4 billion. </p>
<h2>China’s Bitcoin Stash Fell By $388 Million</h2>
<p>Bitcoin is trading below $28,500 and looks likely to edge even lower, considering the formation in the daily chart. With every tick lower, China and other countries, including Ukraine and Georgia, are losing money.</p>
<a href="https://www.tradingview.com/x/7FtHM1CE/" rel="nofollow"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/7FtHM1CE/" alt="Bitcoin Price On April 20| Source: BTCUSDT On Binance, TradingView" width="1280" height="595" /></a>
<p>The loss could even be bigger for the Chinese considering their big stash of BTC, which translates to around 0.924% of the total fixed supply of 21 million, according to Bitcoin Treasuries data.</p>

<p>Records show that China holds 194,000 BTC, 833,000 ETH, and a variety of other unnamed cryptocurrencies. These digital assets were confiscated from the PlusToken scam in 2019 and were worth over $3 billion.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">FUN FACT: Government of China<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f1e8-1f1f3.png" alt="🇨🇳" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> is a crypto whale.</p>
<p>Chinese authorities seized 194k BTC, 833k ETH, and others from the PlusToken scam in 2019. They forfeited these $6 billion-worth assets to the national treasury.</p>
<p>FWIW, MicroStrategy has 130k <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24BTC&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$BTC</a>. <a href="https://t.co/Ilqp7EnenL" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/Ilqp7EnenL</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Ki Young Ju (@ki_young_ju) <a href="https://twitter.com/ki_young_ju/status/1587917712126144512?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">November 2, 2022</a></p></blockquote>
<p></p>
<p>According to reports, these assets were tied to the country’s national treasury. Still, some funds associated with the scam are reportedly being regularly sent to mixers and liquidated at spot rates, impacting prices.</p>
<p>However, whether the Chinese government still holds these assets remain unknown. There is no official Bitcoin address to verify the status of these coins.</p>
<p>PlusToken Scam was a global Ponzi scheme targeting Chinese and South Korean investors. It started in April 2018, taking advantage of unsuspecting people who thought they could make quick money from an investment opportunity. </p>
<p>All users had to pay for registration using cryptocurrencies, mainly BTC, before investing. Perpetrators said they were developing cryptocurrency products. </p>
<p>Six Chinese nationals were arrested in Vanuatu and extradited to China to face the law in June 2019. A year later, the Chinese Ministry of Public Security said they arrested other suspects, recovering over $3 billion of crypto assets.</p>
<h2>United States Is A Crypto Leader </h2>
<p>Cryptocurrency trading and related operations, including mining, are banned in China. Therefore, whether Chinese authorities will “trade” these cryptocurrencies for other assets is unclear for now.</p>

<p>The country outlawed trading in 2017 and mining in 2021, forcing crypto miners, mainly of Bitcoin, to other jurisdictions. Since the ban, the United States has emerged as the biggest host of crypto mining operations. China accounted for over 50% of all crypto mining operations at peak.</p>
<p>According to <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://companiesmarketcap.com/bitcoin-mining/largest-bitcoin-mining-companies-by-marketcap/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">trackers</a>, the largest public Bitcoin mining companies are in the United States and Canada. Riot Blockchain is the largest publicly listed Bitcoin mining company with a market cap of $1.82 billion.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/China-Bitcoin-460x260.jpg" width="460" height="260" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>XRP Correction Continues: Elliott Waves Theory Predicts Wave 2 At $0.38</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/xrp-correction-continues-elliott-waves-theory-predicts-wave-2-at-0-38/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 21:00:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple (XRP) Price Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrpusdt]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=528032</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Since reaching its yearly high of $0.5842 on March 29th, XRP has experienced a significant price drop. The token has lost its bullish momentum and failed to breach higher levels, disappointing investors who were optimistic about the uptrend of one of the largest cryptocurrencies in the market. It is worth noting that XRP&#8217;s recent price drop is part of a wider market correction affecting the entire cryptocurrency market. Despite this, trader and crypto analyst &#8220;Dark Defender&#8221; believes that there is still further correction ahead for XRP. Related Reading: Is The Final Shakeout Moment Coming For Bitcoin? Expert Weighs In No Signs Of Recovery For XRP? On April 1st, Dark Defender made a bold prediction for the price of XRP based on Elliott Waves theory. According to Dark Defender, the token completed its first wave (W1) at around $0.59 and is expected to enter a second wave (W2) that will find support between $0.48 and $0.38. As of now, there have been no changes to Dark Defender&#8217;s prediction, and XRP remains in correction unless it breaks its resistance level of $0.59 and stays above it for three consecutive days. Dark Defender has provided a list of support levels for XRP, including $0.4812, $0.45544, $0.42044, and $0.38813. The analyst believes that XRP will finish this last correction at one of these levels before targeting the $3 mark.  Furthermore, the analyst has provided a bullish prediction for XRP&#8217;s future, stating that the third wave (W3) of this structure is expected to reach between $2 and $3.47 by the end of this year. However, this wave 3 above $1.33 will be the predecessor of the Grand Wave 3. In scenario 2, Dark Defender predicts that XRP will continue to rise in value. As of this writing, XRP is currently trading at $0.4582, which represents a drop of over 2.6% in the last 24 hours. On wider time frames, the token has recorded significant drops of 11% and 9.2% in the seven and fourteen-day time frames, respectively. This means that if Dark Defender’s prediction is correct, XRP may still have plenty of downtrends to experience, potentially reaching the lower lows of March 21st at $0.380. XRP&#8217;s Wide Adoption Continues To Increase XRP has been gaining traction in recent months, with its unique utility in cross-border payments attracting attention from financial institutions and investors, which has been raising with its continuous innovations to provide a better service to its users.  According to pro-XRP lawyer John Deaton, Uphold, a digital platform that allows users to buy, sell, and hold various cryptocurrencies and traditional currencies, currently holds $1.04 billion in XRP, making XRP the single largest asset holding on the platform. This amount is significantly greater than Uphold’s Bitcoin holdings, which currently stand at $131 million. In addition, the token volume accounted for 28.33% of total transactions on Uphold&#8217;s platform. This indicates a growing demand for XRP among Uphold&#8217;s user base and suggests a positive outlook for the cryptocurrency&#8217;s future growth and adoption. Related Reading: Shiba Inu Whales On Buying Spree, Add 311 Billion Tokens During Price Dip Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com  &#160;]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Since reaching its yearly high of $0.5842 on March 29th, XRP has experienced a significant price drop. The token has lost its bullish momentum and failed to breach higher levels, disappointing investors who were optimistic about the uptrend of one of the largest cryptocurrencies in the market.</p>
<p>It is worth noting that XRP&#8217;s recent price drop is part of a wider market correction affecting the entire cryptocurrency market. Despite this, trader and crypto analyst &#8220;Dark Defender&#8221; <a href="https://twitter.com/DefendDark/status/1649329730624057345?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">believes </a>that there is still further correction ahead for XRP.</p>

<h2><b>No Signs Of Recovery For XRP?</b></h2>
<p>On April 1st, Dark Defender made a bold prediction for the price of XRP based on Elliott Waves theory. According to Dark Defender, the token completed its first wave (W1) at around $0.59 and is expected to enter a second wave (W2) that will find support between $0.48 and $0.38.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large wp-image-528034" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/FuOXb0TWYAc8_qE-860x484.jpg" alt="XRP" width="860" height="484" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/FuOXb0TWYAc8_qE-860x484.jpg 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/FuOXb0TWYAc8_qE-460x259.jpg 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/FuOXb0TWYAc8_qE-768x432.jpg 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/FuOXb0TWYAc8_qE-750x422.jpg 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/FuOXb0TWYAc8_qE-1140x641.jpg 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/FuOXb0TWYAc8_qE.jpg 1366w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" />
<p>As of now, there have been no changes to Dark Defender&#8217;s prediction, and XRP remains in correction unless it breaks its resistance level of $0.59 and stays above it for three consecutive days. Dark Defender has provided a list of support levels for XRP, including $0.4812, $0.45544, $0.42044, and $0.38813. The analyst believes that XRP will finish this last correction at one of these levels before targeting the $3 mark. </p>
<p>Furthermore, the analyst has provided a bullish prediction for XRP&#8217;s future, stating that the third wave (W3) of this structure is expected to reach between $2 and $3.47 by the end of this year. However, this wave 3 above $1.33 will be the predecessor of the Grand Wave 3. In scenario 2, Dark Defender predicts that XRP will continue to rise in value.</p>
<p>As of this writing, XRP is currently trading at $0.4582, which represents a drop of over 2.6% in the last 24 hours. On wider time frames, the token has recorded significant drops of 11% and 9.2% in the seven and fourteen-day time frames, respectively. This means that if Dark Defender’s prediction is correct, XRP may still have plenty of downtrends to experience, potentially reaching the lower lows of March 21st at $0.380.</p>
<b>XRP&#8217;s Wide Adoption Continues To Increase</b>
<p>XRP has been gaining traction in recent months, with its unique utility in cross-border payments attracting attention from financial institutions and investors, which has been raising with its continuous innovations to provide a better service to its users. </p>
<p><a href="https://twitter.com/JohnEDeaton1/status/1647297372613910532?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">According </a>to pro-XRP lawyer John Deaton, Uphold, a digital platform that allows users to buy, sell, and hold various cryptocurrencies and traditional currencies, currently holds $1.04 billion in XRP, making XRP the single largest asset holding on the platform. This amount is significantly greater than Uphold’s Bitcoin holdings, which currently stand at $131 million.</p>
<p>In addition, the token volume accounted for 28.33% of total transactions on Uphold&#8217;s platform. This indicates a growing demand for XRP among Uphold&#8217;s user base and suggests a positive outlook for the cryptocurrency&#8217;s future growth and adoption.</p>

<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large wp-image-528033" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/XRPUSDT_2023-04-21_14-25-42_8d0dd-860x407.png" alt="XRP" width="860" height="407" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/XRPUSDT_2023-04-21_14-25-42_8d0dd-860x407.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/XRPUSDT_2023-04-21_14-25-42_8d0dd-460x218.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/XRPUSDT_2023-04-21_14-25-42_8d0dd-768x363.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/XRPUSDT_2023-04-21_14-25-42_8d0dd-1536x727.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/XRPUSDT_2023-04-21_14-25-42_8d0dd-750x355.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/XRPUSDT_2023-04-21_14-25-42_8d0dd-1140x539.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/XRPUSDT_2023-04-21_14-25-42_8d0dd.png 1814w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" />
<p>Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com </p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/stormseeker-rX12B5uX7QM-unsplash-307x460.jpg" width="307" height="460" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Time To Pay Attention: Bitcoin Reaches &#8220;Logical&#8221; Level</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/time-to-pay-attention-bitcoin-reaches-logical-level/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tony "The Bull"]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 20:04:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bollinger bands]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=528037</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin price is experiencing one of its more significant corrections since the trend began to change directions.  According to the creator of the Bollinger Bands, it’s once again “time to pay attention” — this time because BTCUSD has pulled back to a “logical” level.  Bitcoin Begins Pullback To Logical Level Bitcoin reached almost double from current bear market lows, nearly convincing the crypto community a new bullish trend had begun. With BTCUSD now down more than 10% from local highs, fear is already back on the air in a major way.  Bulls are now all but silent, after just recently declaring the bull market has returned. Bears are already celebrating the correction as continuation of the bearish trend getting underway. Related Reading: Brace Yourself: The Most Explosive Move In Bitcoin In Years Has Begun More tactical technicians, like John Bollinger, simply believe it’s “time to pay attention,” and haven’t yet taken a side. The quote has become a bit of a catchphrase for the creator of the Bollinger Bands. But what exactly is he talking about? The creator of the Bollinger Bands has spoken &#124; BTCUSD on TradingView.com All About The Bollinger Bands The Bollinger Bands are a volatility measuring tool. The tool’s creator recently pointed out an expansion after a lengthy phase or narrowing. This behavior is referred to as a “squeeze” and suggests an uptick in volatility is ahead. Which is precisely what we are witnessing now.  Volatility is the measure of price dispersion across a timeframe, and after very little movement, BTCUSD is like a rollercoaster once again. Ups and downs are par for the course. Related Reading: This “Super” Bitcoin Technical Tool Says Limited Resistance Remains  The Bollinger Bands are made up of a 20-period simple moving average (SMA), to where price pulled back to and has now broken below. The upper and lower bands are set at two standard deviations of the SMA. The next logical level to look for support would be the lower band, located at around $27,000. Once Bitcoin hits the level it could continue downward with strength or snap back to the top of the band.  One thing is for sure, the tool predicting volatility was accurate. Now it’s time to pay attention. As a journalist I often cover the greatest calls by the best in the biz. As a trader, I never forget the corresponding price action, allowing me to learn at every turn. Same vibes. Pay attention. pic.twitter.com/cbpjaK9Ntd &#8212; Tony &#34;The Bull&#34; (@tonythebullBTC) April 20, 2023 Follow @TonyTheBullBTC &#38; @coinchartist_io on Twitter or join the TonyTradesBTC Telegram for exclusive daily market insights and technical analysis education. Please note: Content is educational and should not be considered investment advice. Featured image from iStockPhoto, Charts from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin price is experiencing one of its more significant corrections since the trend began to change directions. </p>
<p>According to the creator of the Bollinger Bands, it’s once again “time to pay attention” — this time because BTCUSD has pulled back to a “logical” level. </p>
<h2>Bitcoin Begins Pullback To Logical Level</h2>
<p>Bitcoin reached almost double from current bear market lows, nearly convincing the crypto community a new bullish trend had begun. With BTCUSD now down more than 10% from local highs, fear is already back on the air in a major way. </p>
<p>Bulls are now all but silent, after just recently declaring the bull market has returned. Bears are already celebrating the correction as continuation of the bearish trend getting underway.</p>

<p>More tactical technicians, like John Bollinger, simply believe it’s “time to pay attention,” and haven’t yet taken a side. The quote has become a bit of a catchphrase for the creator of the Bollinger Bands. But what exactly is he talking about?</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-large wp-image-528039" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/BTCUSD_2023-04-21_15-33-50-860x371.png" alt="BTCUSD_2023-04-21_15-33-50" width="860" height="371" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/BTCUSD_2023-04-21_15-33-50-860x371.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/BTCUSD_2023-04-21_15-33-50-460x198.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/BTCUSD_2023-04-21_15-33-50-768x331.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/BTCUSD_2023-04-21_15-33-50-1536x663.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/BTCUSD_2023-04-21_15-33-50-2048x883.png 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/BTCUSD_2023-04-21_15-33-50-750x323.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/BTCUSD_2023-04-21_15-33-50-1140x492.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" /></p>

<h2>All About The Bollinger Bands</h2>
<p>The <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/topic/bollinger-bands/">Bollinger Bands</a> are a volatility measuring tool. The tool’s creator recently pointed out an expansion after a lengthy phase or narrowing. This behavior is referred to as a “squeeze” and suggests an uptick in volatility is ahead. Which is precisely what we are witnessing now. </p>
<p>Volatility is the measure of price dispersion across a timeframe, and after very little movement, BTCUSD is like a rollercoaster once again. Ups and downs are par for the course.</p>

<p>The Bollinger Bands are made up of a 20-period simple moving average (SMA), to where price pulled back to and has now broken below. The upper and lower bands are set at two standard deviations of the SMA.</p>
<p>The next logical level to look for support would be the lower band, located at around $27,000. Once Bitcoin hits the level it could continue downward with strength or snap back to the top of the band. </p>
<p>One thing is for sure, the tool predicting volatility was accurate. Now it’s time to pay attention.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">As a journalist I often cover the greatest calls by the best in the biz. </p>
<p>As a trader, I never forget the corresponding price action, allowing me to learn at every turn. </p>
<p>Same vibes. Pay attention. <a href="https://t.co/cbpjaK9Ntd" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/cbpjaK9Ntd</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Tony &quot;The Bull&quot; (@tonythebullBTC) <a href="https://twitter.com/tonythebullBTC/status/1649156364860628993?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">April 20, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p></p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/iStock-1294571597-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tornado Cash Suffers 13% Bear Hit, Will Parole Save Price?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/tornado-cash-suffers-bear-hit-parole-save-price/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mudiaga Iritare]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 20:00:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[TORN Token]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tornado Cash]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tornado Cash price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=527955</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Tornado Cash token (TORN) is trading on a negative 13% in today&#8217;s trade session, canceling its previous day&#8217;s gains and rally, which saw the token rise close to the $12 mark. Coinmarketcap data reveals the token to be trading at $8.77 at the time of writing, a significant drop from where it was in price yesterday. The TORN token and its decentralized mixing service platform became controversial when its developer, Alexey Pertev, was arrested mid-last year allegedly for money laundering. However, news about the possible jail release of Alexey circulated the industry yesterday, April 20, and created a rally for the TORN token. Related Reading: FTT Token On a 8% Rockslide Despite FTX Ray Of Hope. Here’s Why Tornado Cash Developer Set To Be Released On This Date According to a recent report, the developer of the TORN token, Alexey Pertev, is expected to be released on April 26, 2023, after spending nine months in detention without trial. The news of his potential release came yesterday when the crypto markets were declining. However, the Tornado Cash token reacted to the news of Alexey&#8217;s release and defied market conditions by displaying bullish price action. While the rally drew investors&#8217; attention, the token could not continue its upward movements today despite positive price speculations by crypto experts and analysts. Alexey Pertev, who is set to be released next Wednesday, will await trial from his home as ruled by a court in the Netherlands. Upon his release, electronic monitoring devices such as an ankle bracelet will be installed on him and other monitoring devices in his home, according to the report. At the time of writing, the TORN token is currently ranked among the top 3 losers in the cryptocurrency market. Alexey Pertev&#8217;s release date is approaching, and we may witness Tornado Cash reacting in price as it did with the news about his release. &#160; TORN token trades in a steep decline after previous day rally &#124; Source: TORNUSD on TradingView &#160; Related Reading: Bitcoin Bears Steal 3%, Time To DCA? Bitcoin Price Impact On TORN Token Bitcoin is on its 3-day bearish candle, failing to break the resistance slightly above the $30,000 price region. BTC price lost momentum after its previous week&#8217;s rally and failed to hold the key support level at $29,200. Today&#8217;s trading session saw Bitcoin falling below $28,000 after it failed to hold $28,600 key support. BTC price fell to a 24-hour low of $27,815 but is now slightly back above the $28,000 price region. Some Altcoins, including the Tornado Cash token, have brutally suffered from the Bitcoin price dump and are still yet to recover. However, a healthy recovery for Bitcoin price will be a good turning point for Tornado Cash as Altcoins are known to react to BTC price movements. BTC price seen trading below support at $28,600 &#124; Souce: BTCUSD on TradingView.com &#160; Featured Image from Istock, Charts from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://ipfs.io/ipns/tornadocash-ipfs.eth/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Tornado Cash</a> token (TORN) is trading on a negative 13% in today&#8217;s trade session, canceling its previous day&#8217;s gains and rally, which saw the token rise close to the $12 mark. Coinmarketcap data reveals the token to be trading at $8.77 at the time of writing, a significant drop from where it was in price yesterday.</p>
<p>The TORN token and its decentralized mixing service platform became controversial when its developer, Alexey Pertev, was arrested mid-last year allegedly for money laundering. However, news about the possible jail release of Alexey circulated the industry yesterday, April 20, and created a rally for the TORN token.
</p>

<h2>Tornado Cash Developer Set To Be Released On This Date</h2>
<p>According to a recent <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tornado-cash-developer-pertsev-freed-110908882.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">report</a>, the developer of the TORN token, Alexey Pertev, is expected to be released on April 26, 2023, after spending nine months in detention without trial.</p>
<p>The news of his potential release came yesterday when the crypto markets were declining. However, the Tornado Cash token reacted to the news of Alexey&#8217;s release and defied market conditions by displaying bullish price action.</p>
<p>While the rally drew investors&#8217; attention, the token could not continue its upward movements today despite positive price speculations by crypto experts and analysts.</p>
<p>Alexey Pertev, who is set to be released next Wednesday, will await trial from his home as ruled by a court in the Netherlands.</p>
<p>Upon his release, electronic monitoring devices such as an ankle bracelet will be installed on him and other monitoring devices in his home, according to the report.</p>
<p>At the time of writing, the TORN token is currently ranked among the top 3 losers in the cryptocurrency market. Alexey Pertev&#8217;s release date is approaching, and we may witness Tornado Cash reacting in price as it did with the news about his release.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/osppCAuG/" alt="Tornado" width="1280" height="595" /></p>

<p>&nbsp;</p>

<h2>Bitcoin Price Impact On TORN Token</h2>
<p>Bitcoin is on its 3-day bearish candle, failing to break the resistance slightly above the $30,000 price region. <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/btc-bears-steal-price-time-to-dca/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BTC</a> price lost momentum after its previous week&#8217;s rally and failed to hold the key support level at $29,200.</p>
<p>Today&#8217;s trading session saw Bitcoin falling below $28,000 after it failed to hold $28,600 key support. BTC price fell to a 24-hour low of $27,815 but is now slightly back above the $28,000 price region.</p>
<p>Some Altcoins, including the Tornado Cash token, have brutally suffered from the Bitcoin price dump and are still yet to recover. However, a healthy recovery for <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-exchange-outflows-spike-bullish-sign/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin price</a> will be a good turning point for Tornado Cash as Altcoins are known to react to BTC price movements.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/IfWR2Kai/" alt="Tornado" width="1280" height="595" /></p>

<p>&nbsp;</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/iStock-1371840452-1-460x248.jpg" width="460" height="248" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Is The Final Shakeout Moment Coming For Bitcoin? Expert Weighs In</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/is-the-final-shakeout-moment-coming-for-bitcoin-expert-weighs-in/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 18:27:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=527977</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[In January of this year, Bitcoin broke above its 200-day MA for the first time since the end of 2021. This was a significant milestone for the cryptocurrency, as it had not seen such a signal in over a year. This breakout was a clear indication of Bitcoin&#8217;s bullish momentum and its potential for further growth in the future. Additionally, Bitcoin retested the 200-day moving average in March and remained well above it, demonstrating its robust behavior. However, the leading cryptocurrency is approaching a lower-level retest at $28,000. Whether Bitcoin will withstand further price decline and continue its bullish trend or if a final shakeout is imminent. Bitcoin&#8217;s Halving Cycle And Potential Dip Below The 200-Day MA Recently, there has been speculation that Bitcoin’s price might be poised for a significant rally as spring arrives. However, the situation is not quite simple as with many things in the crypto world.  According to the expert in the cryptocurrency industry, Mr. Ben Lily, the current halving cycle is an important factor to consider when evaluating Bitcoin’s price movements. When BTC comes off halving cycle lows, it commonly does not immediately clear the 200-day moving average (MA) and stays above it. Instead, it tends to return below the 200-day MA before ultimately moving on to form all-time highs. This pattern can be observed in the chart below, which shows the 200-day MA (represented by the dark red line) and the orange circles, which indicate when the price dipped below the 200-day MA. Furthermore, Lily argues that nothing suggests that the market should expect anything different this time. He believes a catalyst coming this summer will coincide with Bitcoin&#8217;s price dipping below the 200-day MA.  FedNow Rollout And Bitcoin: A Tale Of Two Timing Additionally, Ben Lily has provided further analysis on the potential impact of the upcoming rollout of the Federal Reserve&#8217;s CBDC, FedNow, on Bitcoin’s price movements. According to Lily, if the rollout occurs as scheduled in July, it could benefit BTC’s price trajectory. However, Lily notes that in each of the last three halving cycles, Bitcoin’s price dipped below the 200-day moving average (MA) between 217 and 315 days before the halving itself. If this pattern holds for the current halving cycle, we can expect BTC’s price to dip below the 200-day MA sometime between June and August. With FedNow set to roll out in the middle of that period, Lily suggests we can expect regulator &#8220;war drumming&#8221; to be at a fever pitch. This could lead to a final shakeout moment as Bitcoin drops below the 200-day MA, creating a higher low in the market. At the moment of writing, Bitcoin, the largest cryptocurrency by market capitalization, is being traded at $28,000, indicating a decrease of over 2.5% in the last 24 hours. And, as reported yesterday by NewsBTC, the $27,700 line is key for Bitcoin, as a breakout below this level could signal a shift in the market sentiment and potentially lead to a further decline in price. Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In January of this year, Bitcoin broke above its 200-day MA for the first time since the end of 2021. This was a significant milestone for the cryptocurrency, as it had not seen such a signal in over a year. This breakout was a clear indication of Bitcoin&#8217;s bullish momentum and its potential for further growth in the future.</p>
<p>Additionally, Bitcoin retested the 200-day moving average in March and remained well above it, demonstrating its robust behavior. However, the leading cryptocurrency is approaching a lower-level retest at $28,000. Whether Bitcoin will withstand further price decline and continue its bullish trend or if a final shakeout is imminent.</p>
<h2><b>Bitcoin&#8217;s Halving Cycle And Potential Dip Below The 200-Day MA</b></h2>
<p>Recently, there has been speculation that Bitcoin’s price might be poised for a significant rally as spring arrives. However, the situation is not quite simple as with many things in the crypto world. </p>
<p><a href="https://jarvislabs.substack.com/p/when-to-expect-the-final-shakeout" rel="nofollow">According </a>to the expert in the cryptocurrency industry, Mr. Ben Lily, the current halving cycle is an important factor to consider when evaluating Bitcoin’s price movements. When BTC comes off halving cycle lows, it commonly does not immediately clear the 200-day moving average (MA) and stays above it.</p>
<p>Instead, it tends to return below the 200-day MA before ultimately moving on to form all-time highs. This pattern can be observed in the chart below, which shows the 200-day MA (represented by the dark red line) and the orange circles, which indicate when the price dipped below the 200-day MA.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large wp-image-527978" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/6b9df245-ec9d-4fb4-ae8d-3ff70e9f75b9_1280x606-860x407.jpg" alt="Bitcoin " width="860" height="407" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/6b9df245-ec9d-4fb4-ae8d-3ff70e9f75b9_1280x606-860x407.jpg 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/6b9df245-ec9d-4fb4-ae8d-3ff70e9f75b9_1280x606-460x218.jpg 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/6b9df245-ec9d-4fb4-ae8d-3ff70e9f75b9_1280x606-768x364.jpg 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/6b9df245-ec9d-4fb4-ae8d-3ff70e9f75b9_1280x606-750x355.jpg 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/6b9df245-ec9d-4fb4-ae8d-3ff70e9f75b9_1280x606-1140x540.jpg 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/6b9df245-ec9d-4fb4-ae8d-3ff70e9f75b9_1280x606.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" />
<p>Furthermore, Lily argues that nothing suggests that the market should expect anything different this time. He believes a catalyst coming this summer will coincide with Bitcoin&#8217;s price dipping below the 200-day MA. </p>
<b>FedNow Rollout And Bitcoin: A Tale Of Two Timing</b>
<p>Additionally, Ben Lily has provided further analysis on the potential impact of the upcoming rollout of the Federal Reserve&#8217;s CBDC, FedNow, on Bitcoin’s price movements. According to Lily, if the rollout occurs as scheduled in July, it could benefit BTC’s price trajectory.</p>
<p>However, Lily notes that in each of the last three halving cycles, Bitcoin’s price dipped below the 200-day moving average (MA) between 217 and 315 days before the halving itself. If this pattern holds for the current halving cycle, we can expect BTC’s price to dip below the 200-day MA sometime between June and August.</p>
<p>With FedNow set to roll out in the middle of that period, Lily suggests we can expect regulator &#8220;war drumming&#8221; to be at a fever pitch. This could lead to a final shakeout moment as Bitcoin drops below the 200-day MA, creating a higher low in the market.</p>
<p>At the moment of writing, Bitcoin, the largest cryptocurrency by market capitalization, is being traded at $28,000, indicating a decrease of over 2.5% in the last 24 hours. And, as <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-in-danger-zone-bulls-must-hold-27700-for-price-recovery-expert-suggests/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">reported</a> yesterday by NewsBTC, the $27,700 line is key for Bitcoin, as a breakout below this level could signal a shift in the market sentiment and potentially lead to a further decline in price.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/ywcwTTsu/" alt="Bitcoin " width="1813" height="858" />
<p>Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/kanchanara-9pCV2MB65y8-unsplash-1-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
