<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	 xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" >

<channel>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://newsbtc.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://newsbtc.com</link>
	<description>Bitcoin &#38; cryptocurrency news today, price &#38; technical analysis</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 02:37:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<link>https://newsbtc.com</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Ethereum Price Looks Ready For Another Leg Higher Over $1,300</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-leg-higher-1300/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 02:37:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=514822</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Ethereum was able to clear the $1,240 resistance zone against the US Dollar. ETH is showing positive signs and there might be a move above the $1,300 resistance. Ethereum is moving higher above the $1,220 and $1,240 resistance levels. The price is now trading above $1,220 and the 100 hourly simple moving average. There was a break above a key contracting triangle with resistance near $1,215 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD (data feed via Kraken). The pair could rise further if there is a clear move above the $1,300 resistance. Ethereum Price Gains Bullish Momentum Ethereum price formed a base above the $1,200 level. ETH started a decent increase and was able to clear the $1,220 resistance zone, similar to bitcoin. There was a break above a key contracting triangle with resistance near $1,215 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD. It opened the doors for a move above the $1,250 resistance zone. The price tested the $1,270 zone and a high is formed near $1,271. Ether price is now trading above $1,220 and the 100 hourly simple moving average. It is now correcting gains below $1,260. There was a move below the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the recent increase from the $1,204 swing low to $1,271 high. Source: ETHUSD on TradingView.com An immediate resistance is near the $1,260 level. The next major resistance is near the $1,275 level. A clear move above the $1,275 resistance could another upward move. In the stated case, the price may perhaps rise towards the $1,300 resistance. The next major resistance could be $1,350, above which the price could surge towards the $1,420 resistance zone. Dips Limited in ETH? If ethereum fails to clear the $1,275 resistance, it could correct further lower. An initial support on the downside is near the $1,240 level. The next major support is near the $1,230 level. It is near the 50% Fib retracement level of the recent increase from the $1,204 swing low to $1,271 high. A downside break below $1,230 might send the price towards the $1,220 support. Any more losses might call for a test of the $1,200 zone. Technical Indicators Hourly MACD – The MACD for ETH/USD is now losing momentum in the bullish zone. Hourly RSI &#8211; The RSI for ETH/USD is now above the 50 level. Major Support Level – $1,230 Major Resistance Level – $1,275]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>Ethereum was able to clear the $1,240 resistance zone against the US Dollar. ETH is showing positive signs and there might be a move above the $1,300 resistance.</em></p>
<ul>
<li>Ethereum is moving higher above the $1,220 and $1,240 resistance levels.</li>
<li>The price is now trading above $1,220 and the 100 hourly simple moving average.</li>
<li>There was a break above a key contracting triangle with resistance near $1,215 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD (data feed via Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could rise further if there is a clear move above the $1,300 resistance.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Ethereum Price Gains Bullish Momentum</h2>
<p>Ethereum price formed a base above the $1,200 level. ETH started a decent increase and was able to clear the $1,220 resistance zone, similar to <a href="https://newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-jumps-to-17k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">bitcoin</a>.</p>
<p>There was a break above a key contracting triangle with resistance near $1,215 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD. It opened the doors for a move above the $1,250 resistance zone. The price tested the $1,270 zone and a high is formed near $1,271.</p>
<p>Ether price is now trading above $1,220 and the <a href="https://newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-rise-1300/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">100 hourly simple moving average</a>. It is now correcting gains below $1,260. There was a move below the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the recent increase from the $1,204 swing low to $1,271 high.</p>
<p><a href="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ethereum-2.png"><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-514823" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ethereum-2.png" alt="Ethereum Price" width="1950" height="1109" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ethereum-2.png 1950w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ethereum-2-460x262.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ethereum-2-860x489.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ethereum-2-768x437.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ethereum-2-1536x874.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ethereum-2-750x427.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ethereum-2-1140x648.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1950px) 100vw, 1950px" /></a></p>
<p>Source: <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/ETHUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">ETHUSD on TradingView.com</a></p>
<p>An immediate resistance is near the $1,260 level. The next major resistance is near the $1,275 level. A clear move above the $1,275 resistance could another upward move. In the stated case, the price may perhaps rise towards the $1,300 resistance. The next major resistance could be $1,350, above which the price could surge towards the $1,420 resistance zone.</p>
<h2>Dips Limited in ETH?</h2>
<p>If ethereum fails to clear the $1,275 resistance, it could correct further lower. An initial support on the downside is near the $1,240 level.</p>
<p>The next major support is near the $1,230 level. It is near the 50% Fib retracement level of the recent increase from the $1,204 swing low to $1,271 high. A downside break below $1,230 might send the price towards the $1,220 support. Any more losses might call for a test of the $1,200 zone.</p>
<p>Technical Indicators</p>
<p>Hourly MACD<strong> – </strong>The MACD for ETH/USD is now losing momentum in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>Hourly RSI<strong> &#8211; </strong>The RSI for ETH/USD is now above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Level – $1,230</p>
<p>Major Resistance Level – $1,275</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Depositphotos_103793088_s-2019-460x251.jpg" width="460" height="251" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Price Jumps To $17K and Prints Bullish Continuation Signal</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-jumps-to-17k/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 01:35:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xbtusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=514819</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin price climbed higher above the $16,800 resistance. BTC could rise further if it clears the $17,000 and $17,050 levels. Bitcoin is slowly moving higher above the $16,800 and $16,850 resistance levels. The price is trading above $16,700 and the 100 hourly simple moving average. There is a major bullish trend line forming with support near $16,700 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Kraken). The pair could rise steadily if there is a close above the $17,000 resistance. Bitcoin Price Climbs Higher Bitcoin price remained stable above the $16,500 support zone. BTC started a decent increase and was able to clear the $16,800 resistance level. The price even surged above the $16,850 level and the 100 hourly simple moving average. There was a spike towards the $17,000 level. A high was formed near $16,987 and the price is now correcting gains. There was a minor move below the $16,900 level. The price spiked below the 50% Fib retracement level of the recent increase from the $16,614 swing low to $16,987 high. Bitcoin price is now trading above $16,700 and the 100 hourly simple moving average. There is also a major bullish trend line forming with support near $16,700 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair. On the upside, an immediate resistance is near the $16,900 level. Source: BTCUSD on TradingView.com The next major resistance is near the $17,000 zone. A proper close above the $17,000 resistance might start a steady increase in the near term. In the stated case, the price may perhaps rise towards the $17,500 level. Any more gains might send the price towards the $18,000 level in the coming sessions. Dips Limited in BTC? If bitcoin price fails to climb the $17,000 resistance, it could start a downside correction. An immediate support on the downside is near the $16,750 level. The 61.8% Fib retracement level of the recent increase from the $16,614 swing low to $16,987 high is also near the $16,750 level. The next major support is near the $16,700 level and the trend line. A clear move below the $16,700 support might send the price towards the $16,500 level. Any more losses might send the price towards $16,350. Technical indicators: Hourly MACD – The MACD is now losing pace in the bullish zone. Hourly RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BTC/USD is now above the 50 level. Major Support Levels – $16,750, followed by $16,700. Major Resistance Levels – $16,900, $17,000 and $17,500.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>Bitcoin price climbed higher above the $16,800 resistance. BTC could rise further if it clears the $17,000 and $17,050 levels.</em></p>
<ul>
<li>Bitcoin is slowly moving higher above the $16,800 and $16,850 resistance levels.</li>
<li>The price is trading above $16,700 and the 100 hourly simple moving average.</li>
<li>There is a major bullish trend line forming with support near $16,700 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could rise steadily if there is a close above the $17,000 resistance.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Bitcoin Price Climbs Higher</h2>
<p>Bitcoin price remained stable above the <a href="https://newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-upside-break-17k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">$16,500 support zone</a>. BTC started a decent increase and was able to clear the $16,800 resistance level.</p>
<p>The price even surged above the $16,850 level and the 100 hourly simple moving average. There was a spike towards the $17,000 level. A high was formed near $16,987 and the price is now correcting gains. There was a minor move below the $16,900 level.</p>
<p>The price spiked below the 50% Fib retracement level of the recent increase from the $16,614 swing low to $16,987 high. Bitcoin price is now trading above $16,700 and the <a href="https://newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-consolidates-16-5k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">100 hourly simple moving average</a>.</p>
<p>There is also a major bullish trend line forming with support near $16,700 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair. On the upside, an immediate resistance is near the $16,900 level.</p>
<p><a href="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-4.png"><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-514820" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-4.png" alt="Bitcoin Price" width="1950" height="1109" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-4.png 1950w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-4-460x262.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-4-860x489.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-4-768x437.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-4-1536x874.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-4-750x427.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-4-1140x648.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1950px) 100vw, 1950px" /></a></p>
<p>Source: <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BTCUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">BTCUSD on TradingView.com</a></p>
<p>The next major resistance is near the $17,000 zone. A proper close above the $17,000 resistance might start a steady increase in the near term. In the stated case, the price may perhaps rise towards the $17,500 level. Any more gains might send the price towards the $18,000 level in the coming sessions.</p>
<h2>Dips Limited in BTC?</h2>
<p>If bitcoin price fails to climb the $17,000 resistance, it could start a downside correction. An immediate support on the downside is near the $16,750 level.</p>
<p>The 61.8% Fib retracement level of the recent increase from the $16,614 swing low to $16,987 high is also near the $16,750 level. The next major support is near the $16,700 level and the trend line. A clear move below the $16,700 support might send the price towards the $16,500 level. Any more losses might send the price towards $16,350.</p>
<p>Technical indicators:</p>
<p>Hourly MACD – The MACD is now losing pace in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>Hourly RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BTC/USD is now above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Levels – $16,750, followed by $16,700.</p>
<p>Major Resistance Levels – $16,900, $17,000 and $17,500.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/shutterstock_1182580207-460x259.jpg" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>US Federal Regulators Warn About Crypto Activities</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/crypto/us-regulators-warn-about-crypto-activities/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[David]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 23:45:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[OFOC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Signature Bank]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=514811</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The crypto space received more regulatory attention through the end of 2022. The collapse of one of the largest global digital asset exchanges brought massive losses to the industry. This event spurred several watchdogs to express concerns and issue warning on cryptocurrency engagement. Some US Federal regulators have recently commented on crypto activities&#8217; risks. The watchdogs include the Federal Reserve, Federal Deposit Insurance Corp, and the Office of the Comptroller of the Currency (OFOC). Related Reading: Litecoin Whale Withdraws $32M In LTC From Binance, Good Sign For Rally? According to the report on Tuesday, January 3, 2023, some officials of the three regulatory agencies warned lenders about exposure to digital assets. They cited that the escalating risks should not extend to the banking system. Regulators Cited Associated Risks With Crypto Engagement The warning from the watchdogs is coming after the fall of the FTX digital asset exchange in 2022. Millions of customers lost their funds on the distressed platform, estimated to be more than 8 billion. From their observations, the US regulators cited the high volatility and vulnerabilities seen in the cryptocurrency space last year. They noted the importance of hedging the banking system properly. This will ensure that the risks in the crypto space cannot extend to banks. Also, the regulators highlighted some risks from digital asset involvement in the banking systems. These include fraud, scams, regulatory uncertainties with digital asset custody, platform vulnerabilities, ambiguous statements from companies, crypto contagions, and others. As banking system regulators, the watchdogs pledged their undivided regulatory diligence. This means increased caution and stricter rules on banking organizations when it comes to digital exposure. FTX Bankruptcy Created More Doubts Before its implosion, FTX is rated among the leading crypto exchanges worldwide. It had millions of users and investors from different sectors. Due to its bankruptcy, several individuals and firms exposed to the platform suffered huge losses. These outplay raised concerns and reactions both within and outside the digital space. As a result, US regulators have tightened their regulatory rules on digital activities. Related Reading: Brace For Impact? Bitcoin Open Interest RSI Forms Bearish Divergence As revealed in the bankruptcy filing, some small banks exposed to the exchange include Signature Bank and Silvergate. But the two banks reported that they had only a minimal portion of total deposits on the distressed exchange. According to the US regulators, the broader financial system received less impact from the collapse of the FTX exchange. But the effect is still devastating for some individuals and firms that invested in the platform. Hence, the US watchdogs are coming up with regulatory measures to avert future occurrences in the financial sector.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The crypto space received more regulatory attention through the end of 2022. The collapse of one of the largest global digital asset exchanges brought massive losses to the industry. This event spurred several watchdogs to express concerns and issue warning on cryptocurrency engagement.</p>
<p>Some US Federal regulators have recently <a href="https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/top-us-bank-watchdogs-issue-joint-warning-on-crypto-activities-1.1865354" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">commented</a> on crypto activities&#8217; risks. The watchdogs include the Federal Reserve, Federal Deposit Insurance Corp, and the Office of the Comptroller of the Currency (OFOC).</p>



<p>According to the report on Tuesday, January 3, 2023, some officials of the three regulatory agencies warned lenders about exposure to digital assets. They cited that the escalating risks should not extend to the banking system.</p>
<h2>Regulators Cited Associated Risks With Crypto Engagement</h2>
<p>The warning from the watchdogs is coming after the fall of the FTX digital asset exchange in 2022. Millions of customers lost their funds on the distressed platform, estimated to be more than 8 billion.</p>
<p>From their observations, the US regulators cited the high volatility and vulnerabilities seen in the cryptocurrency space last year. They noted the importance of hedging the banking system properly. This will ensure that the risks in the crypto space cannot extend to banks.</p>
<p>Also, the regulators highlighted some risks from digital asset involvement in the banking systems. These include fraud, scams, regulatory uncertainties with digital asset custody, platform vulnerabilities, ambiguous statements from companies, crypto contagions, and others.</p>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-514813 size-large" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/TOTAL_2023-01-05_02-17-04-860x501.png" alt="Crypto" width="860" height="501" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/TOTAL_2023-01-05_02-17-04-860x501.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/TOTAL_2023-01-05_02-17-04-460x268.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/TOTAL_2023-01-05_02-17-04-768x447.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/TOTAL_2023-01-05_02-17-04-750x437.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/TOTAL_2023-01-05_02-17-04-1140x664.png 1140w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/TOTAL_2023-01-05_02-17-04.png 1437w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" />
<p>As banking system regulators, the watchdogs pledged their undivided regulatory diligence. This means increased caution and stricter rules on banking organizations when it comes to digital exposure.</p>
FTX Bankruptcy Created More Doubts
<p>Before its implosion, FTX is rated among the leading crypto exchanges worldwide. It had millions of users and investors from different sectors.</p>
<p>Due to its bankruptcy, several individuals and firms exposed to the platform suffered huge losses. These outplay raised concerns and reactions both within and outside the digital space. As a result, US regulators have tightened their regulatory rules on digital activities.</p>

<p>As revealed in the bankruptcy filing, some small banks exposed to the exchange include Signature Bank and Silvergate. But the two banks reported that they had only a minimal portion of total deposits on the distressed exchange.</p>
<p>According to the US regulators, the broader financial system received less impact from the collapse of the FTX exchange. But the effect is still devastating for some individuals and firms that invested in the platform.</p>
<p>Hence, the US watchdogs are coming up with regulatory measures to avert future occurrences in the financial sector.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/pexels-redrecords-©️-2743739-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bottom Signal: Bitcoin MVRV Ratio Falls To Three-Year Lows</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-mvrv-ratio-falls-to-3-year-lows/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Best Owie]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 23:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC MVRV Ratio]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MVRV Ratio]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=514782</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin is still stalling in terms of its price movement and has not made any significant jumps in the past couple of weeks. However, there could be a change in the trajectory of the digital asset in the coming weeks as the Bitcoin MVRV Ratio could be announcing a bottom signal. Bitcoin MVRV Ratio Reaches 2019 Lows Co-founder and CEO of on-chain data analysis firm Cryptoquant recently took to Twitter to share an interesting chart. The image showed that the bitcoin MVRV Ratio has fallen to levels that have not been seen since 2019 &#8211; three years ago. Related Reading: Bitcoin Mining Difficulty Sees Sharp 3.59% Drop Now, the bitcoin MVRV Ratio compares the market capitalization of BTC to its realized value. This helps to determine if the digital asset is actually trading at a fair value, if it’s overvalued, or if it is currently undervalued. The lower the value falls, the more undervalued BTC is. The times when the BTC MVRV Ratio has fallen to similar levels as the one shown in the Cryptoquant chart has been when the market had reached its bottom. This is during bear markets when prices decline drastically for a stretched-out period of time before bouncing back up. MVRV Ratio falls to 3-year low &#124; Source: Cryptoquant Looking at the chart, it is easy to spot the times when the MVRV Ratio had been so low was when the previous bottom was reached. One time was in 2015, and the other time was in 2019, a couple of months before the bull market was triggered. If history is anything to go by, then this chart shows that the BTC bottom is already in, or very close to it. However, going by the previous timelines of when the MVRV Ratio has declined so low, it could be a few months at least before another bull market is triggered.  What To Do With Such Trends With the bitcoin MVRV Ratio being so low, it does provide a unique opportunity for investors to buy the digital asset at one of the lowest possible prices before another bull rally. BTC being so undervalued in previous years has only ended in a bull cycle that saw its price hit a new all-time high. Related Reading: Santiment Paints Bullish Picture For XRP, But This May Not Be The Case Even if this is not the bottom, it may be very close to it, so investors may not suffer heavy losses even if the price ended up falling lower. The lack of interest in the market in the market has beaten down investor sentiment but it brings into play a strategy proposed by legendary investor Warren Buffett: “Be greedy when others are fearful.” BTC is trending at $16,855 at the time of this writing. It is up 0.64% in the last 24 hours and 1.21% in the last 7 days. Follow Best Owie on Twitter for market insights, updates, and the occasional funny tweet… Featured image from Medium, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="p2">Bitcoin is still stalling in terms of its price movement and has not made any significant jumps in the past couple of weeks. However, there could be a change in the trajectory of the digital asset in the coming weeks as the Bitcoin MVRV Ratio could be announcing a bottom signal.</p>
<h2 class="p2">Bitcoin MVRV Ratio Reaches 2019 Lows</h2>
<p class="p2">Co-founder and CEO of on-chain data analysis firm Cryptoquant recently took to Twitter to <a href="https://twitter.com/ki_young_ju/status/1610416459766763520?s=20&amp;t=8X82kN3HGvyQM_NyBYKNMw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">share</a> an interesting chart. The image showed that the bitcoin MVRV Ratio has fallen to levels that have not been seen since 2019 &#8211; three years ago.</p>

<p class="p2">Now, the bitcoin MVRV Ratio compares the market capitalization of BTC to its realized value. This helps to determine if the digital asset is actually trading at a fair value, if it’s overvalued, or if it is currently undervalued. The lower the value falls, the more undervalued BTC is.</p>
<p class="p2">The times when the BTC MVRV Ratio has fallen to similar levels as the one shown in the Cryptoquant chart has been when the market had reached its bottom. This is during bear markets when prices decline drastically for a stretched-out period of time before bouncing back up.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-514785 aligncenter" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/bitcoin-MVRV-Ratio-460x262.jpeg" alt="bitcoin MVRV Ratio" width="460" height="262" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/bitcoin-MVRV-Ratio-460x262.jpeg 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/bitcoin-MVRV-Ratio-860x490.jpeg 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/bitcoin-MVRV-Ratio-768x437.jpeg 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/bitcoin-MVRV-Ratio-750x427.jpeg 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/bitcoin-MVRV-Ratio-1140x649.jpeg 1140w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/bitcoin-MVRV-Ratio.jpeg 1328w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px" /></p>

<p class="p2">Looking at the chart, it is easy to spot the times when the MVRV Ratio had been so low was when the previous bottom was reached. One time was in 2015, and the other time was in 2019, a couple of months before the bull market was triggered.</p>
<p class="p2">If history is anything to go by, then this chart shows that the BTC bottom is already in, or very close to it. However, going by the previous timelines of when the MVRV Ratio has declined so low, it could be a few months at least before another bull market is triggered. </p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/yCmm9u1A/" alt="Bitcoin price chart from TradingView.com" width="3284" height="1646" /></p>
<h2 class="p2">What To Do With Such Trends</h2>
<p class="p2">With the bitcoin MVRV Ratio being so low, it does provide a unique opportunity for investors to buy the digital asset at one of the lowest possible prices before another bull rally. BTC being so undervalued in previous years has only ended in a bull cycle that saw its price hit a new all-time high.</p>

<p class="p2">Even if this is not the bottom, it may be very close to it, so investors may not suffer heavy losses even if the price ended up falling lower. The lack of interest in the market in the market has beaten down investor sentiment but it brings into play a strategy proposed by legendary investor Warren Buffett: “Be greedy when others are fearful.”</p>
<p class="p2">BTC is trending at $16,855 at the time of this writing. It is up 0.64% in the last 24 hours and 1.21% in the last 7 days.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-bottom-460x320.jpeg" width="460" height="320" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Former CFO Pleads Guilty: Funds Used To Trade Crypto &#038; Meme Stocks</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/former-cfo-pleads-guilty-trade-crypto/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samuel Edyme]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 20:34:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[court]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[virtual currency]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=514701</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[With the prolonged bear market in crypto ongoing, one will think most people should be losing money. While that is true, another thing also true is the increase in crimes in the bear market. On today’s news, the ex-chief financial officer has pleaded guilty in court for embezzling more than $5 million from multiple special purpose acquisition companies (SPACs) to trade meme stocks and cryptocurrencies. Going by the name Cooper Morgenthau, the former chief financial officer on Tuesday pleaded guilty to wire fraud charges in the U.S. District Judge Paul Engelmayer in Manhattan federal court Former Finance Exec Allegedly Committed Crimes  According to Authorities, Morgenthau had embezzled over $1.2 million between June 2021 and August 2022 from African Gold Acquisition Corp, a blank check company, and underhanded the crime by forging its account statements, and spent or lost all of it in crypto and meme stock trading. Subsequent to that, the SEC said Morgenthau raised a total of $4.7 million from investors in SPACs, aliased as Strategic Metals Acquisition Corp, to cover his losses but lost most of the funds in trading crypto. At his scheduled April 25 sentencing, Morgenthau is said to face a likely jail sentence of about 6 to 7-1/4 years under recommended federal guidelines. Related Reading: Former CFO Pleads Guilty: Funds Used To Trade Crypto &#38; Meme Stocks Ex-CFO Settled For An Agreement  Morgenthau settled for an agreement to forfeit $5.11 million and pay an equal amount in restitution, as well as settle related civil charges by the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission. His Background in the African Gold company seems as though the illegal embezzlement of funds has been a recurring activity from Morgenthau. African Gold, which was established to buy a gold mining business and based in New York, had raised $414 million in a Feb. 2021 initial public offering. The SEC said the company eventually laid off Morgenthau last year in August after discovering his run away with funds and vendors declining to work for the company.  According to African Gold, it terminated Morgenthau at the time after knowing about his &#8220;improper withdrawals” endeavor to conceal them. U.S. Attorney Damian Williams in Manhattan noted in a statement that given the pleading guilty, Morgenthau &#8220;acknowledged encroaching the trust that he owed to his public and private investors.&#8221;  Related Reading: Bitcoin Coinbase Inflows Spike, Is This Bearish For BTC? Meanwhile, the crypto market still seems to be in a confused state with a small rally happening in Bitcoin and other altcoins. So far, Bitcoin has increased by 1.12% in the last 24 hours, gaining over $100 in price. As shown in the chart above, chances are we could see a retrace soon to take out the liquidity in the vector candle. As for other Altcoins, they all also seem to be following the same path as Bitcoin. At the time of writing, Ethereum is up 3% with a trading price of $1251.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>With the prolonged bear market in crypto ongoing, one will think most people should be losing money. While that is true, another thing also true is the increase in crimes in the bear market. On today’s news, the ex-chief financial officer has pleaded guilty in court for embezzling more than $5 million from multiple special purpose acquisition companies (SPACs) to trade <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/the-popularity-of-nft-and-meme-stocks-attract-multi-million-dollar-investments/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">meme stocks </a>and cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p>Going by the name Cooper Morgenthau, the former chief financial officer on Tuesday pleaded guilty to wire fraud charges in the U.S. District Judge Paul Engelmayer in Manhattan federal court</p>
<h2>Former Finance Exec Allegedly Committed Crimes </h2>
<p>According to Authorities, Morgenthau had embezzled over $1.2 million between June 2021 and August 2022 from African Gold Acquisition Corp, a blank check company, and underhanded the crime by forging its account statements, and spent or lost all of it in crypto and meme stock <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/student-400k-cryptocurrency-taxes/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">trading</a>.</p>
<p>Subsequent to that, the SEC <a href="https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ex-cfo-pleads-guilty-stealing-223844651.html" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">said</a> Morgenthau raised a total of $4.7 million from investors in SPACs, aliased as Strategic Metals Acquisition Corp, to cover his losses but lost most of the funds in trading <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/solana/solana-leads-crypto-market-gains/">crypto</a>. At his scheduled April 25 sentencing, Morgenthau is said to face a likely jail sentence of about 6 to 7-1/4 years under recommended federal guidelines.</p>



<h2>Ex-CFO Settled For An Agreement </h2>
<p>Morgenthau settled for an agreement to forfeit $5.11 million and pay an equal amount in restitution, as well as settle related civil charges by the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission. His Background in the African Gold company seems as though the illegal embezzlement of funds has been a recurring activity from Morgenthau.</p>
<p>African <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-vs-gold-mark-cuban-picks-btc/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">Gold</a>, which was established to buy a gold mining business and based in New York, had raised $414 million in a Feb. 2021 initial public offering. The SEC said the company eventually laid off Morgenthau last year in August after discovering his run away with funds and vendors declining to work for the company. </p>
<p>According to African Gold, it terminated Morgenthau at the time after knowing about his &#8220;improper withdrawals” endeavor to conceal them. U.S. Attorney Damian Williams in Manhattan noted in a statement that given the pleading guilty, Morgenthau &#8220;acknowledged encroaching the trust that he owed to his public and private investors.&#8221; </p>



<p>Meanwhile, the <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/crypto-market-remained-fearful-2022-2023-different/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">crypto market </a>still seems to be in a confused state with a small rally happening in Bitcoin and other altcoins. So far, Bitcoin has increased by 1.12% in the last 24 hours, gaining over $100 in price.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-514702 size-medium" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTC-USDT-Chart-460x212.jpg" alt="" width="460" height="212" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTC-USDT-Chart-460x212.jpg 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTC-USDT-Chart-860x397.jpg 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTC-USDT-Chart-768x355.jpg 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTC-USDT-Chart-750x346.jpg 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTC-USDT-Chart-1140x526.jpg 1140w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTC-USDT-Chart.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px" />As shown in the chart above, chances are we could see a retrace soon to take out the liquidity in the vector candle. As for other Altcoins, they all also seem to be following the same path as Bitcoin. At the time of writing, <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/ethereum-defi-suffered-decline-total-value-locked/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">Ethereum</a> is up 3% with a trading price of $1251.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/pleaded-guilty-cryptocurrency-1-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Coinbase Inflows Spike, Is This Bearish For BTC?</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-coinbase-inflow-spike-bearish-btc/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hououin Kyouma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 19:00:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin bearish]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Exchange Inflows]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Exchange Coinbase]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=514775</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[On-chain data shows the Bitcoin inflows to Coinbase have spiked recently, a sign that may turn out to be bearish for the crypto. Bitcoin Exchange Inflows To Coinbase Register High Values As pointed out by an analyst in a CryptoQuant post, a total of 20k BTC was transferred to Coinbase recently. The &#8220;exchange inflows&#8221; is an indicator that measures the total amount of Bitcoin currently being transferred to an exchange (which, in this case, is Coinbase). When this metric&#8217;s value is high, investors send many coins to the exchange right now. Since one of the main reasons holders deposit to exchanges is for selling-related purposes, this trend can have bearish implications for the price of the crypto. On the other hand, low values suggest investors aren&#8217;t making many deposits to the exchange. Such a trend could either be bullish or neutral for BTC, depending on whether the market-wide inflows are also down or not. Related Reading: Litecoin Whale Withdraws $32M In LTC From Binance, Good Sign For Rally? Now, here is a chart that shows the trend in the Bitcoin inflows to the crypto exchange Coinbase over the last couple of months: Looks like the value of the metric has been high on several occasions in recent days &#124; Source: CryptoQuant As shown in the above graph, the Bitcoin exchange inflow to Coinbase has recorded many sizeable spikes in the last couple of weeks. However, as is apparent, there were no significant price moves following any of these large deposits. These spikes were not that big individually. So if the investors who made these transfers dumped their coins as soon as they completed the transactions, it would make sense that they couldn&#8217;t cause any volatility. However, the quant notes that there could be another scenario here. What if the holders responsible for these inflows haven&#8217;t pulled the trigger on the selling yet? It&#8217;s not unusual for investors to deposit their coins to exchanges in advance, waiting for the right movements in the price to exit. Related Reading: Brace For Impact? Bitcoin Open Interest RSI Forms Bearish Divergence All these transfers amounted to around 20,000 BTC entering into Coinbase&#8217;s wallets. At the current exchange rate, this stack would be worth around $336 million, which is certainly large enough to cause volatility in the crypto&#8217;s price if sold all at once. &#8220;Of course, if it were sold right after the deposit, the situation would be different, but you need to be careful if it hasn&#8217;t been sold yet,&#8221; cautions the analyst. BTC Price At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading around $16,800, up 1% in the last week. BTC seems to have seen a small increase in the last few days &#124; Source: BTCUSD on TradingView Featured image from Kanchanara on Unsplash.com, charts from TradingView.com, CryptoQuant.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On-chain data shows the Bitcoin inflows to Coinbase have spiked recently, a sign that may turn out to be bearish for the crypto.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Exchange Inflows To Coinbase Register High Values</h2>
<p>As pointed out by an analyst in a CryptoQuant <a href="https://cryptoquant.com/quicktake/63b4c2842fce6a57fcf1dd8b-What-if-it-hasnt-sold-yet" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">post</a>, a total of 20k BTC was transferred to Coinbase recently. The &#8220;<a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-bullish-whale-exchange-inflows-down/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">exchange inflows</a>&#8221; is an indicator that measures the total amount of Bitcoin currently being transferred to an exchange (which, in this case, is Coinbase).</p>
<p>When this metric&#8217;s value is high, investors send many coins to the exchange right now. Since one of the main reasons holders deposit to exchanges is for selling-related purposes, this trend can have bearish implications for the price of the crypto.</p>
<p>On the other hand, low values suggest investors aren&#8217;t making many deposits to the exchange. Such a trend could either be bullish or neutral for BTC, depending on whether the market-wide inflows are also down or not.</p>

<p>Now, here is a chart that shows the trend in the Bitcoin inflows to the <a href="https://newsbtc.com/terra-luna/terra-luna-up-rumor-coinbase-buys-lunc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">crypto exchange Coinbase</a> over the last couple of months:</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone aligncenter" src="https://img.cryptoquant.com/4739/quicktake/B4LRs1J_faddc82b7043641fbe1d5fc081b01c1e706ef58cf46e08451600e791ecc850f3.png" alt="Bitcoin Exchange Inflow to Coinbase" width="1280" height="806" /></p>

<p>As shown in the above graph, the Bitcoin exchange inflow to Coinbase has recorded many sizeable spikes in the last couple of weeks. However, as is apparent, there were no significant price moves following any of these large deposits.</p>
<p>These spikes were not that big individually. So if the investors who made these transfers dumped their coins as soon as they completed the transactions, it would make sense that they couldn&#8217;t cause any <a href="https://newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-volatility-hits-all-time-low/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">volatility</a>.</p>
<p>However, the quant notes that there could be another scenario here. What if the holders responsible for these inflows haven&#8217;t pulled the trigger on the selling yet? It&#8217;s not unusual for investors to deposit their coins to exchanges in advance, waiting for the right movements in the price to exit.</p>

<p>All these transfers amounted to around 20,000 BTC entering into Coinbase&#8217;s wallets. At the current exchange rate, this stack would be worth around $336 million, which is certainly large enough to cause volatility in the crypto&#8217;s price if sold all at once.</p>
<p>&#8220;Of course, if it were sold right after the deposit, the situation would be different, but you need to be careful if it hasn&#8217;t been sold yet,&#8221; cautions the analyst.</p>
<h2>BTC Price</h2>
<p>At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading around $16,800, up 1% in the last week.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone wp-image-514786 size-large aligncenter" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/chart-5-860x480.png" alt="Bitcoin Price Chart" width="860" height="480" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/chart-5-860x480.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/chart-5-460x257.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/chart-5-768x429.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/chart-5-750x418.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/chart-5.png 975w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" /></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/kanchanara-7E3QGntO66M-unsplash-460x306.jpg" width="460" height="306" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>How This 25-Year-Old Traded $2 Billion In Crypto From His Parents&#8217; Home</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/this-25-year-traded-2b-crypto-parents-home/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reynaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 18:09:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=514800</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Per public filings with the Australian Securities and Investment Commission, a 25-year-old registered a million-dollar-worth trading company at his parents’ house. According to a report, the company successfully traded over $2 billion in Bitcoin and other cryptocurrencies. Related Reading: Solana Leads Crypto Market Gains, How Long Will This Continue? The trading desk is PO Street Capital, and its founder Darren Nguyen lives in an Australian suburb. The report claims that Nguyen and his company tried to keep a low profile and avoided attracting attention over the past two years. However, public records were discovered by journalists showcasing a $7 million profit in 2021 and a 1,400% profit when compared with 2020. The trading desk then scored a $460,000 profit as the crypto bear cycle ended. Crypto Trader Scores Record Profit In 2021 Bull Market In late 2020, Bitcoin revisited its previous all-time high at $20,000. In subsequent months, the cryptocurrency went on a massive bull run. By February 2021, the Bitcoin price was trading at $30,000 before moving upward and reaching a new all-time high north of $60,000. As the cryptocurrency doubled in price, the small Australian trading desk saw its profits swell. As BTC’s price traded to the upside, other cryptocurrencies saw similar or higher profits. The second crypto by market capitalization, Ethereum, rose from under $100 to an all-time high of $4,500. The report claims that PO Street Capital disclosed its performance with the Australian regulator in 2022. However, there is no record of its current profits or trading activity. With the Bitcoin and Ethereum price trending to the downside, an unfavorable macroeconomic condition, high inflation, and an overall downside trend in risk-on assets, PO Street Capital might have seen its profits dwindle. These conditions have led to the downfall of major companies in the nascent sector. From once-a-billion dollar hedge fund Three Arrows Capital (3AC) and the second largest crypto exchange in the world, FTX, prominent companies have had to halt operations or declare bankruptcy protection. Related Reading: Bitcoin Price Plays Catch-Up With Altcoins, Why $28,000 Is A Key Level As of this writing, Bitcoin trades at $16,900 with a 2% profit in the last 24 hours. Other cryptocurrencies in the crypto top 10 by market cap record similar profits and seem poised for further appreciation.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Per public <a href="https://www.businessinsider.com/crypto-investor-traded-2-billion-from-parents-suburban-home-2023-1" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">filings</a> with the Australian Securities and Investment Commission, a 25-year-old registered a million-dollar-worth trading company at his parents’ house. According to a report, the company successfully traded over $2 billion in Bitcoin and other cryptocurrencies. </strong></p>

<p>The trading desk is PO Street Capital, and its founder Darren Nguyen lives in an Australian suburb. The report claims that Nguyen and his company tried to keep a low profile and avoided attracting attention over the past two years.</p>
<p>However, public records were discovered by journalists showcasing a $7 million profit in 2021 and a 1,400% profit when compared with 2020. The trading desk then scored a $460,000 profit as the crypto bear cycle ended.</p>
<h2>Crypto Trader Scores Record Profit In 2021 Bull Market</h2>
<p>In late 2020, Bitcoin revisited its previous all-time high at $20,000. In subsequent months, the cryptocurrency went on a massive bull run.</p>
<p>By February 2021, the Bitcoin price was trading at $30,000 before moving upward and reaching a new all-time high north of $60,000. As the cryptocurrency doubled in price, the small Australian trading desk saw its profits swell.</p>
<p>As BTC’s price traded to the upside, other cryptocurrencies saw similar or higher profits. The second crypto by market capitalization, Ethereum, rose from under $100 to an all-time high of $4,500.</p>
<p>The report claims that PO Street Capital disclosed its performance with the Australian regulator in 2022. However, there is no record of its current profits or trading activity.</p>
<p>With the Bitcoin and Ethereum price trending to the downside, an unfavorable macroeconomic condition, high inflation, and an overall downside trend in risk-on assets, PO Street Capital might have seen its profits dwindle.</p>
<p>These conditions have led to the downfall of major companies in the nascent sector. From once-a-billion dollar hedge fund Three Arrows Capital (3AC) and the second largest crypto exchange in the world, FTX, prominent companies have had to halt operations or declare bankruptcy protection.</p>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-514806 size-large" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Crypto-860x376.png" alt="Bitcoin BTC BTCUSDT Crypto" width="860" height="376" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Crypto-860x376.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Crypto-460x201.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Crypto-768x336.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Crypto-1536x672.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Crypto-750x328.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Crypto-1140x499.png 1140w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Crypto.png 1813w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" />

<p>As of this writing, Bitcoin trades at $16,900 with a 2% profit in the last 24 hours. Other cryptocurrencies in the crypto top 10 by market cap record similar profits and seem poised for further appreciation.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/bitcoin-g219dd9e00_1280-460x345.jpg" width="460" height="345" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Solana Leads Crypto Market Gains, How Long Will This Continue?</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/solana/solana-leads-crypto-market-gains/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Best Owie]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 17:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Solana]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sol]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SOL Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Solana performance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SOLUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SOLUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=514781</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Solana (SOL) has been ahead of the rest of the crypto market when it comes to gains. The market had seen renewed interest following the holidays which led to a small recovery here and there especially for the large players but Solana had been able to break completely from the trend and record double-digit gains in the last couple of days. What Is Driving Solana’s Growth? Despite being at the forefront of massive FUD that has dragged its price down toward two-year lows, Solana has now been able to recover a good amount of gains over the last few days. While the comments from Ethereum founder Vitalik Buterin in support of the blockchain had helped, there was another factor pushing the price higher. Related Reading: Santiment Paints Bullish Picture For XRP, But This May Not Be The Case A new meme coin known as BONK had graced the Solana ecosystem and after being airdropped to holders of major NFT projects, the price of the meme coin had soared. The resulting gains would see investors FOMO into the cryptocurrency and since they needed to trade on the Solana network, the price of SOL had surged given all of the new attention it was receiving. In two days, SOL ballooned to become one of the best performers in the space coming into the new year. It is up over 16% in the last 24 hours alone and the price of the digital asset has moved from the loss territory into the green over the last week. It is now sitting at almost 37% gains for investors over this time period, according to data from Coinmarketcap. Can SOL Hold The Gains? Right now, the growth of SOL in the market is still largely driven by the FOMO triggered by the BONK meme coin. Since the hype around this coin has been waxing strong, it is expected that interest will remain high among investors, thereby sustaining the growth trend recorded by Solana. Related Reading: Bitcoin Mining Difficulty Sees Sharp 3.59% Drop However, it is important to keep in mind that the BONK cryptocurrency is largely driven by hype, and just like any other meme coin, it is expected that this hype would die down at some point. Now, once this happens, the decline in interest would also significantly impact the price of SOL, dragging it down along with it. That is unless something else comes up to drive the price of SOL higher. It is also expected that some profit-taking would begin, where investors would begin to dump SOL to claim the gains already being seen. This, as well, will contribute to a wind-down, and a downward correction would follow. But this correction is not expected to claim more than 10% of current profits given that the price of SOL is now trading above its 20-day moving average of $12.3. SOL is changing hands at $13.72 at the time of this writing. It has overtaken Shiba Inu to become the 15th largest cryptocurrency with a market cap of $5.04 billion. Follow Best Owie on Twitter for market insights, updates, and the occasional funny tweet… Featured image from Analytics Insight, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="p2">Solana (SOL) has been ahead of the rest of the crypto market when it comes to gains. The market had seen renewed interest following the holidays which led to a small recovery here and there especially for the large players but Solana had been able to break completely from the trend and record double-digit gains in the last couple of days.</p>
<h2 class="p2">What Is Driving Solana’s Growth?</h2>
<p class="p2">Despite being at the forefront of massive FUD that has dragged its price down toward two-year lows, Solana has now been able to recover a good amount of gains over the last few days. While the <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/solana/solana-support-from-ethereum-founder/">comments from Ethereum founder Vitalik Buterin</a> in support of the blockchain had helped, there was another factor pushing the price higher.</p>

<p class="p2">A new meme coin known as BONK had graced the Solana ecosystem and after being airdropped to holders of major NFT projects, the price of the meme coin had soared. The resulting gains would see investors FOMO into the cryptocurrency and since they needed to trade on the Solana network, the price of SOL had surged given all of the new attention it was receiving.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/72Dnthx0/" alt="Solana (SOL) price chart from TradingView.com" width="3284" height="1646" /></p>
<p class="p2">In two days, SOL ballooned to become one of the best performers in the space coming into the new year. It is up over 16% in the last 24 hours alone and the price of the digital asset has moved from the loss territory into the green over the last week. It is now sitting at almost 37% gains for investors over this time period, according to data from Coinmarketcap.</p>
<h2 class="p2">Can SOL Hold The Gains?</h2>
<p class="p2">Right now, the growth of SOL in the market is still largely driven by the FOMO triggered by the BONK meme coin. Since the hype around this coin has been waxing strong, it is expected that interest will remain high among investors, thereby sustaining the growth trend recorded by Solana.</p>

<p class="p2">However, it is important to keep in mind that the BONK cryptocurrency is largely driven by hype, and just like any other meme coin, it is expected that this hype would die down at some point. Now, once this happens, the decline in interest would also significantly impact the price of SOL, dragging it down along with it. That is unless something else comes up to drive the price of SOL higher.</p>
<p class="p2">It is also expected that some profit-taking would begin, where investors would begin to dump SOL to claim the gains already being seen. This, as well, will contribute to a wind-down, and a downward correction would follow. But this correction is not expected to claim more than 10% of current profits given that the price of SOL is now trading above its 20-day moving average of $12.3.</p>
<p class="p2">SOL is changing hands at $13.72 at the time of this writing. It has overtaken Shiba Inu to become the 15th largest cryptocurrency with a market cap of $5.04 billion.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Solana-SOL-460x256.jpeg" width="460" height="256" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Price Plays Catch-Up With Altcoins, Why $28,000 Is A Key Level</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-price-catch-up-28000-is-key-level/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reynaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 14:41:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=514763</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Bitcoin price is finally seeing some profits, but it seems weak compared to other crypto assets. The macroeconomic environment is waking up, shaking things across all asset classes.  Related Reading: Ethereum Stakers In Massive Loss As 80% of Staked ETH Is In The Red As of this writing, the Bitcoin price trades at $16,800 with sideways movement in the last 24 hours. In the crypto top 10, BTC is lagging behind Ethereum, Binance Coin, and Cardano. These cryptocurrencies are positively reacting to the start of 2023.  Bitcoin Price Aims For Higher Levels Per a recent report from the trading desk QCP Capital, institutions are returning to action and allocating capital in Gold and other assets. The precious metal has seen a 15% rally in the past 60 days and keeps trending upwards.  The trading desk believes institutions are allocating into &#8220;alternative assets&#8221; or stores of value. The Bitcoin price is yet to benefit from this trend, but the crypto market is recording some profits. In particular, the non-fungible token space.  This sector is coming back to life after months of declining activity. Popular NFT collections experienced 2 to 3x profits in late 2022 and are likely to maintain the trend. QCP Capital noted Bitcoin and Ethereum&#8217;s price action:  (…) in line with Gold and NFTs, BTC and ETH are playing catch up to some extent at the start of the year. Despite the mini rally, BTC is still trading in an extremely tight falling wedge &#8211; with 18k the key breakout level to the topside. If the Bitcoin price can flip $18,000 and trend higher on the back of institutional allocation to alternative assets, the cryptocurrency could reclaim higher levels. The trading desk points to $28,000 as a critical level to watch.  This level is the neckline of the &#8220;Head and Shoulders&#8221; pattern formed by BTC in the past two years. In addition, $28,000 has confluence with the 61.8% Fibonacci Retracement level, meaning many players will keep an eye on it.  What Could Operate As An Obstacle For Bitcoin In the short term, the Bitcoin price is seeing resistance at its current levels. Analyst Caleb Franzen claims that BTC is likely to continue seeing resistance around these prices and higher.  Related Reading: Brace For Impact? Bitcoin Open Interest RSI Forms Bearish Divergence In 2022, the levels at $17,000 operated as critical support. Once lost, these levels turned into significant resistance, likely creating friction for the cryptocurrency. As the analyst pointed out, Bitcoin was already rejected from these levels in an attempt to rally beyond the $18,000 mark. Franzen said: Bitcoin is decisively within a potential resistance range. Even if price manages to break above this diagonal resistance channel, we can&#8217;t ignore overhead resistance from the former 2022 support range. We&#8217;ve already been rejected there once&#8230;]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>The Bitcoin price is finally seeing some profits, but it seems weak compared to other crypto assets. The macroeconomic environment is waking up, shaking things across all asset classes. </strong></p>

<p>As of this writing, the Bitcoin price trades at $16,800 with sideways movement in the last 24 hours. In the crypto top 10, BTC is lagging behind Ethereum, Binance Coin, and Cardano. These cryptocurrencies are positively reacting to the start of 2023. </p>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-514780 size-large" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-price-BTC-BTCUSDT-1-860x376.png" alt="Bitcoin price BTC BTCUSDT" width="860" height="376" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-price-BTC-BTCUSDT-1-860x376.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-price-BTC-BTCUSDT-1-460x201.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-price-BTC-BTCUSDT-1-768x336.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-price-BTC-BTCUSDT-1-1536x672.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-price-BTC-BTCUSDT-1-750x328.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-price-BTC-BTCUSDT-1-1140x499.png 1140w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-price-BTC-BTCUSDT-1.png 1813w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" />
<h2>Bitcoin Price Aims For Higher Levels</h2>
<p>Per a recent <a href="https://twitter.com/QCPCapital/status/1610549208955912192" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">report</a> from the trading desk QCP Capital, institutions are returning to action and allocating capital in Gold and other assets. The precious metal has seen a 15% rally in the past 60 days and keeps trending upwards. </p>
<p>The trading desk believes institutions are allocating into &#8220;alternative assets&#8221; or stores of value. The Bitcoin price is yet to benefit from this trend, but the crypto market is recording some profits. In particular, the non-fungible token space. </p>
<p>This sector is coming back to life after months of declining activity. Popular NFT collections experienced 2 to 3x profits in late 2022 and are likely to maintain the trend. QCP Capital noted Bitcoin and Ethereum&#8217;s price action: </p>
<blockquote><p>(…) in line with Gold and NFTs, BTC and ETH are playing catch up to some extent at the start of the year. Despite the mini rally, BTC is still trading in an extremely tight falling wedge &#8211; with 18k the key breakout level to the topside.</p></blockquote>
<p>If the Bitcoin price can flip $18,000 and trend higher on the back of institutional allocation to alternative assets, the cryptocurrency could reclaim higher levels. The trading desk points to $28,000 as a critical level to watch. </p>
<p>This level is the neckline of the &#8220;Head and Shoulders&#8221; pattern formed by BTC in the past two years. In addition, $28,000 has confluence with the 61.8% Fibonacci Retracement level, meaning many players will keep an eye on it. </p>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-514779 size-medium" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-price-BTC-BTCUSDT-chart-2-fib-458x460.jpeg" alt="Bitcoin price BTC BTCUSDT chart 2 fib" width="458" height="460" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-price-BTC-BTCUSDT-chart-2-fib-458x460.jpeg 458w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-price-BTC-BTCUSDT-chart-2-fib-857x860.jpeg 857w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-price-BTC-BTCUSDT-chart-2-fib-200x200.jpeg 200w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-price-BTC-BTCUSDT-chart-2-fib-768x771.jpeg 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-price-BTC-BTCUSDT-chart-2-fib-42x42.jpeg 42w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-price-BTC-BTCUSDT-chart-2-fib-75x75.jpeg 75w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-price-BTC-BTCUSDT-chart-2-fib-750x753.jpeg 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-price-BTC-BTCUSDT-chart-2-fib-1140x1144.jpeg 1140w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-price-BTC-BTCUSDT-chart-2-fib.jpeg 1268w" sizes="(max-width: 458px) 100vw, 458px" />
What Could Operate As An Obstacle For Bitcoin
<p>In the short term, the Bitcoin price is seeing resistance at its current levels. Analyst Caleb Franzen <a href="https://twitter.com/CalebFranzen/status/1610640812521422848/photo/1" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">claims</a> that BTC is likely to continue seeing resistance around these prices and higher. </p>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-514778 size-large" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-3-860x483.jpeg" alt="Bitcoin BTC BTCUSDT Chart 3" width="860" height="483" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-3-860x483.jpeg 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-3-460x258.jpeg 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-3-768x431.jpeg 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-3-1536x863.jpeg 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-3-2048x1150.jpeg 2048w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-3-750x421.jpeg 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-3-1140x640.jpeg 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" />

<p>In 2022, the levels at $17,000 operated as critical support. Once lost, these levels turned into significant resistance, likely creating friction for the cryptocurrency. As the analyst pointed out, Bitcoin was already rejected from these levels in an attempt to rally beyond the $18,000 mark. Franzen said:</p>
<blockquote><p>Bitcoin is decisively within a potential resistance range. Even if price manages to break above this diagonal resistance channel, we can&#8217;t ignore overhead resistance from the former 2022 support range. We&#8217;ve already been rejected there once&#8230;</p></blockquote>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-460x306.jpeg" width="460" height="306" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum Stakers In Massive Loss As 80% of Staked ETH Is In The Red</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/ethereum-stakers-in-massive-loss/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samuel Edyme]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 14:30:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technical analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=514754</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The bear market has resulted in multiple losses for individuals and even large entities, and according to recent data shared by crypto analytics site, Dune analytics, the majority of all ETH stakers are in the loss while fewer stakers remain in the money. The reason behind the result of more losses than profit is due to the market conditions starting in 2021 after the Ethereum Beacon chain was launched, to the present. ETH had reached a new all-time high (ATH) but has also fallen by more than 50% from the ATH. Related Reading: Ethereum Price Key Trend is Forming and Swift Recovery Could Occur Weekly Staked ETH Fall To Lowest Levels as Only 20% Of ETH Staked Is In Money The January 4 published data further showed that 80% of ETH staked are currently recording losses. The stakers who happen to be part of the 20% still in money are those that staked ETH at prices lower than the current levels.  Per the data, a significant chunk of staked ETH was staked when ETH was still in the $600 price range — this dates back to December 2020 when the Beacon Chain was launched. Though ETH has since increased to a point where it’s now 50% higher than the 2020 price level, 80% of the currently staked ETH was staked at prices equal to or above $1,200. Following the massive losses recorded in staked ETH, the amount of weekly staked ETH has seen a sharp decline with fewer ETH staked since the last quarter of 2022. Over the past week, only a total of 25,000 ETH has been staked.  Prior to the extreme market conditions, figures of roughly 150,000 ETH were being staked per week. Should ETH continue into a downward movement, chances are there could be massive withdrawals from ETH staking contracts when a withdrawal mechanism is implemented later this year.  Considering The Long Term Perspective  Another narrative worth considering is the long-term perspective. Given the fact that most stakers already had an initial idea of keeping their ETH for the long term, they might as well turn a blind eye to the current price levels of Ethereum.  Besides, staking ETH directly or through an exchange would usually involve a committed two-year lockup period. For context, 15.9 million ETH is currently staked, representing 13.2% of the entire supply, according to Dune data reports.  Related Reading: Ethereum Price Relatively Muted, Bulls Still Aim Key Upside Break However, even with the dip that seems to be never-ending, there are still hopes for Ethereum and even other altcoins. As of the time of writing, ETH is up by over 3% in the last 24 hours with a trading volume of $5.2 billion over the same time period. Furthermore, a reversal is expected to happen, given the sharp upwards movements in what seems to be a false move. Featured image from istock, Dune analytics and TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The bear market has resulted in multiple losses for individuals and even large entities, and according to recent <a href="https://dune.com/hildobby/ETH2-Deposits?utm_source=Dune" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">data</a> shared by crypto analytics site, Dune analytics, the majority of all ETH stakers are in the loss while fewer stakers remain in the money.</p>
<p>The reason behind the result of more losses than profit is due to the market conditions starting in 2021 after the <a href="https://newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-rise-1300/">Ethereum</a> Beacon chain was launched, to the present. ETH had reached a new all-time high (ATH) but has also fallen by more than 50% from the ATH.</p>

<h2>Weekly Staked ETH Fall To Lowest Levels as Only 20% Of ETH Staked Is In Money</h2>
<p>The January 4 published data further showed that 80% of ETH staked are currently recording losses. The stakers who happen to be part of the 20% still in money are those that staked <a href="https://newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-faces-hurdles-1250/">ETH</a> at prices lower than the current levels. </p>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-514764 size-medium" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/photo_5886306117607340888_y-460x259.jpg" alt="Dune analytics stats on staked ETH prices" width="460" height="259" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/photo_5886306117607340888_y-460x259.jpg 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/photo_5886306117607340888_y-860x484.jpg 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/photo_5886306117607340888_y-768x432.jpg 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/photo_5886306117607340888_y-750x422.jpg 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/photo_5886306117607340888_y-1140x641.jpg 1140w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/photo_5886306117607340888_y.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px" />
<p>Per the data, a significant chunk of staked ETH was staked when ETH was still in the $600 price range — this dates back to December 2020 when the Beacon Chain was launched. Though ETH has since increased to a point where it’s now 50% higher than the 2020 price level, 80% of the currently staked ETH was staked at prices equal to or above $1,200.</p>
<p>Following the massive losses recorded in staked <a href="https://newsbtc.com/press-releases/why-orbeon-protocol-orbn-bitcoin-btc-and-ethereum-eth-are-market-leaders/">ETH</a>, the amount of weekly staked ETH has seen a sharp decline with fewer ETH staked since the last quarter of 2022. Over the past week, only a total of 25,000 ETH has been staked. </p>
<p>Prior to the extreme market conditions, figures of roughly 150,000 ETH were being staked per week. Should ETH continue into a downward movement, chances are there could be massive withdrawals from ETH staking contracts when a withdrawal mechanism is implemented later this year. </p>
<h2>Considering The Long Term Perspective </h2>
<p>Another narrative worth considering is the long-term perspective. Given the fact that most stakers already had an initial idea of keeping their ETH for the long term, they might as well turn a blind eye to the current price levels of<a href="https://newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-lacks-momentum-above-1200-why-bears-are-comfortable/"> Ethereum</a>. </p>
<p>Besides, staking ETH directly or through an exchange would usually involve a committed two-year lockup period. For context, 15.9 million ETH is currently staked, representing 13.2% of the entire supply, according to Dune data reports. </p>

<p>However, even with the dip that seems to be never-ending, there are still hopes for Ethereum and even other <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/currency-expert-altcoins-bitcoin-ethereum/">altcoins</a>. As of the time of writing, ETH is up by over 3% in the last 24 hours with a trading volume of $5.2 billion over the same time period.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-514765 size-medium" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ETHUSDT-Chart-460x246.jpg" alt="Ethereum price chart from trading view" width="460" height="246" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ETHUSDT-Chart-460x246.jpg 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ETHUSDT-Chart-860x460.jpg 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ETHUSDT-Chart-768x410.jpg 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ETHUSDT-Chart-750x401.jpg 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ETHUSDT-Chart-1140x609.jpg 1140w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ETHUSDT-Chart.jpg 1366w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px" />Furthermore, a reversal is expected to happen, given the sharp upwards movements in what seems to be a false move.</p>
<p>Featured image from istock, Dune analytics and TradingView</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ethereum-460x329.jpg" width="460" height="329" />	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
