<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
>

<channel>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.newsbtc.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<description>Bitcoin &#38; cryptocurrency news today, price &#38; technical analysis</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 10:43:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Lisk Foundation To Convert 1,000 Bitcoin To ETH, Reason To Worry?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/lisk-foundation-to-convert-1000-bitcoin-to-eth/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jake Simmons]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 11:50:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=532261</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Max Kordek, the co-founder and CEO of Lisk recently announced via Twitter that the Lisk Foundation will convert 1,000 Bitcoin (BTC) to Ethereum (ETH) in the next 10 weeks, which will be held as part of the foundation&#8217;s long-term treasury. As Kordek explained in a commentary, the Lisk Foundation wants to stake its ETH, &#8220;but it won&#8217;t happen right away.&#8221; The project gained wider notoriety during the Initial Coin Offering (ICO) craze in 2016 and 2017. At the time, the decentralized apps platform raised 14,000 Bitcoin. That sum was worth about $5.7 million at the time, making the campaign the second most successful cryptocurrency crowdfunding to that point. With a market cap of $106 million, the Lisk Token (LSK) ranks 195th among the largest cryptocurrencies according to CoinMarketCap today. At press time, LSK was trading at $0.828 and is down 5.7% in the last 24 hours. Reasons Why Lisk Is Converting Bitcoin To ETH Lisk Foundation will sell 1,000 BTC in chunks of 100 BTC per week to reduce risks with related third parties. Subsequently, the purchased ETH will be deposited into a 2-of-3 multisig account, with each Lisk Foundation board member holding one key each. Related Reading: Why Is Bitcoin And The Crypto Market Down Today? Notably, the project will keep 500 BTC, which the co-founder said will be used to pay expenses in 2024 and 2025. Moreover, Kordek added that the Lisk Foundation has &#8220;about enough fiat until the next Bitcoin halving.&#8221; According to Kordek, there are three reasons for this move: first, the tweet states that Ethereum is the largest blockchain platform in the world. &#8220;Treasury-wise we want to go where blockchain applications are being built,&#8221; Kordek wrote, emphasizing as a second reason that ETH has &#8220;acceptable risks&#8221; from a Treasury wise point of view. Related Reading: Winner Takes All: Bitcoin And DXY Compete For Global Financial Dominance Third, he said, it allows for a sustainable, long-term return (via staking). &#8220;Treasury-wise it makes sense to go into an appreciating, deflationary, yield-generating asset,&#8221; Kordek said. The Lisk Foundation is exchanging 1000 BTC into ETH over the next 10 weeks and will hold onto them as part of its long-term treasury. 🧵 Continue reading to learn more.. How: The 1000 BTC are being sold in chunks of 100 BTC per week to reduce risks with associated… &#8212; Max Kordek (@maxkordek) May 11, 2023 Will It Have An Impact On BTC Price? Even though the Bitcoin and crypto market is very illiquid due to Operation Choke Point 2.0 in the United States at the moment, the impact on the Bitcoin price should be marginal due to the 1,000 BTC split over 10 weeks. 100 BTC is an order size that the market can easily digest. In the last 24 hours, the trading volume of BTC was approximately 19.4 billion. At press time, the Bitcoin price was at $26,388. For now, the key support is at the 100-day Exponential Moving Average (EMA), located at $26,227. Over the next few hours, it remains to be seen if this support can be held, if not, the area at $25,200 comes into focus. Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Max Kordek, the co-founder and CEO of Lisk recently <a href="https://twitter.com/maxkordek/status/1656629386689363970?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">announced</a> via Twitter that the Lisk Foundation will convert 1,000 Bitcoin (BTC) to Ethereum (ETH) in the next 10 weeks, which will be held as part of the foundation&#8217;s long-term treasury. As Kordek explained in a commentary, the Lisk Foundation wants to stake its ETH, &#8220;but it won&#8217;t happen right away.&#8221;</p>
<p>The project gained wider notoriety during the Initial Coin Offering (ICO) craze in 2016 and 2017. At the time, the decentralized apps platform raised 14,000 Bitcoin. That sum was worth about $5.7 million at the time, making the campaign the second most successful cryptocurrency crowdfunding to that point.</p>
<p>With a market cap of $106 million, the Lisk Token (LSK) ranks 195th among the largest cryptocurrencies according to CoinMarketCap today. At press time, LSK was trading at $0.828 and is down 5.7% in the last 24 hours.</p>
<h2>Reasons Why Lisk Is Converting Bitcoin To ETH</h2>
<p>Lisk Foundation will sell 1,000 BTC in chunks of 100 BTC per week to reduce risks with related third parties. Subsequently, the purchased ETH will be deposited into a 2-of-3 multisig account, with each Lisk Foundation board member holding one key each.</p>

<p>Notably, the project will keep 500 BTC, which the co-founder said will be used to pay expenses in 2024 and 2025. Moreover, Kordek added that the Lisk Foundation has &#8220;about enough fiat until the next Bitcoin halving.&#8221;</p>
<p>According to Kordek, there are three reasons for this move: first, the tweet states that Ethereum is the largest blockchain platform in the world. &#8220;Treasury-wise we want to go where blockchain applications are being built,&#8221; Kordek wrote, emphasizing as a second reason that ETH has &#8220;acceptable risks&#8221; from a Treasury wise point of view.</p>

<p>Third, he said, it allows for a sustainable, long-term return (via staking). &#8220;Treasury-wise it makes sense to go into an appreciating, deflationary, yield-generating asset,&#8221; Kordek said.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">The Lisk Foundation is exchanging 1000 BTC into ETH over the next 10 weeks and will hold onto them as part of its long-term treasury.</p>
<p><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f9f5.png" alt="🧵" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> Continue reading to learn more..</p>
<p>How:</p>
<p>The 1000 BTC are being sold in chunks of 100 BTC per week to reduce risks with associated…</p>
<p>&mdash; Max Kordek (@maxkordek) <a href="https://twitter.com/maxkordek/status/1656629386689363970?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">May 11, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p></p>
<h2>Will It Have An Impact On BTC Price?</h2>
<p>Even though the Bitcoin and crypto market is very <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin-price-threatened-by-liquidity-crisis/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">illiquid</a> due to Operation Choke Point 2.0 in the United States at the moment, the impact on the Bitcoin price should be marginal due to the 1,000 BTC split over 10 weeks.</p>
<p>100 BTC is an order size that the market can easily digest. In the last 24 hours, the trading volume of BTC was approximately 19.4 billion.</p>
<p>At press time, the Bitcoin price was at $26,388. For now, the key support is at the 100-day Exponential Moving Average (EMA), located at $26,227. Over the next few hours, it remains to be seen if this support can be held, if not, the area at $25,200 comes into focus.</p>
<img decoding="async" class="wp-image-532272 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSD_2023-05-12_12-34-13.png" alt="Bitcoin price" width="3625" height="1672" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSD_2023-05-12_12-34-13.png 3625w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSD_2023-05-12_12-34-13-460x212.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSD_2023-05-12_12-34-13-860x397.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSD_2023-05-12_12-34-13-768x354.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSD_2023-05-12_12-34-13-1536x708.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSD_2023-05-12_12-34-13-2048x945.png 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSD_2023-05-12_12-34-13-750x346.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSD_2023-05-12_12-34-13-1140x526.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 3625px) 100vw, 3625px" />

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/iStock-912157946-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Does The Bitcoin Price Dump Signal The Start Of Another Bear Market?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/does-the-bitcoin-price-dump-signal-the-start-of-another-bear-market/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Best Owie]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 10:50:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Fear And Greed Index]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=532264</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The last two days have been especially rocky for the Bitcoin price as it has fluctuated heavily between trying for a recovery and then crashing even further. As a result of this, the price of the digital asset has revisited the $26,000 level once more and the new bearish trend may point to more decline for the cryptocurrency. Bitcoin Loses $27,000 Support After a rollercoaster response to the CPI data release, the price of Bitcoin had reclaimed $27,000 and the bulls quickly tried to establish support above $27,000. This level would hold for about a day, but by Thursday, bears made easy pickings of it, dragging the price of BTC down to as low as $26,200. Related Reading: Matrixport Report: Here’s What Happens To Bitcoin If Inflation Continues To Fall This decline in price has dragged the cryptocurrency to dangerously bearish levels. One of these is the fact that it is now trading below its 50-day moving average. For a digital asset like BTC, maintaining its 50-day SMA is important, especially if the asset is going to see an upside in the coming days. BTC returns to $26,000 level &#124; Source: BTCUSD on TradingView.com However, as this trend continues, it will not be surprising to see BTC lose footing above its 100-day MA. If this happens, then the digital asset could be in free fall for a while which could see it return to the $20,000 level. Unless there is a sudden turn in investor sentiment, the bear market may have returned in full bloom. Crypto Investors Becoming Wary As the price of Bitcoin has suffered, so has the sentiment of investors moved into the more negative territory. BTC’s rise above $31,000 brought the Fear &#38; Greed Index to a high of 69 in April. However, there has since been a shift in how investors have been looking at the market. Over the last three weeks, the Fear &#38; Greed Index has shown a 20-point decline which puts the market back into neutral territory. While this level is not necessarily bad when taken at face value, the fact that the index has declined from greed back to neutral is concerning. Fear &#38; Greed Index turns neutral &#124; Source: alternative.me If anything, this decline indicates that investors are becoming more wary of the market. When things like these occur, it means that investors are not willing to put money into the market. Volumes decline as a result of this and price fall in response to the lack of momentum. Related Reading: Total Number Of Shiba Inu Addresses In Profit Drops As Market Braces For Impact Currently, support for BTC lies at $26,000 which is shaky at best. Unless there is a significant accumulation of the digital asset over the coming days, then the weekend which is characterized by low volumes and volatility could prove detrimental for the cryptocurrency At the time of writing, BTC is changing hands at a price of $26,291, down 4.22% in the last 24 hours. Follow Best Owie on Twitter for market insights, updates, and the occasional funny tweet… Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The last two days have been especially rocky for the Bitcoin price as it has fluctuated heavily between trying for a recovery and then crashing even further. As a result of this, the price of the digital asset has revisited the $26,000 level once more and the new bearish trend may point to more decline for the cryptocurrency.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Loses $27,000 Support</h2>
<p>After a rollercoaster response to the CPI data release, the price of Bitcoin had reclaimed $27,000 and the bulls quickly tried to establish support above $27,000. This level would hold for about a day, but by Thursday, bears made easy pickings of it, dragging the price of BTC down to as low as $26,200.</p>

<p>This decline in price has dragged the cryptocurrency to dangerously bearish levels. One of these is the fact that it is now trading below its 50-day moving average. For a digital asset like BTC, maintaining its 50-day SMA is important, especially if the asset is going to see an upside in the coming days.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/EvoEnMYk/" alt="Bitcoin price chart from TradingView.com" width="2854" height="1724" /></p>

<p>However, as this trend continues, it will not be surprising to see BTC lose footing above its 100-day MA. If this happens, then the digital asset could be in free fall for a while which could see it return to the $20,000 level. Unless there is a sudden turn in investor sentiment, the bear market may have returned in full bloom.</p>
<h2>Crypto Investors Becoming Wary</h2>
<p>As the price of Bitcoin has suffered, so has the sentiment of investors moved into the more negative territory. BTC’s rise above $31,000 brought the Fear &amp; Greed Index to a high of 69 in April. However, there has since been a shift in how investors have been looking at the market.</p>
<p>Over the last three weeks, the Fear &amp; Greed Index has shown a 20-point decline which puts the market back into neutral territory. While this level is not necessarily bad when taken at face value, the fact that the index has declined from greed back to neutral is concerning.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-532266 aligncenter" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-Fear-Greed-Index-460x152.png" alt="Bitcoin Fear &amp; Greed Index" width="460" height="152" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-Fear-Greed-Index-460x152.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-Fear-Greed-Index-860x284.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-Fear-Greed-Index-768x253.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-Fear-Greed-Index-1536x507.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-Fear-Greed-Index-2048x676.png 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-Fear-Greed-Index-750x248.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-Fear-Greed-Index-1140x376.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px" /></p>

<p>If anything, this decline indicates that investors are becoming more wary of the market. When things like these occur, it means that investors are not willing to put money into the market. Volumes decline as a result of this and price fall in response to the lack of momentum.</p>

<p>Currently, support for BTC lies at $26,000 which is shaky at best. Unless there is a significant accumulation of the digital asset over the coming days, then the weekend which is characterized by low volumes and volatility could prove detrimental for the cryptocurrency</p>
<p>At the time of writing, BTC is changing hands at a price of $26,291, down 4.22% in the last 24 hours.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/iStock-1316129074-460x251.jpg" width="460" height="251" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum Loses Grip On $1,800: Will The Bulls Barge In To Save The Day?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/ethereum-loses-grip-on-1800-will-the-bulls-barge-in-to-save-the-day/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 09:40:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eth price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price action]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=532248</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Ethereum (ETH), the world&#8217;s second-largest cryptocurrency by market capitalization, has been experiencing a period of volatility in recent days. After hitting the $2,000 mark last month, the price of Ethereum has dropped sharply, falling below the $1,800 level on multiple occasions.  This has left investors wondering whether the bulls will step in to save the day and push the price back up. The cryptocurrency market as a whole has been experiencing a period of uncertainty, with many investors questioning the sustainability of the recent bull run. Despite these challenges, Ethereum has remained a key player in the cryptocurrency ecosystem, with many investors remaining bullish on its long-term prospects. Related Reading: SPONGE Lists On 2 Major Exchanges: Will It Beat Pepe’s Solid Price Performance? Ethereum (ETH) Value Drops As Market Volatility Persists According to CoinGecko, Ethereum&#8217;s current price has taken a sharp dive, plunging to $1,760. This marks a significant 24-hour decline of 3.2% and a week-long decrease of 7.2%. This comes after Ethereum made a new high in mid-April, surpassing $2,100.  Source: Coingecko Although it experienced a retracement, the $1,800 support level prevented further decline and has remained stable for the past two weeks, provided Bitcoin does not drop below $27,000. If Ethereum experiences aggressive demand at its current levels, the $1,800 support level may come to the bulls&#8217; rescue. However, if Bitcoin drops to $26,000, Ethereum&#8217;s support level could crack, exposing it to further selloffs.  In such a scenario, Ethereum could retreat to lower support levels at $1,700 or even $1,500. It&#8217;s worth noting that upper resistance levels to consider are at $2,000 and $2,100. Market-Wide Selloff Blamed For ETH Retreat As the cryptocurrency market continues to experience volatility, investors are keeping a close eye on Ethereum&#8217;s price movements. With the current drop below $1,800, many are wondering where Ethereum is heading next. Some analysts believe that Ethereum&#8217;s decline is a result of a market-wide sell-off, driven by concerns over Bitcoin&#8217;s regulatory crackdowns. Others suggest that the recent decline in Ethereum&#8217;s price could be attributed to concerns over its high transaction fees and network congestion. Looking ahead, its current support level remains a critical factor in Ethereum&#8217;s price trajectory. If the bulls step in to save the day and push the price back up, Ethereum could reclaim its previous support levels and continue its upward trend.  ETHUSD loses handle on $1,800. Chart: TradingView.com Related Reading: SHIB Holders, Get Ready: Latest Shiba Inu Update Could Be A Game Changer However, if the bears continue to dominate the market and push the price below the $1,800 support level, Ethereum could experience further declines. The cryptocurrency market remains unpredictable, and investors should exercise caution when making investment decisions. While Ethereum&#8217;s long-term prospects remain positive, short-term price movements are subject to a range of factors that could impact its value in the near term. (This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk) -Featured image from BuzzFeed]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ethereum (ETH), the world&#8217;s second-largest cryptocurrency by market capitalization, has been experiencing a period of volatility in recent days. </p>
<p>After hitting the $2,000 mark last month, the price of Ethereum has dropped sharply, falling below the $1,800 level on multiple occasions. </p>
<p>This has left investors wondering whether the bulls will step in to save the day and push the price back up.</p>
<p>The cryptocurrency market as a whole has been experiencing a period of uncertainty, with many investors questioning the sustainability of the recent bull run. </p>
<p>Despite these challenges, Ethereum has remained a key player in the cryptocurrency ecosystem, with many investors remaining bullish on its long-term prospects.</p>

<h2><strong>Ethereum (ETH) Value Drops As Market Volatility Persists</strong></h2>
<p>According to <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/ethereum" rel="nofollow">CoinGecko</a>, Ethereum&#8217;s current price has taken a sharp dive, plunging to $1,760. This marks a significant 24-hour decline of 3.2% and a week-long decrease of 7.2%. This comes after Ethereum made a new high in mid-April, surpassing $2,100. </p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-532252 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ethereum-9.png" alt="" width="1140" height="66" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ethereum-9.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ethereum-9-460x27.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ethereum-9-860x50.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ethereum-9-768x44.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ethereum-9-750x43.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 1140px) 100vw, 1140px" /></p>

<p>Although it experienced a retracement, the $1,800 support level prevented further decline and has remained stable for the past two weeks, provided Bitcoin does not drop below $27,000.</p>
<p>If Ethereum experiences aggressive demand at its current levels, the $1,800 support level may come to the bulls&#8217; rescue. However, if Bitcoin drops to $26,000, Ethereum&#8217;s support level could crack, exposing it to further selloffs. </p>
<p>In such a scenario, Ethereum could retreat to lower support levels at $1,700 or even $1,500. It&#8217;s worth noting that <a href="https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bitcoin-slips-ether-inches-above-110744752.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">upper resistance levels</a> to consider are at $2,000 and $2,100.</p>
<h2><strong>Market-Wide Selloff Blamed For ETH Retreat</strong></h2>
<p>As the cryptocurrency market continues to experience volatility, investors are keeping a close eye on Ethereum&#8217;s price movements. With the current drop below $1,800, many are wondering where Ethereum is heading next.</p>
<p>Some analysts believe that Ethereum&#8217;s decline is a result of a market-wide sell-off, driven by concerns over Bitcoin&#8217;s regulatory crackdowns. </p>
<p>Others suggest that the recent decline in Ethereum&#8217;s price could be attributed to concerns over its <a href="https://u.today/ethereum-gas-skyrocketing-as-trader-paid-64-eth-in-fees-whats-happening" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">high transaction fees</a> and network congestion.</p>
<p>Looking ahead, its current support level remains a critical factor in Ethereum&#8217;s price trajectory. If the bulls step in to save the day and push the price back up, Ethereum could reclaim its previous support levels and continue its upward trend. </p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/t4c73wXd/" width="2047" height="979" /></p>


<p>However, if the bears continue to dominate the market and push the price below the $1,800 support level, Ethereum could experience further declines.</p>
<p>The cryptocurrency market remains unpredictable, and investors should exercise caution when making investment decisions. </p>
<p>While Ethereum&#8217;s long-term prospects remain positive, short-term price movements are subject to a range of factors that could impact its value in the near term.</p>
<p><em>(This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk)</em></p>
<p><em>-Featured image from BuzzFeed</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/a-49-460x312.png" width="460" height="312" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>SHIB Holders, Get Ready: Latest Shiba Inu Update Could Be A Game Changer</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/shib-update-could-be-a-game-changer/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 08:41:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[meme coins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price action]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIB price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shiba Inu]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=532232</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Shiba Inu (SHIB) experienced a decline in social dominance over the past week, indicating a decrease in popularity for the meme coin. Despite being oversold based on its Relative Strength Index (RSI), other indicators were bearish, suggesting a potential further decline in price.  However, SHIB has a history of responding rapidly to updates within its ecosystem, and a forthcoming Shibarium update could potentially reverse the downward trend. With the release of the Shibarium update, there may be a potential opportunity for the coin to regain its footing and improve its market performance. Related Reading: SPONGE Lists On 2 Major Exchanges: Will It Beat Pepe’s Solid Price Performance? Shiba Inu&#8217;s Shibarium Update Makes Progress In a tweet, Shiba Inu-focused account Lucie unveiled new details about the much-anticipated Shibarium update for Shiba Inu. According to the tweet, the Shiba Inu team is currently working on implementing VOR and OoO on the Shibarium beta testnet. The next step will be to deploy the 0o0 and VOR Router smart contracts on Shibarium Layer 2 and then activate the Oracle applications to fulfill data requests. #ShibariumBETA UPDATE May 2023 OoO&#38; VOR Deployment on Shibarium testnet “We are currently in the process of deploying both VOR and OoO on Shibarium beta testnet. To date, we have deployed the FUND Test token on Shibarium beta testnet, and have successfully bridged L1 to L2. We… pic.twitter.com/CWwgC4j0ht — 𝐋𝐔𝐂𝐈𝐄 (@LucieSHIB) May 10, 2023 Furthermore, the team has made headway in transferring FUND test tokens between L1 (Goerli) and L2, which is a significant development. As of now, the FUND Test token has been deployed on the Shibarium beta testnet, and L1 has been successfully bridged to L2. SHIB market cap inches lower at $5.11 billion. Chart: TradingView.com This update indicates that the Shibarium project is making steady progress towards its launch. With the deployment of smart contracts and the successful transfer of test tokens, the team is one step closer to bringing the full potential of the Shibarium to the Shiba Inu ecosystem. Shiba Inu Price Reaction Investors and analysts had hoped that the Shibarium update would provide the much-needed boost to Shiba Inu&#8217;s market performance. However, it appears that the market sentiment towards SHIB has not changed, and the downward trend in its value has persisted. Shiba Inu suffered a decline not just in its price but also in its popularity within the crypto space, as evidenced by its dwindling social dominance. According to data from CryptoQuant, SHIB&#8217;s exchange reserve has also been on the decline, suggesting that the token is not currently under any significant selling pressure. Source: CryptoQuant Related Reading: Render (RNDR) Poised To Weather Market Storm With Solid AI Prospects Meanwhle, Shiba Inu&#8217;s value, as per CoinGecko, currently stands at a modest $0.00000865, marking a 2.5% drop in the past 24 hours and a 13.3% decrease over the last seven days. Source: Coingecko -Featured image from Analytics Insight]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Shiba Inu (SHIB) experienced a decline in social dominance over the past week, indicating a decrease in popularity for the meme coin. Despite being oversold based on its Relative Strength Index (RSI), other indicators were bearish, suggesting a potential further decline in price. </p>
<p>However, SHIB has a history of responding rapidly to updates within its ecosystem, and a forthcoming Shibarium update could potentially reverse the downward trend.</p>
<p>With the release of the Shibarium update, there may be a potential opportunity for the coin to regain its footing and improve its market performance.</p>

<h2><strong>Shiba Inu&#8217;s Shibarium Update Makes Progress</strong></h2>
<p><a href="https://twitter.com/LucieSHIB/status/1656274670998667264" rel="nofollow">In a tweet</a>, Shiba Inu-focused account Lucie unveiled new details about the much-anticipated Shibarium update for Shiba Inu. According to the tweet, the Shiba Inu team is currently working on implementing VOR and OoO on the Shibarium beta testnet. The next step will be to deploy the 0o0 and VOR Router smart contracts on Shibarium Layer 2 and then activate the Oracle applications to fulfill data requests.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en"><a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/ShibariumBETA?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#ShibariumBETA</a> UPDATE May 2023</p>
<p>OoO&amp; VOR Deployment on Shibarium testnet</p>
<p>“We are currently in the process of deploying both VOR and OoO on Shibarium beta testnet.
To date, we have deployed the FUND Test token on Shibarium beta testnet, and have successfully bridged L1 to L2. We… <a href="https://t.co/CWwgC4j0ht" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/CWwgC4j0ht</a></p>
<p>— 𝐋𝐔𝐂𝐈𝐄 (@LucieSHIB) <a href="https://twitter.com/LucieSHIB/status/1656274670998667264?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">May 10, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p>Furthermore, the team has made headway in transferring FUND test tokens between L1 (Goerli) and L2, which is a significant development. As of now, the FUND Test token has been deployed on the Shibarium beta testnet, and L1 has been successfully bridged to L2.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/pcXEKUjg/" width="2047" height="979" /></p>

<p>This update indicates that the Shibarium project is making steady progress towards its launch. With the deployment of smart contracts and the successful transfer of test tokens, the team is one step closer to bringing the full potential of the Shibarium to the Shiba Inu ecosystem.</p>
<h2><strong>Shiba Inu Price Reaction</strong></h2>
<p>Investors and analysts had hoped that the Shibarium update would provide the much-needed boost to Shiba Inu&#8217;s market performance. However, it appears that the market sentiment towards SHIB has not changed, and the downward trend in its value has persisted.</p>
<p>Shiba Inu suffered a decline not just in its price but also in its popularity within the crypto space, as evidenced by its dwindling social dominance. </p>
<p>According to data from <a href="https://cryptoquant.com/asset/shib/summary" rel="nofollow">CryptoQuant</a>, SHIB&#8217;s exchange reserve has also been on the decline, suggesting that the token is not currently under any significant selling pressure.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-532234 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/a-45.png" alt="" width="817" height="436" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/a-45.png 817w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/a-45-460x245.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/a-45-768x410.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/a-45-750x400.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 817px) 100vw, 817px" /></p>


<p>Meanwhle, Shiba Inu&#8217;s value, as per <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/shiba-inu" rel="nofollow">CoinGecko</a>, currently stands at a modest $0.00000865, marking a 2.5% drop in the past 24 hours and a 13.3% decrease over the last seven days.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-532242 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/a-46.png" alt="" width="1132" height="64" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/a-46.png 1132w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/a-46-460x26.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/a-46-860x49.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/a-46-768x43.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/a-46-750x42.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 1132px) 100vw, 1132px" /></p>

<p><em>-Featured image from Analytics Insight</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/a-47-460x256.png" width="460" height="256" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum Bears Hesitate But Further Downsides Seem Likely</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-bears-hesitate-1650/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 08:34:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=532209</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Ethereum price is moving lower below the $1,800 support against the US Dollar. ETH could accelerate lower toward the $1,650 support in the near term. Ethereum is currently moving lower from the $1,850 resistance zone. The price is trading below $1,820 and the 100-hourly Simple Moving Average. There is a major bearish trend line forming with resistance near $1,800 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD (data feed via Kraken). The pair could start a decent increase if there is a move above the $1,800 and $1,830 resistance levels. Ethereum Price Turns Red Ethereum’s price failed to start a recovery wave above the $1,850 resistance zone. ETH remained in a bearish zone and traded below the $1,830 support, similar to Bitcoin. The decline was such that the price even broke the $1,800 support. A new weekly low is formed near $1,770 and the price is now trading in the red zone. Ether is well below $1,820 and the 100-hourly Simple Moving Average. There is also a major bearish trend line forming with resistance near $1,800 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD. Immediate resistance is near the $1,800 level or the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the recent decline from the $1,888 swing high to the $1,770 low. The next resistance sits near $1,830 or the 50% Fib retracement level of the recent decline from the $1,888 swing high to the $1,770 low, above which Ethereum could test the 100-hourly Simple Moving Average.  If there is a move above the $1,830 and $1,840 resistance levels, the price might rise toward the $1,880 level. Any more gains above the $1,880 resistance zone could start a decent increase toward the $1,920 resistance. More Losses in ETH? If Ethereum fails to clear the $1,830 resistance, it could continue to move down. Initial support on the downside is near the $1,770 level. The next major support is near the $1,740 zone. If there is a clear move below the $1,740 support, the bears could gain strength and the price might decline heavily. The price might drop toward the $1,650 support zone in the stated case. Any more losses may perhaps take the price toward the $1,600 level in the near term. Technical Indicators Hourly MACD – The MACD for ETH/USD is now gaining momentum in the bearish zone. Hourly RSI &#8211; The RSI for ETH/USD is below the 50 level. Major Support Level – $1,770 Major Resistance Level – $1,830 Chart from Tradingview]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>Ethereum price is moving lower below the $1,800 support against the US Dollar. ETH could accelerate lower toward the $1,650 support in the near term.</em></p>
<ul>
<li>Ethereum is currently moving lower from the $1,850 resistance zone.</li>
<li>The price is trading below $1,820 and the 100-hourly Simple Moving Average.</li>
<li>There is a major bearish trend line forming with resistance near $1,800 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD (data feed via Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could start a decent increase if there is a move above the $1,800 and $1,830 resistance levels.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Ethereum Price Turns Red</h2>
<p>Ethereum’s price failed to start a recovery wave above the $1,850 resistance zone. ETH remained in a bearish zone and traded below the $1,830 support, similar to <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-breakdown-25k/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Bitcoin</a>.</p>
<p>The decline was such that the price even broke the $1,800 support. A new weekly low is formed near $1,770 and the price is now trading in the red zone. Ether is well below $1,820 and the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-see-liftoff-if-its-able-to-hold-one-crucial-level/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">100-hourly Simple Moving Average</a>. There is also a major bearish trend line forming with resistance near $1,800 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD.</p>
<p>Immediate resistance is near the $1,800 level or the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the recent decline from the $1,888 swing high to the $1,770 low.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-532238 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ethereum-ETH-ETHUSDT-860x396.jpg" alt="Ethereum ETH ETHUSDT" width="860" height="396" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ethereum-ETH-ETHUSDT-860x396.jpg 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ethereum-ETH-ETHUSDT-460x212.jpg 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ethereum-ETH-ETHUSDT-768x353.jpg 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ethereum-ETH-ETHUSDT-750x345.jpg 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ethereum-ETH-ETHUSDT-1140x525.jpg 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ethereum-ETH-ETHUSDT.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" />
<p>The next resistance sits near $1,830 or the 50% Fib retracement level of the recent decline from the $1,888 swing high to the $1,770 low, above which Ethereum could test the 100-hourly Simple Moving Average.  If there is a move above the $1,830 and $1,840 resistance levels, the price might rise toward the $1,880 level. Any more gains above the $1,880 resistance zone could start a decent increase toward the $1,920 resistance.</p>
<h2>More Losses in ETH?</h2>
<p>If Ethereum fails to clear the $1,830 resistance, it could continue to move down. Initial support on the downside is near the $1,770 level.</p>
<p>The next major support is near the $1,740 zone. If there is a clear move below the $1,740 support, the bears could gain strength and the price might decline heavily. The price might drop toward the $1,650 support zone in the stated case. Any more losses may perhaps take the price toward the $1,600 level in the near term.</p>
<p>Technical Indicators</p>
<p>Hourly MACD<strong> – </strong>The MACD for ETH/USD is now gaining momentum in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>Hourly RSI<strong> &#8211; </strong>The RSI for ETH/USD is below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Level – $1,770</p>
<p>Major Resistance Level – $1,830</p>
<p>Chart from Tradingview</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/iStock-1333288705-460x312.jpg" width="460" height="312" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Why Is Bitcoin And The Crypto Market Down Today?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/why-is-bitcoin-and-the-crypto-market-down-today/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jake Simmons]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 07:15:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=532213</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin price continues to fall, dragging the broader crypto market down with it. BTC is down 4.52% in the last 24 hours, while ETH is down 4.10%. With a current price of $26,289, Bitcoin records its lowest value since March 14 this year, when the price dipped as low as $26,544. Why Is Bitcoin And Crypto Down? As always, the reasons for the deep pullback of the Bitcoin price are complex. Remarkably, there was actually good news on Wednesday, May 10, as the CPI continued to fall causing the Bitcoin price to rise as high as $28,317. However, then fake news about an alleged sale of 9,800 BTC by the U.S. government shook the market. The Bitcoin price flash crashed as a result and has seemingly not been able to recover since. But this narrative is only half the story. A variety of other factors are currently weighing on the crypto market: the dollar index (DXY) is currently experiencing a bounce and was recently able to hold above the historically important support, the liquidity issue intensified once again with the departure of US market makers Jump and Jane Street, BTC formed a (supposed) head and shoulders pattern in the 1-day chart, the congestion of the Bitcoin and Ethereum blockchains and last but not least a lot of FUD (US government selling, Binance US and Grayscale). Related Reading: Whales Keep Buying Bitcoin, What They Might Know That You Don’t Not surprisingly, uncertainty in the Bitcoin and crypto market is currently quite high. The Dollar Index (DXY) is currently hovering above historically crucial support at 101.8. Since early April, DXY has already been suspiciously close to support, but has so far been able to fend off any attack from the bears. As Christopher Inks of Texas Wet Capital writes, the DXY saw another move higher yesterday (to 102.056) and is currently preventing a rally in risk assets: The $DXY rally is making longs difficult this morning. So, if you&#8217;re trying to get long on risk-off assets it&#8217;s best to wait and watch for a bit. Liquidity Issues, A Bearish Chart Pattern And FUD Another bitter blow to the crypto market on Tuesday was the news of Jump and Jane Street&#8217;s departure from the U.S. crypto market. The move by the two major market makers comes as a result of regulatory uncertainty in the US. As NewsBTC reported, liquidity has been a huge problem before, which could now get worse. Due to low liquidity, higher volatility is likely as larger buy and sell orders move the market faster. In addition, a (supposed) head and shoulders pattern on Bitcoin&#8217;s 1-day chart is currently causing fear among traders. The pattern may signal a crash to $25,000. Remember the bearish diamond pattern that everyone was shilling at 21-22k? It’s H&#38;S now, just saying! https://t.co/2HlUIZ1XrJ pic.twitter.com/yyivuwcF82 &#8212; tedtalksmacro (@tedtalksmacro) May 12, 2023 Adding to the uncertainty has certainly been the congestion of the Bitcoin blockchain by Ordinals and the controversial BRC-20 meme coins, which are seen as a DDoS attack by part of the community. Although 300,000 transactions are still waiting for confirmation in the mempool, the problem is slowly easing. Related Reading: Winner Takes All: Bitcoin And DXY Compete For Global Financial Dominance The popularity of Bitcoin Ordinals transactions is declining. Trading volume has dropped for three consecutive days after reaching an all-time high of $18.13 million on May 8. Yesterday, trading volume fell to $4.86 million. The number of transactions has also dropped from 17,000 to 6,000. UniSat&#8217;s market share has dropped from 80-90% to 50-60% currently. #Bitcoin block size war 2.0? 👀 According to Dune data, transactions through Unisat have grown exponentially since the beginning of May. 🚨 Unisat, the core wallet of BRC20, is developed by a Chinese development team of the BSV community. pic.twitter.com/DfW46mbhZb &#8212; Jake Simmons (@realJakeSimmons) May 11, 2023 Last but not least, there are currently some unconfirmed rumors (FUD) circulating about Binance US and Grayscale. Binance US caused a stir in the last few days because the Bitcoin price showed a high price premium. The reasons have been the subject of much speculation. Grayscale is currently being hotly debated because DCG supposedly owes bankrupt crypto lender Genesis Trading about $575 million in May, with the loans coming due next week. The rumor says that Grayscale may be selling something on Coinbase to cover the capital needed to repay the loan. At press time, the Bitcoin price stood at $26,289, initially receiving support from the 100-day EMA. Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin price continues to fall, dragging the broader crypto market down with it. BTC is down 4.52% in the last 24 hours, while ETH is down 4.10%. With a current price of $26,289, Bitcoin records its lowest value since March 14 this year, when the price dipped as low as $26,544.</p>
<h2>Why Is Bitcoin And Crypto Down?</h2>
<p>As always, the reasons for the deep pullback of the Bitcoin price are complex. Remarkably, there was actually good <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-price-blasts-above-28000-following-4-9-april-cpi-report/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">news</a> on Wednesday, May 10, as the CPI continued to fall causing the Bitcoin price to rise as high as $28,317.</p>
<p>However, then fake news about an alleged sale of 9,800 BTC by the U.S. government shook the market. The Bitcoin price flash crashed as a result and has seemingly not been able to recover since. But this narrative is only half the story.</p>
<p>A variety of other factors are currently weighing on the crypto market: the dollar index (DXY) is currently experiencing a bounce and was recently able to hold above the historically important support, the liquidity issue intensified once again with the departure of US market makers Jump and Jane Street, BTC formed a (supposed) head and shoulders pattern in the 1-day chart, the congestion of the Bitcoin and Ethereum blockchains and last but not least a lot of FUD (US government selling, Binance US and Grayscale).</p>

<p>Not surprisingly, uncertainty in the Bitcoin and crypto market is currently quite high. The Dollar Index (DXY) is currently hovering above historically crucial support at 101.8. Since early April, DXY has already been suspiciously close to support, but has so far been able to fend off any attack from the bears.</p>
<p>As Christopher Inks of Texas Wet Capital <a href="https://twitter.com/TXWestCapital/status/1656662539500126208" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">writes</a>, the DXY saw another move higher yesterday (to 102.056) and is currently preventing a rally in risk assets:</p>
<blockquote><p><strong>The $DXY rally is making longs difficult this morning. So, if you&#8217;re trying to get long on risk-off assets it&#8217;s best to wait and watch for a bit.</strong></p></blockquote>
<h2>Liquidity Issues, A Bearish Chart Pattern And FUD</h2>
<p>Another bitter blow to the crypto market on Tuesday was the news of Jump and Jane Street&#8217;s departure from the U.S. crypto market. The move by the two major market makers comes as a result of regulatory uncertainty in the US.</p>
<p>As NewsBTC <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-liquidity-crisis-gets-worse-what-it-means-price/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">reported</a>, liquidity has been a huge problem before, which could now get worse. Due to low liquidity, higher volatility is likely as larger buy and sell orders move the market faster.</p>
<p>In addition, a (supposed) head and shoulders pattern on Bitcoin&#8217;s 1-day chart is currently causing fear among traders. The pattern may signal a crash to $25,000.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Remember the bearish diamond pattern that everyone was shilling at 21-22k?</p>
<p>It’s H&amp;S now, just saying! <a href="https://t.co/2HlUIZ1XrJ" rel="nofollow">https://t.co/2HlUIZ1XrJ</a> <a href="https://t.co/yyivuwcF82" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/yyivuwcF82</a></p>
<p>&mdash; tedtalksmacro (@tedtalksmacro) <a href="https://twitter.com/tedtalksmacro/status/1656936477597765633?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">May 12, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p></p>
<p>Adding to the uncertainty has certainly been the congestion of the Bitcoin blockchain by Ordinals and the controversial BRC-20 meme coins, which are seen as a DDoS attack by part of the community. Although 300,000 transactions are still waiting for confirmation in the mempool, the problem is slowly easing.</p>

<p>The popularity of Bitcoin Ordinals transactions is declining. Trading volume has <a href="https://twitter.com/WuBlockchain/status/1656844781623074817" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">dropped</a> for three consecutive days after reaching an all-time high of $18.13 million on May 8. Yesterday, trading volume fell to $4.86 million. The number of transactions has also dropped from 17,000 to 6,000. UniSat&#8217;s market share has dropped from 80-90% to 50-60% currently.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr"><a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Bitcoin?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#Bitcoin</a> block size war 2.0?</p>
<p><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f440.png" alt="👀" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> According to Dune data, transactions through Unisat have grown exponentially since the beginning of May.</p>
<p><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f6a8.png" alt="🚨" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> Unisat, the core wallet of BRC20, is developed by a Chinese development team of the BSV community. <a href="https://t.co/DfW46mbhZb" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/DfW46mbhZb</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Jake Simmons (@realJakeSimmons) <a href="https://twitter.com/realJakeSimmons/status/1656597553217937409?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">May 11, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p></p>
<p>Last but not least, there are currently some unconfirmed rumors (FUD) circulating about Binance US and Grayscale. Binance US caused a stir in the last few days because the Bitcoin price showed a high price premium. The reasons have been the subject of much speculation.</p>
<p>Grayscale is currently being hotly debated because DCG supposedly owes bankrupt crypto lender Genesis Trading about $575 million in May, with the loans coming due next week. The rumor <a href="https://twitter.com/52kskew/status/1655403214152556547" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">says</a> that Grayscale may be selling something on Coinbase to cover the capital needed to repay the loan.</p>
<p>At press time, the Bitcoin price stood at $26,289, initially receiving support from the 100-day EMA.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-532216 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSD_2023-05-12_08-47-22.png" alt="Bitcoin price" width="3625" height="1672" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSD_2023-05-12_08-47-22.png 3625w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSD_2023-05-12_08-47-22-460x212.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSD_2023-05-12_08-47-22-860x397.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSD_2023-05-12_08-47-22-768x354.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSD_2023-05-12_08-47-22-1536x708.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSD_2023-05-12_08-47-22-2048x945.png 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSD_2023-05-12_08-47-22-750x346.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSD_2023-05-12_08-47-22-1140x526.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 3625px) 100vw, 3625px" />

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/iStock-1410473543-460x259.jpg" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Price Technical Breakdown Could Take BTC Toward $25K</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-breakdown-25k/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 02:36:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xbtusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=532206</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin price is moving lower below the $28,000 level. BTC is at risk of a downside break toward the $25,000 support in the near term. Bitcoin struggled to recover above the $27,500 and $27,800 resistance levels. The price is trading below $27,500 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average. There are two bearish trend lines forming with resistance near $27,000 and $27,800 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Kraken). The pair could continue to move down if it breaks the $26,750 support zone. Bitcoin Price Extends Decline Bitcoin price failed to start a recovery wave above the $27,800 level. BTC remained in a bearish zone and settled below the $27,500 support zone. The bears were able to push the price below the $27,000 level. A low is formed near $26,720 and the price is now showing a lot of bearish signs. It is still trading below $27,500 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average. There are also two bearish trend lines forming with resistance near $27,000 and $27,800 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair. Bitcoin price is likely to face sellers near the $27,000 level or the 23.6% Fib retracement level recent drop from the $28,335 swing high to the $26,720 low. The next major resistance is near the $27,350 level. The main resistance is now forming near the next trend line and $27,800. It is close to the 50% Fib retracement level recent drop from the $28,335 swing high to the $26,720 low. Source: BTCUSD on TradingView.com A close above the $27,800 resistance and the 100 hourly Simple moving average might start a decent increase. The next key resistance is near $28,000, above which the price might climb toward the $28,500 resistance. More Losses in BTC? If Bitcoin’s price fails to clear the $27,500 resistance, it could continue to move down. Immediate support on the downside is near the $26,750 level. The next major support is near the $26,500 zone, below which the price might gain bearish momentum. In the stated case, it could revisit the $26,000 level. Any more losses might take Bitcoin toward the $25,000 level in the near term. Technical indicators: Hourly MACD – The MACD is now gaining pace in the bearish zone. Hourly RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BTC/USD is now below the 50 level. Major Support Levels – $26,750, followed by $26,000. Major Resistance Levels – $27,000, $27,350, and $27,800.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>Bitcoin price is moving lower below the $28,000 level. BTC is at risk of a downside break toward the $25,000 support in the near term.</em></p>
<ul>
<li>Bitcoin struggled to recover above the $27,500 and $27,800 resistance levels.</li>
<li>The price is trading below $27,500 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average.</li>
<li>There are two bearish trend lines forming with resistance near $27,000 and $27,800 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could continue to move down if it breaks the $26,750 support zone.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Bitcoin Price Extends Decline</h2>
<p>Bitcoin price failed to start a recovery wave above the $27,800 level. BTC remained in a <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-turns-sell-28k/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">bearish zone</a> and settled below the $27,500 support zone.</p>
<p>The bears were able to push the price below the $27,000 level. A low is formed near $26,720 and the price is now showing a lot of bearish signs. It is still trading below $27,500 and the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-consolidates-27k/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">100 hourly Simple moving average</a>. There are also two bearish trend lines forming with resistance near $27,000 and $27,800 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair.</p>
<p>Bitcoin price is likely to face sellers near the $27,000 level or the 23.6% Fib retracement level recent drop from the $28,335 swing high to the $26,720 low.</p>
<p>The next major resistance is near the $27,350 level. The main resistance is now forming near the next trend line and $27,800. It is close to the 50% Fib retracement level recent drop from the $28,335 swing high to the $26,720 low.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-9.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-532207" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-9.png" alt="Bitcoin Price" width="1834" height="845" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-9.png 1834w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-9-460x212.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-9-860x396.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-9-768x354.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-9-1536x708.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-9-750x346.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-9-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1834px) 100vw, 1834px" /></a></p>
<p>Source: <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BTCUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">BTCUSD on TradingView.com</a></p>
<p>A close above the $27,800 resistance and the 100 hourly Simple moving average might start a decent increase. The next key resistance is near $28,000, above which the price might climb toward the $28,500 resistance.</p>
<h2>More Losses in BTC?</h2>
<p>If Bitcoin’s price fails to clear the $27,500 resistance, it could continue to move down. Immediate support on the downside is near the $26,750 level.</p>
<p>The next major support is near the $26,500 zone, below which the price might gain bearish momentum. In the stated case, it could revisit the $26,000 level. Any more losses might take Bitcoin toward the $25,000 level in the near term.</p>
<p>Technical indicators:</p>
<p>Hourly MACD – The MACD is now gaining pace in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>Hourly RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BTC/USD is now below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Levels – $26,750, followed by $26,000.</p>
<p>Major Resistance Levels – $27,000, $27,350, and $27,800.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/shutterstock_271682210-460x299.jpg" width="460" height="299" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Justin Sun Will Now Publicly Trade Meme Coins Like PEPE, Best Time To Copy Trade Him?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/justin-sun-will-now-publicly-trade-meme-coins-like-pepe-best-time-to-copy-trade-him/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dalmas Ngetich]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 23:00:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[changpeng zhao]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[huobi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Justin Sun]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[meme coins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PEPE]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[poloniex]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SUI]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[TRON]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=531328</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Justin Sun, the vocal crypto supporter and co-founder of Tron and chief executive officer (CEO) of BitTorrent, says he will begin actively trading meme coins like PEPE.  Justin Sun Eying Meme Coins In a tweet on May 11, Sun, known for being a crypto whale, actively holding and transferring colossal sums of coins in the past, said he would begin actively trading meme coins and promising projects straight from his public cryptocurrency address.  However, as a disclaimer, all profits will be donated to charity.  I&#39;ve decided to begin actively trading meme coins and promising projects through my public address. Please note, I will personally bear all potential losses from these trades, and any profits made will be donated entirely to charity. &#8212; H.E. Justin Sun 孙宇晨 (@justinsuntron) May 11, 2023 He also added that though he might decide to buy certain coins and get exposure to a promising meme coin project, the said coin or project, regardless of its potential, may not be listed on Huobi or Poloniex. These are some of the early and most liquid cryptocurrency exchanges listing hundreds of tokens that Sun occupies an influential executive seat. Related Reading: Why Justin Sun’s Stablecoin USDD Is Struggling To Maintain Its Dollar Peg It is still unclear which project Sun has an eye on. At the same time, it could not be determined which of his crypto addresses the co-founder will use when trading meme coins.  Although Sun might be the co-founder of Tron, he has not shied from engaging in other projects deployed on public networks like Ethereum and others. Tron Co-founder Warned By Binance Following a warning from Changpeng Zhao, the CEO of Binance, the world’s largest exchange by client count and trading volumes, Sun reversed a $56 million transfer he had made in early May. There were concerns that Sun was planning a token grab of SUI, the native currency of the Sui Network.  Our team told Justin, if he uses any of these to grab the LaunchPool Sui token, we will &#34;take action against it&#34;. SMH. Binance LaunchPool are meant as air drops for our retail users, not just for a few whales. On the bright side, blockchains are transparent&#8230; https://t.co/8Xs1oXjfVd &#8212; CZ 🔶 Binance (@cz_binance) May 1, 2023 WhaleAlert flagged Sun’s bulk $56 million transfer in TUSD. Before Zhao said, Binance would take action if he block-bought SUI from the Binance Launchpool. The exchange clarified that it wanted a fair airdrop to include active retailers and not “just a few crypto whales.”  Through the Launchpool, users can stake their crypto assets like SUI, providing liquidity, before receiving staking rewards.  Sun later apologized for the huge transfer, saying it was in error. The real intention, he clarified, was in the market-making of TUSD, a stablecoin. The Tron founder said: Regrettably, some of our team members were not fully aware of the intended purpose for these funds and inadvertently used a portion of them to participate in exchange campaigns. Upon realizing this error, we immediately contacted the exchange team and arranged for a full refund of the funds. Related Reading: TRX Surges Over 600% Following Justin Sun’s Deal With FTX It is not immediately clear how Sun will proceed in trading and how the community will react to his purchases once he starts picking out worthy meme coin projects. Even so, what’s clear is that his addresses, like those of other influential crypto founders like Ethereum’s co-founder Vitalik Buterin, will be actively tracked and copied. Feature Image From Canva, Chart From TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Justin Sun, the vocal crypto supporter and co-founder of Tron and chief executive officer (CEO) of BitTorrent, says he will begin actively trading meme coins like PEPE. </p>
<h2>Justin Sun Eying Meme Coins</h2>
<p>In a tweet on May 11, Sun, known for being a crypto whale, actively holding and transferring colossal sums of coins in the past, said he would begin actively trading meme coins and promising projects straight from his public cryptocurrency address. </p>
<p>However, as a disclaimer, all profits will be donated to charity. </p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">I&#39;ve decided to begin actively trading meme coins and promising projects through my public address. Please note, I will personally bear all potential losses from these trades, and any profits made will be donated entirely to charity.</p>
<p>&mdash; H.E. Justin Sun 孙宇晨 (@justinsuntron) <a href="https://twitter.com/justinsuntron/status/1656598894158159872?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">May 11, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p></p>
<p>He also added that though he might decide to buy certain coins and get exposure to a promising meme coin project, the said coin or project, regardless of its potential, may not be listed on Huobi or Poloniex. These are some of the early and most liquid cryptocurrency exchanges listing hundreds of tokens that Sun occupies an influential executive seat.</p>

<p>It is still unclear which project Sun has an eye on. At the same time, it could not be determined which of his crypto addresses the co-founder will use when trading meme coins. </p>
<p>Although Sun might be the co-founder of Tron, he has not shied from engaging in other projects deployed on public networks like Ethereum and others.</p>
<h2>Tron Co-founder Warned By Binance</h2>
<p>Following a warning from Changpeng Zhao, the CEO of Binance, the world’s largest exchange by client count and trading volumes, Sun reversed a $56 million transfer he had made in early May. There were concerns that Sun was planning a token grab of SUI, the native currency of the Sui Network. </p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Our team told Justin, if he uses any of these to grab the LaunchPool Sui token, we will &quot;take action against it&quot;. SMH.</p>
<p>Binance LaunchPool are meant as air drops for our retail users, not just for a few whales.</p>
<p>On the bright side, blockchains are transparent&#8230; <a href="https://t.co/8Xs1oXjfVd" rel="nofollow">https://t.co/8Xs1oXjfVd</a></p>
<p>&mdash; CZ <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f536.png" alt="🔶" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> Binance (@cz_binance) <a href="https://twitter.com/cz_binance/status/1652949031524376579?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">May 1, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p></p>
<p>WhaleAlert flagged Sun’s bulk $56 million transfer in TUSD. Before Zhao said, Binance would take action if he block-bought SUI from the Binance Launchpool. The exchange clarified that it wanted a fair airdrop to include active retailers and not “just a few crypto whales.” </p>
<p>Through the Launchpool, users can stake their crypto assets like SUI, providing liquidity, before receiving staking rewards. </p>
<a href="https://www.tradingview.com/x/bbU1iWP9/" rel="nofollow"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/bbU1iWP9/" alt="SUI Price On May 11| Source: SUIUSDT On Binance, TradingView" width="1280" height="595" /></a>
<p>Sun later <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://twitter.com/justinsuntron/status/1652954970000617474" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">apologized</a> for the huge transfer, saying it was in error. The real intention, he clarified, was in the market-making of TUSD, a stablecoin. The Tron founder said:</p>
<blockquote><p>Regrettably, some of our team members were not fully aware of the intended purpose for these funds and inadvertently used a portion of them to participate in exchange campaigns. Upon realizing this error, we immediately contacted the exchange team and arranged for a full refund of the funds.</p></blockquote>

<p>It is not immediately clear how Sun will proceed in trading and how the community will react to his purchases once he starts picking out worthy meme coin projects. Even so, what’s clear is that his addresses, like those of other influential crypto founders like Ethereum’s co-founder Vitalik Buterin, will be actively tracked and copied.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Justin-Sun-Meme-Coin-460x260.jpg" width="460" height="260" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Nightmare: OFAC To Allegedly Place Milady Wallet Owners On Blacklist</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/crypto/crypto-nightmare-ofac-to-allegedly-place-milady-wallet-owners-on-blacklist/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 22:00:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LADYS]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Milady]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=531326</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The frenzy around meme-based cryptocurrencies continues, with a new player stealing the headlines from PEPE coin. Milady is the latest entrant in this space, and its self-organized meme coin, LADYS, is based on an anime avatar non-fungible token (NFT) collection. In just 24 hours, the value of Milady&#8217;s LADYS coin surged by an astonishing 5,250% and reached a trading price of $0.0000001528. Related Reading: Winner Takes All: Bitcoin And DXY Compete For Global Financial Dominance Milady Crypto Holders Beware? However, The surge in the value of Milady&#8217;s LADYS coin has been accompanied by a concerning rumor. It has been suggested that wallets holding Milady coins will be placed on the Office of Foreign Assets Control (OFAC) blacklist. This list maintained by the US Treasury Department identifies individuals and organizations subject to economic sanctions and other restrictions. The reasons behind this rumor are unclear, and it is important to note that any official sources have not confirmed it. However, such a move by the US government could have serious implications for anyone holding Milady coins. Being placed on the OFAC blacklist could make it difficult for individuals to conduct financial transactions or access certain services. It is unclear why such sanctions would target Milady. While using cryptocurrencies for illicit purposes has been a concern for regulators, there is no evidence to suggest that Milady or its LADYS coin is being used for anything illegal. Additionally, the idea that wallets holding a particular cryptocurrency would be targeted for sanctions is unusual. Despite the concerning rumor that wallets holding Milady coins may be placed on the OFAC blacklist, the cryptocurrency continues to experience a powerful uptrend and post significant gains. Milady&#8217;s LADYS coin has surged by over 71.5% within the last 24 hours. Despite the rumors, this remarkable growth indicates that investors and traders still show confidence in the cryptocurrency. Will LADYS Coin Follow The Footsteps Of DOGE And SHIBA INU For 100x Growth? In the world of cryptocurrency, the rise of meme-based coins has been nothing short of phenomenal. Coins like DOGE and SHIBA INU have skyrocketed in value, delivering massive returns to early investors. Some wonder whether Milady&#8217;s LADYS coin could be the next big thing in the meme coin world. According to Crypto Koryo, a popular cryptocurrency analyst, Milady&#8217;s LADYS coin has followed the same formula as other successful meme coins. The project&#8217;s Twitter and Telegram accounts were created on May 6th, and just two days later, the LADYS token went live. On the same day, the project posted its first tweet. However, what caught Crypto Koryo&#8217;s attention was that Milady&#8217;s team quickly reached out to several big influencers on Twitter. These influencers, including GevCrypto, AlmiraCrypto, and GiveAwayHost, have a combined following of over 2 million people. While these followers may be fake or bought, they are still enough to give Milady&#8217;s LADYS coin visibility and exposure to a large audience. The success of meme coins like DOGE and SHIBA INU has shown that social media hype and speculation can drive massive price increases quickly. However, as Crypto Koryo points out, the future of Milady&#8217;s LADYS coin is far from certain. While the coin has grown significantly, it could just as easily crash and burn depending on various factors. Compared to its nearest competitor PEPE coin, LADYS coin is currently leading the meme coin frenzy. While Milady&#8217;s LADYS has experienced significant growth, PEPE coin has suffered a decline of over 28% since yesterday. Related Reading: Bitcoin Bearish Chart Pattern Looms, Legendary Trader Sounds Warning Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The frenzy around meme-based cryptocurrencies continues, with a new player stealing the headlines from PEPE coin. Milady is the latest entrant in this space, and its self-organized meme coin, LADYS, is based on an anime avatar non-fungible token (NFT) collection. In just 24 hours, the value of Milady&#8217;s LADYS coin surged by an astonishing 5,250% and reached a trading price of $0.0000001528.</p>

<h2><b>Milady Crypto Holders Beware?</b></h2>
<p>However, The surge in the value of Milady&#8217;s LADYS coin has been accompanied by a concerning rumor. It has been suggested that wallets holding Milady coins will be placed on the Office of Foreign Assets Control (OFAC) blacklist. This list maintained by the US Treasury Department identifies individuals and organizations subject to economic sanctions and other restrictions.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">BREAKING: Tomorrow morning every wallet who owns a Milady will be placed on the OFAC Blacklist <a href="https://t.co/ifbpLuQIqN" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/ifbpLuQIqN</a></p>
<p>&mdash; David G <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f3f9.png" alt="🏹" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> (@d_gilz) <a href="https://twitter.com/d_gilz/status/1656465814546161664?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">May 11, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p></p>
<p>The reasons behind this rumor are unclear, and it is important to note that any official sources have not confirmed it. However, such a move by the US government could have serious implications for anyone holding Milady coins. Being placed on the OFAC blacklist could make it difficult for individuals to conduct financial transactions or access certain services.</p>
<p>It is unclear why such sanctions would target Milady. While using cryptocurrencies for illicit purposes has been a concern for regulators, there is no evidence to suggest that Milady or its LADYS coin is being used for anything illegal. Additionally, the idea that wallets holding a particular cryptocurrency would be targeted for sanctions is unusual.</p>
<p>Despite the concerning rumor that wallets holding Milady coins may be placed on the OFAC blacklist, the cryptocurrency continues to experience a powerful uptrend and post significant gains. Milady&#8217;s LADYS coin has surged by over 71.5% within the last 24 hours. Despite the rumors, this remarkable growth indicates that investors and traders still show confidence in the cryptocurrency.</p>
<b>Will LADYS Coin Follow The Footsteps Of DOGE And SHIBA INU For 100x Growth?</b>
<p>In the world of cryptocurrency, the rise of meme-based coins has been nothing short of phenomenal. Coins like DOGE and SHIBA INU have skyrocketed in value, delivering massive returns to early investors. Some wonder whether Milady&#8217;s LADYS coin could be the next big thing in the meme coin world.</p>
<p><a href="https://twitter.com/CryptoKoryo/status/1656721234795560980?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">According </a>to Crypto Koryo, a popular cryptocurrency analyst, Milady&#8217;s LADYS coin has followed the same formula as other successful meme coins. The project&#8217;s Twitter and Telegram accounts were created on May 6th, and just two days later, the LADYS token went live. On the same day, the project posted its first tweet.</p>
<p>However, what caught Crypto Koryo&#8217;s attention was that Milady&#8217;s team quickly reached out to several big influencers on Twitter. These influencers, including GevCrypto, AlmiraCrypto, and GiveAwayHost, have a combined following of over 2 million people. While these followers may be fake or bought, they are still enough to give Milady&#8217;s LADYS coin visibility and exposure to a large audience.</p>
<p>The success of meme coins like DOGE and SHIBA INU has shown that social media hype and speculation can drive massive price increases quickly. However, as Crypto Koryo points out, the future of Milady&#8217;s LADYS coin is far from certain. While the coin has grown significantly, it could just as easily crash and burn depending on various factors.</p>
<p>Compared to its nearest competitor PEPE coin, LADYS coin is currently leading the meme coin frenzy. While Milady&#8217;s LADYS has experienced significant growth, PEPE coin has suffered a decline of over 28% since yesterday.</p>

<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/fS0da6LU/" alt="Milady " width="1813" height="858" />
<p>Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ross-sneddon-D6qSe3gjrfY-unsplash-307x460.jpg" width="307" height="460" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Elon Musk Stepping Down as Twitter CEO, Will This Be The End of Dogecoin?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/dogecoin/elon-musk-stepping-down-as-twitter-ceo-will-this-be-the-end-of-dogecoin/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dalmas Ngetich]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 21:04:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DOGE prices]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[elon musk]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[twitter]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=531334</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Elon Musk, the owner of Twitter and a big supporter of Dogecoin, the original meme coin, is stepping down as the CEO of the social media platform to focus on product development. He will act as the chief technology officer (CTO) of Twitter. Elon Musk Stepping Down As Twitter CEO In a Tweet on late May 11, the technology billionaire said Twitter has since hired a CEO whom she will take over in six weeks. Excited to announce that I’ve hired a new CEO for X/Twitter. She will be starting in ~6 weeks! My role will transition to being exec chair &#38; CTO, overseeing product, software &#38; sysops. &#8212; Elon Musk (@elonmusk) May 11, 2023 Meanwhile, DOGE, like the rest of the crypto market, is down 32% from its April 2023 peak and likely to slide even lower following this announcement. Related Reading: Dogecoin Limps In A Bearish Market: What Traders Should Watch Out For Musk is an ardent supporter of cryptocurrencies and has specifically expressed his admiration for DOGE, the meme token. In numerous instances, DOGE prices have rallied following comments from Musk, mostly posted on Twitter. Like most meme coins, some argue that DOGE has no fundamental value, with supporters keen on riding the coin&#8217;s bullish and bearish cycles. During the last bull cycle, DOGE rallied to over $0.70, peaking when Elon Musk appeared on Saturday Night Live (SNL) show saying he was the &#8220;Doge master.&#8221;  Over the past few months, DOGE has crashed by over 85%, slumping to $0.05 in Q4 2022. However, this didn&#8217;t prevent Elon Musk from tweeting about the project. In April, DOGE prices rocketed when Twitter, the company Musk presently leads, temporarily changed its logo to the Shiba Inu dog associated with the meme project.  In response, DOGE spiked, adding as much as $4 billion, surging from around $0.07 to $0.10. Musk said he delivered on his promise by temporarily replacing the blue bird logo representing Twitter with Shiba Inu. As promised pic.twitter.com/Jc1TnAqxAV &#8212; Elon Musk (@elonmusk) April 3, 2023 Sued For Supporting Dogecoin Last month, the billionaire asked a United States court to dismiss the $258 billion racketeering lawsuit. In the case, Musk is accused of running a scheme to support DOGE.  An extract from the lawsuit reads: Defendants were aware since 2019 that Dogecoin had no value yet promoted Dogecoin to profit from its trading. Musk used his pedestal as World&#8217;s richest man to operate and manipulate the Dogecoin Pyramid Scheme for profit, exposure, and amusement. Related Reading: PEPE Price Prediction: Can Pepe Coin Flip Dogecoin? How DOGE reacts in the days ahead is yet to be seen, with Elon Musk stepping down as the CEO of Twitter. Feature Image From Canva, Chart From TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Elon Musk, the owner of Twitter and a big supporter of Dogecoin, the original meme coin, is stepping down as the CEO of the social media platform to focus on product development. He will act as the chief technology officer (CTO) of Twitter.</p>
<h2>Elon Musk Stepping Down As Twitter CEO</h2>
<p>In a Tweet on late May 11, the technology billionaire said Twitter has since hired a CEO whom she will take over in six weeks.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Excited to announce that I’ve hired a new CEO for X/Twitter. She will be starting in ~6 weeks!</p>
<p>My role will transition to being exec chair &amp; CTO, overseeing product, software &amp; sysops.</p>
<p>&mdash; Elon Musk (@elonmusk) <a href="https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1656748197308674048?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">May 11, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p></p>
<p>Meanwhile, DOGE, like the rest of the crypto market, is down 32% from its April 2023 peak and likely to slide even lower following this announcement.</p>

<p>Musk is an ardent supporter of cryptocurrencies and has specifically expressed his admiration for DOGE, the meme token. In numerous instances, DOGE prices have rallied following comments from Musk, mostly posted on Twitter.</p>
<p>Like most meme coins, some argue that DOGE has no fundamental value, with supporters keen on riding the coin&#8217;s bullish and bearish cycles. During the last bull cycle, DOGE rallied to over $0.70, peaking when Elon Musk appeared on Saturday Night Live (SNL) show saying he was the &#8220;Doge master.&#8221; </p>
<p>Over the past few months, DOGE has crashed by over 85%, slumping to $0.05 in Q4 2022. However, this didn&#8217;t prevent Elon Musk from tweeting about the project.</p>
<a href="https://www.tradingview.com/x/sjVzjTJV/" rel="nofollow"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/sjVzjTJV/" alt="Dogecoin Price On May 11: Source: DOGEUSDT On Binance, TradingView" width="1280" height="595" /></a>
<p>In April, DOGE prices rocketed when Twitter, the company Musk presently leads, temporarily changed its logo to the Shiba Inu dog associated with the meme project. </p>
<p>In response, DOGE spiked, adding as much as $4 billion, surging from around $0.07 to $0.10. Musk said he delivered on his promise by temporarily replacing the blue bird logo representing Twitter with Shiba Inu.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">As promised <a href="https://t.co/Jc1TnAqxAV" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/Jc1TnAqxAV</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Elon Musk (@elonmusk) <a href="https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1642976364080041984?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">April 3, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p></p>
<h2>Sued For Supporting Dogecoin</h2>
<p>Last month, the billionaire asked a United States court to <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.reuters.com/legal/transactional/elon-musk-sued-258-billion-over-alleged-dogecoin-pyramid-scheme-2022-06-16/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">dismiss</a> the $258 billion racketeering lawsuit. In the <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.classaction.org/media/johnson-v-musk-et-al.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">case</a>, Musk is accused of running a scheme to support DOGE. </p>
<p>An extract from the lawsuit reads:</p>
<blockquote><p>Defendants were aware since 2019 that Dogecoin had no value yet promoted Dogecoin to profit from its trading. Musk used his pedestal as World&#8217;s richest man to operate and manipulate the Dogecoin Pyramid Scheme for profit, exposure, and amusement.</p></blockquote>

<p>How DOGE reacts in the days ahead is yet to be seen, with Elon Musk stepping down as the CEO of Twitter.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Elon-Musk-Dogecoin-460x260.jpg" width="460" height="260" />	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
