<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
>

<channel>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.newsbtc.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<description>Bitcoin &#38; Cryptocurrency News Today</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 20:19:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Bitcoin (BTC) Lower Timeframe Outlook: $26,800 Breakthrough Could Spark Rally</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-btc-lower-timeframe-outlook-26800-breakthrough-could-spark-rally/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 00:00:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=537308</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC), the largest cryptocurrency in the market, made a fake attempt to breach the $27,500 barrier on Tuesday. Since then, it has been trading sideways, moving within a narrow channel.  The 50-day Moving Average, which is the nearest resistance, is at $27,200. Meanwhile, the strongest support is at the 200-day MA, placed at $25,200.  For Bitcoin to initiate a fully formed bull run in the market, it is essential to hold this support level, if BTC bulls expect another attempt to breach the $30,000 mark and propel the market in full force, the $25,200 support level is crucial, and it needs to be held to achieve this goal. Related Reading: Here’s How Current Bitcoin Capitulation Compares With Past Crashes XRP And LTC Poised For Breakouts As Bitcoin Eyes $28,000 The lower timeframe picture for Bitcoin is straightforward, according to cryptocurrency analyst Michael Van de Poppe. He believes that for BTC to continue its upward trend, it needs to break through the $26,800 level. If that level is breached and flipped, Van de Poppe predicts that $27,500 is a likely next target, with the possibility of further breakouts on XRP and Litecoin (LTC). Van de Poppe&#8217;s analysis is based on technical indicators and market trends. He highlights the significance of the $26,800 level as a key resistance level that must be overcome for BTC to gain momentum. The cryptocurrency has been trading in a narrow range, and a breakout could signal a shift in market sentiment. Van de Poppe&#8217;s predictions align with the overall bullish sentiment in the cryptocurrency market, with many analysts expecting BTC to continue its upward trajectory. However, there are also concerns about potential price corrections and volatility, which could impact short-term market movements. BTC In Period of Stability, Revisiting 200-Week MA Despite Downside Volatility According to cryptocurrency analyst Rekt Capital, BTC is currently in a period of stability. If this stability continues, BTC could revisit the $27,600 level and potentially break out. However, BTC is still retesting the 200-week Moving Average despite downside volatility below it during the week. Furthermore, BTC is currently trading below a series of Lower Highs, which is represented by the blue line in the chart. To move higher, BTC needs to invalidate this series of Lower Highs. On the other hand, the 200-week MA is acting as support, as indicated by the orange line in the chart. Together, these factors are creating a pennant-like structure, which is a pattern that typically indicates price compression and is often followed by a period of volatility. Rekt Capital&#8217;s analysis suggests that BTC is at a critical juncture, with the potential for a breakout or a breakdown depending on how it interacts with the 200-week MA and the series of Lower Highs. Related Reading: LUNC Token Continues To Surge During Market Uncertainty, What’s Behind It? Despite the potential risks, many investors remain bullish on BTC and other cryptocurrencies, with the overall market continuing to show strength and resilience. As institutional adoption of cryptocurrencies continues to grow, the demand for BTC and other digital assets is expected to increase, potentially driving prices higher in the long term. Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin (BTC), the largest cryptocurrency in the market, made a fake attempt to breach the $27,500 barrier on Tuesday. Since then, it has been trading sideways, moving within a narrow channel. </p>
<p>The 50-day Moving Average, which is the nearest resistance, is at $27,200. Meanwhile, the strongest support is at the 200-day MA, placed at $25,200. </p>
<p>For Bitcoin to initiate a fully formed bull run in the market, it is essential to hold this support level, if BTC bulls expect another attempt to breach the $30,000 mark and propel the market in full force, the $25,200 support level is crucial, and it needs to be held to achieve this goal.</p>

<h2>XRP And LTC Poised For Breakouts As Bitcoin Eyes $28,000</h2>
<p>The lower timeframe picture for Bitcoin is straightforward, <a href="https://twitter.com/CryptoMichNL/status/1667175968845250563?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">according </a>to cryptocurrency analyst Michael Van de Poppe. He believes that for BTC to continue its upward trend, it needs to break through the $26,800 level. If that level is breached and flipped, Van de Poppe predicts that $27,500 is a likely next target, with the possibility of further breakouts on XRP and Litecoin (LTC).</p>
<p>Van de Poppe&#8217;s analysis is based on technical indicators and market trends. He highlights the significance of the $26,800 level as a key resistance level that must be overcome for BTC to gain momentum. The cryptocurrency has been trading in a narrow range, and a breakout could signal a shift in market sentiment.</p>
<p>Van de Poppe&#8217;s predictions align with the overall bullish sentiment in the cryptocurrency market, with many analysts expecting BTC to continue its upward trajectory. However, there are also concerns about potential price corrections and volatility, which could impact short-term market movements.</p>
BTC In Period of Stability, Revisiting 200-Week MA Despite Downside Volatility
<p><a href="https://twitter.com/rektcapital/status/1666819605220986881?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">According </a>to cryptocurrency analyst Rekt Capital, BTC is currently in a period of stability. If this stability continues, BTC could revisit the $27,600 level and potentially break out. However, BTC is still retesting the 200-week Moving Average despite downside volatility below it during the week.</p>
<p>Furthermore, BTC is currently trading below a series of Lower Highs, which is represented by the blue line in the chart. To move higher, BTC needs to invalidate this series of Lower Highs.</p>
<img decoding="async" class="size-large wp-image-537312" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/FyG7USMaQAgN3sF-860x628.jpg" alt="Bitcoin " width="860" height="628" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/FyG7USMaQAgN3sF-860x628.jpg 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/FyG7USMaQAgN3sF-460x336.jpg 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/FyG7USMaQAgN3sF-768x561.jpg 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/FyG7USMaQAgN3sF-1536x1123.jpg 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/FyG7USMaQAgN3sF-750x548.jpg 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/FyG7USMaQAgN3sF-1140x833.jpg 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/FyG7USMaQAgN3sF.jpg 1850w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" loading="lazy"/>
<p>On the other hand, the 200-week MA is acting as support, as indicated by the orange line in the chart. Together, these factors are creating a pennant-like structure, which is a pattern that typically indicates price compression and is often followed by a period of volatility.</p>
<p>Rekt Capital&#8217;s analysis suggests that BTC is at a critical juncture, with the potential for a breakout or a breakdown depending on how it interacts with the 200-week MA and the series of Lower Highs.</p>

<p>Despite the potential risks, many investors remain bullish on BTC and other cryptocurrencies, with the overall market continuing to show strength and resilience. As institutional adoption of cryptocurrencies continues to grow, the demand for BTC and other digital assets is expected to increase, potentially driving prices higher in the long term.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/iUUeXhz8/" alt="Bitcoin " width="1813" height="858"/>
<p>Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/iStock-531282429-1-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin &#8220;Throwback&#8221; Could Trigger Flawless Technical Bottom Formation</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-throwback-flawless-technical-bottoming-formation/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tony "The Bull"]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 23:01:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xbt]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xbtusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=537304</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin price is struggling after failing to make it above resistance last month. Combined with the recent pressure on the crypto market applied by the US SEC, things aren&#8217;t looking great for bulls. However, the correction has stopped precisely at a key level that could indicate a &#8220;throwback&#8221; is in process. If confirmed, BTCUSD could trade above $40,000 per coin in the near future. A Closer Look At The Technical Bottom Formation In Crypto The study of technical analysis uses past price history to predict probabilities in future market movements. Certain patterns have been discovered time and time again, that produce reasonably replicable results. From the size or shape of the pattern, analysts can derive roughly how far the associated breakout should travel. Related Reading: Bitcoin Retests Moving Average That Marked All Major Market Bottoms Bitcoin price action over the last year has formed what appears to be a technically flawless inverse head and shoulders pattern. The inverse head and shoulders is a bullish reversal pattern that appears at the bottom of a trend as it change direction. It consists of a left shoulder, head, a right shoulder, and a neckline. The head must be lower than each shoulder, and the neckline is of extra importance, because that&#8217;s where the abundance of orders are associated. Is this a throwback to the neckline? &#124; BTCUSD on TradingView.com What Exactly Is A Bitcoin Throwback, And Why Does It Matter? A throwback occurs after a breakout of the neckline, when the market isn&#8217;t convinced of the bullish move. The neckline holding is a sign to others that the pattern could confirm, and more traders pile in creating a breakout and strong move higher. When using the example as a comparison, the resulting breakout could reach as much as over $40,000 per BTC. Related Reading: Rare Crypto Signal Emerges That Could Spark Another 2017-Style Boom When bullish patterns fail, the result is called a &#8220;busted&#8221; pattern and can cause a further crash as long traders are stopped out below the neckline. Stop loss levels are placed below the neckline, because a confirmed pattern will not breach below this point. Therefore, for the pattern to confirm, holding the neckline is especially critical. Will we see this bullish chart pattern ultimately confirm, or fail? This chart appeared in issue #7 of CoinChartist VIP alongside a dozen other exclusive crypto charts. Tony is the author of the CoinChartist (VIP) newsletter. Follow @TonyTheBullBTC &#38; @coinchartist_io on Twitter. Or join the TonyTradesBTC Telegram for daily market insights and technical analysis education. Please note: Content is educational and should not be considered investment advice. Featured image from iStockPhoto, Charts from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin price is struggling after failing to make it above resistance last month. Combined with the recent pressure on the crypto market applied by the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/coinbase/coinbase-ceo-takes-on-sec-igniting-crypto-communitys-passion-for-clarity/">US SEC</a>, things aren&#8217;t looking great for bulls.</p>
<p>However, the correction has stopped precisely at a key level that could indicate a &#8220;throwback&#8221; is in process. If confirmed, BTCUSD could trade above $40,000 per coin in the near future.</p>
<h2>A Closer Look At The Technical Bottom Formation In Crypto</h2>
<p>The study of <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/topic/what-is-technical-analysis/">technical analysis</a> uses past price history to predict probabilities in future market movements. Certain patterns have been discovered time and time again, that produce reasonably replicable results. From the size or shape of the pattern, analysts can derive roughly how far the associated breakout should travel.</p>

<p>Bitcoin price action over the last year has formed what appears to be a technically flawless <a href="https://coinchartist.io/inverse-head-and-shoulders/education/chart-patterns/" rel="nofollow">inverse head and shoulders pattern</a>. The inverse head and shoulders is a bullish reversal pattern that appears at the bottom of a trend as it change direction. It consists of a left shoulder, head, a right shoulder, and a neckline. The head must be lower than each shoulder, and the neckline is of extra importance, because that&#8217;s where the abundance of orders are associated.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-large wp-image-537305 aligncenter" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTC1_2023-06-09_14-36-49-860x493.png" alt="bitcoin BTC1!_2023-06-09_14-36-49" width="860" height="493" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTC1_2023-06-09_14-36-49-860x493.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTC1_2023-06-09_14-36-49-460x264.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTC1_2023-06-09_14-36-49-768x441.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTC1_2023-06-09_14-36-49-1536x881.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTC1_2023-06-09_14-36-49-2048x1175.png 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTC1_2023-06-09_14-36-49-750x430.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTC1_2023-06-09_14-36-49-1140x654.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/></p>

<h2>What Exactly Is A Bitcoin Throwback, And Why Does It Matter?</h2>
<p>A throwback occurs after a breakout of the neckline, when the market isn&#8217;t convinced of the bullish move. The neckline holding is a sign to others that the pattern could confirm, and more traders pile in creating a breakout and strong move higher. When using the example as a comparison, the resulting breakout could reach as much as over $40,000 per BTC.</p>

<p>When bullish patterns fail, the result is called a &#8220;busted&#8221; pattern and can cause a further crash as long traders are stopped out below the neckline. Stop loss levels are placed below the neckline, because a confirmed pattern will not breach below this point. Therefore, for the pattern to confirm, holding the neckline is especially critical. Will we see this bullish chart pattern ultimately confirm, or fail?</p>
<p>This chart appeared in <a href="https://coinchartist.substack.com/p/issue-7-calm-before-the-storm" rel="nofollow">issue #7 of CoinChartist VIP</a> alongside a dozen other exclusive crypto charts.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/iStock-1198591342-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Investor Sentiment Refuses To Budge, But Can The Weekend Change This?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/crypto/crypto-investor-sentiment-refuses-to-budge-but-can-the-weekend-change-this/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Best Owie]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 23:00:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Fear & Greed Index]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto investors]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto market]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[regulation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=537216</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Crypto investor sentiment has been in the same place for over a month as investors have been hard-pressed to make a decision. This comes amid heightened regulatory headwinds with the United States Securities &#38; Exchange Commission suing the likes of Binance and Coinbase. But could a change be coming soon? Crypto Fear &#38; Greed Index Remains Neutral Following the market surge of Q1 2023 where Bitcoin was able to reclaim the $30,000 level, the market has been in a somewhat downward spiral since then. This has cumulated in investors being unwilling to place bets on whether the market will move up or down, bringing the Crypto Fear &#38; Greed Index to one of its longest stretches in neutral territory. Related Reading: Cardano (ADA) Declines As Market Recovers Amid Security Charges Presently, the index is sitting at a complete dead center of 50 on the scale which ranks sentiment from 1-100. 1-25 marks the extreme fear territory, 26-46 marks the fear level, 54-75 means greed and 76-100 is extreme greed. The 47-53 range is reserved for the neutral territory. At this point, the index points to a lack of activity from investors. This is understandable given that investors are currently waiting for more clarity from regulators to determine if investing in the digital assets right now is a good idea or not. Fear &#38; Greed Index spends over one month in neutral &#124; Source: alternative.me The index has now spent the better part of the last month in this neutral territory as the tug-of-war between the bulls and the bears come to a standstill. So there is no significant movement expected in either direction while it remains this way. Can The Weekend Shift Market Sentiment? The weekend has historically been a period of time characterized by low volatility due to reduced market participation from investors as they take a break from the markets. However, there have also been times when the weekend has come with the most bullish or bearish movements for the market. Total market cap sitting at $1.074 trillion as investors capitulate &#124; Source: Crypto Total Market Cap on TradingView.com As the market heads into another weekend, the possibility of a shift occurring during this time, although not very high, remains present. This is because, with low momentum, it is easier for the markets to swing one way or another with less volume than required on a weekday. Related Reading: Here’s Why Ethereum Could Be At Risk Of Falling To $1,000 Again Given this, there could be a rapid surge if bulls are able to beat the $27,000 level for Bitcoin in the next couple of days. But bears are awarded just as much opportunity during this time, especially if Bitcoin fails to hold the $26,000 support. Nevertheless, a swift movement in either direction could shake investors out of their current wary state to jump back into the market once more. Follow Best Owie on Twitter for market insights, updates, and the occasional funny tweet… Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="p2">Crypto investor sentiment has been in the same place for over a month as investors have been hard-pressed to make a decision. This comes amid heightened regulatory headwinds with the United States Securities &amp; Exchange Commission suing the likes of Binance and Coinbase. But could a change be coming soon?</p>
<h2 class="p2">Crypto Fear &amp; Greed Index Remains Neutral</h2>
<p class="p2">Following the market surge of Q1 2023 where Bitcoin was able to reclaim the $30,000 level, the market has been in a somewhat downward spiral since then. This has cumulated in investors being unwilling to place bets on whether the market will move up or down, bringing the Crypto Fear &amp; Greed Index to one of its longest stretches in neutral territory.</p>

<p class="p2">Presently, the index is sitting at a complete dead center of 50 on the scale which ranks sentiment from 1-100. 1-25 marks the extreme fear territory, 26-46 marks the fear level, 54-75 means greed and 76-100 is extreme greed. The 47-53 range is reserved for the neutral territory.</p>
<p class="p2">At this point, the index points to a lack of activity from investors. This is understandable given that investors are currently waiting for more clarity from regulators to determine if investing in the digital assets right now is a good idea or not.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-537219 aligncenter" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Crypto-market-sentiment-neutral-460x166.png" alt="Crypto market sentiment neutral" width="460" height="166" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Crypto-market-sentiment-neutral-460x166.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Crypto-market-sentiment-neutral-860x311.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Crypto-market-sentiment-neutral-768x277.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Crypto-market-sentiment-neutral-1536x555.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Crypto-market-sentiment-neutral-2048x740.png 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Crypto-market-sentiment-neutral-750x271.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Crypto-market-sentiment-neutral-1140x412.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px"/></p>

<p class="p2">The index has now spent the better part of the last month in this neutral territory as the tug-of-war between the bulls and the bears come to a standstill. So there is no significant movement expected in either direction while it remains this way.</p>
<h2 class="p2">Can The Weekend Shift Market Sentiment?</h2>
<p class="p2">The weekend has historically been a period of time characterized by low volatility due to reduced market participation from investors as they take a break from the markets. However, there have also been times when the weekend has come with the most bullish or bearish movements for the market.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/AI8rh777/" alt="Crypto total market cap chart from TradingView.com" width="2882" height="1724"/></p>

<p class="p2">As the market heads into another weekend, the possibility of a shift occurring during this time, although not very high, remains present. This is because, with low momentum, it is easier for the markets to swing one way or another with less volume than required on a weekday.</p>

<p class="p2">Given this, there could be a rapid surge if bulls are able to beat the $27,000 level for Bitcoin in the next couple of days. But bears are awarded just as much opportunity during this time, especially if Bitcoin fails to hold the $26,000 support.</p>
<p class="p2">Nevertheless, a swift movement in either direction could shake investors out of their current wary state to jump back into the market once more.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/iStock-483661187-1-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tron Upward Price Momentum At Risk Unless Key Resistance Is Breached</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/tron/tron-upward-price-momentum-at-risk-unless-key-resistance-is-breached/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[anushsamal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 21:30:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Tron]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[TRON]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[TRX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[trxusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[TRXUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=537261</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Over the past few weeks, the price of Tron (TRX) has experienced an upward movement. However, it has struggled to break through a crucial resistance level for a significant period of time. In the last 24 hours, TRX saw a 1% increase, while on the weekly chart, it recorded a 3% gain. The bullish momentum has been maintained since surpassing the $0.68 price level. The technical outlook suggests a potential shift towards bullish influence. Related Reading: Cardano Price Threatens Multi-Month Low Unless Bulls Defend This Support Demand and accumulation indicators have shown improvement in the daily timeframe. While Tron has managed to resist the broader market sentiments affecting other altcoins, it remains vulnerable to fluctuations in the Bitcoin price. To sustain its daily gains, it is crucial for TRX to surpass the immediate resistance level. Failure to do so may result in a reversal of its upward trend. The increase in the TRX market capitalization indicates that demand has started to revisit the market. Tron Price Analysis: One-Day Chart At the time of writing, Tron (TRX) was trading at $0.078. The altcoin faced overhead resistance at $0.079, and a successful move above this level would likely propel TRX above the $0.080 mark. However, if it is rejected at $0.079, the coin could experience a significant decline. It is worth noting that TRX has previously faced rejection at the $0.083 level, which will serve as an important resistance. On the downside, the nearest support for Tron is located at $0.074. If TRX fails to hold above this support level, it may drop further to $0.068. The trading volume of TRX in the last session was green, suggesting that buyers have started to establish control over the price. Technical Analysis Following a period of decreased investor interest earlier this month, Tron (TRX) is currently showing signs of recovery in terms of demand on the daily chart. The Relative Strength Index (RSI) indicates that buyers are exerting dominance in the market, as it is above the half-line. This suggests a positive sentiment and increased buying pressure. Additionally, the price of TRX has moved above the 20-Simple Moving Average (SMA) line, indicating that buyers are in control of the price momentum in the market. This further supports the notion that buyer dominance is prevailing. To sustain this buyer momentum, it is crucial for TRX to break past the $0.079 resistance level. If TRX successfully surpasses this level, it may continue its upward movement Contrary to rising demand, TRX has maintained sell signals on the daily chart based on the Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD) indicator. The MACD histogram formed red bars, indicating sell signals for the altcoin. This suggests a potential decline in price if TRX fails to move above the immediate resistance level. Related Reading: MATIC Price Shows Bullish Formation – What’s Next? Furthermore, the Chaikin Money Flow (CMF), which measures capital inflows and outflows, is below the half-line. The upcoming trading sessions will be crucial for TRX to determine its future direction. Featured Image From UnSplash, Charts From TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Over the past few weeks, the price of Tron (TRX) has experienced an upward movement. However, it has struggled to break through a crucial resistance level for a significant period of time.</p>
<p>In the last 24 hours, TRX saw a 1% increase, while on the weekly chart, it recorded a 3% gain. The bullish momentum has been maintained since surpassing the $0.68 price level. The technical outlook suggests a potential shift towards bullish influence.</p>

<p>Demand and accumulation indicators have shown improvement in the daily timeframe. While Tron has managed to resist the broader market sentiments affecting other altcoins, it remains vulnerable to fluctuations in the Bitcoin price.</p>
<p>To sustain its daily gains, it is crucial for TRX to surpass the immediate resistance level. Failure to do so may result in a reversal of its upward trend. The increase in the TRX market capitalization indicates that demand has started to revisit the market.</p>
<h2>Tron Price Analysis: One-Day Chart</h2>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-537262 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/TRXUSD_2023-06-09_21-04-31.png" alt="Tron" width="1817" height="830" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/TRXUSD_2023-06-09_21-04-31.png 1817w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/TRXUSD_2023-06-09_21-04-31-460x210.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/TRXUSD_2023-06-09_21-04-31-860x393.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/TRXUSD_2023-06-09_21-04-31-768x351.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/TRXUSD_2023-06-09_21-04-31-1536x702.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/TRXUSD_2023-06-09_21-04-31-750x343.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/TRXUSD_2023-06-09_21-04-31-1140x521.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1817px) 100vw, 1817px"/>
<p>At the time of writing, Tron (TRX) was trading at $0.078. The altcoin faced overhead resistance at $0.079, and a successful move above this level would likely propel TRX above the $0.080 mark. However, if it is rejected at $0.079, the coin could experience a significant decline.</p>
<p>It is worth noting that TRX has previously faced rejection at the $0.083 level, which will serve as an important resistance. On the downside, the nearest support for Tron is located at $0.074.</p>
<p>If TRX fails to hold above this support level, it may drop further to $0.068. The trading volume of TRX in the last session was green, suggesting that buyers have started to establish control over the price.</p>
<h2>Technical Analysis</h2>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-537263 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/TRXUSD_2023-06-09_21-05-23.png" alt="Tron" width="1817" height="743" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/TRXUSD_2023-06-09_21-05-23.png 1817w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/TRXUSD_2023-06-09_21-05-23-460x188.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/TRXUSD_2023-06-09_21-05-23-860x352.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/TRXUSD_2023-06-09_21-05-23-768x314.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/TRXUSD_2023-06-09_21-05-23-1536x628.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/TRXUSD_2023-06-09_21-05-23-750x307.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/TRXUSD_2023-06-09_21-05-23-1140x466.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1817px) 100vw, 1817px"/>
<p>Following a period of decreased investor interest earlier this month, Tron (TRX) is currently showing signs of recovery in terms of demand on the daily chart. The Relative Strength Index (RSI) indicates that buyers are exerting dominance in the market, as it is above the half-line. This suggests a positive sentiment and increased buying pressure.</p>
<p>Additionally, the price of TRX has moved above the 20-Simple Moving Average (SMA) line, indicating that buyers are in control of the price momentum in the market.</p>
<p>This further supports the notion that buyer dominance is prevailing. To sustain this buyer momentum, it is crucial for TRX to break past the $0.079 resistance level. If TRX successfully surpasses this level, it may continue its upward movement</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-537264 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/TRXUSD_2023-06-09_21-06-21.png" alt="Tron" width="1816" height="743" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/TRXUSD_2023-06-09_21-06-21.png 1816w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/TRXUSD_2023-06-09_21-06-21-460x188.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/TRXUSD_2023-06-09_21-06-21-860x352.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/TRXUSD_2023-06-09_21-06-21-768x314.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/TRXUSD_2023-06-09_21-06-21-1536x628.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/TRXUSD_2023-06-09_21-06-21-750x307.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/TRXUSD_2023-06-09_21-06-21-1140x466.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1816px) 100vw, 1816px"/>
<p>Contrary to rising demand, TRX has maintained sell signals on the daily chart based on the Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD) indicator.</p>
<p>The MACD histogram formed red bars, indicating sell signals for the altcoin. This suggests a potential decline in price if TRX fails to move above the immediate resistance level.</p>

<p>Furthermore, the Chaikin Money Flow (CMF), which measures capital inflows and outflows, is below the half-line. The upcoming trading sessions will be crucial for TRX to determine its future direction.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/kanchanara-U7cibaQXa8Q-unsplash-460x306.jpg" width="460" height="306" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance.US Suspends USD Deposits And Withdrawals Amid SEC Pressure</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/binance/binance-us-suspends-usd-deposits-and-withdrawals-amid-sec-pressure/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 20:30:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance US]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=537256</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Binance.US, in response to the aggressive tactics employed by the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) in its ideological campaign against the American digital asset industry, on its official Twitter handle has announced the suspension of USD deposits and impending fiat (USD) withdrawal pause. The exchange cites the need to protect its customers and platform amidst the challenges created by the SEC&#8217;s actions. While transitioning to a crypto-only exchange temporarily, Binance.US  assures its customers of maintaining 1:1 reserves for all customer assets, with crypto-related services remaining fully operational. Binance Prioritizing Customer Protection And Defending the Digital Asset Industry Binance.US&#8217;s proactive steps aim to prioritize customer interests and ensure the security of their assets. The suspension of USD deposits and notification regarding the impending pause in fiat withdrawal channels come as a defensive measure to address the challenges posed by the SEC&#8217;s aggressive tactics. The exchange encourages its customers to take appropriate action with their USD holdings in light of these developments. Related Reading: Former SEC Chairman Deserves Appreciation From Ripple, Alderoty States Despite the temporary suspension of USD-related services, Binance.US emphasizes that trading, staking, deposits, and withdrawals in cryptocurrencies will continue to operate without interruption. The exchange assures its customers that any potential downtime in processing withdrawals may be attributed to elevated volumes and weekend bank closures. ​&#8221;​Our priority is, and has always been, our customers. We are taking these proactive steps as we–for a time–transition to a crypto-only exchange,” the exchange said. “To be clear, we maintain 1:1 reserves for all customer assets. Any downtime in processing withdrawals may be the result of elevated volumes and weekend bank closures. Moreover, trading, staking, deposits and withdrawals in crypto remain fully operational.” BNB struggles to hold above $260 support &#124; Source: BNBUSD on TradingView.com While Binance.US expresses openness to a productive compromise that enables a thriving digital asset marketplace in America, it vows to vigorously defend itself, its customers, and the industry against what it considers meritless attacks by the SEC. The exchange remains committed to protecting its customers&#8217; interests and ensuring the continued growth and development of the digital asset ecosystem. Related Reading: Crypto Market Tension: ADA, BNB, MATIC, SOL Crash Over 10% In Past Week In conclusion,  the recent developments surrounding Binance.US and its response to the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) demonstrate the exchange&#8217;s unwavering commitment to its customers and the digital asset industry. Customers are urged to take appropriate action with their USD holdings in response to the SEC&#8217;s aggressive tactics as early as June 13,2023. Meanwhile, Binance’s native token BNB has continued to struggle in the market. The digital asset crashed over 10% when the SEC first announced its lawsuit and has seen mounting selling pressure since. It is currently trading at a price of $262.76, down 0.86% in the last 24 hours. Featured image from BBC, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Binance.US, in response to the aggressive tactics employed by the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) in its ideological campaign against the American digital asset industry, on its <a href="https://twitter.com/BinanceUS/status/1666996908651323393?s=20" rel="nofollow">official Twitter handle</a> has announced the suspension of USD deposits and impending fiat (USD) withdrawal pause.</p>
<p>The exchange cites the need to protect its customers and platform amidst the challenges created by the SEC&#8217;s actions. While transitioning to a crypto-only exchange temporarily, Binance.US  assures its customers of maintaining 1:1 reserves for all customer assets, with crypto-related services remaining fully operational.</p>
<h2>Binance Prioritizing Customer Protection And Defending the Digital Asset Industry</h2>
<p>Binance.US&#8217;s proactive steps aim to prioritize customer interests and ensure the security of their assets. The suspension of USD deposits and notification regarding the impending pause in fiat withdrawal channels come as a defensive measure to address the challenges posed by the SEC&#8217;s aggressive tactics. The exchange encourages its customers to take appropriate action with their USD holdings in light of these developments.</p>

<p>Despite the temporary suspension of USD-related services, Binance.US emphasizes that trading, staking, deposits, and withdrawals in cryptocurrencies will continue to operate without interruption. The exchange assures its customers that any potential downtime in processing withdrawals may be attributed to elevated volumes and weekend bank closures.</p>
<p>​&#8221;​Our priority is, and has always been, our customers. We are taking these proactive steps as we–for a time–transition to a crypto-only exchange,” the exchange said. “To be clear, we maintain 1:1 reserves for all customer assets. Any downtime in processing withdrawals may be the result of elevated volumes and weekend bank closures. Moreover, trading, staking, deposits and withdrawals in crypto remain fully operational.”</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/rbtHGXIg/" alt="Binance Coin (BNB) price chart from TradingView.com" width="2158" height="1686"/></p>

<p>While Binance.US expresses openness to a productive compromise that enables a thriving digital asset marketplace in America, it vows to vigorously defend itself, its customers, and the industry against what it considers meritless attacks by the SEC. The exchange remains committed to protecting its customers&#8217; interests and ensuring the continued growth and development of the digital asset ecosystem.</p>

<p>In conclusion,  the recent developments surrounding Binance.US and its response to the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) demonstrate the exchange&#8217;s unwavering commitment to its customers and the digital asset industry. Customers are urged to take appropriate action with their USD holdings in response to the SEC&#8217;s aggressive tactics as early as June 13,2023.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, Binance’s native token BNB has continued to struggle in the market. The digital asset crashed over 10% when the SEC first announced its lawsuit and has seen mounting selling pressure since. It is currently trading at a price of $262.76, down 0.86% in the last 24 hours.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/IMG_0007-460x258.jpeg" width="460" height="258" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Here&#8217;s How Current Bitcoin Capitulation Compares With Past Crashes</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/current-bitcoin-capitulation-compares-past-crashes/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hououin Kyouma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 19:30:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin capitulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Crashes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin short-term holders]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=537187</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[On-chain data shows that Bitcoin short-term holders are depositing 0.82% of their supply to exchanges. Here&#8217;s how these inflows compare with past crashes. Bitcoin Short-Term Holder Inflows Have Been Elevated Recently The BTC market can be divided into two broad investor groups, one of which is the &#8220;short-term holder (STHs) cohort.&#8221; The STHs are investors who have been holding onto their coins since less than 155 days ago. Generally, the Bitcoin holders belonging to this group are the weakest hands in the market, as they may easily sell at the sight of any sharp volatility or uncertainty in the market. The opposite cohort is called the &#8220;long-term holder (LTH) group,&#8221; and it naturally includes all participants that have been carrying their BTC in their wallets since more than 155 days ago. These LTHs usually hold for large stretches of times, and they are the diamond hands in the sector who need to be pushed a lot before they start panic selling their coins. Recently, the Bitcoin market has observed the emergence of FUD in the market, as a result of the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) suing cryptocurrency exchanges Binance and Coinbase. The market has acted volatile in both directions, but overall the price of the asset has gone down since the volatility has arrived. Obviously, in times like these, the STHs would be the first ones to break. In a new tweet, the on-chain analytics firm Glassnode has looked at the exchange inflow data of the STHs, to see how they are coping with the current situation. The below chart shows the trend in the Bitcoin exchange inflow for these investors over the past year: Looks like the value of the metric has been a bit high in recent days &#124; Source: Glassnode on Twitter As you can see in the above graph, the Bitcoin exchange inflow for the STHs has been climbing recently and has now hit relatively high levels. The &#8220;exchange inflow&#8221; here refers to a metric that tracks the amount of the asset that these investors have been depositing into the wallets of centralized exchanges. Related Reading: Bitcoin Bearish Signal: Dormant 1,433 BTC Moves After 10+ Years One of the main reasons why investors transfer their coins to these platforms is for selling-related purposes, so the exchange inflow data for these holders can provide us with hints about their current selling behavior. In the context of the current discussion, a modified version of the exchange inflow is being used; one that measures the inflows in terms of the percentage of the total STH Bitcoin supply. The STH exchange inflow has hit a value of 0.82% recently, meaning that these investors have recently been sending around 0.82% of their supply to these platforms. Related Reading: Bitcoin Price Defies Gravity But Here Is Why It Could Decline Again This is certainly not a small value, but when compared to other panic selling events in the past year, namely the LUNA collapse, the FTX crash, and the relief rally in March 2023 (all marked with red on the chart), the current inflows are still quite low. This would mean that the latest uncertainty in the Bitcoin market hasn&#8217;t yet been enough to push the STHs into capitulating at levels similar to historical capitulation events. BTC Price At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading around $26,600, down 2% in the last week. BTC has been consolidating in the last few days &#124; Source: BTCUSD on TradingView Featured image from Maxim Hopman on Unsplash.com, charts from TradingView.com, Glassnode.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On-chain data shows that Bitcoin short-term holders are depositing 0.82% of their supply to exchanges. Here&#8217;s how these inflows compare with past crashes.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Short-Term Holder Inflows Have Been Elevated Recently</h2>
<p>The BTC market can be divided into two broad investor groups, one of which is the &#8220;<a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-short-term-holder-profit-nov-2021/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">short-term holder (STHs) cohort</a>.&#8221; The STHs are investors who have been holding onto their coins since less than 155 days ago.</p>
<p>Generally, the Bitcoin holders belonging to this group are the weakest hands in the market, as they may easily sell at the sight of any sharp volatility or uncertainty in the market.</p>
<p>The opposite cohort is called the &#8220;<a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-long-term-holders-holding-price-decline/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">long-term holder (LTH) group</a>,&#8221; and it naturally includes all participants that have been carrying their BTC in their wallets since more than 155 days ago.</p>
<p>These LTHs usually hold for large stretches of times, and they are the diamond hands in the sector who need to be pushed a lot before they start panic selling their coins.</p>
<p>Recently, the Bitcoin market has observed the emergence of FUD in the market, as a result of the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/breaking-news-ticker/coinbase-caught-in-sec-legal-crossfire-coin-price-suffers/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">suing</a> cryptocurrency exchanges Binance and Coinbase.</p>
<p>The market has acted volatile in both directions, but overall the price of the asset has gone down since the volatility has arrived. Obviously, in times like these, the STHs would be the first ones to break.</p>
<p>In a new tweet, the on-chain analytics firm <a href="https://twitter.com/glassnode/status/1666757119314362368" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Glassnode</a> has looked at the exchange inflow data of the STHs, to see how they are coping with the current situation.</p>
<p>The below chart shows the trend in the Bitcoin exchange inflow for these investors over the past year:</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone aligncenter" src="https://pbs.twimg.com/media/FyGBVTLXoAEWcim?format=png&amp;name=4096x4096" alt="Bitcoin Short-Term Holder Exchange Inflow" width="4052" height="2334"/></p>

<p>As you can see in the above graph, the Bitcoin exchange inflow for the STHs has been climbing recently and has now hit relatively high levels. The &#8220;exchange inflow&#8221; here refers to a metric that tracks the amount of the asset that these investors have been depositing into the wallets of centralized exchanges.</p>

<p>One of the main reasons why investors transfer their coins to these platforms is for selling-related purposes, so the exchange inflow data for these holders can provide us with hints about their current selling behavior.</p>
<p>In the context of the current discussion, a modified version of the exchange inflow is being used; one that measures the inflows in terms of the percentage of the total STH Bitcoin supply.</p>
<p>The STH exchange inflow has hit a value of 0.82% recently, meaning that these investors have recently been sending around 0.82% of their supply to these platforms.</p>

<p>This is certainly not a small value, but when compared to other panic selling events in the past year, namely the LUNA collapse, the FTX crash, and the relief rally in March 2023 (all marked with red on the chart), the current inflows are still quite low.</p>
<p>This would mean that the latest uncertainty in the Bitcoin market hasn&#8217;t yet been enough to push the STHs into capitulating at levels similar to historical capitulation events.</p>
<h2>BTC Price</h2>
<p>At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading around $26,600, down 2% in the last week.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium aligncenter" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/vAD6lnn6/" alt="Bitcoin Price Chart" width="1533" height="911"/></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/maxim-hopman-fiXLQXAhCfk-unsplash-2-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>LUNC Token Continues To Surge During Market Uncertainty, What&#8217;s Behind It?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/lunc-token-continues-to-surge-during-market-uncertainty-whats-behind-it/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Kent Glory]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 18:30:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LUNC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LUNC analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LUNC price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LUNCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Terra Classic]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=537212</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Terra Classic (LUNC), the original chain left behind after the Terra Luna/UST collapse, has given a glimmer of hope to investors over the past few days. LUNC went into an uptrend amid heightened market uncertainty and bearish investor sentiment. The token has registered impressive gains over the past few days, leaving one to wonder about the reason behind such improvement.  At the time of writing, LUNC price has increased by 0.71% in the last 24 hours and 16.95% over the past seven days. High Buying Pressure Pushes LUNC Price Amid Bearish Sentiments The increased activities on the Terra Classic network are seemingly one of the factors behind LUNC&#8217;s recent price gains. Based on Coinmarketcap data, LUNC’s market capitalization and trading volume have gained 17.75% above yesterday’s value.  Related Reading: ApeCoin Holders Suffer Financial Pain As 95% Endure Negative Returns Although the price surge momentum has reduced slightly, LUNC remains among the top cryptos by trading volume. LUNC’s price increase has secured it a place among top cryptocurrencies in terms of trading volume. Other Notable Factors Behind LUNC Price Gains The price surge followed after the LUNC Burn Army shared news of the v2.1.0 upgrade proposal on June 3. The proposal&#8217;s governance vote started on June 7, while the upgrade will go live on June 14. This development generated a buzz in the LUNC community, attracting more attention to the LUNC token.  The v2.1.0 upgrade is one of the biggest events in the Terra Classic community. It aims to bring LUNC to parity with other blockchains, including Terra 2.0 and Cosmos chains. This parity will allow developers and projects to resume building on the Terra Classic Chain. The v2.1.0 upgrade adds new features and improvements to Terra Classic, including allowing a minimum of 5% commission for validators aimed at promoting fair compensation.  Also, it comes with Cosmwasm and two other security updates touted to improve the ecosystem&#8217;s security and reliability. Furthermore, the soon-coming upgrade will bring several notable changes to the Terra Classic ecosystem. The WasmVM upgrade will introduce multi-chain interoperability, extending Terra Classic’s capabilities.  Community-focused Improvement Initiatives Besides the v2.1.0 upgrade, several other community-backed initiatives are responsible for LUNC’s recent price boosts and trading volume increase. Among these is the token burn initiative, which enhances the network’s utility.  Furthermore, on June 6, the LUNC Burn Army introduced the Bug Bounty Incentive Program to foster application functionality, enhanced security, and network resilience. The Bug Bounty initiative aims to compensate ethical hackers, security researchers, and developers who identify and report security vulnerabilities. Related Reading: Here’s Why Ethereum Could Be At Risk Of Falling To $1,000 Again Moreover, the recently introduced LUNC burn initiative that saw over 1 billion LUNC tokens wiped from circulation is among the factors boosting the token&#8217;s price. These improvement proposals have helped to increase investor interest in LUNC and are among the drivers of the current price surge. Featured image from Pixabay and chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Terra Classic (LUNC), the original chain left behind after the Terra Luna/UST collapse, has given a glimmer of hope to investors over the past few days. LUNC went into an uptrend amid heightened market uncertainty and bearish investor sentiment.</p>
<p>The token has registered impressive gains over the past few days, leaving one to wonder about the reason behind such improvement. </p>
<p>At the time of writing, <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/terra-luna/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">LUNC price</a> has increased by 0.71% in the last 24 hours and 16.95% over the past seven days.</p>
<h2>High Buying Pressure Pushes LUNC Price Amid Bearish Sentiments</h2>
<p>The increased activities on the Terra Classic network are seemingly one of the factors behind LUNC&#8217;s recent price gains. Based on Coinmarketcap data, LUNC’s market capitalization and trading volume have gained 17.75% above yesterday’s value. </p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/apecoin-holders-suffer-financial-pain-as-95-endure-negative-returns/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">ApeCoin Holders Suffer Financial Pain As 95% Endure Negative Returns</a></p>
<p>Although the price surge momentum has reduced slightly, LUNC remains among the top cryptos by trading volume. LUNC’s price increase has secured it a place among top cryptocurrencies in terms of trading volume.</p>
<h2>Other Notable Factors Behind LUNC Price Gains</h2>
<p>The price surge followed after the LUNC Burn Army shared <a href="https://twitter.com/luncburnarmy/status/1664824269216309248?t=N2cj6EJEttUn7woi1MqVAw&amp;s=19" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">news</a> of the v2.1.0 upgrade proposal on June 3. The proposal&#8217;s governance vote started on June 7, while the upgrade will go live on June 14. This development generated a buzz in the LUNC community, attracting more attention to the LUNC token. </p>
<p>The v2.1.0 upgrade is one of the biggest events in the Terra Classic community. It aims to bring LUNC to parity with other blockchains, including Terra 2.0 and Cosmos chains. This parity will allow developers and projects to resume building on the Terra Classic Chain.</p>
<p>The v2.1.0 upgrade adds new features and improvements to Terra Classic, including allowing a minimum of 5% commission for validators aimed at promoting fair compensation. </p>
<p>Also, it comes with Cosmwasm and two other security updates touted to improve the ecosystem&#8217;s security and reliability. Furthermore, the soon-coming upgrade will bring several notable changes to the Terra Classic ecosystem. The WasmVM upgrade will introduce multi-chain interoperability, extending Terra Classic’s capabilities. </p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/srZiidpg/" alt="LUNCUSD price chart" width="979" height="538"/>
Community-focused Improvement Initiatives
<p>Besides the v2.1.0 upgrade, several other community-backed initiatives are responsible for LUNC’s recent price boosts and trading volume increase. Among these is the token burn initiative, which enhances the network’s utility. </p>
<p>Furthermore, on June 6, the LUNC Burn Army <a href="https://commonwealth.im/terra-classic/discussion/11605-luna-classic-bug-bounty-incentive-program" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">introduced</a> the Bug Bounty Incentive Program to foster application functionality, enhanced security, and network resilience. The Bug Bounty initiative aims to compensate ethical hackers, security researchers, and developers who identify and report security vulnerabilities.</p>

<p>Moreover, the recently introduced LUNC <a href="https://twitter.com/LunaBurnTracker/status/1642097485307957252?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">burn initiative</a> that saw over <a href="https://finder.terra.money/classic/tx/6C38E169A0319E8B29B24CC737CBA2C3E8B3741651F941F48DF62252C9F64B15" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">1 billion LUNC</a> tokens wiped from circulation is among the factors boosting the token&#8217;s price. These improvement proposals have helped to increase investor interest in LUNC and are among the drivers of the current price surge.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/LUNC-460x298.jpg" width="460" height="298" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Avalanche Approaches Vital Support Level, What Comes Next?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/avalanche/avalanche-approaches-vital-support-level-what-comes-next/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[anushsamal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 17:30:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Avalanche]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AVAX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AVAXUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AVAXUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=537202</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Avalanche (AVAX) has experienced a bearish trend over the past few months, particularly after being rejected from the $17.50 price level. This rejection has allowed the bears to exert significant control over the price. In the last 24 hours, AVAX made a slight upward movement of 0.5%. On the weekly chart, it has lost approximately 3.5% of its value. With the technical outlook on the daily timeframe, the bears have an advantage. Both demand and accumulation indicators remain low on the chart, indicating a decrease in buying strength. Related Reading: Bearish BNB Signs Hint Downtrend May Persist Beyond Expectations It is worth noting that the recent volatility displayed by Bitcoin has influenced the price patterns of many altcoins, including AVAX. In order for altcoins like AVAX to surpass their immediate resistance levels, Bitcoin needs to stay above the $26,000 price mark. Presently, AVAX is trading close to a critical support level. If sellers exert more pressure, the altcoin may experience a significant decline in value. The decrease in market capitalization for AVAX indicates a lower buying strength in the market. Avalanche Price Analysis: One-Day Chart As of the time of writing, AVAX was trading at $13.90. The coin faces an overhead resistance at $14, and if it manages to surpass this level, it is likely to encounter strong resistance at $14.20. On the downside, if the price falls from its current level, it may break below the support mark at $13.80. This may lead the altcoin to trade near the $13.50 price level. The trading volume of AVAX in the last session was low, indicating that sellers still have an advantage in the market. Technical Analysis During the months of May and towards the end of April, AVAX experienced low buying strength. The Relative Strength Index (RSI) indicated that sellers had control over the price, as the RSI remained below the half-line and showed a downward trend at the time of writing. Additionally, the price moved below the 20-Simple Moving Average (SMA), suggesting low demand and indicating that sellers were driving the price momentum in the market.  If the price of AVAX attempts to rise above the $14 mark, it is expected that demand will return to the market. In line with other technical indicators, AVAX has shown reduced buying signals, indicating a downtrend. The Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD) is a momentum indicator that helps identify price reversals.  In the case of AVAX, it displayed declining green histograms, suggesting diminishing buy signals. Related Reading: MATIC Price Shows Bullish Formation – What’s Next? The Bollinger Bands, which measure price volatility and fluctuations, tightened at the time of writing. This tightening indicates that there is a possibility of increased volatility in the price of AVAX in the upcoming trading sessions. When the Bollinger Bands tighten, it often indicates a potential breakout in the near future. Featured Image From UnSplash, Charts From TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[









<p>Avalanche (AVAX) has experienced a bearish trend over the past few months, particularly after being rejected from the $17.50 price level. This rejection has allowed the bears to exert significant control over the price. In the last 24 hours, AVAX made a slight upward movement of 0.5%. On the weekly chart, it has lost approximately 3.5% of its value.</p>
<p>With the technical outlook on the daily timeframe, the bears have an advantage. Both demand and accumulation indicators remain low on the chart, indicating a decrease in buying strength.</p>

<p>It is worth noting that the recent volatility displayed by Bitcoin has influenced the price patterns of many altcoins, including AVAX. In order for altcoins like AVAX to surpass their immediate resistance levels, Bitcoin needs to stay above the $26,000 price mark.</p>
<p>Presently, AVAX is trading close to a critical support level. If sellers exert more pressure, the altcoin may experience a significant decline in value. The decrease in market capitalization for AVAX indicates a lower buying strength in the market.</p>
<h2>Avalanche Price Analysis: One-Day Chart</h2>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-537215 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/AVAXUSD_2023-06-09_17-46-33.png" alt="Avalanche" width="1817" height="830" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/AVAXUSD_2023-06-09_17-46-33.png 1817w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/AVAXUSD_2023-06-09_17-46-33-460x210.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/AVAXUSD_2023-06-09_17-46-33-860x393.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/AVAXUSD_2023-06-09_17-46-33-768x351.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/AVAXUSD_2023-06-09_17-46-33-1536x702.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/AVAXUSD_2023-06-09_17-46-33-750x343.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/AVAXUSD_2023-06-09_17-46-33-1140x521.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1817px) 100vw, 1817px"/>
<p>As of the time of writing, AVAX was trading at $13.90. The coin faces an overhead resistance at $14, and if it manages to surpass this level, it is likely to encounter strong resistance at $14.20.</p>
<p>On the downside, if the price falls from its current level, it may break below the support mark at $13.80. This may lead the altcoin to trade near the $13.50 price level. The trading volume of AVAX in the last session was low, indicating that sellers still have an advantage in the market.</p>
<h2>Technical Analysis</h2>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-537221 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/AVAXUSD_2023-06-09_17-47-19.png" alt="Avalanche" width="1817" height="743" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/AVAXUSD_2023-06-09_17-47-19.png 1817w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/AVAXUSD_2023-06-09_17-47-19-460x188.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/AVAXUSD_2023-06-09_17-47-19-860x352.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/AVAXUSD_2023-06-09_17-47-19-768x314.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/AVAXUSD_2023-06-09_17-47-19-1536x628.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/AVAXUSD_2023-06-09_17-47-19-750x307.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/AVAXUSD_2023-06-09_17-47-19-1140x466.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1817px) 100vw, 1817px"/>
<p>During the months of May and towards the end of April, AVAX experienced low buying strength. The Relative Strength Index (RSI) indicated that sellers had control over the price, as the RSI remained below the half-line and showed a downward trend at the time of writing.</p>
<p>Additionally, the price moved below the 20-Simple Moving Average (SMA), suggesting low demand and indicating that sellers were driving the price momentum in the market.  If the price of AVAX attempts to rise above the $14 mark, it is expected that demand will return to the market.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-537226 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/AVAXUSD_2023-06-09_18-43-15.png" alt="Avalanche" width="1817" height="743" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/AVAXUSD_2023-06-09_18-43-15.png 1817w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/AVAXUSD_2023-06-09_18-43-15-460x188.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/AVAXUSD_2023-06-09_18-43-15-860x352.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/AVAXUSD_2023-06-09_18-43-15-768x314.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/AVAXUSD_2023-06-09_18-43-15-1536x628.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/AVAXUSD_2023-06-09_18-43-15-750x307.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/AVAXUSD_2023-06-09_18-43-15-1140x466.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1817px) 100vw, 1817px"/>
<p>In line with other technical indicators, AVAX has shown reduced buying signals, indicating a downtrend. The Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD) is a momentum indicator that helps identify price reversals.  In the case of AVAX, it displayed declining green histograms, suggesting diminishing buy signals.</p>

<p>The Bollinger Bands, which measure price volatility and fluctuations, tightened at the time of writing. This tightening indicates that there is a possibility of increased volatility in the price of AVAX in the upcoming trading sessions. When the Bollinger Bands tighten, it often indicates a potential breakout in the near future.</p>











]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/johannes-waibel-WdBQHcIiSIw-unsplash-460x309.jpg" width="460" height="309" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Shiba Inu (SHIB) Price At The Most Crucial Point In Its History?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/shiba-inu-shib-price-at-most-crucial-point-in-history/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jake Simmons]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 16:25:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Shiba Inu]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIB]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=537204</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[After Shiba Inu (SHIB) had a fabulous rally at the beginning of the year, the price has been in a sustained downturn since February 5, which neither the beta launch of Shibarium nor an increase in monthly burn rates were able to prevent. With the price currently trading at $0.00000804, SHIB is thus at possibly the most important point in its young history. A look at the 1-day chart reveals that SHIB reached a local high of $0.00001575 on February 5, 2023. From that point until early May, the price formed a descending triangle with a horizontal trend line at $0.000010 acting as support for a long time. This price level was also aligned with the 23.6% Fibonacci level. Most Important Moment In Shiba Inu Price History? When the trend line was broken to the downside, the downtrend continued rapidly. All year-to-date gains were wiped out. However, one last hope may now be a triple bottom chart pattern, which the Shiba Inu price is currently exhibiting. The price area at $0.00000776 served as the last support back in mid-June 2022 and late December 2022, and now again. Shiba Inu meets all three characteristics of the chart pattern. Related Reading: Shiba Inu Hits Crucial Barrier – How This May Impact Investor Sentiment First, the three lows must be roughly equal in price and spaced apart by a certain distance (June and December 2022, June 2023). Second, volume must be decreasing throughout the pattern, which is a sign that the bears are losing strength. Looking at the time pattern of SHIB trading volume, this condition can also be considered to be met. Third, Shiba Inu has been in a steady downtrend with lower highs since the all-time high of late October 2021. Hence, the decisive moment might have come now: While the trading volume decreases during downward movements, the volume should increase during upward movements when the price breaks through the resistance levels. Only if that happens, a trend reversal seems possible. A very first resistance to break through is at $0.0000817. If successful, the 50-day Exponential Moving Average (EMA) currently at $0.00000907 could come into focus. However, probably the most important resistance to confirm a fake breakout is the 23.6% Fibonacci level at $0.000010. Related Reading: Shiba Inu (SHIB) Price Could Soar To Major Highs Soon, Here’s Why The bullish case of Shiba Inu is also supported by a possible bullish divergence of the RSI in the 1-day chart. This occurs when the RSI indicates an oversold condition (SHIB&#8217;s RSI dropped as low as 24 in May), followed by a higher low associated with lower price lows. Thus, the RSI of Shiba Inu price in the 1-day chart could indicate bullish momentum. The break above the oversold zone in recent days could be a signal for a new buy position. But the bearish case is still strong as well. SHIB traders do not want to see a drop below $0.00000716 at any cost. If this happens, it would be an alarming signal that SHIB could test the September 2021 low around $0,000006. Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>After Shiba Inu (SHIB) had a fabulous rally at the beginning of the year, the price has been in a sustained downturn since February 5, which neither the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/shiba-inu-jumps-4-as-lead-dev-reveals-when-shibarium/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">beta launch</a> of Shibarium nor an increase in monthly burn <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/shiba-inu-continues-rally-as-shib-burn-rate-spikes-over-20-in-the-past-day/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">rates</a> were able to prevent. With the price currently trading at $0.00000804, SHIB is thus at possibly the most important point in its young history.</p>
<p>A look at the 1-day chart reveals that SHIB reached a local high of $0.00001575 on February 5, 2023. From that point until early May, the price formed a descending triangle with a horizontal trend line at $0.000010 acting as support for a long time. This price level was also aligned with the 23.6% Fibonacci level.</p>
<h2>Most Important Moment In Shiba Inu Price History?</h2>
<p>When the trend line was broken to the downside, the downtrend continued rapidly. All year-to-date gains were wiped out. However, one last hope may now be a triple bottom chart pattern, which the Shiba Inu price is currently exhibiting.</p>
<p>The price area at $0.00000776 served as the last support back in mid-June 2022 and late December 2022, and now again. Shiba Inu meets all three characteristics of the chart pattern.</p>

<p>First, the three lows must be roughly equal in price and spaced apart by a certain distance (June and December 2022, June 2023). Second, volume must be decreasing throughout the pattern, which is a sign that the bears are losing strength. Looking at the time pattern of SHIB trading volume, this condition can also be considered to be met.</p>
<p>Third, Shiba Inu has been in a steady downtrend with lower highs since the all-time high of late October 2021. Hence, the decisive moment might have come now: While the trading volume decreases during downward movements, the volume should increase during upward movements when the price breaks through the resistance levels. Only if that happens, a trend reversal seems possible.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-537224 size-full" style="font-weight: 600;text-align: center" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/SHIBUSD_2023-06-09_15-06-14.png" alt="Shiba Inu price SHIB" width="3625" height="1672" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/SHIBUSD_2023-06-09_15-06-14.png 3625w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/SHIBUSD_2023-06-09_15-06-14-460x212.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/SHIBUSD_2023-06-09_15-06-14-860x397.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/SHIBUSD_2023-06-09_15-06-14-768x354.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/SHIBUSD_2023-06-09_15-06-14-1536x708.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/SHIBUSD_2023-06-09_15-06-14-2048x945.png 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/SHIBUSD_2023-06-09_15-06-14-750x346.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/SHIBUSD_2023-06-09_15-06-14-1140x526.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 3625px) 100vw, 3625px"/>
<p>A very first resistance to break through is at $0.0000817. If successful, the 50-day Exponential Moving Average (EMA) currently at $0.00000907 could come into focus. However, probably the most important resistance to confirm a fake breakout is the 23.6% Fibonacci level at $0.000010.</p>

<p>The bullish case of Shiba Inu is also supported by a possible bullish divergence of the RSI in the 1-day chart. This occurs when the RSI indicates an oversold condition (SHIB&#8217;s RSI dropped as low as 24 in May), followed by a higher low associated with lower price lows.</p>
<p>Thus, the RSI of Shiba Inu price in the 1-day chart could indicate bullish momentum. The break above the oversold zone in recent days could be a signal for a new buy position. But the bearish case is still strong as well.</p>
<p>SHIB traders do not want to see a drop below $0.00000716 at any cost. If this happens, it would be an alarming signal that SHIB could test the September 2021 low around $0,000006.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/iStock-1353098980-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Former SEC Chairman Deserves Appreciation From Ripple, Alderoty States</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/ripple/former-sec-chairman-deserves-appreciation-from-ripple-alderoty-states/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Eli Dambel]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 15:30:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrp]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrpusdt]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=537218</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Ripple General Counsel Stuart Alderoty, recently acknowledged the former United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) Chairman, Late Harvey Pitt, in a tweet expressing gratitude towards his contribution.   He added that Ripple owes a debt of gratitude to Harvey for providing a comprehensive description employed by the SEC to enforce compliance with securities laws. Alderoty further cites Pitt&#8217;s argument in the Tetragon vs. Ripple case, stating it is the court&#8217;s responsibility, not the commission&#8217;s, to decide if an asset qualifies as a security. Alderoty Highlights Pitt&#8217;s Report on SEC Lawsuit Process In the tweet, Alderoty added Pitt&#8217;s report in the Tetragon Fin. Grp. vs. Ripple lawsuit as an attachment. The Ripple general counsel drew attention to a comment Pitt made regarding the process of an enforcement action conducted by the SEC. Related Reading: Bitcoin Bearish Signal: Dormant 1,433 BTC Moves After 10+ Years Pitt’s report states an enforcement action begins when the SEC files a lawsuit against an entity in a federal court. He also noted that commissioners that vote to bring an enforcement action are minimally involved once the litigation commences. The former chairman clarified that once the SEC initiates legal proceedings, the commission&#8217;s role shifts to that of an advocate for its stance. Also, he emphasized that the court holds the ultimate authority to determine if the asset in question qualifies as a security. For context, Pitt died in Washington on May 30, 2023, at 78 years, due to a sudden illness. He became the SEC Chairperson in 2001 but resigned after 18 months due to various corporate scandals, including the notorious Enron scandal. Notably, Pitt served as the US Securities and Exchange Commission chairman under the reign of President George Bush. SEC vs. Ripple Legal Battle and Controversy Over Crypto Asset Securities It is worth noting that the lawsuit filed against Ripple by the SEC has lasted over two years, resulting in Ripple spending about $200 million to fight back. The SEC accuses Ripple of selling an asset as an unregistered security, while Ripple says the asset should be seen as a digital currency rather than a security. In addition to XRP, the SEC has recently designated various other crypto assets as securities.  This list includes ADA, CHZ, SOL, AXS, FIL, ICP, FLOW, NEAR, MATIC, VGX, SAND, DASH, BNB, BUSD, ATOM, MANA, ALGO, and COTI. Following the SEC&#8217;s decision to label multiple crypto assets as securities, the commission has encountered several criticisms from the crypto community. SEC Chair Gary Gensler had asserted that most crypto assets, excluding Bitcoin, are considered securities.  Nevertheless, Gensler did not explain how he reached this conclusion regarding the legal classification of these &#8220;most&#8221; cryptocurrencies. Meanwhile, in a recent tweet by Alderoty, he said that despite what Gensler said, the Securities and Exchange Commission does not have a magic regulatory wand to convert any token to securities. He added that he’s looking forward to how the Congress and Courts will follow up the case. Featured image from Pixabay and chart from Tradingview.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ripple General Counsel Stuart Alderoty, recently acknowledged the former United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) Chairman, Late Harvey Pitt, <a href="https://twitter.com/s_alderoty/status/1666949240101167104" rel="nofollow">in a tweet</a> expressing gratitude towards his contribution.  </p>
<p>He added that Ripple owes a debt of gratitude to Harvey for providing a comprehensive description employed by the SEC to enforce compliance with securities laws.</p>
<p>Alderoty further cites Pitt&#8217;s argument in the Tetragon vs. Ripple case, stating it is the court&#8217;s responsibility, not the commission&#8217;s, to decide if an asset qualifies as a security.</p>
<h2>Alderoty Highlights Pitt&#8217;s Report on SEC Lawsuit Process</h2>
<p>In the tweet, Alderoty added Pitt&#8217;s<a href="https://twitter.com/s_alderoty/status/1666949240101167104" rel="nofollow"> report</a> in the Tetragon Fin. Grp. vs. Ripple lawsuit as an attachment. The Ripple general counsel drew attention to a comment Pitt made regarding the process of an enforcement action conducted by the SEC.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-bearish-1433-btc-dormant-10-years-moves/?swcfpc=1">Bitcoin Bearish Signal: Dormant 1,433 BTC Moves After 10+ Years</a></p>
<p>Pitt’s report states an enforcement action begins when the SEC files a lawsuit against an entity in a federal court. He also noted that commissioners that vote to bring an enforcement action are minimally involved once the litigation commences.</p>
<p>The former chairman clarified that once the SEC initiates legal proceedings, the commission&#8217;s role shifts to that of an advocate for its stance. Also, he emphasized that the court holds the ultimate authority to determine if the asset in question qualifies as a security.</p>
<p>For context, Pitt died in Washington on May 30, 2023, at 78 years, due to a sudden illness. He became the SEC Chairperson in 2001 but resigned after 18 months due to various corporate scandals, including the notorious Enron scandal.</p>
<p>Notably, Pitt served as the US Securities and Exchange Commission chairman under the reign of President George Bush.</p>
<h2>SEC vs. Ripple Legal Battle and Controversy Over Crypto Asset Securities</h2>
<p>It is worth noting that the lawsuit filed against Ripple by the SEC has lasted over two years, resulting in <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/08/ripple-will-have-spent-200-million-fighting-sec-lawsuit-ceo-says.html#:~:text=Ripple%20CEO%20Brad%20Garlinghouse%20speaks,19%2C%202021.&amp;text=Ripple%20will%20have%20spent%20%24200%20million%20defending%20itself%20against%20a,Brad%20Garlinghouse%20told%20CNBC%20Monday." rel="nofollow">Ripple spending</a> about $200 million to fight back.</p>
<p>The SEC accuses Ripple of selling an asset as an unregistered security, while Ripple says the asset should be seen as a digital currency rather than a security.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-537220 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPUSDT_2023-06-09_17-57-07-860x454.png" alt="Former SEC Chairman Deserves Ripple&#039;s Appreciation, Alderoty States" width="860" height="454" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPUSDT_2023-06-09_17-57-07-860x454.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPUSDT_2023-06-09_17-57-07-460x243.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPUSDT_2023-06-09_17-57-07-768x406.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPUSDT_2023-06-09_17-57-07-1536x811.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPUSDT_2023-06-09_17-57-07-2048x1082.png 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPUSDT_2023-06-09_17-57-07-750x396.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPUSDT_2023-06-09_17-57-07-1140x602.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/>
<p>In addition to XRP, the SEC has recently designated various other crypto assets as securities.  This list includes ADA, CHZ, SOL, AXS, FIL, ICP, FLOW, NEAR, MATIC, VGX, SAND, DASH, BNB, BUSD, ATOM, MANA, ALGO, and COTI.</p>
<p>Following the SEC&#8217;s decision to label multiple crypto assets as securities, the commission has encountered several criticisms from the crypto community. SEC Chair Gary Gensler <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2022/06/27/cramer-monday-sec-chair-gensler-speaks-pioneer-ceo-says-no-to-biden.html" rel="nofollow">had asserted</a> that most crypto assets, excluding Bitcoin, are considered securities. </p>
<p>Nevertheless, Gensler did not explain how he reached this conclusion regarding the legal classification of these &#8220;most&#8221; cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, in a recent tweet by Alderoty, he <a href="https://twitter.com/s_alderoty/status/1666129461715120129" rel="nofollow">said</a> that despite what Gensler said, the Securities and Exchange Commission does not have a magic regulatory wand to convert any token to securities. He added that he’s looking forward to how the Congress and Courts will follow up the case.</p>
<p>Featured image from Pixabay and chart from Tradingview.com</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ripple-gf51139c6b_1280-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
