<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
>

<channel>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.newsbtc.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<description>Bitcoin &#38; cryptocurrency news today, price &#38; technical analysis</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 16:06:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>LUNC Burn Tax Set To Rise To 0.5% As KuCoin Proposal Receives Approval</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/lunc-burn-tax-set-to-rise-to-0-5-as-kucoin-proposal-receives-approval/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Dunn]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 13:50:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[burn]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[KuCoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LUNCUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=534204</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[After garnering the required votes, a major proposal has just passed in the KuCoin network. The proposal aimed at raising Terra Classic LUNC burns tax to 0.5%.  Following the positive results, KuCoin declared increasing the LUNC network burn rate from 0.2% to the proposed 0.5%.  LUNC Network Burn Tax Spikes On KuCoin KuCoin took to Twitter to announce the increase in the burn tax. In its announcement, KuCoin stated that it would facilitate the Terra Classic LUNC and TerraClassicUSD (USTC) increase on its platform following the burn tax activation. Related Reading: Shiba Inu Falls Below Critical Support, Is It Time For You To Buy? Notably, the activation will occur at the designated Terrra Classic block height of 12,902,399 and take effect on May 23.  Once activated, KuCoin will pay users more for transactions involving the two crypto assets, LUNC and USTC. Apart from the increased payments, the burn rate tax will reduce LUNC supply.  But there&#8217;s still a downside to the increased burn rate tax as it will reduce the trading volume. This is why many exchanges rejected such proposals in the past.  Notably, KuCoin has always supported such increases even when other exchanges delay. For instance, the exchange first supported a September 2022 Terra Classic burn tax of 1.2% even before the proposal passed.    Other exchanges, including Crypto.com, MEXC, and Binance, only later declared support for the burn tax.  But after the proposal passed, data implied that the increase reduced the trading volume for LUNC. Many investors stopped trading with the asset due to the spike in fees. Related Reading: NFT Market Takes A Hit: Sales Could Drop Below $1 Billion For The First Time In 2023 Following the outcome, the LUNC community voted to reduce the burn tax to 0.2%, attracting the support of crypto exchanges such as Binance.  After the reduction, the Terra Classic community brought up another proposal to increase the burn tax rate, but it wasn’t implemented.  Latest Burn Tax Increase Proposal, 3 Others Gain Massive Support While other proposals to increase the burn tax after reducing it from 1.2% to 0.2% failed due to several debates and arguments, the latest one received massive support. One of the reasons proposal 11515 passed was the conservative increase, which wouldn&#8217;t spike fees and discourage investors. The proposal focused mainly on reducing the excess supply of LUNC tokens in the market to prevent oversaturation and its associated risks.  But, it is not the only proposal submitted to the LUNC community. An active member raised 3 other proposals, plus the burn tax increase to enhance economic policies on the network.  The three others aimed at augmenting demand by increasing staking rewards, whitelisting smart contracts to enhance chain utility and volume, and increasing community pool funding to bolster developer funding. -Featured image from Pexels, chart from Tradingview]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>After garnering the required votes, a major proposal has just passed in the KuCoin network. The proposal aimed at raising Terra Classic LUNC burns tax to 0.5%. </p>
<p>Following the positive results, KuCoin declared increasing the LUNC network burn rate from 0.2% to the proposed 0.5%. </p>
<h2>LUNC Network Burn Tax Spikes On KuCoin</h2>
<p>KuCoin took to <a href="https://twitter.com/kucoincom/status/1659158748924100610?" rel="nofollow">Twitter</a> to announce the increase in the burn tax. In its announcement, KuCoin stated that it would facilitate the Terra Classic LUNC and TerraClassicUSD (USTC) increase on its platform following the burn tax activation.</p>

<p>Notably, the activation will occur at the designated Terrra Classic block height of 12,902,399 and take effect on May 23. </p>
<p>Once activated, KuCoin will pay users more for transactions involving the two crypto assets, LUNC and USTC. Apart from the increased payments, the burn rate tax will reduce LUNC supply. </p>
<p>But there&#8217;s still a downside to the increased burn rate tax as it will reduce the trading volume. This is why many exchanges rejected such proposals in the past. </p>
<p>Notably, KuCoin has always supported such increases even when other exchanges delay. For instance, <a href="https://www.kucoin.com/news/en-kucoin-will-support-the-tax-burn-proposal-of-the-terra-classic-lunc-community-20220907" rel="nofollow">the exchange first supported</a> a September 2022 Terra Classic burn tax of 1.2% even before the proposal passed.   </p>
<p>Other exchanges, including Crypto.com, MEXC, and Binance, only later declared support for the burn tax. </p>
<p>But after the proposal passed, <a href="https://medium.com/@strathcole/the-1-2-tax-kills-our-volume-does-it-though-a-deeper-analysis-b58163078b79" rel="nofollow">data implied</a> that the increase reduced the trading volume for LUNC. Many investors stopped trading with the asset due to the spike in fees.</p>

<p>Following the outcome, the LUNC community voted to reduce the burn tax to 0.2%, <a href="https://twitter.com/binance/status/1582625797231497217?" rel="nofollow">attracting the support</a> of crypto exchanges such as Binance. </p>
<p>After the reduction, the Terra Classic community brought up another proposal to increase the burn tax rate, <a href="https://twitter.com/ClassyCrypto_/status/1596659582755274752?" rel="nofollow">but it wasn’t implemented</a>. </p>
<h2>Latest Burn Tax Increase Proposal, 3 Others Gain Massive Support</h2>
<p>While other proposals to increase the burn tax after reducing it from 1.2% to 0.2% failed due to several debates and arguments, the latest one received massive support.</p>
<img decoding="async" class="wp-image-534206 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/LUNCUSDT_2023-05-20_17-08-49-860x370.png" alt="LUNC" width="860" height="370" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/LUNCUSDT_2023-05-20_17-08-49-860x370.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/LUNCUSDT_2023-05-20_17-08-49-460x198.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/LUNCUSDT_2023-05-20_17-08-49-768x331.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/LUNCUSDT_2023-05-20_17-08-49-1536x661.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/LUNCUSDT_2023-05-20_17-08-49-750x323.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/LUNCUSDT_2023-05-20_17-08-49-1140x491.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/LUNCUSDT_2023-05-20_17-08-49.png 1714w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" loading="lazy"/>
<p>One of the reasons proposal 11515 passed was the conservative increase, which wouldn&#8217;t spike fees and discourage investors.</p>
<p>The proposal focused mainly on reducing the excess supply of LUNC tokens in the market to prevent oversaturation and its associated risks. </p>
<p>But, it is not the only proposal submitted to the LUNC community. An active member <a href="https://classic-agora.terra.money/t/new-economic-policy-for-terra-classic-set-of-4-proposals-to-align-incentives/50415" rel="nofollow">raised</a> 3 other proposals, plus the burn tax increase to enhance economic policies on the network. </p>
<p>The three others aimed at augmenting demand by increasing staking rewards, whitelisting smart contracts to enhance chain utility and volume, and increasing community pool funding to bolster developer funding.</p>
<p><em>-Featured image from Pexels, chart from Tradingview</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/flame-ge8230230f_1280-460x306.jpg" width="460" height="306" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin And Ethereum Supply Drops To Record Lows Unseen Since 2015 And 2017</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/all/bitcoin-and-ethereum-supply-plummet-to-record-lows/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Edyme]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 13:32:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[All]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=534205</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Amid the tussle between the bulls and bears in the crypto market over the past week, the circulating supply of both Bitcoin (BTC) and Ethereum (ETH) has reached record lows, triggering speculation about the potential impact on the cryptocurrency market. Data provided by Santiment reveals a significant decrease in the amount of BTC and ETH held on exchanges, suggesting a shift in investor behavior. Bitcoin And Ethereum Supply Plummets On Exchanges According to Santiment&#8217;s data, the circulating supply of BTC on exchanges currently stands at a mere 5.7%, marking its lowest level since December 2017 when the cryptocurrency surged to an all-time high of $20,000. Related Reading: Ethereum Price Faces Confluence Of Bearish Factors and At Risk of Another Decline Similarly, the supply of ETH on exchanges has dropped to 10.1%, the lowest since its inception in 2015. This trend indicates that crypto investors are actively buying and withdrawing their coins from exchanges, opting for alternative storage methods. Santiment tweeted earlier today: Bitcoin &#38; Ethereum both continue to quietly see more and more of their existing supplies move into self custody. Though not a perfect indicator, declining coins on exchanges generally hint at future bull runs, given enough time playing out. Notably, one key reason behind the declining supply of BTC and ETH on exchanges, particularly in the case of Ethereum, is the increasing popularity of staking. Ethereum 2.0&#8217;s transition to a proof-of-stake (PoS) consensus mechanism has provided ETH holders with the opportunity to stake their coins and participate in securing the network while earning rewards. Stakers lock up their ETH in specialized wallets, ensuring its active involvement in the network&#8217;s operations rather than leaving it idle on exchanges. This shift towards staking is motivated by the desire to earn passive income and contribute to the long-term growth and security of the Ethereum ecosystem. On the other hand, the Bitcoin decrease on exchanges is not so clear, however, the possible reason can be attributed to investors looking to keep their BTC holdings for a long time. This could be due to the feared upcoming global recession which has made many turn to the idea of saving funds for the supposed &#8220;rainy days.&#8221; Implications On The Crypto Market The dwindling supply of Bitcoin and Ethereum on exchanges could have significant implications for the broader cryptocurrency market mostly positively. Firstly, it suggests a decreasing selling pressure as fewer coins are readily available for trading. This &#8220;hints at future bull runs,&#8221; according to Santiment. With a limited supply on exchanges, potential buyers might face greater difficulty acquiring these digital assets, leading to increased demand and potentially driving up the prices of both Bitcoin and Ethereum. Additionally, the reduced presence of BTC and ETH on exchanges may indicate a growing confidence among long-term holders. Investors are likely becoming more inclined to hold their coins in secure wallets or participate in staking, signaling a belief in the future potential and value appreciation of these cryptocurrencies. Related Reading: Whale Alert: 1,750 Bitcoin (BTC) Moved To Exchange, Massive Plunge Incoming? This shift in behavior reflects a maturing market where participants are increasingly focused on the underlying technology and long-term prospects rather than short-term trading. Regardless, both BTC and ETH haven&#8217;t made any significant movement in the past week. BTC&#8217;s price has experienced little upward trend up by 0.3%. BTC has surged from a low of $26,819 seen last Saturday to trading as high as above $27,000 on Thursday. In contrast, ETH&#8217;s price has experienced a slight upward trend up by 0.6% in the past week. ETH has surged from a low of $1,795 last Saturday to trading above $1,800, at the time of writing. -Featured image from Shutterstock, Chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Amid the tussle between the bulls and bears in the crypto market over the past week, the circulating supply of both Bitcoin (BTC) and Ethereum (ETH) has reached record lows, triggering speculation about the potential impact on the cryptocurrency market.</p>
<p><a href="https://twitter.com/santimentfeed/status/1659830319724519425?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Data</a> provided by Santiment reveals a significant decrease in the amount of BTC and ETH held on exchanges, suggesting a shift in investor behavior.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin And Ethereum Supply Plummets On Exchanges</h2>
<p>According to Santiment&#8217;s data, the circulating supply of <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/whale-alert-1750-bitcoin-btc-moved-to-exchange-massive-plunge-incoming/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">BTC on exchanges</a> currently stands at a mere 5.7%, marking its lowest level since December 2017 when the cryptocurrency surged to an all-time high of $20,000. </p>

<p>Similarly, the supply of ETH on exchanges has dropped to 10.1%, the lowest since its inception in 2015. This trend indicates that crypto investors are actively buying and withdrawing their coins from exchanges, opting for alternative storage methods.</p>
<p>Santiment tweeted earlier today:</p>
<blockquote><p>Bitcoin &amp; Ethereum both continue to quietly see more and more of their existing supplies move into self custody. Though not a perfect indicator, declining coins on exchanges generally hint at future bull runs, given enough time playing out.</p></blockquote>
<p>Notably, one key reason behind the declining supply of BTC and ETH on exchanges, particularly in the case of Ethereum, is the increasing popularity of staking. Ethereum 2.0&#8217;s transition to a proof-of-stake (PoS) consensus mechanism has provided ETH holders with the opportunity to <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/ethereum-whale-resurfaces-after-2-years/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">stake their coins</a> and participate in securing the network while earning rewards. </p>
<p>Stakers lock up their ETH in specialized wallets, ensuring its active involvement in the network&#8217;s operations rather than leaving it idle on exchanges. This shift towards staking is motivated by the desire to earn passive income and contribute to the long-term growth and security of the Ethereum ecosystem.</p>
<p>On the other hand, the Bitcoin decrease on exchanges is not so clear, however, the possible reason can be attributed to investors looking to keep their BTC holdings for a long time. This could be due to the feared upcoming global recession which has made many turn to the idea of saving funds for the supposed &#8220;rainy days.&#8221;</p>
<h2>Implications On The Crypto Market</h2>
<p>The dwindling supply of Bitcoin and Ethereum on exchanges could have significant implications for the broader cryptocurrency market mostly positively. Firstly, it suggests a decreasing selling pressure as fewer coins are readily available for trading. This &#8220;hints at future bull runs,&#8221; according to Santiment.</p>
<p>With a limited supply on exchanges, <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-shrimp-accumulation-surge/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">potential buyers</a> might face greater difficulty acquiring these digital assets, leading to increased demand and potentially driving up the prices of both Bitcoin and Ethereum.</p>
<p>Additionally, the reduced presence of BTC and ETH on exchanges may indicate a growing confidence among long-term holders. Investors are likely becoming more inclined to hold their coins in secure wallets or participate in staking, signaling a belief in the future potential and value appreciation of these cryptocurrencies.</p>

<p>This shift in behavior reflects a maturing market where participants are increasingly focused on the underlying technology and long-term prospects rather than short-term trading.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/gNKuk3rC/" alt="Bitcoin (BTC)’s price chart on TradingView" width="2768" height="1556"/>
<p>Regardless, both BTC and ETH haven&#8217;t made any significant movement in the past week. BTC&#8217;s price has experienced little upward trend up by 0.3%. BTC has surged from a low of $26,819 seen last Saturday to trading as high as above $27,000 on Thursday.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/CwItfiWj/" alt="Ethereum (ETH)’s price chart on TradingView" width="2768" height="1556"/>
<p>In contrast, <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-bearish-1825/?swcfpc=1">ETH&#8217;</a>s price has experienced a slight upward trend up by 0.6% in the past week. ETH has surged from a low of $1,795 last Saturday to trading above $1,800, at the time of writing.</p>
<p><em>-Featured image from Shutterstock, Chart from TradingView</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Bitcoin-1-460x333.jpg" width="460" height="333" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cardano Surpasses 500 Million ADA In TVL &#8211; How About Its Impact On Price?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/cardano/cardano-surpasses-500-million-ada-in-tvl-no-significant-impact-on-price/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Opeyemi Sule]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 12:40:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[ADA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=534160</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The total value locked (TVL) on the Cardano blockchain has hit a significant milestone after crossing 500 million ADA. This would come just a month and a few days after TapTools predicted an exponential increase in the network’s TVL. In this prediction, TapTools, a Cardano portfolio tracker, also reported different factors that could be pivotal to Cardano’s explosive growth in the coming months. Related Reading: Bitcoin ‘Shrimp’ Catch Soars To All-Time High Of 1.31 Million Coins – Details Cardano DeFi Ecosystem Hits 500 Million ADA In TVL Data from DeFi TVL aggregator DefiLlama reveals that the total value locked on the Cardano network now stands at 505.114 million ADA. This is equivalent to $186.18 million when converted to U.S. dollars. Source: DefiLlama This new milestone represents a staggering 91.9% increase in total value locked since the turn of the year. Meanwhile, in the last month, Cardano’s TVL has jumped by nearly 8%, indicating a steady adoption of its DeFi ecosystem. On-chain data shows that Minswap is, by a distance, the leading protocol on the network, with a TVL of $55.56 million. In fact, the decentralized exchange boasts a market share dominance of 29.84%. Minswap protocol is followed by Indigo, a collateralized debt protocol, with a total value of $28.5 million locked on it. WingRiders, Liqwid, and Djed Stablecoin are three other notable protocols on the Cardano DeFi ecosystem, with TVLs of $17.51 million, $15.42 million, and $13.71 million, respectively. It is important to note that total value locked is a metric that estimates the amount of cryptocurrency locked in DeFi protocols on a particular blockchain. It is calculated by summing up the value of all the crypto assets locked in various DeFi protocols on a blockchain. TVL can be represented in the native token of a blockchain (as in ADA for Cardano) or in USD. ADA Price Shows No Significant Action A skyrocketing total value locked is often an indicator of increased activity in a DeFi ecosystem. However, Cardano’s impressive TVL growth hasn&#8217;t particularly impacted the price of ADA, the blockchain’s native token. As of this writing, one ADA token trades at $0.3655, losing 1% of its value in the last 24 hours. The price of ADA has been moving sideways recently, dipping by only 0.5% in the last seven days. ADAUSD trading at $$0.3652 &#124; Source: ADAUSD chart from TradingView That said, a broader look at the market reveals that ADA has been on a steady decline, losing more than 13% of its value in the past month. The cryptocurrency boasts a daily trading volume of approximately $129.3 million.  According to data from CoinGecko, ADA ranks as the seventh-largest cryptocurrency, with a total market cap of $12.79 billion. Related Reading: Lido’s ETH Deposits Reach Record High Amid Stagnant stETH Withdrawals -Featured image from Solodev, chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The total value locked (TVL) on the Cardano blockchain has hit a significant milestone after crossing 500 million ADA. This would come just a month and a few days after <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/ada/cardanos-tvl-set-for-exponential-growth/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">TapTools predicted an exponential increase</a> in the network’s TVL.</p>
<p>In this prediction, TapTools, a Cardano portfolio tracker, also reported different factors that could be pivotal to Cardano’s explosive growth in the coming months.</p>

<h2>Cardano DeFi Ecosystem Hits 500 Million ADA In TVL</h2>
<p>Data from DeFi TVL aggregator<a href="https://defillama.com/chain/Cardano" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow"> DefiLlama</a> reveals that the total value locked on the Cardano network now stands at 505.114 million ADA. This is equivalent to $186.18 million when converted to U.S. dollars.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium wp-image-534173 aligncenter" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/photo_2023-05-20_11-29-09-460x227.jpg" alt="Cardano" width="460" height="227" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/photo_2023-05-20_11-29-09-460x227.jpg 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/photo_2023-05-20_11-29-09-860x424.jpg 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/photo_2023-05-20_11-29-09-768x378.jpg 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/photo_2023-05-20_11-29-09-750x370.jpg 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/photo_2023-05-20_11-29-09.jpg 1116w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px"/></p>
<p style="text-align: center">Source: DefiLlama</p>
<p>This new milestone represents a staggering 91.9% increase in total value locked since the turn of the year. Meanwhile, in the last month, Cardano’s TVL has jumped by nearly 8%, indicating a steady adoption of its DeFi ecosystem.</p>
<p>On-chain data shows that Minswap is, by a distance, the leading protocol on the network, with a TVL of $55.56 million. In fact, the decentralized exchange boasts a market share dominance of 29.84%.</p>
<p>Minswap protocol is followed by Indigo, a collateralized debt protocol, with a total value of $28.5 million locked on it. WingRiders, Liqwid, and Djed Stablecoin are three other notable protocols on the Cardano DeFi ecosystem, with TVLs of $17.51 million, $15.42 million, and $13.71 million, respectively.</p>
<p>It is important to note that total value locked is a metric that estimates the amount of cryptocurrency locked in DeFi protocols on a particular blockchain. It is calculated by summing up the value of all the crypto assets locked in various DeFi protocols on a blockchain. TVL can be represented in the native token of a blockchain (as in ADA for Cardano) or in USD.</p>
<h2>ADA Price Shows No Significant Action</h2>
<p>A skyrocketing total value locked is often an indicator of increased activity in a DeFi ecosystem. However, Cardano’s impressive TVL growth hasn&#8217;t particularly impacted the price of ADA, the blockchain’s native token.</p>
<p>As of this writing, one ADA token trades at $0.3655, losing 1% of its value in the last 24 hours. The price of ADA has been moving sideways recently, dipping by only 0.5% in the last seven days.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/K12HyuhT/" alt="Cardano" width="1008" height="591"/></p>

<p>That said, a broader look at the market reveals that ADA has been on a steady decline, losing more than 13% of its value in the past month. The cryptocurrency boasts a daily trading volume of approximately $129.3 million. </p>
<p>According to <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/cardano" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">data from CoinGecko</a>, ADA ranks as the seventh-largest cryptocurrency, with a total market cap of $12.79 billion.</p>




]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Cardano-1536x997-1-460x299.jpg" width="460" height="299" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Injective (INJ) Surges By 19% Following &#8216;Surprise&#8217; NFT Announcement</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/altcoin/injective-inj-surges-by-19-following-surprise-nft-initiative/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Semilore Faleti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 11:58:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[INJ]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Injective]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Santiment]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=534157</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Injective (INJ) is one of the few tokens to have racked up impressive gains in the last week. While most of the assets in the crypto market were marked by insignificant price actions leading to little gains or losses, INJ stood out with an excellent price movement to become one of the biggest weekly gainers.  According to data from CoinMarketCap, Injective’s price gained by 19% in the last seven days boasting of a market performance only beaten by four other tokens &#8211; RNDR, AGIX, MASK, and CFX &#8211; in the entire top 100 crypto ranking.  INJ initially began the week trading around a price region of $6.08 and soon recorded consecutive gains and losses before experiencing a price hike on May 17 to hit a market price of $6.7 Following this price boost, INJ showed signs of consolidation for the next two days before starting its current bullish run. Related Reading: Shiba Inu Falls Below Critical Support, Is It Time For You To Buy? NFT Surprise Announcement Boosts INJ Price  Interestingly, the price rally by INJ in the last week appears to be due to an exciting announcement made by the project developers six days ago. On May 13, the team behind the Injective blockchain tweeted a statement urging the user community to interact more with dApps built on Injective or its L1 chain, stating there could be a chance to receive an “NFT-related surprise.” This announcement sparked much excitement within the Injective community, which has been represented not just in price but also in the network activity.  According to a tweet by @Iryna_Everstake, blockchain manager at network validator service Everstake pool, the Injective blockchain recorded a substantial increase in several network parameters over the last week as follows &#8211; +688K INJ staked, +470 delegators, +130 new wallets, and +295M in cumulative trading volume.  At the time of writing, INJ is trading around $7.0, having gone up 4.73% in the last day. However, it is worth noting that INJ is down by 13.8% from its value as of a month ago. That said, with a circulating supply of 80 million tokens, INJ has a stunning market cap value of $563.7 million. INJ Trading At $7.098 &#124; Source: INJUSD chart on Tradingview.com Related Reading: NFT Market Takes A Hit: Sales Could Drop Below $1 Billion For The First Time In 2023 Altcoins End The Week With Massive Whale Movement Asides from INJ&#8217;s impressive performance this week, another talking point for most investors was the unexpected big altcoin transactions that capped off the work week. According to the on-chain analytics platform Santiment, some mid and low-market cap assets recorded whale activity to the tune of eight-figure transactions. Source: Santiment Of these many assets, MTL, POWR, AERGO, and DIAA recorded the biggest transactions, which were $37.89M, $30.74M, $30.23M, and $18.92M, respectively.  That said, Santiment stated that when small assets such as these record such high transactions, they could be up to something and thus are worth investors’ attention. -Featured Image: injective.com, chart from Tradingview.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Injective (INJ) is one of the few tokens to have racked up impressive gains in the last week. While most of the assets in the crypto market were marked by insignificant price actions leading to little gains or losses, INJ stood out with an excellent price movement to become one of the biggest weekly gainers. </p>
<p>According to <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/injective/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">data from CoinMarketCap</a>, Injective’s price gained by 19% in the last seven days boasting of a market performance only beaten by four other tokens &#8211; RNDR, AGIX, MASK, and CFX &#8211; in the entire top 100 crypto ranking. </p>
<p>INJ initially began the week trading around a price region of $6.08 and soon recorded consecutive gains and losses before experiencing a price hike on May 17 to hit a market price of $6.7</p>
<p>Following this price boost, INJ showed signs of consolidation for the next two days before starting its current bullish run.</p>


<h2><strong>NFT Surprise Announcement Boosts INJ Price </strong></h2>

<p>Interestingly, the price rally by INJ in the last week appears to be due to an exciting announcement made by the project developers six days ago.</p>
<p>On May 13, the team behind the Injective blockchain<a href="https://twitter.com/injective_/status/1657394070996615170?s=46&amp;t=JAUmthpFclo8jS4VJkm3DQ" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow"> tweeted</a> a statement urging the user community to interact more with dApps built on Injective or its L1 chain, stating there could be a chance to receive an “NFT-related surprise.”</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">It might be a good idea to interact with dApps built on Injective or the L1 chain itself.</p>
<p>Make a transfer, trade on a dex built on Injective, bridge assets, stake INJ, etc.</p>
<p>Who knows there might be an NFT related surprise in the works <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f609.png" alt="😉" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /></p>
<p>&mdash; Injective <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f977.png" alt="🥷" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> (@Injective_) <a href="https://twitter.com/Injective_/status/1657394070996615170?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">May 13, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p></p>
<p>This announcement sparked much excitement within the Injective community, which has been represented not just in price but also in the network activity. </p>
<p>According to a <a href="https://twitter.com/iryna_everstake/status/1659466585793331202?s=46&amp;t=JAUmthpFclo8jS4VJkm3DQ" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">tweet</a> by @Iryna_Everstake, blockchain manager at network validator service Everstake pool, the Injective blockchain recorded a substantial increase in several network parameters over the last week as follows &#8211; +688K INJ staked, +470 delegators, +130 new wallets, and +295M in cumulative trading volume. </p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">The Injective community seems to be following the advice to interact w/ dApps or the chain itself to get ready for an upcoming NFT-related surprise<a href="https://twitter.com/Injective_?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">@Injective_</a> stats over the last 5 days: +688K <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24INJ&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$INJ</a> staked, +470 delegators, +130 new wallets, +295M in cumulative trading volume <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f977.png" alt="🥷" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> <a href="https://t.co/N9z9aWw5aQ" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/N9z9aWw5aQ</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Iryna | Everstake <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f977.png" alt="🥷" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> (@iryna_everstake) <a href="https://twitter.com/iryna_everstake/status/1659466585793331202?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">May 19, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p></p>
<p>At the time of writing, INJ is trading around $7.0, having gone up 4.73% in the last day. However, it is worth noting that INJ is down by 13.8% from its value as of a month ago. That said, with a circulating supply of 80 million tokens, INJ has a stunning market cap value of $563.7 million.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/Wmr9Kl4L/" alt="Injective" width="1479" height="913"/></p>




<h2><strong>Altcoins End The Week With Massive Whale Movement</strong></h2>
<p>Asides from INJ&#8217;s impressive performance this week, another talking point for most investors was the unexpected big altcoin transactions that capped off the work week. According to the on-chain analytics platform <a href="https://twitter.com/santimentfeed/status/1659746600888188928?s=46&amp;t=JAUmthpFclo8jS4VJkm3DQ" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Santiment</a>, some mid and low-market cap assets recorded whale activity to the tune of eight-figure transactions.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-large wp-image-534161" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/FwiZsWjagAEKLU1-860x390.jpeg" alt="Injective" width="860" height="390" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/FwiZsWjagAEKLU1-860x390.jpeg 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/FwiZsWjagAEKLU1-460x209.jpeg 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/FwiZsWjagAEKLU1-768x348.jpeg 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/FwiZsWjagAEKLU1-1536x696.jpeg 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/FwiZsWjagAEKLU1-2048x929.jpeg 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/FwiZsWjagAEKLU1-750x340.jpeg 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/FwiZsWjagAEKLU1-1140x517.jpeg 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/></p>

<p>Of these many assets, MTL, POWR, AERGO, and DIAA recorded the biggest transactions, which were $37.89M, $30.74M, $30.23M, and $18.92M, respectively.  That said, Santiment stated that when small assets such as these record such high transactions, they could be up to something and thus are worth investors’ attention.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/og-new-460x242.jpeg" width="460" height="242" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>XRP Emerges As Top Performing Crypto With 55% Surge &#8211; Messari Report</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/xrp-emerges-as-top-performing-crypto-with-55-surge-messari-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Eli Dambel]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 11:50:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[messari]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrpusdt]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=534177</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Amid the prevailing bearish trend in the crypto market, XRP has stayed afloat above other assets with impressive gains. A report from a leading crypto market intelligence product provider, Messari, revealed the Ripple native currency XRP took the lead in the overall crypto market in Q1. XRP Takes The Lead In Overall Crypto Market According to data from Messari, XRP outperformed other crypto assets with a 55% surge on a quarter-on-quarter (QoQ) basis.  From the report, the market cap of XRP grew by a whopping 59.9% in the first quarter of the year. The value increased from $17.4 billion on January 1 to $27.4 billion on March 31. Related Reading: Crypto Assets Flow From Ethereum To BSC, Are Users Escaping High Gas Fees? Notably, the growth rate for XRP’s market cap exceeded the cumulative crypto market cap that witnessed a 46% surge within the same period.  Messari&#8217;s report also showed that XRP kicked off the year with a trading price of $0.35 as of January 1. With the increasing volatility in the crypto market during the beginning of 2023, XRP rallied progressively through the days. As of January 23, XRP&#8217;s price hit $0.43 before retracting due to the influence of the bears. The token closed in January with a 19.71% increase in value. The second month wasn’t quite eventful for XRP as the price gradually dipped to $0.36 amid the downtrend in the overall crypto market. However, XRP ended February with a 7.27% drop as the price hit $0.37. Then XRP’s price rally took a more aggressive look in March. The price of XRP ranged from the beginning of March. But it gained momentum from March 21 as XRP broke the resistance level at $0.400. XRP sustained its volatility and pushed higher with a more bullish stance through the remaining days in March. The token rallied beyond the $0.500 region and progressed higher. Messari noted that XRP hit a 10-month high of $0.5850 on March 29, following a two-week price surge of 56%. This price rally was peculiar to XRP, although most crypto assets posted a decline during the period.  Finally, XRP closed with a price of $0.54 on March 31, a 43% price surge for the month. The feat pushed the token to an overall price gain of 55% in Q1 2023. XRP Performance Analysis In Q1 2023 Besides the XRP’s price performance, the Messari report also highlighted other performance indicators for the token. The data shows an increase in XRP&#8217;s overall network activity metrics in Q1. The total active addresses and average daily transactions surged by 13.9% and 10.7%, respectively, on a QoQ basis. Related Reading: Ethereum Price Faces Confluence Of Bearish Factors and At Risk of Another Decline The total active addresses grew from the receiving addresses, which increased from 47,000 to 55,000 through a 17.1% surge. But XRP sending addresses dropped by 7.2%. -Featured image from Pixabay and chart from Tradingview.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Amid the prevailing bearish trend in the crypto market, XRP has stayed afloat above other assets with impressive gains. A report from a leading crypto market intelligence product provider, Messari, revealed the Ripple native currency XRP took the lead in the overall crypto market in Q1.</p>
<h2>XRP Takes The Lead In Overall Crypto Market</h2>
<p>According to <a href="https://messari.io/report/state-of-xrp-ledger-q1-2023" rel="nofollow">data from Messari</a>, XRP outperformed other crypto assets with a 55% surge on a quarter-on-quarter (QoQ) basis. </p>
<p>From the report, the market cap of XRP grew by a whopping 59.9% in the first quarter of the year. The value increased from $17.4 billion on January 1 to $27.4 billion on March 31.</p>

<p>Notably, the growth rate for XRP’s market cap exceeded the cumulative crypto market cap that witnessed a 46% surge within the same period. </p>
<p>Messari&#8217;s report also showed that XRP kicked off the year with a trading price of $0.35 as of January 1. With the increasing volatility in the crypto market during the beginning of 2023, XRP rallied progressively through the days. As of January 23, XRP&#8217;s price hit $0.43 before retracting due to the influence of the bears. The token closed in January with a 19.71% increase in value.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-534180 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSDT_2023-05-20_15-55-24-860x471.png" alt="XRP Emerges Top Performing Crypto With A 55% Surge QoQ, Messari Report" width="860" height="471" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSDT_2023-05-20_15-55-24-860x471.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSDT_2023-05-20_15-55-24-460x252.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSDT_2023-05-20_15-55-24-768x420.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSDT_2023-05-20_15-55-24-750x411.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSDT_2023-05-20_15-55-24-1140x624.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSDT_2023-05-20_15-55-24.png 1529w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/>
<p>The second month wasn’t quite eventful for XRP as the price gradually dipped to $0.36 amid the downtrend in the overall crypto market. However, XRP ended February with a 7.27% drop as the price hit $0.37.</p>
<p>Then XRP’s price rally took a more aggressive look in March. The price of XRP ranged from the beginning of March. But it gained momentum from March 21 as XRP broke the resistance level at $0.400.</p>
<p>XRP sustained its volatility and pushed higher with a more bullish stance through the remaining days in March. The token rallied beyond the $0.500 region and progressed higher.</p>
<p>Messari noted that XRP hit a 10-month high of $0.5850 on March 29, following a two-week price surge of 56%. This price rally was peculiar to XRP, although most crypto assets posted a decline during the period. </p>
<p>Finally, XRP closed with a price of $0.54 on March 31, a 43% price surge for the month. The feat pushed the token to an overall price gain of 55% in Q1 2023.</p>
<h2>XRP Performance Analysis In Q1 2023</h2>
<p>Besides the XRP’s price performance, the Messari report also highlighted other performance indicators for the token.</p>
<p>The data shows an increase in XRP&#8217;s overall network activity metrics in Q1. The total active addresses and average daily transactions surged by 13.9% and 10.7%, respectively, on a QoQ basis.</p>

<p>The total active addresses grew from the receiving addresses, which increased from 47,000 to 55,000 through a 17.1% surge. But XRP sending addresses dropped by 7.2%.</p>
<p><em>-Featured image from Pixabay and chart from Tradingview.com</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/coin-g7ab8cd001_1280-460x305.jpg" width="460" height="305" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Chainlink (LINK) Price Down Today As Bears Take Control &#8211; Here&#8217;s Why</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/link/chainlink-price-down-today/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Eli Dambel]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 11:14:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[LINK]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AI]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bears]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[chainlink]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[linkusdt]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=534147</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Chainlink has dropped slightly in the market today as bears seized control of its price. LINK’s current price depicts a loss of 87.7% from its all-time high of $52.88 on May 10, 2021. Related Reading: Decentraland (MANA) Leads Crypto Market Gains, Here’s Why The asset has been fluctuating between the $6 and $7 price levels since the beginning of May and is currently at the $6 price level. LINK is also recording a sideways trend on the daily chart, and its trading volume has also tanked by over 32%.  The recent price action is primarily influenced by macroeconomic factors such as inflation, regulatory laws and investor sentiment. LINK Price Analysis LINK is in a sideways trend today, forming a red candle on the daily chart. It is trading below its 50-day and 200-Simple Moving Averages (SMA), a short and long-term bearish sentiment. Also, its Relative Strength Index (RSI) is at 41.30 and dropping out of the neutral zone to the oversold region of 30, confirming the bearish trend. LINK&#8217;s Moving Average Convergence/Divergence (MACD) is just above its signal line and shows convergence, a bearish signal. Also, the MACD indicator displays a negative value. LINK is just above its nearest support level of $6.362, which has proved critical after the 6.177 price level provided initial support. However, its signals on the daily chart look bearish, hinting at a further price drop for the asset. However, if the bulls mount a rally, LINK will encounter resistance at the $6.753 and the $6.907 price levels. LINK enjoyed a positive price movement in 2023. However, the bears are currently controlling the market. It will likely drop into an oversold region before the bulls rally again. Recent Trends On LINK&#8217;s Network Likely To Affect Its Price Chainlink NFTFi NFTFi is a new concept combining NFTs and decentralized finance (DeFi) solutions. It aims at adding value and liquidity to the growing NFT market. Chainlink adopted this technological upgrade enabling lending and borrowing. NFT holders now lock digital assets as collateral to acquire liquidity for another digital asset. Related Reading: Bitcoin Reclaims $27,000, Here Are The Factors Driving The Recovery Such individuals become qualified to borrow digital assets by paying interest to lenders. This innovation shows why Chainlink has performed well in 2023 and is set for a further price boost if more investors adopt its tokens and upgrades.  Chainlink Upcoming Spring Hackathon 2023 The Chainlink Hackathon event will begin on April 28 and run until June 9, 2023. It is an initiative from the developers to interact and network with the growing Chainlink community.  It features several categories, such as Artificial Intelligence (AI), NFT and gaming, and DAO, and a grand prize of $25,000. Hackathons create great networking opportunities and exchange of ideas among the crypto community.  Also, it brings developers and coders together to interact and generate ideas, thereby boosting a network’s visibility, utility, and adoption. -Featured image from Pixabay and chart from Tradingview.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Chainlink has dropped slightly in the market today as bears seized control of its price. LINK’s current price depicts a loss of 87.7% from its all-time high of $52.88 on May 10, 2021.</p>

<p>The asset has been fluctuating between the $6 and $7 price levels since the beginning of May and is currently at the $6 price level. LINK is also recording a sideways trend on the daily chart, and its trading volume has also tanked by over 32%. </p>
<p>The recent price action is primarily influenced by macroeconomic factors such as inflation, regulatory laws and investor sentiment.</p>
<h2><strong>LINK Price Analysis</strong></h2>
<p>LINK is in a sideways trend today, forming a red candle on the daily chart. It is trading below its 50-day and 200-Simple Moving Averages (SMA), a short and long-term bearish sentiment.</p>
<p>Also, its Relative Strength Index (RSI) is at 41.30 and dropping out of the neutral zone to the oversold region of 30, confirming the bearish trend.</p>
<p>LINK&#8217;s Moving Average Convergence/Divergence (MACD) is just above its signal line and shows convergence, a bearish signal. Also, the MACD indicator displays a negative value.</p>
<p>LINK is just above its nearest support level of $6.362, which has proved critical after the 6.177 price level provided initial support. However, its signals on the daily chart look bearish, hinting at a further price drop for the asset. However, if the bulls mount a rally, LINK will encounter resistance at the $6.753 and the $6.907 price levels.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-534174 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/LINKUSDT_2023-05-20_15-31-50-860x470.png" alt="Chainlink Plummets as Bears Take Control: Here&#039;s Why The Price Is Down Today" width="860" height="470" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/LINKUSDT_2023-05-20_15-31-50-860x470.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/LINKUSDT_2023-05-20_15-31-50-460x252.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/LINKUSDT_2023-05-20_15-31-50-768x420.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/LINKUSDT_2023-05-20_15-31-50-750x410.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/LINKUSDT_2023-05-20_15-31-50-1140x624.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/LINKUSDT_2023-05-20_15-31-50.png 1530w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/>
<p>LINK enjoyed a positive price movement in 2023. However, the bears are currently controlling the market. It will likely drop into an oversold region before the bulls rally again.</p>
<h2><strong>Recent Trends On LINK&#8217;s Network Likely To Affect Its Price</strong></h2>
Chainlink NFTFi
<p><a href="https://blog.chain.link/nftfi/" rel="nofollow">NFTFi</a> is a new concept combining NFTs and decentralized finance (DeFi) solutions. It aims at adding value and liquidity to the growing NFT market.</p>
<p>Chainlink adopted this technological upgrade enabling lending and borrowing. <a href="https://docs.chain.link/data-feeds/nft-floor-price/" rel="nofollow">NFT holders</a> now lock digital assets as collateral to acquire liquidity for another digital asset.</p>

<p>Such individuals become qualified to borrow digital assets by paying interest to lenders. This innovation shows why Chainlink has performed well in 2023 and is set for a further price boost if more investors adopt its tokens and upgrades. </p>
Chainlink Upcoming Spring Hackathon 2023
<p>The <a href="https://chain.link/hackathon?utm_medium=social&amp;utm_source=twitter&amp;utm_campaign=spring-2023-hackathon&amp;agid=sttqzbunpgke" rel="nofollow">Chainlink Hackathon event</a> will begin on April 28 and run until June 9, 2023. It is an initiative from the developers to interact and network with the growing Chainlink community. </p>
<p>It features several categories, such as Artificial Intelligence (AI), NFT and gaming, and DAO, and a grand prize of $25,000. Hackathons create great networking opportunities and exchange of ideas among the crypto community. </p>
<p>Also, it brings developers and coders together to interact and generate ideas, thereby boosting a network’s visibility, utility, and adoption.</p>
<p><em>-Featured image from Pixabay and chart from Tradingview.com</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/36916c121ba1402fbc496bf825c3052b-1-460x259.png" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Can BRC-20 Tokens Become The Face of the Next Bull Run?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/can-brc-20-tokens-become-the-face-of-the-next-bull-run/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[NewsBTC]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 10:01:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=534232</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[In May 2021, a Shiba Inu-inspired coin had retail investors flocking to cryptocurrency. Dogecoin was an unlikely marker of one of the all-time bull run highs. But it goes to show that when you find the right meme, you can chorale a community to show up in force. The rise of Dogecoin felt like cryptocurrency had finally reached its tipping point. Then, the likes of Terra and FTX destroyed consumer confidence, and we all know what happened next. Now we need something to draw us out of crypto winter. Just like Dogecoin did two years ago — and almost to the day — a new BRC-20 token could mark the start of more bullish times for cryptocurrencies. Let’s delve into BRC-20 tokens to discover what they really are. Revealing the captivating rise of a token that could well become Doge&#8217;s arch nemesis, and the bellwether of Bitcoin summer. The Rise of BRC-20 Tokens BRC-20 tokens have emerged as a novel &#8220;token standard&#8221; on the Bitcoin network. BRC-20 tokens make it possible to mint individual satoshis with information about an entire collection of tokens, meaning you can spin up a Dogecoin-like crypto on Bitcoin. They first captured the attention of the diehard crypto community in March 2023, and the market capitalization of all BRC-20 tokens is now close to $1 billion. That said, no individual token had broken out beyond the core community. At least, that was the case — until just a couple of days ago. The ‘Bitcoin Cat’ Taking On Ethereum Trust is lacking in the cryptocurrency space right now, so a bull run looks anything but imminent. But if we can find a point of trust to bring the everyday investors back to the blockchain, then who knows. Perhaps Bitcoin meme coins are the way. After all, Bitcoin is the most trusted cryptocurrency, the OG. And the rise of the BRC-20 token standard shows the trend might just kick start ‘Bitcoin summer.’  All we need is the right meme, and it looks like we might have just stumbled across a contender: a newly-minted BRC-20 token with the face of a recognisably agitated cat deployed onto Bitcoin just two days ago.  The token, aptly called $GRUM, saw over 50% of its 21 billion supply minted within the first few hours before soon selling out. This made it the only BRC-20 token in the top-25 by holder count to have minted such a high portion of its supply to such a broad investor base so quickly. The token’s initial success reflected its ‘fair launch process,’ wherein anyone could mint up to one million $GRUM. The absence of allocations ensured a level playing field for all, instilling further trust from the community.  But perhaps there’s something more prescient there.  Can $GRUM bring back the bulls? The convergence of BRC-20 tokens and the meme coin revolution on Bitcoin has opened up exciting new possibilities in the crypto space. $GRUM, with its swift ascent and rapidly expanding community, showcases its potential to become a new favorite. The move would help more retail investors understand and perhaps join the BRC-20 meme coin wave, which could force the dogs and frogs of Ethereum to take a back seat. This Bitcoin token seems to have the memetic power to draw huge attention. Note: The above article is for illustrative purposes only and does not constitute financial advice.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p style="font-weight: 400">In May 2021, a Shiba Inu-inspired coin had retail investors flocking to cryptocurrency. Dogecoin was an unlikely marker of one of the all-time bull run highs. But it goes to show that when you find the right meme, you can chorale a community to show up in force.</p>
<p>The rise of Dogecoin felt like cryptocurrency had finally reached its tipping point. Then, the likes of Terra and FTX destroyed consumer confidence, and we all know what happened next. Now we need something to draw us out of crypto winter.</p>
<p style="font-weight: 400">Just like <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/dogecoin/dogecoin-shiba-inu-whales-move-massive-dumping/">Dogecoin</a> did two years ago — and almost to the day — a new BRC-20 token could mark the start of more bullish times for cryptocurrencies. Let’s delve into BRC-20 tokens to discover what they really are.</p>
<p style="font-weight: 400">Revealing the captivating rise of a token that could well become Doge&#8217;s arch nemesis, and the bellwether of Bitcoin summer.</p>
<h2>The Rise of BRC-20 Tokens</h2>
<p>BRC-20 tokens have emerged as a novel &#8220;token standard&#8221; on the Bitcoin network. BRC-20 tokens make it possible to mint individual satoshis with information about an entire collection of tokens, meaning you can spin up a Dogecoin-like crypto on Bitcoin.</p>
<p style="font-weight: 400">They first captured the attention of the diehard crypto community in March 2023, and the market capitalization of all BRC-20 tokens is now close to $1 billion. That said, no individual token had broken out beyond the core community.</p>
<p style="font-weight: 400">At least, that was the case — until just a couple of days ago.</p>
<h2>The ‘Bitcoin Cat’ Taking On Ethereum</h2>
<p>Trust is lacking in the cryptocurrency space right now, so a bull run looks anything but imminent. But if we can find a point of trust to bring the everyday investors back to the blockchain, then who knows.</p>
<p style="font-weight: 400">Perhaps Bitcoin meme coins are the way. After all, Bitcoin is the most trusted cryptocurrency, the OG. And the rise of the BRC-20 token standard shows the trend might just kick start ‘Bitcoin summer.’ </p>
<p style="font-weight: 400">All we need is the right meme, and it looks like we might have just stumbled across a contender: a <a href="https://unisat.io/brc20/GRUM" rel="nofollow">newly-minted BRC-20 token</a> with the face of a <a href="https://twitter.com/GrumpyBRC" rel="nofollow">recognisably agitated cat</a> deployed onto Bitcoin just two days ago. </p>
<p>The token, aptly called $GRUM, saw over 50% of its 21 billion supply minted within the first few hours before soon selling out. This made it the only <a href="https://unisat.io/brc20" rel="nofollow">BRC-20 token in the top-25 by holder count</a> to have minted such a high portion of its supply to such a broad investor base so quickly.</p>
<p style="font-weight: 400">The token’s initial success reflected its ‘fair launch process,’ wherein anyone could mint up to one million $GRUM. The absence of allocations ensured a level playing field for all, instilling further trust from the community. </p>
<p style="font-weight: 400">But perhaps there’s something more prescient there. </p>
<h2>Can $GRUM bring back the bulls?</h2>
<p style="font-weight: 400">The convergence of BRC-20 tokens and the meme coin revolution on Bitcoin has opened up exciting new possibilities in the crypto space. $GRUM, with its swift ascent and rapidly expanding community, showcases its potential to become a new favorite.</p>
<p style="font-weight: 400">The move would help more retail investors understand and perhaps join the BRC-20 meme coin wave, which could force the dogs and frogs of Ethereum to take a back seat. This Bitcoin token seems to have the memetic power to draw huge attention.</p>
<p style="font-weight: 400"><i>Note: The above article is for illustrative purposes only and does not constitute financial advice.</i></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/iStock-1015828796-460x263.jpg" width="460" height="263" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Shiba Inu Falls Below Critical Support, Is It Time For You To Buy?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/shiba-inu-falls-below-critical-support-is-it-time-for-you-to-buy/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Best Owie]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 23:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Shiba Inu]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIB]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIB price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIBUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIBUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=534028</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Shiba Inu remains one of the most popular meme coins but the performance of the cryptocurrency in the last year has been discouraging for holders. Despite remaining the second-largest meme coin, it has continued to decline in price and this has caused the asset to fall below very crucial support. And now that SHIB is now sitting at the $0.000008 level, is it a good time to buy the meme coin? Shiba Inu Falls Below Critical Level For Shiba Inu, the $0.000009 price level has served as good support for it through the ups and downs of the crypto market over the last year. This made it the most important point for bears to beat if they were to take control of the digital asset. However, over the last week, SHIB has fallen below $0.000009 which could present a good buying opportunity for the digital asset. Related Reading: Decentraland (MANA) Leads Crypto Market Gains, Here’s Why One reason why buying SHIB could be a good play right now is that the developments by the team are yet to reflect in the performance of the coin. Also, with the launch of the four new hubs in Shib: The Metaverse coming soon, the meme coin could see renewed interest and this interest could lead to a price rally. SHIB price falls below $0.000009 support &#124; Source: SHIBUSD on TradingView.com The market has also been consolidating for a while with the likes of Bitcoin and Ethereum trading sideways for the last week. Once this consolidation ends, the likelihood of these large assets rallying upward remains high. And as always, a rally in these top cryptocurrencies would pull the rest of the market up with it. If Bitcoin were to move above $30,000 again, SHIB could go as high as $0.00001 once more, which would mean a more than 10% gain for investors in the short run. Over the long term, the gains could be higher, assuming that the market has not completely exited its bull trend. SHIB Could Be A Breakout Star The Shiba Inu team continues to rapidly develop the ecosystem and the latest in its long line of products is its SHIB-themed cold wallets. These wallets have been in the works for a while and the official SHIB handle confirmed on Twitter that the wallets will be ready for preorder on May 29. The wallets are being developed in partnership with Swiss company Tangem to allow users to hold more than 6,000 coins. #SHIBARMY! @Tangem is about to unleash SHIB-themed cold wallets! 🎉 These card-shaped vaults are set to become your new best friend for safeguarding our ecosystem&#39;s tokens. Get ready to fetch your own when pre-orders kick off on 29th May: https://t.co/6jXEBjOCP5 pic.twitter.com/7kAfLZYHPG &#8212; Shib (@Shibtoken) May 18, 2023 Developments such as these have proven to be good for the meme coin. Additionally, SHIB’s price is sitting at almost 90% of its all-time high price, which, historically, has been a good level to purchase cryptocurrencies at. Related Reading: Bitcoin Reclaims $27,000, Here Are The Factors Driving The Recovery Nevertheless, SHIB still leaves a lot to be desired since its volume has declined to $92 million, indicating a drop in activity in the meme coin. However, it also presents an opportunity for a rapid rise and an uptick in momentum can easily help the cryptocurrency grow around 10% from here. Follow Best Owie on Twitter for market insights, updates, and the occasional funny tweet… Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="p2">Shiba Inu remains one of the most popular meme coins but the performance of the cryptocurrency in the last year has been discouraging for holders. Despite remaining the second-largest meme coin, it has continued to decline in price and this has caused the asset to fall below very crucial support. And now that SHIB is now sitting at the $0.000008 level, is it a good time to buy the meme coin?</p>
<h2 class="p2">Shiba Inu Falls Below Critical Level</h2>
<p class="p2">For Shiba Inu, the $0.000009 price level has served as good support for it through the ups and downs of the crypto market over the last year. This made it the most important point for bears to beat if they were to take control of the digital asset. However, over the last week, SHIB has fallen below $0.000009 which could present a good buying opportunity for the digital asset.</p>

<p class="p2">One reason why buying SHIB could be a good play right now is that the developments by the team are yet to reflect in the performance of the coin. Also, with the launch of the four new hubs in Shib: The Metaverse coming soon, the meme coin could see renewed interest and this interest could lead to a price rally.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/54nRHgaE/" alt="Shiba Inu price chart from TradingView.com" width="2854" height="1610"/></p>

<p class="p2">The market has also been consolidating for a while with the likes of Bitcoin and Ethereum trading sideways for the last week. Once this consolidation ends, the likelihood of these large assets rallying upward remains high. And as always, a rally in these top cryptocurrencies would pull the rest of the market up with it.</p>
<p class="p2">If Bitcoin were to move above $30,000 again, SHIB could go as high as $0.00001 once more, which would mean a more than 10% gain for investors in the short run. Over the long term, the gains could be higher, assuming that the market has not completely exited its bull trend.</p>
<h2 class="p2">SHIB Could Be A Breakout Star</h2>
<p class="p2">The Shiba Inu team continues to rapidly develop the ecosystem and the latest in its long line of products is its SHIB-themed cold wallets. These wallets have been in the works for a while and the official SHIB handle confirmed on Twitter that the wallets will be ready for preorder on May 29. The wallets are being developed in partnership with Swiss company Tangem to allow users to hold more than 6,000 coins.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr"><a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/SHIBARMY?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#SHIBARMY</a>! <a href="https://twitter.com/Tangem?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">@Tangem</a> is about to unleash SHIB-themed cold wallets! <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f389.png" alt="🎉" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> These card-shaped vaults are set to become your new best friend for safeguarding our ecosystem&#39;s tokens. Get ready to fetch your own when pre-orders kick off on 29th May: <a href="https://t.co/6jXEBjOCP5" rel="nofollow">https://t.co/6jXEBjOCP5</a> <a href="https://t.co/7kAfLZYHPG" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/7kAfLZYHPG</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Shib (@Shibtoken) <a href="https://twitter.com/Shibtoken/status/1659250370109898759?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">May 18, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p></p>
<p class="p5">Developments such as these have proven to be good for the meme coin. Additionally, SHIB’s price is sitting at almost 90% of its all-time high price, which, historically, has been a good level to purchase cryptocurrencies at.</p>

<p class="p5">Nevertheless, SHIB still leaves a lot to be desired since its volume has declined to $92 million, indicating a drop in activity in the meme coin. However, it also presents an opportunity for a rapid rise and an uptick in momentum can easily help the cryptocurrency grow around 10% from here.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/iStock-1327123774-1-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Gas Crisis Averted: NFT Marketplaces Witness Dramatic Reduction in Ethereum Fees</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/ethereum/gas-crisis-averted-nft-marketplaces-witness-dramatic-reduction-in-ethereum-fees/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Edyme]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 20:50:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NFT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=534098</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Ethereum gas consumption landscape is transforming significantly as Non-Fungible Token (NFT) marketplaces no longer dominate the network&#8217;s gas usage. According to a report by Nansen, a crypto analytics platform, NFTs have fallen behind in doing the most in Ethereum gas fees.  Notably, while Ethereum&#8217;s transition to proof-of-stake, in an event known as &#8220;The Merge,&#8221; is anticipated to address high gas prices, investors are now exploring alternatives like Cardano, which boasts greater cost-efficiency following its recent Hydra upgrade. Ethereum&#8217;s Gas Consumption Shift According to data revealed by Nansen on Friday, there&#8217;s currently a noteworthy shift in Ethereum&#8217;s gas consumption patterns. NFT marketplaces, which once held the top spot, now account for a mere 3% of total gas usage. Related Reading: Crypto Assets Flow From Ethereum To BSC, Are Users Escaping High Gas Fees? Surprisingly, decentralized exchange (DEX) Uniswap has emerged as the primary gas consumer, representing 31.99% of gas consumption. This shift indicates a diversification in Ethereum&#8217;s transactional activity and a reduction in NFT-related gas usage. Nansen noted: Gone were the days of NFTs topping the Ethereum gas-consuming charts. This week, of the top 20 gas consumers, OpenSea and Blur accounted for less than 10% combined. And against all gas consumers, the NFT marketplaces were just over 3%. Uniswap in contrast was 10x more &#8211; 31.99%. This substantial decline in NFT-related gas consumption can be attributed to various factors, including the network&#8217;s congestion caused by an influx of meme coin trading, notably the recently hyped frog-themed meme coin PEPE. This surge in meme coin transactions resulted in heightened gas prices, prompting users to explore alternatives and alleviating the burden on NFT marketplaces. Navigating the Gas Crisis Ethereum&#8216;s gas crisis has persisted despite The Merge, which is said to enhance scalability and reduce gas fees by migrating the network to a proof-of-stake consensus model. In response, some investors have sought solace in blockchain platforms offering cost-efficient alternatives. With its recent Hydra upgrade, Cardano has gained attention for its ability to handle transactions more economically. The implementation of Hydra&#8217;s layer-2 scaling solution has positioned Cardano as a viable option for users seeking relief from Ethereum&#8217;s high gas prices. The recent decrease in NFT marketplaces&#8217; gas consumption marks a significant turning point in Ethereum&#8217;s gas crisis. As decentralized finance (DeFi) protocols and other transaction-heavy platforms take the lead in gas consumption, the burden on NFT marketplaces has lessened. Related Reading: Ethereum Price Faces Confluence Of Bearish Factors and At Risk of Another Decline However, the broader Ethereum community anticipates the implementation of updates on the mainnet to address the persistent gas issues and improve scalability on the network.  Meanwhile, Ethereum&#8217;s price has experienced an upward trend in the past week, up by 2.4%. ETH has surged from a low of $1,771 seen last Friday to trading as high as above $1,800 later this week.  Ethereum market capitalization has also recorded huge gains in the past 7 days. ETH&#8217;s market cap has surged over 2% from a cap low of $215 billion to a high of $218 billion on Friday. Meanwhile, ETH’s daily trading volume has plunged throughout the week from a high of $10 billion last Friday to $5.5 billion in the last 24 hours. Interestingly, the asset has picked up from where it left off, rallying 1.1% in the last 24 hours. ETH currently trades slightly above $1,800 with a price of $1,811 at the time of writing. Featured image from Unsplash, Chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ethereum gas consumption landscape is transforming significantly as Non-Fungible Token (NFT) marketplaces no longer dominate the network&#8217;s gas usage. According to a <a href="https://twitter.com/nansen_ai/status/1659459667108724737?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">report</a> by Nansen, a crypto analytics platform, NFTs have fallen behind in doing the most in Ethereum gas fees. </p>
<p>Notably, while Ethereum&#8217;s transition to proof-of-stake, in an event known as &#8220;The Merge,&#8221; is anticipated to address high gas prices, investors are now <a href="https://twitter.com/cashpognft/status/1658955629908590593?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">exploring alternatives like Cardano</a>, which boasts greater cost-efficiency following its recent <a href="https://cardanofeed.com/cardano-ada-is-expected-to-hit-the-moon-by-its-hydra-update-12362.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Hydra upgrade</a>.</p>
<h2>Ethereum&#8217;s Gas Consumption Shift</h2>
<p>According to data revealed by Nansen on Friday, there&#8217;s currently a noteworthy shift in <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/ethereum/crypto-assets-flow-from-ethereum-to-bsc-are-users-escaping-high-gas-fees/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Ethereum&#8217;s gas consumption</a> patterns. NFT marketplaces, which once held the top spot, now account for a mere 3% of total gas usage.</p>

<p>Surprisingly, decentralized exchange (DEX) Uniswap has emerged as the primary gas consumer, representing 31.99% of gas consumption. This shift indicates a diversification in Ethereum&#8217;s transactional activity and a reduction in NFT-related gas usage. Nansen noted:</p>
<blockquote><p>Gone were the days of NFTs topping the Ethereum gas-consuming charts. This week, of the top 20 gas consumers, OpenSea and Blur accounted for less than 10% combined. And against all gas consumers, the NFT marketplaces were just over 3%. Uniswap in contrast was 10x more &#8211; 31.99%.</p></blockquote>
<p>This substantial decline in NFT-related gas consumption can be attributed to various factors, including the network&#8217;s congestion caused by an influx of meme coin trading, notably the recently hyped frog-themed meme coin PEPE.</p>
<p>This surge in meme coin transactions resulted in heightened gas prices, prompting users to explore alternatives and alleviating the burden on NFT marketplaces.</p>
<h2>Navigating the Gas Crisis</h2>
<p><a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/ethereum-whale-resurfaces-after-2-years/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Ethereum</a>&#8216;s gas crisis has persisted despite The Merge, which is said to enhance scalability and reduce gas fees by migrating the network to a proof-of-stake consensus model. In response, some investors have sought solace in blockchain platforms offering cost-efficient alternatives. </p>
<p>With its recent Hydra upgrade, Cardano has gained attention for its ability to handle transactions more economically. The implementation of Hydra&#8217;s layer-2 scaling solution has positioned Cardano as a viable option for users seeking relief from Ethereum&#8217;s high gas prices.</p>
<p>The recent decrease in NFT marketplaces&#8217; gas consumption marks a significant turning point in Ethereum&#8217;s gas crisis. As decentralized finance (DeFi) protocols and other transaction-heavy platforms take the lead in gas consumption, the burden on NFT marketplaces has lessened.</p>

<p>However, the broader Ethereum community anticipates the implementation of updates on the mainnet to address the persistent gas issues and improve scalability on the network. </p>
<p>Meanwhile, <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-bearish-1825/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Ethereum&#8217;s price</a> has experienced an upward trend in the past week, up by 2.4%. ETH has surged from a low of $1,771 seen last Friday to trading as high as above $1,800 later this week. </p>
<p>Ethereum market capitalization has also recorded huge gains in the past 7 days. ETH&#8217;s market cap has surged over 2% from a cap low of $215 billion to a high of $218 billion on Friday. Meanwhile, ETH’s daily trading volume has plunged throughout the week from a high of $10 billion last Friday to $5.5 billion in the last 24 hours.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/9szHkC5G/" alt="Ethereum (ETH)’s price chart on TradingView" width="2768" height="1556"/>
<p>Interestingly, the asset has picked up from where it left off, rallying 1.1% in the last 24 hours. ETH currently trades slightly above $1,800 with a price of $1,811 at the time of writing.</p>
<p>Featured image from Unsplash, Chart from TradingView</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ETH-460x297.jpg" width="460" height="297" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>NFT Market Takes A Hit: Sales Could Drop Below $1 Billion For The First Time In 2023</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/nft-market/nft-market-takes-a-hit-sales-could-drop-below-1-billion-for-the-first-time-in-2023/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 19:18:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[NFT market]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NFT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=534073</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Non-Fungible Tokens (NFT) industry has been a hub of innovation and growth over the past year, but as it approaches the midway point of 2023, the market is showing signs of maturation and change. According to a recent report by DappRadar, NFT sales could fall below $1 billion for the first time this year. Related Reading: XRP Ledger On Fire: Daily Transactions Skyrocket 10.7% In Q1 2023 NFT Market Facing Headwinds According to the report, the NFT market shows signs of a potential shift in May 2023, with the trading volume reaching $333 million from $2.3 million in sales, a trend that may result in the first month of this year with a trading volume under $1 billion. Despite this decline in sales, the NFT industry is still showing strong activity and engagement, with daily unique active wallets (dUAW) linked to NFT activities reaching 173,000, marking a 27% increase from the previous month. However, the NFT market is facing significant challenges, with many traders selling their large NFT holdings at a loss to participate in the Memecoin frenzy, according to DappRadar. This has led to an uptick in on-chain activity, driving Ethereum’s gas fees above $100 and negatively impacting the volume of low-value NFT trades on the blockchain. Despite this, the NFT market is still experiencing significant developments and events. Elon Musk’s tweet on May 10, 2023, referencing the Milady Maker collection, fueled a trading volume spike, reaching $13.95 million and doubling the number of trades in the same week.  Additionally, the Pudgy Penguins project secured $9 million in seed funding, debuting the Pudgy Toys collection, which amassed a total trading volume of $7.89 million the following week. Furthermore, the top ten NFT sales reveal stalwarts like the Bored Ape Yacht Club and CryptoPunks dominating the NFT landscape. However, a new entrant has emerged in the sixth position &#8211; an ADA handle, a personal crypto domain on the ADA blockchain, sold for $182,089, equivalent to 500,000 ADA.  Bitcoin Ordinals vs. NFTs Bitcoin Ordinals, a new form of digital asset, has become a hot topic in the decentralized app (dapp) community since its launch by software engineer Casey Rodarmor on January 21. This protocol has garnered a significant following, with over 7.4 million Ordinals minted at the time of writing. Ordinals differ from NFTs as they house all their data directly on-chain, earning the label “digital artifacts”. This feature makes Ordinals a potential technical upgrade to NFTs and a shift in Bitcoin&#8217;s cultural landscape. However, the rise of Ordinals and the BRC-20 token standard, which enables the deployment of meme coins on the Bitcoin blockchain, has provoked concern among Bitcoin maxis. These innovations have strained the Bitcoin network, leading to a backlog of unconfirmed transactions and increased fees. The spike in transaction demand caused fees to soar to $31 on May 8, 2023, according to DappRadar’s report.  Despite the challenges, the increased activity has boosted miner fees, enhancing the overall security of the Bitcoin blockchain. The surge in fees indicates a growing number of people using Bitcoin for non-financial purposes, such as creating and trading Ordinals and speculation on tokens. The Ordinals Protocol has given rise to intriguing collections and impressive sales, with Ordinal Punks and TwelveFold as notable examples. These collections have seen trading volumes, in the past 30 days, of 11.85 BTC and 14.9 BTC, respectively, indicating significant interest and engagement in the new digital asset. Related Reading: Lido’s ETH Deposits Reach Record High Amid Stagnant stETH Withdrawals The introduction of Bitcoin Ordinals represents an exciting development in the NFT space, opening up new possibilities for digital asset creation and trading. However, it also highlights the need for continued innovation and upgrades to address the challenges posed by increased activity and demand on the Bitcoin network.  Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Non-Fungible Tokens (NFT) industry has been a hub of innovation and growth over the past year, but as it approaches the midway point of 2023, the market is showing signs of maturation and change. According to a recent <a href="https://dappradar.com/blog/nft-market-nearing-sub-1-billion-era" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">report </a>by DappRadar, NFT sales could fall below $1 billion for the first time this year.</p>

<h2><b>NFT Market Facing Headwinds</b></h2>
<p>According to the report, the NFT market shows signs of a potential shift in May 2023, with the trading volume reaching $333 million from $2.3 million in sales, a trend that may result in the first month of this year with a trading volume under $1 billion.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large wp-image-534075" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Screenshot_40-860x565.jpg" alt="NFT" width="860" height="565" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Screenshot_40-860x565.jpg 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Screenshot_40-460x302.jpg 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Screenshot_40-768x505.jpg 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Screenshot_40-750x493.jpg 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Screenshot_40.jpg 864w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/>
<p>Despite this decline in sales, the NFT industry is still showing strong activity and engagement, with daily unique active wallets (dUAW) linked to NFT activities reaching 173,000, marking a 27% increase from the previous month.</p>
<p>However, the NFT market is facing significant challenges, with many traders selling their large NFT holdings at a loss to participate in the Memecoin frenzy, according to DappRadar. This has led to an uptick in on-chain activity, driving Ethereum’s gas fees above $100 and negatively impacting the volume of low-value NFT trades on the blockchain.</p>
<p>Despite this, the NFT market is still experiencing significant developments and events. Elon Musk’s tweet on May 10, 2023, referencing the Milady Maker collection, fueled a trading volume spike, reaching $13.95 million and doubling the number of trades in the same week. </p>
<p>Additionally, the Pudgy Penguins project secured $9 million in seed funding, debuting the Pudgy Toys collection, which amassed a total trading volume of $7.89 million the following week.</p>
<p>Furthermore, the top ten NFT sales reveal stalwarts like the Bored Ape Yacht Club and CryptoPunks dominating the NFT landscape. However, a new entrant has emerged in the sixth position &#8211; an ADA handle, a personal crypto domain on the ADA blockchain, sold for $182,089, equivalent to 500,000 ADA. </p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-534076" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Screenshot_39.jpg" alt="NFT" width="861" height="669" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Screenshot_39.jpg 861w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Screenshot_39-460x357.jpg 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Screenshot_39-768x597.jpg 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Screenshot_39-750x583.jpg 750w" sizes="(max-width: 861px) 100vw, 861px"/>
<b>Bitcoin Ordinals vs. NFTs</b>
<p>Bitcoin Ordinals, a new form of digital asset, has become a hot topic in the decentralized app (dapp) community since its launch by software engineer Casey Rodarmor on January 21. This protocol has garnered a significant following, with over 7.4 million Ordinals minted at the time of writing. </p>
<p>Ordinals differ from NFTs as they house all their data directly on-chain, earning the label “digital artifacts”. This feature makes Ordinals a potential technical upgrade to NFTs and a shift in Bitcoin&#8217;s cultural landscape.</p>
<p>However, the rise of Ordinals and the BRC-20 token standard, which enables the deployment of meme coins on the Bitcoin blockchain, has provoked concern among Bitcoin maxis. These innovations have strained the Bitcoin network, leading to a backlog of unconfirmed transactions and increased fees. The spike in transaction demand caused fees to soar to $31 on May 8, 2023, according to DappRadar’s report. </p>
<p>Despite the challenges, the increased activity has boosted miner fees, enhancing the overall security of the Bitcoin blockchain. The surge in fees indicates a growing number of people using Bitcoin for non-financial purposes, such as creating and trading Ordinals and speculation on tokens.</p>
<p>The Ordinals Protocol has given rise to intriguing collections and impressive sales, with Ordinal Punks and TwelveFold as notable examples. These collections have seen trading volumes, in the past 30 days, of 11.85 BTC and 14.9 BTC, respectively, indicating significant interest and engagement in the new digital asset.</p>

<p>The introduction of Bitcoin Ordinals represents an exciting development in the NFT space, opening up new possibilities for digital asset creation and trading. However, it also highlights the need for continued innovation and upgrades to address the challenges posed by increased activity and demand on the Bitcoin network. </p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/uuXvKtyV/" alt="NFT" width="1813" height="858"/>
<p>Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/iStock-1472939339-460x264.jpg" width="460" height="264" />	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
