<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	 xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" >

<channel>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://newsbtc.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://newsbtc.com</link>
	<description>Bitcoin &#38; cryptocurrency news today, price &#38; technical analysis</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 09:26:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<link>https://newsbtc.com</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>No Santa For Cryptos This Year: Large Cap Coins Touch December Lows</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/crypto/no-santa-for-crypto-this-year-large-cap-coins/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Anifowoshe Ibrahim]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 09:26:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BNBUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ltc/usd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=513144</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[As Bitcoin hits new lows at year-end, other large-cap altcoins have followed suit. There seems to be no love for crypto this year-end, as Santa has refused to show up. General Crypto Market Cap Plunges As it stands, crypto traders and investors seemed to have their hands up in resignation. Trading volume across major exchanges has been highly compressed. The general market capitalization across all digital assets is down around 2.6% monthly, at $774 billion. Crypto total market cap stands at $770 billion on daily chart. Source: TradingView The Bitcoin jump to $16,800 was a faint attempt at a bullish rally. The cryptocurrency continues to experience more downside, falling to its lowest in 3 weeks. Ethereum added 3.5% on Tuesday, having closed 130 basis points (bps) lower on Monday. The second largest crypto by market cap rose into the $1,200 region. ETH seems to collide with higher resistance at the $1,230 level. This could be challenging with the 14-day RSI now hovering directly below a ceiling of 47,000. Related Reading: Litecoin Continues To Slide, Now Below Shiba Inu In Market Cap The prices for Solana and Polkadot are currently trading at $12.36 (up 0.5%), $4.59 (down 0.8%), respectively. On the weekly chart, Polka Dot has decreased by 11.1% while Solana has decreased by 7.2%. During the past week, Polygon has lost 12.2%. Talking about some of the prominent stablecoins, Tether, USD Coin, and Binance USD are trading at $1 (flat), $1 (down 0.1%), and $0.99 (flat), respectively. Terra Classic is listed at $0.00011 (down 3.78%). Binance&#8217;s BNB soared 0.2% over the last 24 hours while meme coins Shiba Inu and Dogecoin took a beating, 3.5% and 4.8% respectively. Ripple’s XRP and Litecoin (LTC) are also in the green, while Polygon (MATIC) has remained virtually unchanged Michaël van de Poppe said that markets have been in bear territory for 19 months already. The trader pointed out that altcoins have been crashing since May 2021 despite the Solana and Polygon cycle. “The first HF [high low] confirmed on HTF [higher-time frame] will be a massive trigger for a relief run,” said Van de Poppe on Twitter. Altcoins Seem Indecisive Despite the plunge in Bitcoin value, altcoins have failed to flip BTC&#8217;s dominance. Over the past few days, many altcoins have gradually recovered while others have continued to suffer loss. For example, the Open Network’s TON lost a whopping 10.6% and gave up a lot of the gains from the past few days, when it was the market’s leader in terms of price performance. Source: Quantify Crypto Trust wallet token (TWT) led the way, rallying by 10.81%, with Flow (FLOW) and Axie Infinity (AXS) seeing gains of 6.53% and 6.18%, respectively. Related Reading: Bitcoin Bearish Signal: ‘Mid-Term’ Holders Show Signs Of Dumping The developments come on the back of news that Binance US will be buying out the assets of Voyager in a deal worth upwards of $1 billion. The exchange has even agreed to send $10 million in advance as a good-faith transfer. According to the press release, The Binance.US bid aims to return crypto to customers in kind, in accordance with court-approved disbursements and platform capabilities. Also, the Bank of Japan&#8217;s announcement to lower its target range for 10-year rates to 50 basis points early in the session caused the Asian equity markets and the NASDAQ mini to decline. Prior to this, the 10-year yield range was 25 basis points away from its aim of 0%. The S&#38;P 500 rose by 0.10%, while the NASDAQ Index concluded the day with a 0.01% gain. Through the afternoon session, the rebound provided support for the cryptocurrency market. Featured image from Unsplash.com, charts from TradingView.com and Quantify Crypto]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>As Bitcoin hits new lows at year-end, other large-cap altcoins have followed suit. There seems to be no love for crypto this year-end, as Santa has refused to show up.</p>
<h2>General Crypto Market Cap Plunges</h2>
<p>As it stands, crypto traders and investors seemed to have their hands up in resignation. Trading volume across major exchanges has been highly compressed. The general market capitalization across all digital assets is down around 2.6% monthly, at $774 billion.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-513146" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/TOTAL_2022-12-21_00-20-05.png" alt="Crypto" width="1479" height="861" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/TOTAL_2022-12-21_00-20-05.png 1479w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/TOTAL_2022-12-21_00-20-05-460x268.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/TOTAL_2022-12-21_00-20-05-860x501.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/TOTAL_2022-12-21_00-20-05-768x447.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/TOTAL_2022-12-21_00-20-05-750x437.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/TOTAL_2022-12-21_00-20-05-1140x664.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1479px) 100vw, 1479px" /></p>

<p>The Bitcoin jump to $16,800 was a faint attempt at a bullish rally. The cryptocurrency continues to experience more downside, falling to its lowest in 3 weeks.</p>
<p>Ethereum added 3.5% on Tuesday, having closed 130 basis points (bps) lower on Monday. The second largest crypto by market cap rose into the $1,200 region.</p>
<p>ETH seems to collide with higher resistance at the $1,230 level. This could be challenging with the 14-day RSI now hovering directly below a ceiling of 47,000.</p>

The prices for Solana and Polkadot are currently trading at $12.36 (up 0.5%), $4.59 (down 0.8%), respectively. On the weekly chart, Polka Dot has decreased by 11.1% while Solana has decreased by 7.2%. During the past week, Polygon has lost 12.2%.
Talking about some of the prominent stablecoins, Tether, USD Coin, and Binance USD are trading at $1 (flat), $1 (down 0.1%), and $0.99 (flat), respectively. Terra Classic is listed at $0.00011 (down 3.78%).

<p>Binance&#8217;s BNB soared 0.2% over the last 24 hours while meme coins Shiba Inu and Dogecoin took a beating, 3.5% and 4.8% respectively.</p>
<p>Ripple’s XRP and Litecoin (LTC) are also in the green, while Polygon (MATIC) has remained virtually unchanged</p>


<p>Michaël van de Poppe said that markets have been in bear territory for 19 months already. The trader pointed out that altcoins have been crashing since May 2021 despite the Solana and Polygon cycle.</p>
<p>“The first HF [high low] confirmed on HTF [higher-time frame] will be a massive trigger for a relief run,” said Van de Poppe on <a href="https://twitter.com/CryptoMichNL/status/1605287671089156096?s=20&amp;t=SYNO2DsdKcdvcmI0jneMKg" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Twitter.</a></p>

<h2>Altcoins Seem Indecisive</h2>
<p>Despite the plunge in Bitcoin value, altcoins have failed to flip BTC&#8217;s dominance. Over the past few days, many altcoins have gradually recovered while others have continued to suffer loss. For example, the Open Network’s TON lost a whopping 10.6% and gave up a lot of the gains from the past few days, when it was the market’s leader in terms of price performance.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-513147" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Screenshot-2022-12-21-at-00-22-22-Ethereum-Bounces-Above-1.2K-Bitcoin-Touches-December-Lows-Market-Watch.png" alt="crypto" width="957" height="476" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Screenshot-2022-12-21-at-00-22-22-Ethereum-Bounces-Above-1.2K-Bitcoin-Touches-December-Lows-Market-Watch.png 957w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Screenshot-2022-12-21-at-00-22-22-Ethereum-Bounces-Above-1.2K-Bitcoin-Touches-December-Lows-Market-Watch-460x229.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Screenshot-2022-12-21-at-00-22-22-Ethereum-Bounces-Above-1.2K-Bitcoin-Touches-December-Lows-Market-Watch-860x428.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Screenshot-2022-12-21-at-00-22-22-Ethereum-Bounces-Above-1.2K-Bitcoin-Touches-December-Lows-Market-Watch-768x382.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Screenshot-2022-12-21-at-00-22-22-Ethereum-Bounces-Above-1.2K-Bitcoin-Touches-December-Lows-Market-Watch-360x180.png 360w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Screenshot-2022-12-21-at-00-22-22-Ethereum-Bounces-Above-1.2K-Bitcoin-Touches-December-Lows-Market-Watch-750x373.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 957px) 100vw, 957px" /></p>

<p>Trust wallet token (TWT) led the way, rallying by 10.81%, with Flow (FLOW) and Axie Infinity (AXS) seeing gains of 6.53% and 6.18%, respectively.</p>
<p><em><strong>Related Reading: <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-bearish-signal-mid-term-dumping/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin Bearish Signal: ‘Mid-Term’ Holders Show Signs Of Dumping</a></strong></em></p>
<p>The developments come on the back of <a href="https://blog.binance.us/voyager-binance-us/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">news</a> that Binance US will be buying out the assets of Voyager in a deal worth upwards of $1 billion. The exchange has even agreed to send $10 million in advance as a good-faith transfer.</p>
<p>According to the press release,</p>
<blockquote><p>The Binance.US bid aims to return crypto to customers in kind, in accordance with court-approved disbursements and platform capabilities.</p></blockquote>
<p>Also, the Bank of Japan&#8217;s announcement to lower its target range for 10-year rates to 50 basis points early in the session caused the Asian equity markets and the NASDAQ mini to decline. Prior to this, the 10-year yield range was 25 basis points away from its aim of 0%.</p>
<p>The S&amp;P 500 rose by 0.10%, while the NASDAQ Index concluded the day with a 0.01% gain. Through the afternoon session, the rebound provided support for the cryptocurrency market.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/crypto-460x345.jpg" width="460" height="345" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Drops To Monthly Low As Year-End Approaches, More Impulsive Decline?</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-drops-to-monthly-low-as-year-end/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Anifowoshe Ibrahim]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 07:59:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=513137</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin moved closer to the $17,000 level on Tuesday. The digital currency dropped to $16,400, its lowest level in the last three weeks. As year-end approaches, BTC could face high volatility and low liquidity. Bitcoin Hit A Brief Surge Bitcoin surged to a short-lived peak of $16,837 in today&#8217;s session, barely 24 hours after hitting $16,398. The cryptocurrency saw an impulsive decline after experiencing significant rejection at the resistance level. The sharp fall has been associated with a straight daily decline for the S&#38;P 500 and general nervousness about the Federal Reserve&#8217;s potential to hike interest rates. BTC/USD trades at $16,870 on the daily chart. Source: TradingView BTC could witness more decline as the year closes given the decline in trading volume and liquidity. This would lead to a spike in the volatility of the asset. Katie Stockton, the founder of Fairlead Strategies LLC, has predicted that BTC could retest November lows, dropping “near $15,600, in the coming weeks.” BTC hit an all-time high of $68,997 on Nov. 8, 2021. But the big crypto produced a major shift in market structure by producing a lower low on the weekly timeframe at $32,995 on January 24. This move confirmed the start of a bear market. Related Reading: Bitcoin Poised To Resume Its Inclination To Outperform, Says Bloomberg Senior Analyst Possible Rally For BTC While the dust settles from the FTX crash and FUD surrounding Binance, the bitcoin price could begin to see a gradual recovery over the next few months. According to Jim Wyckoff, “Neither the bulls nor the bears have any near-term technical advantage.” This suggests that traders will continue to see “more choppy and sideways trading on the daily chart into the end of the year – barring any major fundamental shock to the marketplace,” Wyckoff concluded. However, a tweet by Crypto Trader, PlanB shows that the next Bitcoin halving is set to take place in 15 months. The build-up in price will not happen for at least 5 months as the U.S. FED will continue to tighten up monetary policy. BTC price will have room to breathe as macroeconomic conditions soften. Schroders, a global asset management firm, made the case that risky assets like Bitcoin have a nearly 80% chance of closing the year with positive returns. Related Reading: Bitcoin Still “Overvalued” According To NVT Ratio The investment firm noted that December was the best-performing month after collecting data on U.S. large-cap stocks since 1926. Schroders estimates that there is a 77.9% likelihood that large-cap stocks will end December with a net gain. The company divides all percentage gains vs. all percentage losses over the course of a month to arrive at these metrics. Investors should keep in mind that this year, the correlation between Bitcoin and the stock market has been over 90%. It may be argued that until the end of the year, the peer-to-peer digital currency will continue to reflect price changes on the stock market. Bitcoin is down 2% from December&#8217;s opening price of $17,167. Thus, following Schroders&#8217; analysis, Bitcoin may rise by 3.5% to reach $17,550 by Jan. 1, 2023. Featured image from Unsplash.com, charts from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin moved closer to the $17,000 level on Tuesday. The digital currency dropped to $16,400, its lowest level in the last three weeks. As year-end approaches, BTC could face high volatility and <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-poised-to-outperform-analyst/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">low liquidity.</a></p>
<h2>Bitcoin Hit A Brief Surge</h2>
<p>Bitcoin surged to a short-lived peak of $16,837 in today&#8217;s session, barely 24 hours after hitting $16,398. The cryptocurrency saw an impulsive decline after experiencing significant rejection at the resistance level.</p>
<p>The sharp fall has been associated with a straight daily decline for the S&amp;P 500 and general nervousness about the Federal Reserve&#8217;s potential to hike interest rates.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-513142" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-20_23-43-27.png" alt="Bitcoin" width="1478" height="861" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-20_23-43-27.png 1478w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-20_23-43-27-460x268.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-20_23-43-27-860x501.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-20_23-43-27-768x447.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-20_23-43-27-750x437.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-20_23-43-27-1140x664.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1478px) 100vw, 1478px" /></p>

<p>BTC could witness more decline as the year closes given the decline in trading volume and liquidity. This would lead to a spike in the volatility of the asset.</p>
<p>Katie Stockton, the founder of Fairlead Strategies LLC, has predicted that BTC could retest November lows, dropping “near $15,600, in the coming weeks.”</p>
<p>BTC hit an all-time high of $68,997 on Nov. 8, 2021. But the big crypto produced a major shift in market structure by producing a lower low on the weekly timeframe at $32,995 on January 24. This move confirmed the start of a bear market.</p>

<h2>Possible Rally For BTC</h2>
<p>While the dust settles from the FTX crash and FUD surrounding Binance, the bitcoin price could begin to see a gradual recovery over the next few months. According to Jim Wyckoff, “Neither the bulls nor the bears have any near-term technical advantage.”</p>
<p>This suggests that traders will continue to see “more choppy and sideways trading on the daily chart into the end of the year – barring any major fundamental shock to the marketplace,” Wyckoff concluded.</p>
<p>However, a <a href="https://twitter.com/100trillionUSD/status/1604924039575007232?s=20&amp;t=f6zeDQ4NA8PfeDKoXdr97g" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">tweet</a> by Crypto Trader, PlanB shows that the next Bitcoin halving is set to take place in 15 months. The build-up in price will not happen for at least 5 months as the U.S. FED will continue to tighten up monetary policy. BTC price will have room to breathe as macroeconomic conditions soften.</p>
<p>Schroders, a global asset management firm, made the case that risky assets like Bitcoin have a nearly 80% chance of closing the year with positive returns.</p>
<p><strong><em>Related Reading: <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-overvalued-according-nvt-ratio/">Bitcoin Still “Overvalued” According To NVT Ratio</a></em></strong></p>
<p>The investment firm noted that December was the best-performing month after collecting data on U.S. large-cap stocks since 1926. Schroders estimates that there is a 77.9% likelihood that large-cap stocks will end December with a net gain. The company divides all percentage gains vs. all percentage losses over the course of a month to arrive at these metrics.</p>
<p>Investors should keep in mind that this year, the correlation between Bitcoin and the stock market has been over 90%. It may be argued that until the end of the year, the peer-to-peer digital currency will continue to reflect price changes on the stock market.</p>
<p>Bitcoin is down 2% from December&#8217;s opening price of $17,167. Thus, following Schroders&#8217; analysis, Bitcoin may rise by 3.5% to reach $17,550 by Jan. 1, 2023.</p>



]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/kanchanara-5ixVD22x22o-unsplash-2-1-scaled-1-460x306.jpg" width="460" height="306" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cardano (ADA) Price Prediction: Downtrend Far From Over, $0.22 Still In Play</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/analysis/ada/cardano-ada-price-prediction-0-22/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 05:25:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[ADA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[adausd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[adausdc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADAUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=513173</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Cardano’s price started a fresh decline after it failed to surpass $0.32. ADA remains at a risk of more losses below $0.25 and $0.245 in the near term. ADA price is gaining bearish momentum below the $0.280 support against the US dollar. The price is trading below $0.280 and the 100 simple moving average (4-hours). There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.2560 on the 4-hours chart of the ADA/USD pair (data source from Kraken). The pair could continue to move down below the $0.245 support zone. Cardano (ADA) Price Could Dive Further In the past few days, cardano’s price saw a steady decline from the $0.320 resistance zone. The bears were able to push the price below the $0.30 and $0.280 support levels. The decline gained pace below the $0.265 level and the 100 simple moving average (4-hours). ADA price even spiked below the $0.250 support zone and traded as low as $0.2481. It is now showing a lot of bearish signs near the $0.250 zone, unlike bitcoin and ethereum. It is trading well below $0.280 and the 100 simple moving average (4-hours). On the upside, an immediate resistance is near the $0.255 zone. There is also a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.2560 on the 4-hours chart of the ADA/USD pair. The first major resistance is forming near the $0.264 zone. It is near the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $0.3188 swing high to $0.2481 low. Source: ADAUSD on TradingView.com The main resistance is now forming near the $0.2840 level. It coincides with the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $0.3188 swing high to $0.2481 low. If there is an upside break above the $0.280 and $0.284 resistance levels, the price could start a strong increase. In the stated case, the price could rise steadily towards the $0.32 level. More Losses? If cardano’s price fails to recover above the $0.255 and $0.264 resistance levels, it could continue to move down. An immediate support on the downside is near the $0.248 level. The next major support is near the $0.245 level. A downside break below the $0.245 level could open the doors for a fresh decline towards $0.220 in the coming days. The next major support is near the $0.200 level. Technical Indicators 4-hours MACD – The MACD for ADA/USD is gaining momentum in the bearish zone. 4-hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for ADA/USD is now below the 50 level. Major Support Levels – $0.245, $0.220 and $0.200. Major Resistance Levels – $0.255, $0.264 and $0.284.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>Cardano’s price started a fresh decline after it failed to surpass $0.32. ADA remains at a risk of more losses below $0.25 and $0.245 in the near term.</em></p>
<ul>
<li>ADA price is gaining bearish momentum below the $0.280 support against the US dollar.</li>
<li>The price is trading below $0.280 and the 100 simple moving average (4-hours).</li>
<li>There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.2560 on the 4-hours chart of the ADA/USD pair (data source from Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could continue to move down below the $0.245 support zone.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Cardano (ADA) Price Could Dive Further</h2>
<p>In the past few days, cardano’s price saw a steady decline from the $0.320 resistance zone. The bears were able to push the price below the $0.30 and $0.280 support levels.</p>
<p>The decline gained pace below the $0.265 level and the 100 simple moving average (4-hours). ADA price even spiked below the $0.250 support zone and traded as low as $0.2481. It is now showing a lot of bearish signs near the $0.250 zone, unlike <a href="https://newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-signals-rejection-17k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">bitcoin</a> and <a href="https://newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-bearish-1220/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">ethereum</a>.</p>
<p>It is trading well below $0.280 and the 100 simple moving average (4-hours). On the upside, an immediate resistance is near the $0.255 zone. There is also a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.2560 on the 4-hours chart of the ADA/USD pair.</p>
<p>The first major resistance is forming near the $0.264 zone. It is near the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $0.3188 swing high to $0.2481 low.</p>
<p><a href="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Cardano-ADA-1.png"><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-513174" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Cardano-ADA-1.png" alt="Cardano (ADA) Price" width="1834" height="845" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Cardano-ADA-1.png 1834w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Cardano-ADA-1-460x212.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Cardano-ADA-1-860x396.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Cardano-ADA-1-768x354.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Cardano-ADA-1-1536x708.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Cardano-ADA-1-750x346.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Cardano-ADA-1-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1834px) 100vw, 1834px" /></a></p>
<p>Source: <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/ADAUSD/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">ADAUSD on TradingView.com</a></p>
<p>The main resistance is now forming near the $0.2840 level. It coincides with the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $0.3188 swing high to $0.2481 low. If there is an upside break above the $0.280 and $0.284 resistance levels, the price could start a strong increase. In the stated case, the price could rise steadily towards the $0.32 level.</p>
<h2>More Losses?</h2>
<p>If cardano’s price fails to recover above the $0.255 and $0.264 resistance levels, it could continue to move down. An immediate support on the downside is near the $0.248 level.</p>
<p>The next major support is near the $0.245 level. A downside break below the $0.245 level could open the doors for a fresh decline towards $0.220 in the coming days. The next major support is near the $0.200 level.</p>
<p>Technical Indicators</p>
<p>4-hours MACD – The MACD for ADA/USD is gaining momentum in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>4-hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for ADA/USD is now below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Levels – $0.245, $0.220 and $0.200.</p>
<p>Major Resistance Levels – $0.255, $0.264 and $0.284.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/shutterstock_259487336-460x297.jpg" width="460" height="297" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum Price Bearish Signal: ETH Below 100 SMA Could Trigger Downside</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-bearish-1220/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 04:43:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=513160</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Ethereum is facing resistance above $1,220 against the US Dollar. ETH could start another decline if it fails to stay above $1,200 and the 100 hourly SMA. Ethereum started an upside correction above the $1,180 resistance zone. The price is now trading above $1,200 and the 100 hourly simple moving average. There is a short-term contracting triangle with resistance near $1,220 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD (data feed via Kraken). The pair could start another upward move if there is a wave above the $1,220 resistance. Ethereum Price Eyes Recovery Ethereum price found support near the $1,150 zone and started a recovery wave. ETH was able to clear the $1,180 and $1,190 levels. The price even climbed above the $1,200 level and the 100 hourly simple moving average, similar to bitcoin. A high was formed near $1,230 before the price started a consolidation phase. Ether price is now trading near the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the recent increase from the $1,150 swing low to $1,230 high. The price is now trading above $1,200 and the 100 hourly simple moving average. There is also a short-term contracting triangle with resistance near $1,220 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD. The first major resistance is near the $1,220 level. Source: ETHUSD on TradingView.com A clear upside break above the $1,220 resistance and then a move above the $1,230 level could initiate a decent increase. The next major resistance could be $1,260. If the bulls clear the $1,260 resistance, the price might rise towards $1,300. Any more gains might send the price towards the $1,350 resistance zone. An intermediate resistance could be near the $1,320 level. Fresh Drop in ETH? If ethereum fails to climb above the $1,220 resistance, it could start another bearish wave. An initial support on the downside is near the $1,200 level. The next major support is near the $1,190 level or the 50% Fib retracement level of the recent increase from the $1,150 swing low to $1,230 high. A clear downside break below $1,190 might push the price lower towards the $1,150 support. Any more losses could lead the price towards the $1,100 support. Technical Indicators Hourly MACD – The MACD for ETH/USD is now losing momentum in the bullish zone. Hourly RSI &#8211; The RSI for ETH/USD is now above the 50 level. Major Support Level – $1,190 Major Resistance Level – $1,220]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>Ethereum is facing resistance above $1,220 against the US Dollar. ETH could start another decline if it fails to stay above $1,200 and the 100 hourly SMA.</em></p>
<ul>
<li>Ethereum started an upside correction above the $1,180 resistance zone.</li>
<li>The price is now trading above $1,200 and the 100 hourly simple moving average.</li>
<li>There is a short-term contracting triangle with resistance near $1,220 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD (data feed via Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could start another upward move if there is a wave above the $1,220 resistance.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Ethereum Price Eyes Recovery</h2>
<p>Ethereum price found support near the $1,150 zone and started a recovery wave. ETH was able to clear the $1,180 and $1,190 levels. The price even climbed above the $1,200 level and the 100 hourly simple moving average, similar to <a href="https://newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-signals-rejection-17k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">bitcoin</a>.</p>
<p>A high was formed near $1,230 before the price started a consolidation phase. Ether price is now trading near the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the recent increase from the $1,150 swing low to $1,230 high.</p>
<p>The price is now trading above $1,200 and the 100 hourly simple moving average. There is also a short-term contracting triangle with resistance near $1,220 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD. The first major resistance is near the $1,220 level.</p>
<p><a href="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Ethereum-15.png"><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-513161" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Ethereum-15.png" alt="Ethereum Price" width="1834" height="845" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Ethereum-15.png 1834w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Ethereum-15-460x212.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Ethereum-15-860x396.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Ethereum-15-768x354.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Ethereum-15-1536x708.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Ethereum-15-750x346.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Ethereum-15-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1834px) 100vw, 1834px" /></a></p>
<p>Source: <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/ETHUSD/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">ETHUSD on TradingView.com</a></p>
<p>A clear upside break above the <a href="https://newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-breaking-this-confluence-resistance-could-start-recovery/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">$1,220 resistance</a> and then a move above the $1,230 level could initiate a decent increase. The next major resistance could be $1,260. If the bulls clear the $1,260 resistance, the price might rise towards $1,300. Any more gains might send the price towards the $1,350 resistance zone. An intermediate resistance could be near the $1,320 level.</p>
<h2>Fresh Drop in ETH?</h2>
<p>If ethereum fails to climb above the $1,220 resistance, it could start another bearish wave. An initial support on the downside is near the $1,200 level.</p>
<p>The next major support is near the $1,190 level or the 50% Fib retracement level of the recent increase from the $1,150 swing low to $1,230 high. A clear downside break below $1,190 might push the price lower towards the $1,150 support. Any more losses could lead the price towards the $1,100 support.</p>
<p>Technical Indicators</p>
<p>Hourly MACD<strong> – </strong>The MACD for ETH/USD is now losing momentum in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>Hourly RSI<strong> &#8211; </strong>The RSI for ETH/USD is now above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Level – $1,190</p>
<p>Major Resistance Level – $1,220</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/iStock-1383710952-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Price Signals Rejection and Poised To Start Another Decline</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-signals-rejection-17k/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 02:24:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xbtusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=513157</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin price is facing resistance near $17,000. BTC could start another decline unless there is a strong move above the $17,000 resistance zone. Bitcoin recovered higher above the $16,800 resistance zone. The price is trading above $16,800 and the 100 hourly simple moving average. There is a rising channel forming with resistance near $17,000 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Kraken). The pair could resume its decline unless there is a close above the $17,000 resistance zone. Bitcoin Price Faces Resistance Bitcoin price found support near the $16,250 zone. BTC traded as low as $16,260 and started a recovery wave. There was a clear move above the $16,500 and $16,600 levels. The bulls were able to push the price above the $16,800 resistance and the 100 hourly simple moving average. The price even spiked above the $17,000 resistance, but upsides were limited. A high was formed near $17,067 and the price is now trading in a range. Bitcoin price declined below the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $16,260 swing low to $17,067 high. It is now trading above $16,800 and the 100 hourly simple moving average. There is also a rising channel forming with resistance near $17,000 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair. On the upside, an immediate resistance is near the $17,000 zone. The first major resistance is near the $17,200 zone. A clear move above the $17,200 resistance might call for a move towards the $17,500 resistance. Source: BTCUSD on TradingView.com The next major resistance is near $18,000, above which the price might gain pace and rise towards the $18,450 resistance zone in the coming sessions. Fresh Decline in BTC? If bitcoin fails to clear the $17,000 resistance, there could be a fresh decline. An immediate support on the downside is near the $16,800 level and the channel trend line. The next major support is near the $16,650 zone. It is close to the 50% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $16,260 swing low to $17,067 high. A downside break below the $16,650 support might call for a drop towards the $16,260 level. Any more losses might send the price towards $16,000. Technical indicators: Hourly MACD – The MACD is now losing pace in the bullish zone. Hourly RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BTC/USD is now above the 50 level. Major Support Levels – $16,800, followed by $16,650. Major Resistance Levels – $17,000, $17,200 and $17,500.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>Bitcoin price is facing resistance near $17,000. BTC could start another decline unless there is a strong move above the $17,000 resistance zone.</em></p>
<ul>
<li>Bitcoin recovered higher above the $16,800 resistance zone.</li>
<li>The price is trading above $16,800 and the 100 hourly simple moving average.</li>
<li>There is a rising channel forming with resistance near $17,000 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could resume its decline unless there is a close above the $17,000 resistance zone.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Bitcoin Price Faces Resistance</h2>
<p>Bitcoin price found support near the $16,250 zone. BTC traded as low as $16,260 and started a <a href="https://newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-vulnerable-below-17k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">recovery wave</a>. There was a clear move above the $16,500 and $16,600 levels.</p>
<p>The bulls were able to push the price above the $16,800 resistance and the 100 hourly simple moving average. The price even spiked above the $17,000 resistance, but upsides were limited. A high was formed near $17,067 and the price is now trading in a range.</p>
<p>Bitcoin price declined below the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $16,260 swing low to $17,067 high. It is now trading above $16,800 and the <a href="https://newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-bearish-16-5k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">100 hourly simple moving average</a>.</p>
<p>There is also a rising channel forming with resistance near $17,000 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair. On the upside, an immediate resistance is near the $17,000 zone. The first major resistance is near the $17,200 zone. A clear move above the $17,200 resistance might call for a move towards the $17,500 resistance.</p>
<p><a href="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-18.png"><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-513158" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-18.png" alt="Bitcoin Price" width="1834" height="845" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-18.png 1834w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-18-460x212.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-18-860x396.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-18-768x354.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-18-1536x708.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-18-750x346.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-18-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1834px) 100vw, 1834px" /></a></p>
<p>Source: <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BTCUSD/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">BTCUSD on TradingView.com</a></p>
<p>The next major resistance is near $18,000, above which the price might gain pace and rise towards the $18,450 resistance zone in the coming sessions.</p>
<h2>Fresh Decline in BTC?</h2>
<p>If bitcoin fails to clear the $17,000 resistance, there could be a fresh decline. An immediate support on the downside is near the $16,800 level and the channel trend line.</p>
<p>The next major support is near the $16,650 zone. It is close to the 50% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $16,260 swing low to $17,067 high. A downside break below the $16,650 support might call for a drop towards the $16,260 level. Any more losses might send the price towards $16,000.</p>
<p>Technical indicators:</p>
<p>Hourly MACD – The MACD is now losing pace in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>Hourly RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BTC/USD is now above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Levels – $16,800, followed by $16,650.</p>
<p>Major Resistance Levels – $17,000, $17,200 and $17,500.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/04/shutterstock_1334283245-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Grayscale May Liquidate 600,000 BTC Holdings Following SEC Opposition To ETF</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/grayscale-may-liquidate-600000-btc-holdings/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Anifowoshe Ibrahim]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 00:12:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[gbtc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[grayscale]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[grayscale bitcoin trust]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=513129</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Grayscale Investments may offer to buy up to 20% of Grayscale Bitcoin Trust  (GBTC) shares. This is a move the company hopes will close the gap between the GBTC share price and the company&#8217;s underlying Bitcoin holdings. Grayscale Can&#8217;t Act Independent Of Investors The Wall Street Journal released a letter by Grayscale CEO Michael Sonnenshein urging that Grayscale would consider issuing a tender offer should the Security and Exchange Commission (SEC) and shareholders give their approval. Being a close-ended fund, GBTC shareholders can only liquidate their holdings on the open market. Under the Williams Act (part of the Securities Exchange Act of 1934) that governs tender offers in the US, an investor tendering for a security must disclose their source of funds, legal agreements related to the offer, and reasons for the offer. GBTC trades at $8.08 on the 24-hour chart. Source: TradingView If the company cannot return GBTC shareholders funds, it will continue to offer the tender until it&#8217;s converted to an ETF. Sonnenshein wrote to investors: In the event we are unsuccessful in pursuing options for returning a portion of the capital to shareholders, we do not currently intend to dissolve GBTC, but would instead continue to operate GBTC without an ongoing redemption program until we are successful in converting it to a spot bitcoin ETF. Grayscale is currently embroiled in a lawsuit with the SEC after its application to convert GBTC to a spot Bitcoin ETF on June 29, 2022. The letter by the CEO was an attempt to ease shareholder concerns after a turbulent few months across the crypto market. Related Reading: GBTC Unlocks Spells Doom For Bitcoin? Top Expert Breaks It Down ETF Conversion Seems To Be Only Option As it stands, Grayscale doesn&#8217;t have a specific timeline for when it may explore other options apart from the ETF conversion. The lawsuit seems to be a long-drawn battle. Grayscale filed its opening brief against the SEC on Oct. 11, 2022. In response, SEC filed a brief on Dec. 13, 2022 denying Grayscale&#8217;s accusations that its rejection was discriminatory and arbitrary. The firm has until Jan. 13, 2023 to respond. Afterwards, a three-judge panel will be selected to listen to oral arguments and rule on the case. Grayscale&#8217;s Bitcoin Trust has roughly $10.78 billion or 633,000 BTC in assets under management. The fund has failed to meet its goal, and it&#8217;s currently changing hands at a 48.8% discount to Bitcoin. Source: YCharts Sonnenshein didn&#8217;t clarify if the business may later sell off its Bitcoin holdings. However, a market dump like Grayscale could see Bitcoin crashin to a fresh yearly low. Grayscale selling off its Bitcoin stash could also drive down confidence in crypto as significant liquidations for those engaged in Bitcoin derivatives markets. This would hurt crypto volumes, and send a bearish crypto market further down. Related Reading: Why The GBTC Discount Could Lead To A Bitcoin Sell-Off Featured image from Finbold, charts from Ycharts, and TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Grayscale Investments may offer to buy up to 20% of Grayscale Bitcoin Trust  (GBTC) shares. This is a move the company hopes will close the gap between the GBTC share price and the company&#8217;s underlying Bitcoin holdings.</p>
<h2>Grayscale Can&#8217;t Act Independent Of Investors</h2>
<p>The Wall Street Journal <a href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/if-grayscales-bitcoin-etf-dreams-fail-firm-may-try-a-tender-offer-ceo-says-11671428078" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">released</a> a letter by Grayscale CEO Michael Sonnenshein <a href="https://grayscale.com/end-of-year-ceo-letter-to-investors-2022/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">urging</a> that Grayscale would consider issuing a tender offer should the Security and Exchange Commission (SEC) and shareholders give their approval. Being a close-ended fund, GBTC shareholders can only liquidate their holdings on the open market.</p>
<p>Under the Williams Act (part of the Securities Exchange Act of 1934) that governs tender offers in the US, an investor tendering for a security must disclose their source of funds, legal agreements related to the offer, and reasons for the offer.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-513133 size-full" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/GBTC_2022-12-20_22-52-31.png" alt="Grayscale" width="1479" height="861" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/GBTC_2022-12-20_22-52-31.png 1479w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/GBTC_2022-12-20_22-52-31-460x268.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/GBTC_2022-12-20_22-52-31-860x501.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/GBTC_2022-12-20_22-52-31-768x447.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/GBTC_2022-12-20_22-52-31-750x437.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/GBTC_2022-12-20_22-52-31-1140x664.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1479px) 100vw, 1479px" /></p>

<p>If the company cannot return GBTC shareholders funds, it will continue to offer the tender until it&#8217;s converted to an ETF.</p>
<p>Sonnenshein wrote to investors:</p>
<blockquote><p>In the event we are unsuccessful in pursuing options for returning a portion of the capital to shareholders, we do not currently intend to dissolve GBTC, but would instead continue to operate GBTC without an ongoing redemption program until we are successful in converting it to a spot bitcoin ETF.</p></blockquote>
<p>Grayscale is currently embroiled in a lawsuit with the SEC after its <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/grayscale-met-with-the-sec-tried-to-convince-them-to-turn-the-gbtc-into-an-etf/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">application</a> to convert GBTC to a spot Bitcoin ETF on June 29, 2022.</p>
<p>The letter by the CEO was an attempt to ease shareholder concerns after a turbulent few months across the crypto market.</p>

<h2>ETF Conversion Seems To Be Only Option</h2>
<p>As it stands, Grayscale doesn&#8217;t have a specific timeline for when it may explore other options apart from the ETF conversion.</p>
<p>The lawsuit seems to be a long-drawn battle. Grayscale filed its opening brief against the SEC on Oct. 11, 2022. In response, SEC filed a brief on Dec. 13, 2022 denying Grayscale&#8217;s accusations that its rejection was discriminatory and arbitrary.</p>
<p>The firm has until Jan. 13, 2023 to respond. Afterwards, a three-judge panel will be selected to listen to oral arguments and rule on the case.</p>
<p>Grayscale&#8217;s Bitcoin Trust has roughly $10.78 billion or 633,000 BTC in assets under management. The fund has failed to meet its goal, and it&#8217;s currently changing hands at a 48.8% discount to Bitcoin.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-513130" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/GBTC-Discount-or-Premium-850x307-1.png" alt="" width="850" height="307" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/GBTC-Discount-or-Premium-850x307-1.png 850w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/GBTC-Discount-or-Premium-850x307-1-460x166.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/GBTC-Discount-or-Premium-850x307-1-768x277.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/GBTC-Discount-or-Premium-850x307-1-750x271.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 850px) 100vw, 850px" /></p>
<p style="text-align: center">Source: <a href="https://ycharts.com/companies/GBTC/discount_or_premium_to_nav" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">YCharts</a></p>
<p>Sonnenshein didn&#8217;t clarify if the business may later sell off its Bitcoin holdings. However, a market dump like Grayscale could see Bitcoin crashin to a fresh yearly low.</p>
<p>Grayscale selling off its Bitcoin stash could also drive down confidence in crypto as significant liquidations for those engaged in Bitcoin derivatives markets. This would hurt crypto volumes, and send a bearish crypto market further down.</p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Grayscale-CEO-recent-crypto-sell-off-hasnt-deterred-investors-460x345.jpg" width="460" height="345" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Shiba Inu Welcomes 10,000 New Holders, Can SHIB Keep Up The Momentum?</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/shiba-inu-welcomes-new-holders/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Best Owie]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 23:00:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Shiba Inu]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIB]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIB holders]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIB price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIBUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIBUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=513040</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Despite the market downturn, Shiba Inu (SHIB) is still seeing growth in terms of its holder base. The meme coin maintains its position as one of the most popular cryptocurrencies as its total holder count has now crossed 1.26 million. 10,000 New Shiba Inu Holders Added In a time when cryptocurrencies across the space are marking a decline in support, Shiba Inu has added over 10,000 new holders in the span of two weeks. This saw the total SHIB holders cross into the 1.26 million territory, marking more growth for the meme coin. In the last 24 hours alone, the number is up by 0.033%, according to data from Etherscan. Related Reading: Ethereum Price Balks As Dormant Whales Reactivate The meme coin also recently marked another milestone after it crossed more than 1.8 million watchlists on Coinmarketcap. The growth comes even as the price of the digital asset suffers multiple setbacks, drastically dragging down the profit margins for investors. Binance, the largest crypto exchange in the world by trading volume, recently released the data for the most-watched cryptocurrencies on the platform, and Shiba Inu emerged in the top three; alongside market leaders Bitcoin and Ethereum. SHIB price struggles at $0.000008 &#124; Source: SHIBUSD on TradingView.com Will SHIB Price Remain Stagnant? SHIB’s price has been quite unresponsive to all of the new milestones being hit. The holder base had been consistently climbing over the last two months but the price of SHIB has not reacted positively in any way. Instead, developments on Shiba Inu seem to be disconnected from the price performance of the native token. Related Reading: Binance Smart Chain User Activity Tanks, Why BNB Price Could Suffer With no meaningful movement following all of these, then it is possible that the meme coin will not be seeing any sort of recovery before the year runs out. It continues to trend just above $0.000008 as the bear market rages on. It is important to keep in mind that the total number of active Shiba Inu addresses currently sits below 5% of its total addresses. This means that there is a decreased activity for the digital asset, which could explain why there have been no positive reactions to the milestones.  The cryptocurrency has also fallen out of favor with large Ethereum whales who no longer hold a significant amount of the cryptocurrency on their balances. This has accelerated the bear case for the meme coin. If momentum does not pick up, then it is possible that SHIB could see the lower side of $0.000007 before the year is over.  Featured image from Crypto News, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="p2">Despite the market downturn, Shiba Inu (SHIB) is still seeing growth in terms of its holder base. The meme coin maintains its position as one of the most popular cryptocurrencies as its total holder count has now crossed 1.26 million.</p>
<h2 class="p2">10,000 New Shiba Inu Holders Added</h2>
<p class="p2">In a time when cryptocurrencies across the space are marking a decline in support, Shiba Inu has added over 10,000 new holders in the span of two weeks. This saw the total SHIB holders cross into the 1.26 million territory, marking more growth for the meme coin. In the last 24 hours alone, the number is up by 0.033%, according to data from <a href="https://etherscan.io/token/0x95aD61b0a150d79219dCF64E1E6Cc01f0B64C4cE" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">Etherscan</a>.</p>

<p class="p2">The meme coin also recently marked another milestone after it crossed more than 1.8 million watchlists on Coinmarketcap. The growth comes even as the price of the digital asset suffers multiple setbacks, drastically dragging down the profit margins for investors.</p>
<p class="p2">Binance, the largest crypto exchange in the world by trading volume, recently released the data for the most-watched cryptocurrencies on the platform, and Shiba Inu emerged in the top three; alongside market leaders Bitcoin and Ethereum.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/nlZVFrvz/" alt="Shiba Inu price chart from TradingView.com" width="3284" height="1760" /></p>

<h2 class="p2">Will SHIB Price Remain Stagnant?</h2>
<p class="p2">SHIB’s price has been quite unresponsive to all of the new milestones being hit. The holder base had been consistently climbing over the last two months but the price of SHIB has not reacted positively in any way. Instead, developments on Shiba Inu seem to be disconnected from the price performance of the native token.</p>

<p class="p2">With no meaningful movement following all of these, then it is possible that the meme coin will not be seeing any sort of recovery before the year runs out. It continues to trend just above $0.000008 as the bear market rages on.</p>
<p class="p2">It is important to keep in mind that the total number of active Shiba Inu addresses currently sits below 5% of its total addresses. This means that there is a decreased activity for the digital asset, which could explain why there have been no positive reactions to the milestones. </p>
<p class="p2">The <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/shiba-inu-falls-out-of-favor-with-ethereum-whales/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">cryptocurrency has also fallen out of favor with large Ethereum whales</a> who no longer hold a significant amount of the cryptocurrency on their balances. This has accelerated the bear case for the meme coin. If momentum does not pick up, then it is possible that SHIB could see the lower side of $0.000007 before the year is over. </p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Shiba-Inu-SHIB-price-460x307.jpeg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Could A Litecoin Fractal Foretell A New Bull Trend In Crypto?</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/litecoin/litecoin-fractal-foretell-bull-trend-crypto/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tony Spilotro]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 22:37:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Litecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ltc/usd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ltcbtc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ltceth]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LTCUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=513138</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The cryptocurrency market continues to feel the darkness of crypto winter, but it could be Litecoin bringing the blossom of a new bull trend, according to a an eerily similar fractal found in LTCUSD daily price charts.  The fractal pattern developed following the most recent pullback, and appears to have a similar structure to a major bull market breakout. Could this be the light at the end of the tunnel for cryptocurrencies? Hawkish Fed Dims Litecoin Rally, But A Fractal Gives Hope After a stellar month leading the market with 40% returns for November, Litecoin has given back nearly half of that thus far in December.  LTC had been on a tear, outperforming top coins like Bitcoin and Ethereum, and clawed its way closer toward making it back into the top ten cryptocurrencies ranked by market cap.  Related Reading: Bitcoin Volatility Explodes Around $18K Level, As Fed Reveals 50 Basis Point Rate Increase But the greater market pullback stemming from a hawkish Fed meeting this month, caused a failure to liftoff in Litecoin.   However, the discovery of a price action fractal in LTCUSD could suggest this recent pullback wasn’t necessarily a failure, but a refueling of sorts — before taking off in an even stronger rally.  The price action is strikingly similar then versus now &#124; LTCUSD on TradingView.com Comparing Price Action Then Vs Now: Will Bulls Get A Break? The fractal begins on Black Thursday in March 2020 — a black swan event few saw coming. Litecoin rebounded and the fractal formed.  Unlike Bitcoin, which made a lower low during the FTX, LTCUSD hasn’t, and instead has followed the same pattern from 2020 almost flawlessly.  Price following the fractal further could lead to some minor continued downside, but ultimately holds at resistance turned support. If the current pullback proves to be a retest and holds, a more obvious rally could materialize. Related Reading: Litecoin Continues To Slide, Now Below Shiba Inu In Market Cap Failure would almost certainly send Litecoin back toward 2018 lows and potentially beyond, making the fractal among one of Litecoin bulls’ best hope for a redemption rally. Importantly, a concurrent reversal taking place in the LTCBTC and LTCETH trading pairs appear to indicate strength in the altcoin relative to the top two crypto assets. However, there is no telling what this might mean for the overall market at this time. Follow @TonySpilotroBTC on Twitter or join the TonyTradesBTC Telegram for exclusive daily market insights and technical analysis education. Please note: Content is educational and should not be considered investment advice. Featured image from iStockPhoto, Charts from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The cryptocurrency market continues to feel the darkness of crypto winter, but it could be <a href="/tag/litecoin" rel="nofollow">Litecoin</a> bringing the blossom of a new bull trend, according to a an eerily similar fractal found in LTCUSD daily price charts. </p>
<p>The fractal pattern developed following the most recent pullback, and appears to have a similar structure to a major bull market breakout. Could this be the light at the end of the tunnel for cryptocurrencies?</p>
<h2>Hawkish Fed Dims Litecoin Rally, But A Fractal Gives Hope</h2>
<p>After a stellar month leading the market with 40% returns for November, Litecoin has given back nearly half of that thus far in December. </p>
<p>LTC had been on a tear, outperforming top coins like Bitcoin and Ethereum, and clawed its way closer toward making it back into the top ten cryptocurrencies ranked by market cap. </p>

<p>But the greater market pullback stemming from a <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-volatility-explodes-fed-reveals-50-basis/">hawkish Fed meeting</a> this month, caused a failure to liftoff in Litecoin.  </p>
<p>However, the discovery of a price action fractal in LTCUSD could suggest this recent pullback wasn’t necessarily a failure, but a refueling of sorts — before taking off in an even stronger rally. </p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-large wp-image-513140 aligncenter" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/2022-12-20-17.33.24-860x531.jpg" alt="2022-12-20 17.33.24" width="860" height="531" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/2022-12-20-17.33.24-860x531.jpg 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/2022-12-20-17.33.24-460x284.jpg 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/2022-12-20-17.33.24-768x474.jpg 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/2022-12-20-17.33.24-750x463.jpg 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/2022-12-20-17.33.24-1140x704.jpg 1140w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/2022-12-20-17.33.24.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" /></p>

<h2>Comparing Price Action Then Vs Now: Will Bulls Get A Break?</h2>
<p>The fractal begins on Black Thursday in March 2020 — a black swan event few saw coming. Litecoin rebounded and the fractal formed. </p>
<p>Unlike Bitcoin, which made a lower low during the FTX, LTCUSD hasn’t, and instead has followed the same pattern from 2020 almost flawlessly. </p>
<p>Price following the fractal further could lead to some minor continued downside, but ultimately holds at resistance turned support. If the current pullback proves to be a retest and holds, a more obvious rally could materialize.</p>

<p>Failure would almost certainly send Litecoin back toward 2018 lows and potentially beyond, making the fractal among one of Litecoin bulls’ best hope for a redemption rally.</p>
<p>Importantly, a concurrent reversal taking place in the LTCBTC and LTCETH trading pairs appear to indicate strength in the altcoin relative to the top two crypto assets. However, there is no telling what this might mean for the overall market at this time.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/iStock-893488994-460x307.jpeg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cardano (ADA) Falls Below Critical Point, Why There Is More Pain To Come</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/analysis/ada/cardano-ada-falls-below-critical-point/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Best Owie]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 17:29:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[ADA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADA price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[adausd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADAUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=513039</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Cardano (ADA) remains one of the hardest-hit cryptocurrencies even before the bear market was officially in full bloom. The digital asset which had seen returns higher than 1,000% during the 2021 bull run would eventually see almost the entirety of those gains wiped out. Despite this, it had been able to maintain above a critical point for a long time. However, the cryptocurrency has now lost its footing, leading to an incredibly bearish outlook for the asset. ADA Price Falls Below $0.3 For a digital asset such as ADA, maintaining above $0.3 was important for it at a time when assets in the space needed to hold on to their critical support levels. Most of Cardano’s investors had thrown their hat in the ring to hold the bears off at $0.3, something they succeeded at until the FTX collapse happened. Related Reading: Binance Smart Chain User Activity Tanks, Why BNB Price Could Suffer Since the contagion had continued to spread across the space, ADA was, as expected, caught in the crossfire. Last week, it had eventually given way to the bears which had then dragged it down below $.30 for the second time in two months. However, this time around, there was no recovery to save the digital asset and it would continue to spiral down. It has now lost more than 14% of its value in the space of a week and is down by almost $0.050 in the same time frame.  ADA drops to $0.25 &#124; Source: ADAUSD on TradingView.com Will Cardano Survive? Although Cardano’s current price path follows the general market price action, it is still far below most of the market in this regard. It is trading well below its 100-day moving average of $0.4 which puts it on a more bearish path compared to the rest of the market. Add in the constant negativity spewed at the digital asset on social media and it is a recipe for disaster. ADA falls below 100-day MA &#124; Source: Barchart It is also possible that the market bottom has not been established yet. If this is to be believed and bitcoin were to drop to $12,000, or as low as $10,000 as predicted by some in the space, then it could mean that ADA holders will record more decline in the value of their holdings. If the market were to decline another 30%, then ADA price could drop as low as $0.10 before the next bull rally begins. Related Reading: Ethereum Price Balks As Dormant Whales Reactivate Nevertheless, the Cardano community holds on to its bullish forecast for the cryptocurrency. According to Price Estimates on Coinmarketcap, there is an expected 84% growth for ADA by the end of 2022 and the projections get higher over a longer timeframe into January 2023. If the estimates come to pass, then ADA could be seeing prices of $0.5 in January. ADA is changing hands at a price of $0.25 at the time of this writing. It is currently down more than 91% from its September 2021 all-time high of $3.10. Featured image from The Coin Republic, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="p2">Cardano (ADA) remains one of the hardest-hit cryptocurrencies even before the bear market was officially in full bloom. The digital asset which had seen returns higher than 1,000% during the 2021 bull run would eventually see almost the entirety of those gains wiped out. Despite this, it had been able to maintain above a critical point for a long time. However, the cryptocurrency has now lost its footing, leading to an incredibly bearish outlook for the asset.</p>
<h2 class="p2">ADA Price Falls Below $0.3</h2>
<p class="p2">For a digital asset such as ADA, maintaining above $0.3 was important for it at a time when assets in the space needed to hold on to their critical support levels. Most of Cardano’s investors had thrown their hat in the ring to hold the bears off at $0.3, something they succeeded at until the FTX collapse happened.</p>

<p class="p2">Since the contagion had continued to spread across the space, ADA was, as expected, caught in the crossfire. Last week, it had eventually given way to the bears which had then dragged it down below $.30 for the second time in two months.</p>
<p class="p2">However, this time around, there was no recovery to save the digital asset and it would continue to spiral down. It has now lost more than 14% of its value in the space of a week and is down by almost $0.050 in the same time frame. </p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/7Ry7lTAj/" alt="Cardano (ADA) price chart from TradingView.com" width="3284" height="1760" /></p>

<h2 class="p2">Will Cardano Survive?</h2>
<p class="p2">Although Cardano’s current price path follows the general market price action, it is still far below most of the market in this regard. It is trading well below its 100-day moving average of $0.4 which puts it on a more bearish path compared to the rest of the market. Add in the constant negativity spewed at the digital asset on social media and it is a recipe for disaster.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-513041 size-medium" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Screen-Shot-2022-12-20-at-11.28.01-460x123.png" alt="Cardano (ADA) falls below 100-day moving average" width="460" height="123" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Screen-Shot-2022-12-20-at-11.28.01-460x123.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Screen-Shot-2022-12-20-at-11.28.01-860x229.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Screen-Shot-2022-12-20-at-11.28.01-768x205.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Screen-Shot-2022-12-20-at-11.28.01-1536x410.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Screen-Shot-2022-12-20-at-11.28.01-2048x546.png 2048w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Screen-Shot-2022-12-20-at-11.28.01-750x200.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Screen-Shot-2022-12-20-at-11.28.01-1140x304.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px" /></p>

<p class="p2">It is also possible that the market bottom has not been established yet. If this is to be believed and bitcoin were to drop to $12,000, or as low as $10,000 as predicted by some in the space, then it could mean that ADA holders will record more decline in the value of their holdings. If the market were to decline another 30%, then ADA price could drop as low as $0.10 before the next bull rally begins.</p>

<p class="p2">Nevertheless, the Cardano community holds on to its bullish forecast for the cryptocurrency. According to <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/cardano/price-estimates/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">Price Estimates on Coinmarketcap</a>, there is an expected 84% growth for ADA by the end of 2022 and the projections get higher over a longer timeframe into January 2023. If the estimates come to pass, then ADA could be seeing prices of $0.5 in January.</p>
<p class="p2">ADA is changing hands at a price of $0.25 at the time of this writing. It is currently down more than 91% from its September 2021 all-time high of $3.10.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Cardano--460x259.jpeg" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Still &#8220;Overvalued&#8221; According To NVT Ratio</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-overvalued-according-nvt-ratio/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hououin Kyouma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 15:31:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin bearish]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin NVT Ratio]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Overvalued]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=513062</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[On-chain data shows signs aren&#8217;t looking good for Bitcoin as the NVT ratio is indicating that the crypto is still overvalued right now. Bitcoin NVT Ratio Continues To Be At High Values As pointed out by an analyst in a CryptoQuant post, BTC is currently overvalued from an on-chain perspective. The &#8220;Network Value to Transactions (NVT) ratio&#8221; is an indicator that measures the ratio between the market cap of Bitcoin and its transaction volume (both in USD). This ratio judges whether the current value of Bitcoin (that is, the market cap) is fair or not, by comparing it against the network&#8217;s ability to transact coins right now (the transaction volume). When the metric has a high value, it means the price of BTC is high compared to the volume, and thus the coin could be inside a bubble at the moment. On the other hand, low values suggest BTC may be undervalued as the chain has a high ability to transact coins (in comparison to the market cap) right now. Related Reading: Litecoin Continues To Slide, Now Below Shiba Inu In Market Cap Here is a chart that shows the trend in the Bitcoin NVT ratio over the past year: Looks like the metric's value has been pretty high during recent weeks &#124; Source: CryptoQuant As the above graph highlights, the Bitcoin NVT ratio jumped up following the LUNA collapse back in May of this year and has since mostly stayed at similar or higher levels. This means that despite the price observing multiple crashes in the period, the coin&#8217;s value still became increasingly overvalued as volumes across the market sharply dropped. Even after the FTX crash, which has delivered another solid blow to the crypto&#8217;s market cap, the metric has only climbed higher as it has registered a new high for the year recently. BTC has only been getting more and more overpriced as the bear has gotten deeper, suggesting the dire state of the market in terms of trading volumes. Related Reading: Bitcoin Bearish Signal: ‘Mid-Term’ Holders Show Signs Of Dumping The quant also notes that the number of UTXOs in loss (basically the amount of wallets/investors in loss), has been consistently rising throughout the bear. The metric continues to ride on a constant uptrend &#124; Source: CryptoQuant Both these signs are certainly not in the favor of Bitcoin and may imply there is further pain ahead for investors. &#8220;A more extended bear market could be seen as a potential risk that could add selling pressure,&#8221; explains the analyst. BTC Price At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading around $16,800, down 5% in the last week. The price action in the asset seems to have been stale in the last few days &#124; Source: BTCUSD on TradingView Featured image from Maxim Hopman on Unsplash.com, charts from TradingView.com, CryptoQuant.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On-chain data shows signs aren&#8217;t looking good for Bitcoin as the NVT ratio is indicating that the crypto is still overvalued right now.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin NVT Ratio Continues To Be At High Values</h2>
<p>As pointed out by an analyst in a CryptoQuant <a href="https://cryptoquant.com/quicktake/63a07ede36ec775f47466f3b-BTC-Evaluation-and-Trading-Perspective-from-On-Chain" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">post</a>, BTC is currently overvalued from an on-chain perspective. The &#8220;<a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-bullish-signal-nvt-ratio-btc-undervalued/">Network Value to Transactions (NVT) ratio</a>&#8221; is an indicator that measures the ratio between the market cap of Bitcoin and its transaction volume (both in USD).</p>
<p>This ratio judges whether the current value of Bitcoin (that is, the market cap) is fair or not, by comparing it against the network&#8217;s ability to transact coins right now (the transaction volume). When the metric has a high value, it means the price of BTC is high compared to the volume, and thus the coin could be inside a bubble at the moment. On the other hand, low values suggest BTC may be undervalued as the chain has a high ability to transact coins (in comparison to the market cap) right now.</p>

<p>Here is a chart that shows the trend in the Bitcoin NVT ratio over the past year:</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone aligncenter" src="https://img.cryptoquant.com/165524/quicktake/elWHFI3Ko_4ade16ab9a5ca400aa560adf3c6692e22209f53fe4253aa66145fc2399c8b36f.png" alt="Bitcoin NVT ratio" width="1778" height="1125" /></p>

<p>As the above graph highlights, the Bitcoin NVT ratio jumped up following the <a href="https://newsbtc.com/terra-luna/did-celsius-withdrawal-trigger-the-terra-luna-collapse-claim-response/">LUNA collapse</a> back in May of this year and has since mostly stayed at similar or higher levels. This means that despite the price observing multiple crashes in the period, the coin&#8217;s value still became increasingly overvalued as volumes across the market sharply dropped.</p>
<p>Even after the <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/company/what-happens-if-crypto-exchange-binance-bust-like-ftx-and-terra/">FTX crash</a>, which has delivered another solid blow to the crypto&#8217;s market cap, the metric has only climbed higher as it has registered a new high for the year recently. BTC has only been getting more and more overpriced as the bear has gotten deeper, suggesting the dire state of the market in terms of trading volumes.</p>

<p>The quant also notes that the number of UTXOs in loss (basically the amount of wallets/investors in loss), has been consistently rising throughout the bear.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="aligncenter" src="https://img.cryptoquant.com/165524/quicktake/hlwwoct_4ade16ab9a5ca400aa560adf3c6692e22209f53fe4253aa66145fc2399c8b36f.png" alt="Bitcoin UTXOs in Loss" width="1789" height="1125" /></p>

<p>Both these signs are certainly not in the favor of Bitcoin and may imply there is further pain ahead for investors. &#8220;A more extended bear market could be seen as a potential risk that could add selling pressure,&#8221; explains the analyst.</p>
<h2>BTC Price</h2>
<p>At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading around $16,800, down 5% in the last week.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone wp-image-513090 size-large aligncenter" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/chart-22-860x481.png" alt="Bitcoin Price Chart" width="860" height="481" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/chart-22-860x481.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/chart-22-460x257.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/chart-22-768x430.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/chart-22-750x420.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/chart-22.png 972w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" /></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/maxim-hopman-fiXLQXAhCfk-unsplash-2-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
