<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"

	xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
	xmlns:geo="http://www.w3.org/2003/01/geo/wgs84_pos#"
	>

<channel>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.newsbtc.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<description>Bitcoin &#38; Cryptocurrency News Today</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 07:54:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-cropped-favicon.png?fit=32%2C32</url>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
<site xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">221170450</site>	<item>
		<title>Voyager Sells 1.4 Trillion Shiba Inu, But There&#8217;s Good News For SHIB</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/voyager-sells-1-4-trillion-shiba-inu-but-good-news/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jake Simmons]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 08:25:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Shiba Inu]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIB]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shibarium]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIBUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Voyager]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=547284</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[In a recent revelation, Lookonchain, the on-chain analysis service, reported that Voyager Digital, the now-bankrupt crypto lending platform, has been offloading its crypto assets on Coinbase in recent days. Over the past four days, the defunct lender has sold 49 different crypto assets, netting approximately $63 million. For the SHIB army the most notable sale was the 1.4 trillion Shiba Inu tokens, which amounted to nearly $14.4 million. Beyond SHIB, Voyager&#8217;s sales included significant amounts of Bitcoin (BTC), Ethereum (ETH), Chainlink (LINK), Polygon (MATIC), and Decentraland (MANA). &#8220;Voyager has been selling assets on #Coinbase for the past 4 days and has sold 49 tokens for ~$63M. Including: 781 BTC ($23M); 9,570 ETH ($17.6M); 1.4T SHIB ($14.4M); 234,660 LINK ($1.74M); 1.87M MATIC ($1.27M); 3M MANA ($1.1M);&#8221;, Lookonchain tweeted. The sales have significantly reduced Voyager&#8217;s crypto holdings. However, they haven&#8217;t entirely emptied their coffers. The on-chain analysis service further detailed Voyager&#8217;s remaining assets: &#8220;Voyager currently holds $11.3M worth of assets, including: 52.4M VGX ($8.27M); 55 BTC ($1.62M); 537K KNC ($371K); 1.18 FTM ($286K); 20.7M STMX ($140K); 4.85M GALA ($111K).&#8221; Related Reading: Shiba Inu (SHIB) Poised For Golden Cross – How Will Prices React? While the sales have drawn attention, there&#8217;s a silver lining for the SHIB community. According to Lookonchain&#8217;s data, Voyager&#8217;s SHIB holdings have been completely liquidated. Thus, Voyager&#8217;s SHIB holding have gone to zero, suggesting a potential reduction in sell pressure on the Shiba Inu token in the future. Shiba Inu Price Shows Resilience Despite the massive sell-off by Voyager, SHIB&#8217;s price remained resilient. The token has seen a surge of over 14.2% in the past week. This bullish momentum is largely attributed to the forthcoming Shibarium mainnet launch at the Blockchain Future Conference, starting today. Investors seem optimistic about SHIB&#8217;s potential, believing that if the layer-2 scaling solution delivers on its promises, the SHIB token could witness even more substantial gains. Related Reading: Shiba Inu Steals The Spotlight, Leaving Bitcoin Behind In A Week Of Price Surges At press time, the Shiba Inu price stood at $0.00001019 after finding support at the 38.2% Fibonacci retracement level ($0.00001007). The key resistance on a daily basis is currently the 50% Fibonacci level at $0.00001121. Should a breakout occur, SHIB could rise 21% from its current price to follow through to the 61.8% Fibonacci level. Major resistance is expected at this price level ($0.00001235). The RSI on a daily basis has been in an ascending trend since the annual low on June 10 and was at 65 at press time. This leaves the SHIB bulls with further room to run. For an explosive double-digit move, the RSI should enter deep overbought territory. For investors, today&#8217;s or tomorrow&#8217;s Shibarium launch should be taken with a grain of salt. As usual for the crypto market, it could be a &#8220;buy the rumor, sell the news&#8221; event, as the impact of the launch might only be seen in the long term over the coming months. In this case, the 200-day EMA at $0.00000938 will be a key support to defend for the bulls. Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In a recent revelation, Lookonchain, the on-chain analysis service, <a href="https://twitter.com/lookonchain/status/1691272802077429761" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">reported</a> that Voyager Digital, the now-bankrupt crypto lending platform, has been offloading its crypto assets on Coinbase in recent days. Over the past four days, the defunct lender has sold 49 different crypto assets, netting approximately $63 million. For the SHIB army the most notable sale was the 1.4 trillion Shiba Inu tokens, which amounted to nearly $14.4 million.</p>
<p>Beyond SHIB, Voyager&#8217;s sales included significant amounts of Bitcoin (BTC), Ethereum (ETH), Chainlink (LINK), Polygon (MATIC), and Decentraland (MANA). &#8220;Voyager has been selling assets on #Coinbase for the past 4 days and has sold 49 tokens for ~$63M. Including: 781 BTC ($23M); 9,570 ETH ($17.6M); 1.4T SHIB ($14.4M); 234,660 LINK ($1.74M); 1.87M MATIC ($1.27M); 3M MANA ($1.1M);&#8221;, Lookonchain tweeted.</p>
<p>The sales have significantly reduced Voyager&#8217;s crypto holdings. However, they haven&#8217;t entirely emptied their coffers. The on-chain analysis service further detailed Voyager&#8217;s remaining assets: &#8220;Voyager currently holds $11.3M worth of assets, including: 52.4M VGX ($8.27M); 55 BTC ($1.62M); 537K KNC ($371K); 1.18 FTM ($286K); 20.7M STMX ($140K); 4.85M GALA ($111K).&#8221;</p>

<p>While the sales have drawn attention, there&#8217;s a silver lining for the SHIB community. According to Lookonchain&#8217;s data, Voyager&#8217;s SHIB holdings have been completely liquidated. Thus, Voyager&#8217;s SHIB holding have gone to zero, suggesting a potential reduction in sell pressure on the Shiba Inu token in the future.</p>
<h2>Shiba Inu Price Shows Resilience</h2>
<p>Despite the massive sell-off by Voyager, SHIB&#8217;s price remained resilient. The token has seen a surge of over 14.2% in the past week. This bullish momentum is largely attributed to the forthcoming Shibarium mainnet launch at the Blockchain Future Conference, starting today. Investors seem optimistic about SHIB&#8217;s potential, believing that if the layer-2 scaling solution delivers on its promises, the SHIB token could witness even more substantial gains.</p>

<p>At press time, the Shiba Inu price stood at $0.00001019 after finding support at the 38.2% Fibonacci retracement level ($0.00001007). The key resistance on a daily basis is currently the 50% Fibonacci level at $0.00001121. Should a breakout occur, SHIB could rise 21% from its current price to follow through to the 61.8% Fibonacci level. Major resistance is expected at this price level ($0.00001235).</p>
<p>The RSI on a daily basis has been in an ascending trend since the annual low on June 10 and was at 65 at press time. This leaves the SHIB bulls with further room to run. For an explosive double-digit move, the RSI should enter deep overbought territory.</p>
<p>For investors, today&#8217;s or tomorrow&#8217;s Shibarium launch should be taken with a grain of salt. As usual for the crypto market, it could be a &#8220;buy the rumor, sell the news&#8221; event, as the impact of the launch might only be seen in the long term over the coming months. In this case, the 200-day EMA at $0.00000938 will be a key support to defend for the bulls.</p>
<img decoding="async" fetchpriority="high" class="wp-image-547296 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SHIBUSD_2023-08-15_09-37-56.png?resize=3628%2C1672" alt="Shiba Inu price" width="3628" height="1672" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SHIBUSD_2023-08-15_09-37-56.png?resize=3628%2C1672?w=3628 3628w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SHIBUSD_2023-08-15_09-37-56.png?resize=3628%2C1672?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SHIBUSD_2023-08-15_09-37-56.png?resize=3628%2C1672?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SHIBUSD_2023-08-15_09-37-56.png?resize=3628%2C1672?w=860 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SHIBUSD_2023-08-15_09-37-56.png?resize=3628%2C1672?w=1536 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SHIBUSD_2023-08-15_09-37-56.png?resize=3628%2C1672?w=2048 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SHIBUSD_2023-08-15_09-37-56.png?resize=3628%2C1672?w=750 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SHIBUSD_2023-08-15_09-37-56.png?resize=3628%2C1672?w=1140 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SHIBUSD_2023-08-15_09-37-56.png?resize=3628%2C1672?w=3000 3000w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" loading="lazy" data-recalc-dims="1"/>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/What-is-SHIB_-1.png?fit=460%2C267" width="460" height="267" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">547284</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Toncoin Solid Climb: Price Spikes By 21% In Surprise Burst</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/all/toncoin-solid-climb-price-spikes-by-21-in-surprise-burst/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 07:37:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[All]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[atlcoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price action]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ton price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Toncoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=547277</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Toncoin (TON) recently saw a remarkable breakthrough, shattering its month-long consolidation phase and providing a glimmer of hope for traders. The coin, which had been confined within a price range of $1.31 to $1.49, broke free from this range-bound pattern, but not without facing its share of challenges. During the consolidation phase, Toncoin exhibited multiple instances of attempting to breach the crucial $1.50 mark. These efforts sparked optimism among bullish market participants, hinting at a potential upward trajectory.  Related Reading: Toncoin (TON) Throws Weight Around To Lead Weekend Top 20 With 22% Rally However, despite their persistence, the coin fell short of breaking through the psychological barrier and ultimately retreated below it. Toncoin Bears Stand Strong But Caution Persists The latest price data reveals that Toncoin reached $1.46, accompanied by a 4.7% rally in the past 24 hours and an impressive seven-day surge of 20.9%. While these numbers might appear promising, a deeper examination of market dynamics suggests a more cautious sentiment among traders and investors. Toncoin price action today. Source: Coingecko The enduring resistance from bearish market forces underscores the prevailing sentiment that the cryptocurrency market might not be fully prepared to sustain an extended climb beyond the $1.50 mark at this juncture. Despite the spirited efforts by the bullish side, the bears have managed to maintain their stronghold, prompting a sense of prudence among market participants. Visualizing the price movement and volatility, a chart in a recent price report juxtaposes Toncoin&#8217;s fluctuations over the past 24 hours with its movement throughout the past week. Toncoin (TON) is currently trading at $1.455. Chart: TradingView.com  Bollinger Bands, represented by gray bands on the chart, indicate the volatility of both daily and weekly price actions. A wider gray area signifies higher volatility, emphasizing the market&#8217;s response to Toncoin&#8217;s price shifts. Volume And Circulating Supply Dynamics  The recent surge in Toncoin&#8217;s trading volume, climbing by an impressive 60.0% over the past week, aligns directionally with the overall circulating supply of the cryptocurrency. Notably, the circulating supply expanded by 0.29%, reaching a total of 3.44 billion. This synchronicity between trading volume and circulating supply underscores the intricate interplay of supply and demand dynamics in influencing Toncoin&#8217;s market performance. As Toncoin breaks free from its month-long consolidation and tests the $1.50 mark, the market is at a crossroads, torn between bullish aspirations and prevailing bearish resistance. Related Reading: XRP Volume Jolt: How Did The $3 Billion Surge Impact Price Action? The cryptocurrency&#8217;s recent price movements highlight the nuanced nature of its journey, where small fluctuations carry significant implications for traders and investors alike.  While the path ahead remains uncertain, market participants continue to watch closely for signs of sustainable momentum that could propel Toncoin to new heights. (This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk). Featured image from Shutterstock ]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Toncoin (TON) recently saw a remarkable breakthrough, shattering its month-long consolidation phase and providing a glimmer of hope for traders. </p>
<p>The coin, which had been confined within a price range of $1.31 to $1.49, broke free from this range-bound pattern, but not without facing its share of challenges.</p>
<p>During the consolidation phase, Toncoin exhibited multiple instances of attempting to breach the crucial $1.50 mark. These efforts sparked optimism among bullish market participants, hinting at a potential upward trajectory. </p>

<p>However, despite their persistence, the coin fell short of breaking through the psychological barrier and ultimately retreated below it.</p>
<h2><strong>Toncoin Bears Stand Strong But Caution Persists</strong></h2>
<p>The latest <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/toncoin" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">price data</a> reveals that Toncoin reached $1.46, accompanied by a 4.7% rally in the past 24 hours and an impressive seven-day surge of 20.9%. While these numbers might appear promising, a deeper examination of market dynamics suggests a more cautious sentiment among traders and investors.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-547292" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-80.png?resize=946%2C67" alt="" width="946" height="67" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-80.png?resize=946%2C67?w=946 946w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-80.png?resize=946%2C67?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-80.png?resize=946%2C67?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-80.png?resize=946%2C67?w=860 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-80.png?resize=946%2C67?w=750 750w" sizes="(max-width: 946px) 100vw, 946px" loading="lazy" data-recalc-dims="1"/></p>

<p>The enduring resistance from bearish market forces underscores the prevailing sentiment that the cryptocurrency market might not be fully prepared to sustain an extended climb beyond the $1.50 mark at this juncture. </p>
<p>Despite the spirited efforts by the bullish side, the bears have managed to maintain their stronghold, prompting a sense of prudence among market participants.</p>
<p>Visualizing the price movement and volatility, a chart in a recent <a href="https://www.benzinga.com/markets/cryptocurrency/23/08/33841955/toncoin-rises-more-than-3-in-24-hours" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">price report </a>juxtaposes Toncoin&#8217;s fluctuations over the past 24 hours with its movement throughout the past week. </p>
<p><img decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/UHkcvdhh/" width="1835" height="893" loading="lazy"/></p>

<p>Bollinger Bands, represented by gray bands on the chart, indicate the volatility of both daily and weekly price actions. A wider gray area signifies higher volatility, emphasizing the market&#8217;s response to Toncoin&#8217;s price shifts.</p>
<h2><strong>Volume And Circulating Supply Dynamics </strong></h2>
<p>The recent surge in Toncoin&#8217;s trading volume, climbing by an impressive 60.0% over the past week, aligns directionally with the overall circulating supply of the cryptocurrency. Notably, the circulating supply expanded by 0.29%, reaching a total of 3.44 billion. </p>
<p>This synchronicity between trading volume and circulating supply underscores the intricate interplay of supply and demand dynamics in influencing Toncoin&#8217;s market performance.</p>
<p>As Toncoin breaks free from its month-long consolidation and tests the $1.50 mark, the market is at a crossroads, torn between bullish aspirations and prevailing <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/TONUSDT/?exchange=KUCOIN" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">bearish resistance</a>. </p>

<p>The cryptocurrency&#8217;s recent price movements highlight the nuanced nature of its journey, where small fluctuations carry significant implications for traders and investors alike. </p>
<p>While the path ahead remains uncertain, market participants continue to watch closely for signs of sustainable momentum that could propel Toncoin to new heights.</p>
<p><em>(This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk).</em></p>
<p><em>Featured image from Shutterstock </em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-79.png?fit=460%2C261" width="460" height="261" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">547277</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>XRP Price at Potentially Significant Turning Point, Key Support Nearby</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/xrp-price-turning-point-0-62/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 05:18:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrp]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrpusdt]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=547271</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Ripple’s token price is consolidating above $0.620 against the US Dollar. XRP price might start a decent increase if there is a clear move above $0.650. Ripple’s token price is moving lower from the $0.6650 resistance against the US dollar. The price is now trading below $0.65 and the 100 simple moving average (4 hours). There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.628 on the 4-hour chart of the XRP/USD pair (data source from Kraken). The pair might continue to decline if there is no move above $0.63 and $0.65. Ripple’s Token Price Dips Again After a recovery wave, Ripple’s XRP struggled to clear the $0.6650 resistance against the US Dollar. A high was formed near $0.6654 before the price started a fresh decline, similar to Bitcoin and Ethereum. There was a move below the $0.650 pivot level. The price declined below the 50% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $0.5926 swing low to the $0.6654 high. The price even declined below the $0.635 support zone. XRP is now trading below $0.65 and the 100 simple moving average (4 hours). There is also a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.628 on the 4-hour chart of the XRP/USD pair. Initial resistance on the upside is near the $0.628 zone and the trend line. The next major resistance is near the $0.650 level and the 100 simple moving average (4 hours). The main resistance is now forming near the $0.6650 zone. Source: XRPUSD on TradingView.com A successful break above the $0.6650 resistance level might send the price toward the $0.70 resistance. Any more gains might call for a test of the $0.720 resistance. More Losses in XRP? If ripple fails to clear the $0.650 resistance zone, it could start another decline. Initial support on the downside is near the $0.620 zone and the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $0.5926 swing low to the $0.6654 high. The next major support is near $0.60. If there is a downside break and a close below the $0.60 level, XRP’s price could extend losses. In the stated case, the price could retest the $0.585 support zone. Technical Indicators 4-Hours MACD – The MACD for XRP/USD is now losing pace in the bearish zone. 4-Hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for XRP/USD is now below the 50 level. Major Support Levels – $0.62, $0.60, and $0.585. Major Resistance Levels – $0.628, $0.650, and $0.665.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>Ripple’s token price is consolidating above $0.620 against the US Dollar. XRP price might start a decent increase if there is a clear move above $0.650.</em></p>
<ul>
<li>Ripple’s token price is moving lower from the $0.6650 resistance against the US dollar.</li>
<li>The price is now trading below $0.65 and the 100 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.628 on the 4-hour chart of the XRP/USD pair (data source from Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair might continue to decline if there is no move above $0.63 and $0.65.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Ripple’s Token Price Dips Again</h2>
<p>After a recovery wave, Ripple’s XRP struggled to clear the $0.6650 resistance against the US Dollar. A high was formed near $0.6654 before the price started a fresh decline, similar to <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-muted-29650/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Bitcoin</a> and <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-plunge-to-1800/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Ethereum</a>.</p>
<p>There was a move below the $0.650 pivot level. The price declined below the 50% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $0.5926 swing low to the $0.6654 high. The price even declined below the $0.635 support zone.</p>
<p>XRP is now trading below $0.65 and the 100 simple moving average (4 hours). There is also a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.628 on the 4-hour chart of the XRP/USD pair.</p>
<p>Initial resistance on the upside is near the $0.628 zone and the trend line. The next major resistance is near the $0.650 level and the 100 simple moving average (4 hours). The main resistance is now forming near the $0.6650 zone.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-547272" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/XRP_Price.png?resize=1024%2C468" alt="XRP Price" width="1024" height="468" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/XRP_Price.png?resize=1024%2C468?w=1835 1835w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/XRP_Price.png?resize=1024%2C468?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/XRP_Price.png?resize=1024%2C468?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/XRP_Price.png?resize=1024%2C468?w=860 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/XRP_Price.png?resize=1024%2C468?w=1536 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/XRP_Price.png?resize=1024%2C468?w=750 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/XRP_Price.png?resize=1024%2C468?w=1140 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" data-recalc-dims="1"/></p>
<p>Source: <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/XRPUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">XRPUSD on TradingView.com</a></p>
<p>A successful break above the $0.6650 resistance level might send the price toward the $0.70 resistance. Any more gains might call for a test of the $0.720 resistance.</p>
<h2>More Losses in XRP?</h2>
<p>If ripple fails to clear the $0.650 resistance zone, it could start another decline. Initial support on the downside is near the $0.620 zone and the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $0.5926 swing low to the $0.6654 high.</p>
<p>The next major support is near $0.60. If there is a downside break and a close below the $0.60 level, XRP’s price could extend losses. In the stated case, the price could retest the $0.585 support zone.</p>
<p>Technical Indicators</p>
<p>4-Hours MACD – The MACD for XRP/USD is now losing pace in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>4-Hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for XRP/USD is now below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Levels – $0.62, $0.60, and $0.585.</p>
<p>Major Resistance Levels – $0.628, $0.650, and $0.665.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/shutterstock_262478576-1.jpg?fit=460%2C368" width="460" height="368" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">547271</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum Price Plunge To $1,800 On The Horizon, As Bulls Show Weak Hands</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-plunge-to-1800/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 04:44:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=547267</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Ethereum price is struggling to rise above the $1,850 zone against the US Dollar. ETH could drop toward the $1,800 support in the near term. Ethereum is trading in a range below the $1,850 and $1,860 resistance levels. The price is trading below $1,850 and the 100-hourly Simple Moving Average. There is a key contracting triangle forming with support near $1,840 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD (data feed via Kraken). The pair could drop toward $1,800 if there is no close above the $1,860 resistance. Ethereum Price Dips Again Ethereum’s price remained below the $1,860 resistance zone and reacted to the downside. ETH topped near $1,853 and declined below the $1,840 level, similar to Bitcoin. A low is formed near $1,837 and the pair is now consolidating losses. It climbed above the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the recent decline from the $1,853 swing high to the $1,837 low. Ether is now trading below $1,850 and the 100-hourly Simple Moving Average. There is also a key contracting triangle forming with support near $1,840 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD. On the upside, the price might face resistance near the $1,845 level or the 100-hourly Simple Moving Average. Source: ETHUSD on TradingView.com The 50% Fib retracement level of the recent decline from the $1,853 swing high to the $1,837 low is also near $1,845. The first key resistance is near the $1,850 level. The next key resistance is near the $1,860 level. A close above the $1,860 level could send the price toward $1,880. Any more gains might send the price toward the $1,920 pivot level, above which the price could rise toward the $2,000 zone. More Losses in ETH? If Ethereum fails to clear the $1,850 resistance, it could continue to move down. Initial support on the downside is near the $1,840 level or the triangle lower trend line. The first major support is near the $1,835 zone. If the bulls fail to protect the $1,835 support, there could be more losses. The next major support is near the $1,800 support level. Any more losses might send the price toward the $1,740 level in the near term. Technical Indicators Hourly MACD – The MACD for ETH/USD is losing momentum in the bearish zone. Hourly RSI &#8211; The RSI for ETH/USD is now below the 50 level. Major Support Level – $1,835 Major Resistance Level – $1,850]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>Ethereum price is struggling to rise above the $1,850 zone against the US Dollar. ETH could drop toward the $1,800 support in the near term.</em></p>
<ul>
<li>Ethereum is trading in a range below the $1,850 and $1,860 resistance levels.</li>
<li>The price is trading below $1,850 and the 100-hourly Simple Moving Average.</li>
<li>There is a key contracting triangle forming with support near $1,840 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD (data feed via Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could drop toward $1,800 if there is no close above the $1,860 resistance.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Ethereum Price Dips Again</h2>
<p>Ethereum’s price remained below the $1,860 resistance zone and reacted to the downside. ETH topped near $1,853 and declined below the $1,840 level, similar to <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-muted-29650/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Bitcoin</a>.</p>
<p>A low is formed near $1,837 and the pair is now consolidating losses. It climbed above the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the recent decline from the $1,853 swing high to the $1,837 low. Ether is now trading below $1,850 and the 100-hourly Simple Moving Average.</p>
<p>There is also a key contracting triangle forming with support near $1,840 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD. On the upside, the price might face resistance near the $1,845 level or the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-rebounds-1830/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">100-hourly Simple Moving Average</a>.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-547268" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Ethereum-3.png?resize=1024%2C468" alt="Ethereum Price" width="1024" height="468" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Ethereum-3.png?resize=1024%2C468?w=1835 1835w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Ethereum-3.png?resize=1024%2C468?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Ethereum-3.png?resize=1024%2C468?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Ethereum-3.png?resize=1024%2C468?w=860 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Ethereum-3.png?resize=1024%2C468?w=1536 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Ethereum-3.png?resize=1024%2C468?w=750 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Ethereum-3.png?resize=1024%2C468?w=1140 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" data-recalc-dims="1"/></p>
<p>Source: <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/ETHUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">ETHUSD on TradingView.com</a></p>
<p>The 50% Fib retracement level of the recent decline from the $1,853 swing high to the $1,837 low is also near $1,845. The first key resistance is near the $1,850 level. The next key resistance is near the $1,860 level. A close above the $1,860 level could send the price toward $1,880. Any more gains might send the price toward the $1,920 pivot level, above which the price could rise toward the $2,000 zone.</p>
<h2>More Losses in ETH?</h2>
<p>If Ethereum fails to clear the $1,850 resistance, it could continue to move down. Initial support on the downside is near the $1,840 level or the triangle lower trend line.</p>
<p>The first major support is near the $1,835 zone. If the bulls fail to protect the $1,835 support, there could be more losses. The next major support is near the $1,800 support level. Any more losses might send the price toward the $1,740 level in the near term.</p>
<p>Technical Indicators</p>
<p>Hourly MACD<strong> – </strong>The MACD for ETH/USD is losing momentum in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>Hourly RSI<strong> &#8211; </strong>The RSI for ETH/USD is now below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Level – $1,835</p>
<p>Major Resistance Level – $1,850</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/shutterstock_1418423411.jpg?fit=460%2C307" width="460" height="307" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">547267</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Price Relatively Muted &#8211; What Could Trigger A Sharp Decline?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-muted-29650/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 03:57:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xbtusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=547264</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin price is still struggling below the $29,650 zone. BTC could gain bearish momentum if there is a close below the $29,100 support. Bitcoin is showing a few bearish signs below the $29,650 zone. The price is trading below $29,400 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average. There is a short-term bullish trend line forming with support near $29,320 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Kraken). The pair could continue to move down if it breaks the $29,250 and $29,100 support levels. Bitcoin Price Stuck Below $30K Bitcoin price remained well below the $30,000 resistance zone. BTC attempted a short-term upward move but the bears were active near the $29,650 resistance zone. A high was formed near $29,657 before there was a fresh decline to $29,250. The price is now consolidating and trading above the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the recent decline from the $29,657 swing high to the $29,250 low. Bitcoin is now trading below $29,400 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average. There is also a short-term bullish trend line forming with support near $29,320 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair. Immediate resistance is near the $29,450 level. It is close to the 50% Fib retracement level of the recent decline from the $29,657 swing high to the $29,250 low. The next major resistance is near $29,500. The main resistance is now forming near the $29,650 level. Source: BTCUSD on TradingView.com A close above the $29,650 resistance could send the price toward the $30,000 resistance zone. Any more gains might change the trend and the price might rise toward $30,500. In the stated case, the price could even rise toward $31,200 or even $32,200 in the coming days. More Losses In BTC? If Bitcoin fails to clear the $29,650 resistance, it could continue to move down. Immediate support on the downside is near the trend line. The next major support is near the $29,250 level. The first key support is near $29,100. A downside break below the $29,100 level might start another steady decline. In the stated case, the price could drop toward $28,400. Technical indicators: Hourly MACD – The MACD is now gaining pace in the bearish zone. Hourly RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BTC/USD is now below the 50 level. Major Support Levels – $29,250, followed by $29,100. Major Resistance Levels – $29,450, $29,650, and $30,000.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>Bitcoin price is still struggling below the $29,650 zone. BTC could gain bearish momentum if there is a close below the $29,100 support.</em></p>
<ul>
<li>Bitcoin is showing a few bearish signs below the $29,650 zone.</li>
<li>The price is trading below $29,400 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average.</li>
<li>There is a short-term bullish trend line forming with support near $29,320 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could continue to move down if it breaks the $29,250 and $29,100 support levels.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Bitcoin Price Stuck Below $30K</h2>
<p>Bitcoin price remained well below the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-grinds-lower-29k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">$30,000 resistance zone</a>. BTC attempted a short-term upward move but the bears were active near the $29,650 resistance zone.</p>
<p>A high was formed near $29,657 before there was a fresh decline to $29,250. The price is now consolidating and trading above the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the recent decline from the $29,657 swing high to the $29,250 low.</p>
<p>Bitcoin is now trading below $29,400 and the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-next-leg-lower-28800/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">100 hourly Simple moving average</a>. There is also a short-term bullish trend line forming with support near $29,320 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair.</p>
<p>Immediate resistance is near the $29,450 level. It is close to the 50% Fib retracement level of the recent decline from the $29,657 swing high to the $29,250 low. The next major resistance is near $29,500. The main resistance is now forming near the $29,650 level.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-547265" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-7.png?resize=1024%2C468" alt="Bitcoin Price" width="1024" height="468" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-7.png?resize=1024%2C468?w=1835 1835w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-7.png?resize=1024%2C468?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-7.png?resize=1024%2C468?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-7.png?resize=1024%2C468?w=860 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-7.png?resize=1024%2C468?w=1536 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-7.png?resize=1024%2C468?w=750 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-7.png?resize=1024%2C468?w=1140 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" data-recalc-dims="1"/></p>
<p>Source: <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BTCUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">BTCUSD on TradingView.com</a></p>
<p>A close above the $29,650 resistance could send the price toward the $30,000 resistance zone. Any more gains might change the trend and the price might rise toward $30,500. In the stated case, the price could even rise toward $31,200 or even $32,200 in the coming days.</p>
<h2>More Losses In BTC?</h2>
<p>If Bitcoin fails to clear the $29,650 resistance, it could continue to move down. Immediate support on the downside is near the trend line.</p>
<p>The next major support is near the $29,250 level. The first key support is near $29,100. A downside break below the $29,100 level might start another steady decline. In the stated case, the price could drop toward $28,400.</p>
<p>Technical indicators:</p>
<p>Hourly MACD – The MACD is now gaining pace in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>Hourly RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BTC/USD is now below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Levels – $29,250, followed by $29,100.</p>
<p>Major Resistance Levels – $29,450, $29,650, and $30,000.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/shutterstock_1610297188.jpg?fit=460%2C256" width="460" height="256" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">547264</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cardano Whales Rapidly Accumulating, ADA Bull Run Incoming?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/cardano/cardano-whales-rapidly-accumulating-ada-bull-run-incoming/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dalmas Ngetich]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 03:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cardano]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Basho]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano whales]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mithril]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=547256</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[There are encouraging on-chain activities in Cardano. According to Santiment, an on-chain analytics platform, on August 14, there were 25,294 wallet addresses with at least 100,000 ADA, the highest in over 16 months. The uptick could signal interest, especially considering that prices are under pressure looking at the performance in the daily chart.  ADA Whales Accumulating Looking at Santiment trends, it appears that ADA whales began accumulating as early as June 2022, and the number has been rising steadily ever since. However, amid this encouraging &#8220;bullish&#8221; signal, ADA prices have fluctuated, edged lower, and diverged with whales&#8217; actions in the past 16 months. ADA is changing hands at around $0.289 at spot rates, down from $0.465 when whales began loading up in mid-June 2022, as seen below.  There are over 25,000 whales with at least 100,000 ADA of writing in mid-August, up by over 3,000 since June 2022. Overall, and as aforementioned, this is a vote of confidence for Cardano and may signal optimism in how ADA&#8217;s future prices could pan out.  Related Reading: Michael Burry’s Massive $1.6 Billion Short: Is A $DXY Collapse The Catalyst For A Crypto Bloodbath? In crypto, token holders closely monitor whale activity, as their actions often influence market sentiment. Their continued accumulation, for example, of ADA, is an endorsement of a project&#8217;s potential and could ignite demand, lifting prices. Conversely, when they offload, it could trigger a sell-off, forcing asset prices lower. ADA whales are buying more of the coin when Cardano&#8217;s market capitalization has been pulling back from 2023 highs. At spot rates, the project&#8217;s market cap is down by at least 35%, dropping from $15.76 billion to $10.1 billion as of mid-August. Even so, ADA is one of the most liquid coins looking at the average daily trading volumes and position in the leader board.  Cardano Building, ADA Resilient But Weak Presently ranked eighth, Cardano is ahead of Solana and Tron but trailing XRP and Dogecoin in the top 10. ADA is trading at $0.289, down roughly 10% from August 2023 highs. While ADA remains within the June to July 2023 trading range, ADA buyers hold an advantageous position looking at candlestick arrangements in the daily chart. Despite recent lower lows, sellers have not yet reversed the gains of July 13, a conspicuous bar that shapes the immediate price action. Related Reading: HBAR Token Spikes 16% In One Day, Can Bulls Sustain the Momentum? Cardano is in the Basho era, where developers look at enhancing scalability and network performance to support intensive decentralized applications (dapps), particularly those in decentralized finance (DeFi). Notable improvements in this phase include pipelining and the release of Mithril, aimed at bolstering network security. Additionally, Cardano&#8217;s leading developer IOG is working on Hydra, a layer-2 solution to boost scalability further using off-chain channels.  Feature image from Canva, chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>There are encouraging on-chain activities in Cardano. According to Santiment, an on-chain analytics platform, on August 14, there were 25,294 wallet addresses with at least 100,000 ADA, the highest in over 16 months.</p>
<p>The <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://app.santiment.net/charts?settings=%7B%22slug%22%3A%22cardano%22%2C%22ticker%22%3A%22ADA%22%2C%22from%22%3A%222020-08-13T07%3A00%3A00.000Z%22%2C%22to%22%3A%222023-08-14T06%3A59%3A59.000Z%22%7D&amp;widgets=%5B%7B%22widget%22%3A%22HolderDistributionWidget%22%2C%22wm%22%3A%5B%22%5B3%3Bholders_distribution%3B100k_to_1M%3B1M_to_10M%3B10M_to_100M%3B100M_to_1B%3B1B_to_inf%5D%22%2C%22price_usd%22%5D%2C%22whm%22%3A%5B%5D%2C%22wax%22%3A%5B0%2C1%5D%2C%22wpax%22%3A%5B%5D%2C%22wc%22%3A%5B%22%23FFCB47%22%2C%22%230a4e1c%22%5D%2C%22ws%22%3A%7B%220%22%3A%7B%22node%22%3A%22area%22%7D%2C%221%22%3A%7B%22node%22%3A%22bar%22%7D%7D%7D%5D" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">uptick</a> could signal interest, especially considering that prices are under pressure looking at the performance in the daily chart. </p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-547260" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Cardano-ADA-22.24.34-14-Aug-2023.png?resize=1024%2C347" alt="Cardano Whales Accumulating" width="1024" height="347" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Cardano-ADA-22.24.34-14-Aug-2023.png?resize=1024%2C347?w=3840 3840w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Cardano-ADA-22.24.34-14-Aug-2023.png?resize=1024%2C347?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Cardano-ADA-22.24.34-14-Aug-2023.png?resize=1024%2C347?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Cardano-ADA-22.24.34-14-Aug-2023.png?resize=1024%2C347?w=860 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Cardano-ADA-22.24.34-14-Aug-2023.png?resize=1024%2C347?w=1536 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Cardano-ADA-22.24.34-14-Aug-2023.png?resize=1024%2C347?w=2048 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Cardano-ADA-22.24.34-14-Aug-2023.png?resize=1024%2C347?w=750 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Cardano-ADA-22.24.34-14-Aug-2023.png?resize=1024%2C347?w=1140 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Cardano-ADA-22.24.34-14-Aug-2023.png?resize=1024%2C347?w=3000 3000w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" data-recalc-dims="1"/>
<h2>ADA Whales Accumulating</h2>
<p>Looking at Santiment trends, it appears that ADA whales began accumulating as early as June 2022, and the number has been rising steadily ever since. However, amid this encouraging &#8220;bullish&#8221; signal, ADA prices have fluctuated, edged lower, and diverged with whales&#8217; actions in the past 16 months. </p>
<p>ADA is changing hands at around $0.289 at spot rates, down from $0.465 when whales began loading up in mid-June 2022, as seen below. </p>
<a href="https://www.tradingview.com/x/vJsamq51/" rel="nofollow"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/vJsamq51/" alt="ADA price on August 14 as Cardano whales accumulate| Source: ADAUSDT on Binance, TradingView" width="1226" height="595"/></a>
<p>There are over 25,000 whales with at least 100,000 ADA of writing in mid-August, up by over 3,000 since June 2022. Overall, and as aforementioned, this is a vote of confidence for Cardano and may signal optimism in how ADA&#8217;s future prices could pan out. </p>

<p>In crypto, token holders closely monitor whale activity, as their actions often influence market sentiment. Their continued accumulation, for example, of ADA, is an endorsement of a project&#8217;s potential and could ignite demand, lifting prices. Conversely, when they offload, it could trigger a sell-off, forcing asset prices lower.</p>
<p>ADA whales are buying more of the coin when Cardano&#8217;s market capitalization has been pulling back from 2023 highs. At spot rates, the project&#8217;s market cap is down by at least 35%, dropping from $15.76 billion to $10.1 billion as of mid-August. Even so, ADA is one of the most liquid coins looking at the average daily trading volumes and position in the leader board. </p>
<h2>Cardano Building, ADA Resilient But Weak</h2>
<p>Presently ranked eighth, Cardano is ahead of Solana and Tron but trailing XRP and Dogecoin in the top 10. ADA is trading at $0.289, down roughly 10% from August 2023 highs. While ADA remains within the June to July 2023 trading range, ADA buyers hold an advantageous position looking at candlestick arrangements in the daily chart. </p>
<p>Despite recent lower lows, sellers have not yet reversed the gains of July 13, a conspicuous bar that shapes the immediate price action.</p>

<p>Cardano is in the Basho era, where developers look at enhancing scalability and network performance to support intensive decentralized applications (dapps), particularly those in decentralized finance (DeFi). Notable improvements in this phase include pipelining and the release of Mithril, aimed at bolstering network security. </p>
<p>Additionally, Cardano&#8217;s leading developer IOG is working on Hydra, a layer-2 solution to boost scalability further using off-chain channels. </p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Crypto-news-Template31.jpg?fit=460%2C260" width="460" height="260" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">547256</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bernstein Predicts Spot ETFs Could Claim 10% Of Bitcoin&#8217;s Market If Greenlit</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bernstein-predicts-spot-etfs-bitcoin-market-if-greenlit/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samuel Edyme]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 01:00:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[etf]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=547215</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[According to Bloomberg, a recent research report from Sanford C. Bernstein has shed light on the potential impact of Exchange Traded Funds (ETFs) on the Bitcoin market dynamics. Related Reading: Silent Bitcoin Storm: Glassnode Uncovers What Lies Beneath The Surface Potential Surge In Bitcoin Market Value Sanford C. Bernstein&#8217;s research indicates that should the US green-light a fund investing directly in spot Bitcoin, ETFs could constitute roughly 10% of Bitcoin&#8217;s market value within the next three years. Such a shift could amplify Bitcoin&#8217;s presence in traditional financial portfolios and potentially foster more significant institutional adoption. According to Bloomberg, Gautam Chhugani, an analyst at Bernstein, highlighted the rising probability of a spot Bitcoin ETF in the report. In a separate report, this same analyst had recently disclosed that the SEC believes that a Bitcoin Spot ETF may be &#8220;unreliable&#8221; since crypto exchanges (such as Coinbase) aren&#8217;t under their oversight, leading to concerns about potential price manipulation and unreliability. While the speculation on the SEC approval of a Spot Bitcoin ETF continues, with the Grayscale Bitcoin Trust currently holding about 4% of all Bitcoin, according to Bloomberg, a direct investment, ETF could more than double this figure, potentially aiding the growth of the crypto investment landscape. The “Growth Flywheel” Effect Once regulatory approval is in place, Bernstein anticipates a &#8220;growth flywheel&#8221; effect propelled by retail and other institutional inflows. Such a cascade effect would be reminiscent of other financial markets where introducing new financial products spurred fresh investments and liquidity waves. Notably, to understand the significance of this, one only needs to consider the broader ETF market&#8217;s growth trajectory. Since their inception, ETFs have grown exponentially, with assets under management surging across various sectors and asset classes. Introducing a Spot Bitcoin ETF would mean integrating a highly liquid, decentralized, and increasingly accepted asset into this mix, further validating Bitcoin&#8217;s place in the financial ecosystem. Meanwhile, Bitcoin&#8217;s price is struggling to break above the $30,000 mark after slipping below that price range last week. As of this writing, the asset trades at $29,623, recording a slight increase of 0.5% over the past 24 hours. Alongside its struggling price, BTC’s market capitalization has increased by more than $10 billion in just the past week. The asset market cap has surged from a high of $560 billion earlier last week to a current cap of $573 billion. Related Reading: Bitcoin Addresses In Loss Soar To One-Month High Amid Mixed Market Indicators The top crypto&#8217;s trading volume has also followed closely with its surging market cap and has seen a significant spike from last week&#8217;s daily trading volume. Bitcoin&#8217;s 24-hour trading volume currently stands at $11.3 billion compared to a lesser volume of $8.7 billion last Monday. Featured image from iStock, Chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>According to <a href="https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/etfs-may-account-for-10-of-bitcoin-market-value-if-approved-bernstein-says-1.1958728" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Bloomberg</a>, a recent research report from Sanford C. Bernstein has shed light on the potential impact of Exchange Traded Funds (ETFs) on the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/silent-bitcoin-storm-glassnode-revelations/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Bitcoin market dynamics</a>.</p>

<h2>Potential Surge In Bitcoin Market Value</h2>
<p>Sanford C. Bernstein&#8217;s research indicates that should the US green-light a fund investing directly in spot Bitcoin, ETFs could constitute roughly 10% of Bitcoin&#8217;s market value within the next three years. </p>
<p>Such a shift could amplify <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-friendly-javier-milei-wins-presidential-primaries/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Bitcoin&#8217;s presence</a> in traditional financial portfolios and potentially foster more significant institutional adoption.</p>
<p>According to Bloomberg, Gautam Chhugani, an analyst at Bernstein, highlighted the rising probability of a spot Bitcoin ETF in the report. </p>
<p>In a separate <a href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/07/03/probability-for-us-approval-of-a-spot-bitcoin-etf-is-fairly-high-bernstein/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">report</a>, this same analyst had recently disclosed that the SEC believes that a Bitcoin Spot ETF may be &#8220;unreliable&#8221; since crypto exchanges (such as Coinbase) aren&#8217;t under their oversight, leading to concerns about potential price manipulation and unreliability.</p>
<p>While the speculation on the SEC approval of a Spot Bitcoin ETF continues, with the Grayscale Bitcoin Trust currently holding about 4% of all Bitcoin, according to Bloomberg, a direct investment, ETF could more than <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/goldman-foresees-q2-2024-fed-rate-cut-boost-bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">double this figure</a>, potentially aiding the growth of the crypto investment landscape.</p>
<h2>The “Growth Flywheel” Effect</h2>
<p>Once regulatory approval is in place, Bernstein anticipates a &#8220;growth flywheel&#8221; effect propelled by retail and other institutional inflows. Such a cascade effect would be reminiscent of other financial markets where introducing new financial products spurred fresh investments and liquidity waves.</p>
<p>Notably, to understand the significance of this, one only needs to consider the broader ETF market&#8217;s growth trajectory. Since their inception, ETFs have grown exponentially, with assets under management surging across various sectors and asset classes.</p>
<p>Introducing a Spot Bitcoin ETF would mean integrating a highly liquid, decentralized, and increasingly accepted asset into this mix, further validating Bitcoin&#8217;s place in the financial ecosystem.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, Bitcoin&#8217;s price is<a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-grinds-lower-29k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener "> struggling to break above the $30,000 mark</a> after slipping below that price range last week. As of this writing, the asset trades at $29,623, recording a slight increase of 0.5% over the past 24 hours.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/C7m9EJOj/" alt="Bitcoin (BTC)’s price chart on TradingView" width="2770" height="1408"/>
<p>Alongside its struggling price, <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-addresses-in-loss-soar-to-one-month-high/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">BTC’s market capitalization</a> has increased by more than $10 billion in just the past week. The asset market cap has surged from a high of $560 billion earlier last week to a current cap of $573 billion.</p>

<p>The top crypto&#8217;s trading volume has also followed closely with its surging market cap and has seen a significant spike from last week&#8217;s daily trading volume. Bitcoin&#8217;s 24-hour trading volume currently stands at $11.3 billion compared to a lesser volume of $8.7 billion last Monday.</p>
<p>Featured image from iStock, Chart from TradingView</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/andre-francois-mckenzie-iGYiBhdNTpE-unsplash-2.jpg?fit=460%2C307" width="460" height="307" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">547215</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>HarryPotterObamaSonic10Inu Casts Spell On The Memecoin Sector And Soars 26%, Which Token Will Follow?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/harrypotterobamasonic10inu-casts-spell-on-the-memecoin-sector-and-soars-26-which-token-will-follow/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reynaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 00:00:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[HarryPotterObamaSonic10Inu]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=547236</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[While Bitcoin and the crypto market experienced, HarryPotterObamaSonic10Inu and the memecoin sector are blooming. Recent data points to double-digit gains across the board for these assets, with the potential for further profits if Bitcoin and larger cryptocurrencies continue trading sideways. Related Reading: Dogecoin Rally Ahead? This Positive Correlation Data Points To A Potential 20% Jump For DOGE As of this writing, HarryPotterObamaSonic10Inu trades at $0.14, with profits of around 30% during the last 24 hours. On the previous seven days, the token saw a 54% profit, but the last month has been the best in performance, with a 246% increase. HarryPotterObamaSonic10Inu Leads Memecoin Sector’s Gains As Bitcoin Acts Like A Stock Data from market tracker CoinGecko indicates that HarryPotterObamaSonic10Inu’s gains have been followed by ElmoERC and DogeKaki. These cryptocurrencies experienced 10% and 11% rallies’ respectively. Other cryptocurrencies that experienced positive price action in the memecoin sector include Mooncat CAT and Mog Coin. The last of these tokens recorded a 17% increase over the past hour and at the time of writing alone. As Bitcoin, Ethereum, and other significant cryptocurrencies trend sideways, traders are attracted to riskier and volatile assets. In addition, these tokens experienced more volatility as they possessed less trading volume and liquidity. In other words, smaller traders can influence the price action on some of these assets. While on Bitcoin, and even Dogecoin (DOGE), traders need billions of dollars to influence the price action. When Will The Bitcoin Price Move Again? But how long can traders in the memecoin sector benefit from a low volatility environment? Per a recent update from Bitfinex Alpha, the current status quo is bound to persist. As seen in the chart below, there has been a record-low liquidation in the derivatives sector, and as a result, prices have remained steady. Traders should look out for catalyst events in the macroeconomics landscape and a potential liquidation spike if they are betting on HarryPotterObamaSonic10Inu and other memecoins. Related Reading: Silent Bitcoin Storm: Glassnode Uncovers What Lies Beneath The Surface If the spike finally comes through, Bitcoin’s price could finally move again, crushing memecoins and the altcoins market. The Bitfinex Alpha report stated: (…) the low volatility regime should continue for a while. The lack of futures liquidations, euphoria and pain in the markets are also the reason for lack of any significant orderflow developments as the BTC price continues to range sideways even after breaking down from a significant range between $29,500 and $31,500. Cover image from Unsplash, chart from Tradingview]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>While Bitcoin and the crypto market experienced, HarryPotterObamaSonic10Inu and the memecoin sector are blooming. Recent data points to double-digit gains across the board for these assets, with the potential for further profits if Bitcoin and larger cryptocurrencies continue trading sideways.</strong></p>

<p>As of this writing, HarryPotterObamaSonic10Inu trades at $0.14, with profits of around 30% during the last 24 hours. On the previous seven days, the token saw a 54% profit, but the last month has been the best in performance, with a 246% increase.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-547248 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/HarryPotterObamaSonic10Inu-Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-1.png?w=860&#038;resize=860%2C410" alt="HarryPotterObamaSonic10Inu" width="860" height="410" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/HarryPotterObamaSonic10Inu-Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-1.png?w=1759 1759w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/HarryPotterObamaSonic10Inu-Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-1.png?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/HarryPotterObamaSonic10Inu-Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-1.png?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/HarryPotterObamaSonic10Inu-Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-1.png?w=860&#038;resize=860%2C410 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/HarryPotterObamaSonic10Inu-Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-1.png?w=1536 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/HarryPotterObamaSonic10Inu-Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-1.png?w=750 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/HarryPotterObamaSonic10Inu-Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-1.png?w=1140 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" data-recalc-dims="1"/>
<h2>HarryPotterObamaSonic10Inu Leads Memecoin Sector’s Gains As Bitcoin Acts Like A Stock</h2>
<p><a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/categories/meme-token" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Data</a> from market tracker CoinGecko indicates that HarryPotterObamaSonic10Inu’s gains have been followed by ElmoERC and DogeKaki. These cryptocurrencies experienced 10% and 11% rallies’ respectively.</p>
<p>Other cryptocurrencies that experienced positive price action in the memecoin sector include Mooncat CAT and Mog Coin. The last of these tokens recorded a 17% increase over the past hour and at the time of writing alone.</p>
<p>As Bitcoin, Ethereum, and other significant cryptocurrencies trend sideways, traders are attracted to riskier and volatile assets. In addition, these tokens experienced more volatility as they possessed less trading volume and liquidity.</p>
<p>In other words, smaller traders can influence the price action on some of these assets. While on Bitcoin, and even Dogecoin (DOGE), traders need billions of dollars to influence the price action.</p>
<h2>When Will The Bitcoin Price Move Again?</h2>
<p>But how long can traders in the memecoin sector benefit from a low volatility environment? Per a recent <a href="https://blog.bitfinex.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitfinex-Alpha-67-1.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">update</a> from Bitfinex Alpha, the current status quo is bound to persist.</p>
<p>As seen in the chart below, there has been a record-low liquidation in the derivatives sector, and as a result, prices have remained steady. Traders should look out for catalyst events in the macroeconomics landscape and a potential liquidation spike if they are betting on HarryPotterObamaSonic10Inu and other memecoins.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-547246 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-1.jpg?w=860&#038;resize=860%2C216" alt="HarryPotterObamaSonic10Inu  Bitcoin BTC BTCUSDT" width="860" height="216" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-1.jpg?w=1724 1724w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-1.jpg?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-1.jpg?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-1.jpg?w=860&#038;resize=860%2C216 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-1.jpg?w=1536 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-1.jpg?w=750 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-1.jpg?w=1140 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" data-recalc-dims="1"/>

<p>If the spike finally comes through, Bitcoin’s price could finally move again, crushing memecoins and the altcoins market. The Bitfinex Alpha report stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>(…) the low volatility regime should continue for a while. The lack of futures liquidations, euphoria and pain in the markets are also the reason for lack of any significant orderflow developments as the BTC price continues to range sideways even after breaking down from a significant range between $29,500 and $31,500.</p></blockquote>
<p>Cover image from Unsplash, chart from Tradingview</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/HarryPotterObamaSonic10Inu-BITCOIN-ETHUSDT.jpg?fit=460%2C307" width="460" height="307" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">547236</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Price Supported By Thin $40 Million Bid Pool, But For How Long?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-price-supported-by-thin-40-million-bid-pool-but-for-how-long/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 23:00:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=547239</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[In the ongoing market turbulence on higher timeframes, Bitcoin (BTC) is at a crucial juncture as a great consolidation phase persists. Research and analysis firm Material Indicators closely monitored the recent weekly candle close/open, paying particular attention to two key factors: the trend line and the 21-day, 21-week, and 21-month moving averages (MA) – all of which are currently influential in shaping market dynamics.  Uncertainty And Potential Turning Point For Bitcoin The opening of the weekly candle below the trend line triggered a “subsequent nosedive,” amplifying concerns. While the 21-week and 21-month moving averages continue to serve as robust support, the 21-day MA has faced a rigorous seven-day testing period, according to the firm’s analysis.  Notably, the tight correlation of the 21-MA across three distinct time frames is rare, indicating that the market is at a critical inflection point.  Despite the compressed volatility witnessed in recent days, the price action observed over the past 24 hours exemplifies the market&#8217;s attempt to shake out weak hands. According to Material Indicators, given the complexity of the current price action, it is prudent to zoom out and gain a broader perspective. Both Trend Precognition algorithms identified these moves on the four-hour chart, emphasizing the significance of adopting a comprehensive outlook. Moreover, according to Materials, the order book reveals a concerning trend in bid liquidity, with less than $40 million holding the price up.  The absence of substantial liquidity below this level raises fundamental worries. However, it also suggests that there may not be sufficient sentiment to drive prices significantly lower – at least not yet.  Related Reading: XRP Volume Jolt: How Did The $3 Billion Surge Impact Price Action? In addition, Material Indicators highlights that the examination of liquidity movements within the order book over the past month paints a picture of continued price volatility with a potential upward bias.  However, the lack of volume raises concerns about the market&#8217;s overall health. Despite a $13 million buy wall at $27,900, the bottom of the channel at $28,300 remains a critical threshold for BTC to extend its current trend. The firm claims: &#8230; the bottom of the channel at $28.3k remains my line in the sand for BTC to extend the trend, and I maintain that we must see weekly candles printing above the 100-Week MA to even consider a bull breakout. BCT Faces Renewed Pressure Amid Strengthening US Dollar As Bitcoin enters a new week of trading, market participants closely monitor the potential impact of the strengthening US Dollar Index ($DXY) on the world&#8217;s leading cryptocurrency.  According to Yan Alleman, co-founder of blockchain analytics firm Glassnode, recent developments suggest that BTC may face renewed pressure due to the upward momentum of the $DXY. Alleman highlights that the $DXY&#8217;s renewed strength could exert downward pressure on Bitcoin&#8217;s price. Historically, there has been an inverse correlation between the value of the US Dollar and the price of BTC, meaning that when the dollar strengthens, Bitcoin often faces headwinds.  However, options pricing indicates a bullish sentiment for Bitcoin in the coming month. Options are financial derivatives that allow traders to speculate on the future price of an underlying asset, in this case, Bitcoin.  The pricing of options contracts suggests an expectation of a bullish move shortly. This aligns with the technical analysis indicating potential upside for Bitcoin. Related Reading: Base TVL Surges 900% In 2 Weeks, What’s Driving The Growth? Analyzing the potential price movements, Alleman notes that it would require nearly twice as much selling pressure to push Bitcoin down to the low $28,000 range compared to the buying pressure needed to surpass the $30,000 level.  This observation suggests that there may be greater support and buying interest at higher price levels, making a sustained drop less likely. As of the time of writing, Bitcoin (BTC) is trading at $29,500, reflecting a marginal 0.4% increase over the past 24 hours. Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In the ongoing market turbulence on higher timeframes, Bitcoin (BTC) is at a crucial juncture as a great consolidation phase persists.</p>
<p>Research and analysis firm Material Indicators closely monitored the recent weekly candle close/open, paying particular attention to <a href="https://twitter.com/MI_Algos/status/1691123111796621312?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">two key factors</a>: the trend line and the 21-day, 21-week, and 21-month moving averages (MA) – all of which are currently influential in shaping market dynamics. </p>
<h2>Uncertainty And Potential Turning Point For Bitcoin</h2>
<p>The opening of the weekly candle below the trend line triggered a “subsequent nosedive,” amplifying concerns. While the 21-week and 21-month moving averages continue to serve as robust support, the 21-day MA has faced a rigorous seven-day testing period, according to the firm’s analysis. </p>
<p>Notably, the tight correlation of the 21-MA across three distinct time frames is rare, indicating that the market is at a critical inflection point. </p>
<p>Despite the compressed volatility witnessed in recent days, the price action observed over the past 24 hours exemplifies the market&#8217;s attempt to shake out weak hands.</p>
<p>According to Material Indicators, given the complexity of the current price action, it is prudent to zoom out and gain a broader perspective. Both Trend Precognition algorithms identified these moves on the four-hour chart, emphasizing the significance of adopting a comprehensive outlook.</p>
<p>Moreover, according to Materials, the order book reveals a concerning trend in bid liquidity, with less than $40 million holding the price up. </p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large wp-image-547241" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F3gKYvaWMAANpQD.jpeg?w=860&#038;resize=860%2C519" alt="Bitcoin " width="860" height="519" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F3gKYvaWMAANpQD.jpeg?w=1375 1375w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F3gKYvaWMAANpQD.jpeg?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F3gKYvaWMAANpQD.jpeg?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F3gKYvaWMAANpQD.jpeg?w=860&#038;resize=860%2C519 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F3gKYvaWMAANpQD.jpeg?w=750 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F3gKYvaWMAANpQD.jpeg?w=1140 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" data-recalc-dims="1"/>
<p>The absence of substantial liquidity below this level raises fundamental worries. However, it also suggests that there may not be sufficient sentiment to drive prices significantly lower – at least not yet. </p>

<p>In addition, Material Indicators highlights that the examination of liquidity movements within the order book over the past month paints a picture of continued price volatility with a potential upward bias. </p>
<p>However, the lack of volume raises concerns about the market&#8217;s overall health. Despite a $13 million buy wall at $27,900, the bottom of the channel at $28,300 remains a critical threshold for BTC to extend its current trend. The firm claims:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8230; the bottom of the channel at $28.3k remains my line in the sand for BTC to extend the trend, and I maintain that we must see weekly candles printing above the 100-Week MA to even consider a bull breakout.</p></blockquote>
<h2>BCT Faces Renewed Pressure Amid Strengthening US Dollar</h2>
<p>As Bitcoin enters a new week of trading, market participants closely monitor the potential impact of the strengthening US Dollar Index ($DXY) on the world&#8217;s leading cryptocurrency. </p>
<p><a href="https://twitter.com/Negentropic_/status/1691134948822994953?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">According </a>to Yan Alleman, co-founder of blockchain analytics firm Glassnode, recent developments suggest that BTC may face renewed pressure due to the upward momentum of the $DXY.</p>
<p>Alleman highlights that the $DXY&#8217;s renewed strength could exert downward pressure on Bitcoin&#8217;s price. Historically, there has been an inverse correlation between the value of the US Dollar and the price of BTC, meaning that when the dollar strengthens, Bitcoin often faces headwinds. </p>
<p>However, options pricing indicates a bullish sentiment for Bitcoin in the coming month. Options are financial derivatives that allow traders to speculate on the future price of an underlying asset, in this case, Bitcoin. </p>
<p>The pricing of options contracts suggests an expectation of a bullish move shortly. This aligns with the technical analysis indicating potential upside for Bitcoin.</p>

<p>Analyzing the potential price movements, Alleman notes that it would require nearly twice as much selling pressure to push Bitcoin down to the low $28,000 range compared to the buying pressure needed to surpass the $30,000 level. </p>
<p>This observation suggests that there may be greater support and buying interest at higher price levels, making a sustained drop less likely.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/HgUNUTZu/" alt="Bitcoin " width="1814" height="858"/>
<p>As of the time of writing, Bitcoin (BTC) is trading at $29,500, reflecting a marginal 0.4% increase over the past 24 hours.</p>
<p>Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Downloader.la-64da6937b2519.jpg?fit=460%2C259" width="460" height="259" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">547239</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>BALD Deployer Moves Proceeds Of The Rug From Base To Ethereum</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/altcoin/bald-deployer-moves-proceeds/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 21:00:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BALD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BALD deployer]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BALD token]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Base]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Base Layer 2]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=547214</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[In a shocking turn of events, the developer behind the controversial meme coin BALD initiated a series of significant transactions, raising eyebrows within the cryptocurrency community. The events surrounding the deployer’s recent actions have left both the coin&#8217;s value and its reputation teetering on the edge. BALD Deployers Send Funds To Kraken Exchange Blockchain analysis platform Lookonchain has revealed that the deployer of the BALD token has executed audacious moves, bridging a staggering 7,000 ETH ($12.9 million) out of the Coinbase Layer 2 network, Base. Of the 7,000 ETH that has been sent to the Ethereum network, the deployer sent 2,100 ETH ($3.87 million) in two different transactions to the Kraken crypto exchange, for purposes that can only be for selling. Related Reading: Bitcoin-Friendly Javier Milei Wins Presidential Primaries In Argentina Following this, the BALD deployer currently holds 4,902 ETH in their balance on the Ethereum blockchain, worth over $9 million at current prices. The wallet’s tokens holdings also remain significant, sitting at $1.115 million at the time of this writing. The recent transactions have now dredged up speculations about who the BALD deployer might be. On-chain investigator ZachXBT previously lent his expertise to the investigations, with findings pointing toward an X (formerly Twitter) user who goes by the username @milkyway16eth due to a previous transaction between the deployer wallet and Milkyway’s wallet. However, there is yet to be any concrete proof if Milkyway is actually the brains behind the rug. A Rollercoaster For Investors The BALD meme coin started making the rounds on X (formerly Twitter) shortly after being launched on Base. The coin which was named after Coinbase’s CEO Brian Armstrong’s bald head rose rapidly, climbing more than 289,000% in less than two days. This growth rate served as an attraction for investors, who bridged quickly to the ETH blockchain to invest in the token. It continued to rise, crossing a $70 million market amid the euphoria. However, this would end up being short-lived. Related Reading: More Selling? Bankrupt Voyager Sends Millions In SHIB And ETH To Coinbase On August 1, the BALD deployer pulled liquidity from the token, making off with 10,705 ETH ($20 million at the time). The coin’s price declined rapidly after this, although the official X account for BALD continued to deny that it was a rug pull. Although BALD continues to trade on the Base network, it has been unable to reclaim its past glory. Its price is down over 90% from its all-time high and recorded 18% losses in the last 24 hours alone, according to data from Coinmarketcap. Its daily trading volume is sitting at $503,000 and its market cap is $9.03 million. Total market cap recovers to $1.154 trillion &#124; Source: Crypto Total Market Cap on Tradingview.com Featured image from Publish0x, chart from Tradingview.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="p1">In a shocking turn of events, the developer behind the controversial meme coin BALD <a href="https://en.ethereumworldnews.com/base-bald-deployer-bridges-kraken/" rel="nofollow">initiated</a> a series of significant transactions, raising eyebrows within the cryptocurrency community. The events surrounding the deployer’s recent actions have left both the coin&#8217;s value and its reputation teetering on the edge.</p>
<h2 class="p1">BALD Deployers Send Funds To Kraken Exchange</h2>
<p class="p1">Blockchain analysis platform Lookonchain has <a href="https://twitter.com/lookonchain/status/1690965940937334784?s=20" rel="nofollow">revealed</a> that the deployer of the BALD token has executed audacious moves, bridging a staggering 7,000 ETH ($12.9 million) out of the Coinbase Layer 2 network, Base.</p>
<p class="p2">Of the 7,000 ETH that has been sent to the Ethereum network, the deployer sent 2,100 ETH ($3.87 million) in two different transactions to the Kraken crypto exchange, for purposes that can only be for selling.</p>

<p class="p2">Following this, the BALD deployer currently holds 4,902 ETH in their balance on the Ethereum blockchain, worth over $9 million at current prices. The wallet’s tokens holdings also remain significant, sitting at $1.115 million at the time of this writing.</p>
<p class="p2">The recent transactions have now dredged up speculations about who the BALD deployer might be. On-chain investigator ZachXBT previously lent his expertise to the investigations, with findings pointing toward an X (formerly Twitter) user who goes by the username @milkyway16eth due to a previous transaction between the deployer wallet and Milkyway’s wallet. However, there is yet to be any concrete proof if Milkyway is actually the brains behind the rug.</p>
<h2 class="p2">A Rollercoaster For Investors</h2>
<p class="p2">The BALD meme coin started making the rounds on X (formerly Twitter) shortly after being <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/29-meme-coins-bald-rugged-base-investors-lose-millions/">launched on Base</a>. The coin which was named after Coinbase’s CEO Brian Armstrong’s bald head rose rapidly, climbing more than 289,000% in less than two days.</p>
<p class="p2">This growth rate served as an attraction for investors, who bridged quickly to the ETH blockchain to invest in the token. It continued to rise, crossing a $70 million market amid the euphoria. However, this would end up being short-lived.</p>

<p class="p2">On August 1, the BALD <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/crypto-uproar-sbf-puppet-master-of-bald/" rel="nofollow">deployer pulled liquidity from the token</a>, making off with 10,705 ETH ($20 million at the time). The coin’s price declined rapidly after this, although the official X account for BALD continued to deny that it was a rug pull.</p>
<p class="p2">Although BALD continues to trade on the Base network, it has been unable to reclaim its past glory. Its price is down over 90% from its all-time high and recorded 18% losses in the last 24 hours alone, according to data from Coinmarketcap. Its daily trading volume is sitting at $503,000 and its market cap is $9.03 million.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/yOUe7Isg/" alt="Crypto total market cap chart from Tradingview.com (BALD on Base)" width="2302" height="1746"/></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Rug-pull-BALD-deployer.png?fit=460%2C258" width="460" height="258" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">547214</post-id>	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
