<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
>

<channel>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.newsbtc.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<description>Bitcoin &#38; cryptocurrency news today, price &#38; technical analysis</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 02:37:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Bears Gains Strength – Is This Renewed Downtrend or Just Correction</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-bears-gains-strength-28k/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 02:37:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xbtusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=530596</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin price is moving lower below $28,000. BTC is approaching the $27,000 support, below which there is a risk of an extended decline to $25,500. Bitcoin is moving lower and trading below the $28,200 pivot level. The price is trading below $28,000 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average. There is a major bearish trend line forming with resistance near $28,150 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Kraken). The pair could continue to move down if there is a move below the $27,000 support. Bitcoin Price Turns Red Bitcoin price started a steady decline after it broke the $28,800 support zone. BTC gained bearish momentum below the $28,200 and $28,000 levels. The bears seem to be gaining strength and they were able to push the price toward the $27,200 support. A low is formed near $27,282 and the price is now consolidating losses. It is trading below $28,000 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average. There is also a major bearish trend line forming with resistance near $28,150 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair. Bitcoin is now facing resistance near the $27,750 level. It is close to the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $29,128 swing high to the $27,282 low. The next major resistance is near the trend line zone or the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $29,128 swing high to the $27,282 low. A close above the trend line resistance might send the price toward the $28,800 resistance. Source: BTCUSD on TradingView.com The next key resistance is near $29,120, above which the price might rise toward the $29,500 resistance zone. Any more gains could open the doors for a decent increase toward the $29,750 resistance. More Losses in BTC? If Bitcoin’s price fails to clear the $28,150 resistance, it could continue to move down. Immediate support on the downside is near the $27,250 level and the recent low. The next major support is near the $27,000 zone, below which the price might drop toward the $26,000 support zone. Any more losses might take Bitcoin toward the $25,500 level in the near term. Technical indicators: Hourly MACD – The MACD is now gaining pace in the bearish zone. Hourly RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BTC/USD is now below the 50 level. Major Support Levels – $27,250, followed by $27,000. Major Resistance Levels – $28,000, $28,150, and $28,800.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>Bitcoin price is moving lower below $28,000. BTC is approaching the $27,000 support, below which there is a risk of an extended decline to $25,500.</em></p>
<ul>
<li>Bitcoin is moving lower and trading below the $28,200 pivot level.</li>
<li>The price is trading below $28,000 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average.</li>
<li>There is a major bearish trend line forming with resistance near $28,150 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could continue to move down if there is a move below the $27,000 support.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Bitcoin Price Turns Red</h2>
<p>Bitcoin price started a <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-rejection-30k/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener">steady decline</a> after it broke the $28,800 support zone. BTC gained bearish momentum below the $28,200 and $28,000 levels.</p>
<p>The bears seem to be gaining strength and they were able to push the price toward the $27,200 support. A low is formed near $27,282 and the price is now consolidating losses. It is trading below $28,000 and the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-bullish-above-30k/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener">100 hourly Simple moving average</a>.</p>
<p>There is also a major bearish trend line forming with resistance near $28,150 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair. Bitcoin is now facing resistance near the $27,750 level. It is close to the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $29,128 swing high to the $27,282 low.</p>
<p>The next major resistance is near the trend line zone or the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $29,128 swing high to the $27,282 low. A close above the trend line resistance might send the price toward the $28,800 resistance.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-6.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-530597" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-6.png" alt="Bitcoin Price" width="1834" height="845" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-6.png 1834w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-6-460x212.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-6-860x396.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-6-768x354.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-6-1536x708.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-6-750x346.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-6-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1834px) 100vw, 1834px" /></a></p>
<p>Source: <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BTCUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">BTCUSD on TradingView.com</a></p>
<p>The next key resistance is near $29,120, above which the price might rise toward the $29,500 resistance zone. Any more gains could open the doors for a decent increase toward the $29,750 resistance.</p>
<h2>More Losses in BTC?</h2>
<p>If Bitcoin’s price fails to clear the $28,150 resistance, it could continue to move down. Immediate support on the downside is near the $27,250 level and the recent low.</p>
<p>The next major support is near the $27,000 zone, below which the price might drop toward the $26,000 support zone. Any more losses might take Bitcoin toward the $25,500 level in the near term.</p>
<p>Technical indicators:</p>
<p>Hourly MACD – The MACD is now gaining pace in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>Hourly RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BTC/USD is now below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Levels – $27,250, followed by $27,000.</p>
<p>Major Resistance Levels – $28,000, $28,150, and $28,800.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/shutterstock_649342378-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Is Bitcoin Crashing Because Of A “Successful” DDOS Attack?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/is-bitcoin-crashing-because-of-a-successful-ddos-attack/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dalmas Ngetich]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 23:00:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Fees]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Ordinals]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ddos]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=530589</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Recent reports suggest that Bitcoin is under a Distributed Denial-of-Service (DDoS) attack, forcing prices lower and transaction fees higher. The attack, observers note, is orchestrated through spam inscriptions that are clogging up the network, inconveniencing users. Bitcoin Is Under Attack? The so-called spam transactions via the Bitcoin Ordinals platform have prompted many to speculate that this is a DDoS attack. Related Reading: Stacks (STX) Surges 10% Due To Bitcoin Network Congestion In a DDoS attack, the malicious actors seek to overwhelm a network or server with traffic from multiple sources, rendering it inaccessible to users. In this case, the target was Bitcoin’s nodes tasked with confirming transactions. Majority of tx&#39;s are currently just spamming the block space. They&#39;re all 152.5vb in size transacting precisely 0.00000546 btc. DDOS test? pic.twitter.com/l9yDTnkuL9 &#8212; Andrew (@dAnconiaMining) May 7, 2023 The memory pool, better known as mempool, stores unconfirmed but valid transactions waiting to be processed and remains clogged with transactions. Analysis shows that the unconfirmed transactions currently exceed 466,000, comprising mostly assets from the Bitcoin Ordinals platform generated from UniSat. UniSat is an open-source wallet and a Chrome extension that allows users to store and transfer Ordinals inscriptions and tokens compliant with the BRC-20 standard. BRC-20 tokens are fungible tokens that are compatible with the Bitcoin network. The wallet had temporarily shut down following many double-spend attacks on the platform. ⚠️Due to some existing issues UniSat Marketplace is temporarily not available for accessing. Sorry for the inconvenience. We&#39;ll keep you updated on this. &#8212; UniSat Wallet &#8211; Store, Inscribe and Search. (@unisat_wallet) April 23, 2023 The marketplace reopened on April 27, 2023, coinciding with the increase in transaction fees and the surge of transactions on the Bitcoin network. As of May 6, the number of on-chain Bitcoin transactions was at record highs. Signs Of What Lies Ahead? There are concerns among analysts that the recent surge in transactions, which resembles a prolonged DDoS attack, could indicate a potential coordinated sabotage by malicious entities. According to the analysts, these actors could be aiming to cause instability and unreliability in the Bitcoin network. In response to the flood of transactions from the Ordinals platform, on-chain transaction fees on Bitcoin have risen as the network congests. Bitcoin is under DoS attack. High transaction fees are the chosen pain point by the attacker, probably to makes bitcoin unusable for smaller players. pic.twitter.com/0J56liNSGf &#8212; iris.to/jogi (@proofofjogi) May 7, 2023 Meanwhile, prices are lower, approaching the $27,000 mark. This level is a critical support level flashing with April 2023 lows. As BTC&#8217;s price continues to fall, investors and traders are increasingly concerned about the overall state of the cryptocurrency market, which is already experiencing significant volatility, with many tokens posting double-digit losses. Related Reading: Bitcoin To Drop Further? Whales Show Signs Of Dumping PEPE, the meme token, is down 33% on the last trading day. While some believe the DDoS attack may be a temporary setback, which would end once the perpetrators run out of BTC, others are worried that it could be a sign of a larger trend of increased cyberattacks on the blockchain. BRC-20 token creations. Shitcoins on #bitcoin is here. Everything is good for bitcoin. We knew high transactions fees were coming, but now we need to figure out a way to navigate this. Good thing is they will eventually run out of bitcoin by doing this. &#8212; Chris Alaimo (@ChrisAlaimo6) May 6, 2023 Feature Image From Canva, Chart From TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Recent reports suggest that Bitcoin is under a Distributed Denial-of-Service (DDoS) attack, forcing prices lower and transaction fees higher. The attack, observers note, is orchestrated through spam inscriptions that are clogging up the network, inconveniencing users.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Is Under Attack?</h2>
<p>The so-called spam transactions via the Bitcoin Ordinals platform have prompted many to speculate that this is a DDoS attack.</p>

<p>In a DDoS attack, the malicious actors seek to overwhelm a network or server with traffic from multiple sources, rendering it inaccessible to users. In this case, the target was Bitcoin’s nodes tasked with confirming transactions.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Majority of tx&#39;s are currently just spamming the block space.</p>
<p>They&#39;re all 152.5vb in size transacting precisely 0.00000546 btc. </p>
<p>DDOS test? <a href="https://t.co/l9yDTnkuL9" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/l9yDTnkuL9</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Andrew (@dAnconiaMining) <a href="https://twitter.com/dAnconiaMining/status/1655019471243804672?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">May 7, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p></p>
<p>The memory pool, better known as mempool, stores unconfirmed but valid transactions waiting to be processed and remains clogged with transactions.</p>
<p>Analysis shows that the unconfirmed transactions currently <a href="https://mempool.space/" rel="nofollow">exceed</a> 466,000, comprising mostly assets from the Bitcoin Ordinals platform generated from UniSat.</p>
<p>UniSat is an open-source wallet and a Chrome extension that allows users to store and transfer Ordinals inscriptions and tokens compliant with the BRC-20 standard.</p>
<p>BRC-20 tokens are fungible tokens that are compatible with the Bitcoin network. The wallet had temporarily shut down following many double-spend attacks on the platform.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr"><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/26a0.png" alt="⚠" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />Due to some existing issues UniSat Marketplace is temporarily not available for accessing.</p>
<p>Sorry for the inconvenience. We&#39;ll keep you updated on this.</p>
<p>&mdash; UniSat Wallet &#8211; Store, Inscribe and Search. (@unisat_wallet) <a href="https://twitter.com/unisat_wallet/status/1650273977481457664?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">April 23, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p></p>
<p>The marketplace reopened on April 27, 2023, coinciding with the increase in transaction fees and the surge of transactions on the Bitcoin network. As of May 6, the number of on-chain Bitcoin transactions was at record highs.</p>
<h2>Signs Of What Lies Ahead?</h2>
<p>There are concerns among analysts that the recent surge in transactions, which resembles a prolonged DDoS attack, could indicate a potential coordinated sabotage by malicious entities. According to the analysts, these actors could be aiming to cause instability and unreliability in the Bitcoin network.</p>
<p>In response to the flood of transactions from the Ordinals platform, on-chain transaction fees on Bitcoin have risen as the network congests.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Bitcoin is under DoS attack. High transaction fees are the chosen pain point by the attacker, probably to makes bitcoin unusable for smaller players. <a href="https://t.co/0J56liNSGf" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/0J56liNSGf</a></p>
<p>&mdash; iris.to/jogi (@proofofjogi) <a href="https://twitter.com/proofofjogi/status/1655157035804098561?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">May 7, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p></p>
<p>Meanwhile, prices are lower, approaching the $27,000 mark. This level is a critical support level flashing with April 2023 lows.</p>
<a href="https://www.tradingview.com/x/le71dAFE/" rel="nofollow"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/le71dAFE/" alt="Bitcoin Price On May 8| Source: BTCUSDT On Binance, TradingView" width="1137" height="794" /></a>
<p>As BTC&#8217;s price continues to fall, investors and traders are increasingly concerned about the overall state of the cryptocurrency market, which is already experiencing significant volatility, with many tokens posting double-digit losses.</p>

<p>PEPE, the meme token, is <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/pepe/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">down</a> 33% on the last trading day. While some believe the DDoS attack may be a temporary setback, which would end once the perpetrators run out of BTC, others are worried that it could be a sign of a larger trend of increased cyberattacks on the blockchain.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">BRC-20 token creations. </p>
<p>Shitcoins on <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/bitcoin?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#bitcoin</a> is here. </p>
<p>Everything is good for bitcoin. We knew high transactions fees were coming, but now we need to figure out a way to navigate this. </p>
<p>Good thing is they will eventually run out of bitcoin by doing this.</p>
<p>&mdash; Chris Alaimo (@ChrisAlaimo6) <a href="https://twitter.com/ChrisAlaimo6/status/1654936758713294850?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">May 6, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p></p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/iStock-1296910866-460x283.jpg" width="460" height="283" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Bull Run In Jeopardy As Parabolic SAR Flips Bearish On Daily Chart</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-bull-run-in-jeopardy-as-parabolic-sar-flips-bearish-on-daily-chart/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 22:00:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=530583</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC), the world&#8217;s largest cryptocurrency, is facing a potential correction as it loses support at a critical level and trades at $27,300. Technical analysis shows that the Parabolic SAR has flipped bearish on the daily chart, indicating a possible downturn shortly. Bitcoin&#8217;s price has also dropped below the 50 exponential moving average (EMA), a critical support level. The Parabolic SAR is a popular technical indicator to identify potential trend reversals in the market. When the indicator flips bearish, it suggests that the asset&#8217;s price could be heading lower. In this case, the bearish signal on Bitcoin&#8217;s daily chart could mean the cryptocurrency is due for a correction. Related Reading: Pro-XRP Lawyer Weighs In On The Ongoing Lawsuit Ruling Brace For Bitcoin Correction As Support Levels Falter According to the trader and technical analyst Ali, If Bitcoin fails to sustain a close above the 50EMA level, it could confirm a potential correction to $26,200 or even $25,000. Furthermore, Bitcoin&#8217;s failure to hold the 50EMA as support is another warning sign for traders.  The 50EMA is a widely watched moving average that shows the average price of an asset over the past 50 days. When an asset&#8217;s price falls below this level, it can be seen as a bearish signal, indicating that the asset may be headed lower. Currently, Bitcoin is down by over 4% in the last 24 hours, trading below the 50EMA; this could confirm a potential correction to $26,200 or even $25,000, according to the analyst. These levels represent significant support zones for Bitcoin; the cryptocurrency could see a further downside if they fail to hold. Furthermore, according to Ali, The Bitcoin network is showing signs of contraction, with declining user adoption and a series of lower highs and lower lows. This decreasing trend of wallet activity could signal a drop in Bitcoin&#8217;s price shortly. As BTC adoption declines, the demand for the cryptocurrency also decreases. This ultimately puts downward pressure on BTC’s price, as fewer people are interested in buying and holding the cryptocurrency. The trend of lower highs and lower lows seen in the Bitcoin network suggests that the cryptocurrency&#8217;s price may be headed for a correction. Added to this, more bad news for Bitcoin bulls mounts; Bitcoin&#8217;s largest whale address, owned by Binance, has been highly active in the market, moving $2.26 billion worth of Bitcoin in just four transactions, according to Santiment data. This sudden movement has caused Bitcoin&#8217;s supply on exchanges to drop from 6.78% to 5.84%, indicating that the whale may transfer Bitcoin to a cold storage or custody solution. BTC Above $25500, Signals Long-Term Bullish Trend Despite recent market fluctuations, BTC is still showing a strong upward trend, according to the analysis of the weekly BTCUSD chart by The Birb Nest, a cryptocurrency and investment platform. Furthermore, BTC is trading above the rising 200-week trend and the flattening 50-week trend, which is a positive indicator.  The Birb Nest has pointed out that the upward trend will likely continue if Bitcoin remains above the $25,500 level. However, the crypto analysis firms keep a potential visit down to the $25,000 level. This level is seen as a key support level for Bitcoin, and a sustained hold above it could signal a bullish outlook for the cryptocurrency. Moreover, The Birb Nest has noted that there has been a weakened relationship between Bitcoin and the S&#38;P 500 prices in recent weeks. This is reflected in the 7-week correlation coefficient, which stands at 0.39. Although the correlation between Bitcoin and the S&#38;P 500 has weakened, it remains positive. This suggests that both assets still share some similarities in terms of price movements. Therefore, if there are gains or losses in large-cap stocks, Bitcoin will likely be somewhat affected. Related Reading: Discovering The Next PEPE And SHIB: Whales To Keep Track Of Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin (BTC), the world&#8217;s largest cryptocurrency, is facing a potential correction as it loses support at a critical level and trades at $27,300. Technical analysis shows that the Parabolic SAR has flipped bearish on the daily chart, indicating a possible downturn shortly. Bitcoin&#8217;s price has also dropped below the 50 exponential moving average (EMA), a critical support level.</p>
<p>The Parabolic SAR is a popular technical indicator to identify potential trend reversals in the market. When the indicator flips bearish, it suggests that the asset&#8217;s price could be heading lower. In this case, the bearish signal on Bitcoin&#8217;s daily chart could mean the cryptocurrency is due for a correction.</p>

<h2><b>Brace For Bitcoin Correction As Support Levels Falter</b></h2>
<p><a href="https://twitter.com/ali_charts/status/1655639221841846276?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">According </a>to the trader and technical analyst Ali, If Bitcoin fails to sustain a close above the 50EMA level, it could confirm a potential correction to $26,200 or even $25,000. Furthermore, Bitcoin&#8217;s failure to hold the 50EMA as support is another warning sign for traders. </p>
<p>The 50EMA is a widely watched moving average that shows the average price of an asset over the past 50 days. When an asset&#8217;s price falls below this level, it can be seen as a bearish signal, indicating that the asset may be headed lower.</p>
<p>Currently, Bitcoin is down by over 4% in the last 24 hours, trading below the 50EMA; this could confirm a potential correction to $26,200 or even $25,000, according to the analyst. These levels represent significant support zones for Bitcoin; the cryptocurrency could see a further downside if they fail to hold.</p>
<p>Furthermore, according to Ali, The Bitcoin network is showing signs of contraction, with declining user adoption and a series of lower highs and lower lows. This decreasing trend of wallet activity could signal a drop in Bitcoin&#8217;s price shortly.</p>
<p>As BTC adoption declines, the demand for the cryptocurrency also decreases. This ultimately puts downward pressure on BTC’s price, as fewer people are interested in buying and holding the cryptocurrency. The trend of lower highs and lower lows seen in the Bitcoin network suggests that the cryptocurrency&#8217;s price may be headed for a correction.</p>
<p>Added to this, more bad news for Bitcoin bulls mounts; Bitcoin&#8217;s largest whale address, owned by Binance, has been highly active in the market, moving $2.26 billion worth of Bitcoin in just four transactions, according to Santiment <a href="https://twitter.com/santimentfeed/status/1655657014973054977?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">data</a>. This sudden movement has caused Bitcoin&#8217;s supply on exchanges to drop from 6.78% to 5.84%, indicating that the whale may transfer Bitcoin to a cold storage or custody solution.</p>
<b>BTC Above $25500, Signals Long-Term Bullish Trend</b>
<p>Despite recent market fluctuations, BTC is still showing a strong upward trend, according to the <a href="https://twitter.com/TheBirbNest/status/1655671088867581964?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">analysis </a>of the weekly BTCUSD chart by The Birb Nest, a cryptocurrency and investment platform. Furthermore, BTC is trading above the rising 200-week trend and the flattening 50-week trend, which is a positive indicator. </p>
<p>The Birb Nest has pointed out that the upward trend will likely continue if Bitcoin remains above the $25,500 level. However, the crypto analysis firms keep a potential visit down to the $25,000 level. This level is seen as a key support level for Bitcoin, and a sustained hold above it could signal a bullish outlook for the cryptocurrency.</p>
<p>Moreover, The Birb Nest has noted that there has been a weakened relationship between Bitcoin and the S&amp;P 500 prices in recent weeks. This is reflected in the 7-week correlation coefficient, which stands at 0.39.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-530587 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Fvof-QXoAIVGuF-860x453.png" alt="Bitcoin " width="860" height="453" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Fvof-QXoAIVGuF-860x453.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Fvof-QXoAIVGuF-460x243.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Fvof-QXoAIVGuF-768x405.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Fvof-QXoAIVGuF-1536x810.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Fvof-QXoAIVGuF-2048x1080.png 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Fvof-QXoAIVGuF-750x395.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Fvof-QXoAIVGuF-1140x601.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" />
<p>Although the correlation between Bitcoin and the S&amp;P 500 has weakened, it remains positive. This suggests that both assets still share some similarities in terms of price movements. Therefore, if there are gains or losses in large-cap stocks, Bitcoin will likely be somewhat affected.</p>

<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/NafArOq1/" alt="Bitcoin " width="1813" height="858" />
<p>Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/andy-holmes-7blhgOFY_O8-unsplash-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Discovering The Next PEPE And SHIB: Whales To Keep Track Of</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/altcoin/discovering-the-next-pepe-and-shib-whales-to-keep-track-of/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Edyme]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 20:30:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[memecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PEPE]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIB]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shiba Inu]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=530543</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Missing out on crypto that becomes the next big thing in crypto can hurt. To avoid this, popular on-chain analyst LookOnChain has sorted out prominent whales to keep an eye on and ease the task of catching the next PEPE. According to the analyst, these whales were very early to notable meme coins such as Shiba Inu (SHIB). LookOnChain noted these whales are “smartMoneys that both bought SHIB and PEPE early and made millions of USD.” Discovering The Next Memecoin That Could Run 100x In a series of threads, LookOnChain unveiled three SmartMoney wallet addresses that invested early before the bull run. Whales are large cryptocurrency investors believed to understand the market well and make early and efficient investment decisions.  They are mostly known to take long-term positions in projects they believe in. Other investors closely follow their actions to capitalize on their investment strategies. Related Reading: Study: Shiba Inu (SHIB) Is More Of A Successful Memecoin Than PEPE and DOGE According to data from Etherscan, the first address highlighted by LookOnChain is one of the earliest SHIB buyers. It purchased 1.31 trillion tokens for $13.5K in February 2021, when the SHIB traded at $0.00000001.  This individual later sold the tokens for $5.81 million during the bull run, earning a profit of over $5.8 million. Interestingly, this same address started investing in PEPE as early as April 17, well before the asset became hype among investors, buying a total of 396.7 billion PEPE with $9,815.  After selling 116.8 billion tokens from its PEPE holdings for $392K, the address now holds 280 billion PEPE, with $1.18 million in realized and unrealized profits. Another address, which began investing in SHIB as early as April 2021, made a profit of $3.84 million on their investment.  This same address started purchasing PEPE on April 19, buying 558.5 billion PEPE with $286K. The current unrealized profit on the token investment held by this address is $1.34 million. LookOnChain also mentioned an address associated with the domain “cryptopolitan.eth” that purchased SHIB in February 2021 at the same time as the first address, making a profit of $2.45 million on the investment.  This same address began purchasing PEPE on April 19, buying 340 billion PEPE with $103,000. As of this writing, cryptopolitan has secured a profit of $695,000 from the frog meme token investment. Related Reading: PEPE Whale Transfers 4.23 Trillion Coins To Binance – Will Price Tank? PEPE: Ran Out Of Gas Meanwhile, the memecoin crashed after making significant waves in the crypto industry over the past week. The memecoin is now beginning to see a price decline, indicating traders are profiting or getting bored of the memecoin.  The token’s rally initially started late last month. This was when the memecoin pumped from a low of $0.00000002 on April 27 to as high as $0.0000042 on May 5. This growth drew the attention of many traders and investors, who saw it as an opportunity to profit from meme-inspired crypto. The price of the token began to decline soon after reaching that peak. As of May 8, the token price had fallen to $0.000000211, representing a decline of 51% from its all-time high. Featured image from The Block, Chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Missing out on crypto that becomes the next big thing in crypto can hurt. To avoid this, popular on-chain analyst LookOnChain has <a href="https://twitter.com/lookonchain/status/1654745103557341184?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">sorted</a> out prominent whales to keep an eye on and ease the task of catching the next PEPE.</p>
<p>According to the analyst, these whales were very early to notable meme coins such as <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/shiba-inu-whales-accumulate-price-drops/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Shiba Inu (SHIB)</a>. LookOnChain noted these whales are “smartMoneys that both bought SHIB and PEPE early and made millions of USD.”</p>
<h2>Discovering The Next Memecoin That Could Run 100x</h2>
<p>In a series of threads, LookOnChain unveiled three SmartMoney wallet addresses that invested early before the bull run. Whales are large cryptocurrency investors believed to understand the market well and make early and efficient investment decisions. </p>
<p>They are mostly known to take long-term positions in projects they believe in. Other investors closely follow their actions to capitalize on their investment strategies.</p>

<p>According to <a href="https://etherscan.io/address/0x778c029675d3e2435cf4c207e981d37c2174bec8" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">data</a> from Etherscan, the first address <a href="https://debank.com/profile/0x778c029675d3e2435cf4c207e981d37c2174bec8" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">highlighted</a> by LookOnChain is one of the earliest SHIB buyers. It purchased 1.31 trillion tokens for $13.5K in February 2021, when the SHIB traded at $0.00000001. </p>
<p>This individual later sold the tokens for $5.81 million during the bull run, earning a profit of over $5.8 million. Interestingly, this same address started investing in <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/shiba-inu-shib-is-successful-memecoin-than-pepe-and-doge/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">PEPE</a> as early as April 17, well before the asset became hype among investors, buying a total of 396.7 billion PEPE with $9,815. </p>
<p>After selling 116.8 billion tokens from its PEPE holdings for $392K, the address now holds 280 billion PEPE, with $1.18 million in realized and unrealized profits. Another <a href="https://debank.com/profile/0x2af8ae409ac94ed6fbd7d6c8751f3fbdf055ab3e" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">address</a>, which began investing in SHIB as early as April 2021, made a profit of $3.84 million on their investment. </p>
<p>This same address started purchasing PEPE on April 19, buying 558.5 billion PEPE with $286K. The current unrealized profit on the token investment held by this address is $1.34 million.</p>
<p>LookOnChain also mentioned an <a href="https://debank.com/profile/0xb8adcc8e382a7c43bdfa2e1c47059a1afec10e06" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">address</a> associated with the domain “cryptopolitan.eth” that purchased SHIB in February 2021 at the same time as the first address, making a profit of $2.45 million on the investment. </p>
<p>This same address began purchasing PEPE on April 19, buying 340 billion PEPE with $103,000. As of this writing, cryptopolitan has secured a profit of $695,000 from the frog meme token investment.</p>

<h2>PEPE: Ran Out Of Gas</h2>
<p>Meanwhile, the memecoin crashed after making significant waves in the crypto industry over the past week. The memecoin is now beginning to see a price decline, indicating traders are profiting or getting bored of the memecoin. </p>
<p>The token’s rally initially started late last month. This was when the memecoin pumped from a low of $0.00000002 on April 27 to as high as $0.0000042 on May 5. This growth drew the attention of many traders and investors, who saw it as an opportunity to profit from meme-inspired crypto.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/NtxASZw0/" alt="PEPE price chart on TradingView" width="2768" height="1556" />
<p>The price of the token began to decline soon after reaching that peak. As of May 8, the token price had fallen to $0.000000211, representing a decline of 51% from its all-time high.</p>
<p>Featured image from The Block, Chart from TradingView</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Pepe-Coin-The-Rise-of-a-New-Meme-Coin-in-2023-750x536-1-460x329.png" width="460" height="329" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Pro-XRP Lawyer Weighs In On The Ongoing Lawsuit Ruling</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/ripple/pro-xrp-lawyer-weighs-in-on-the-ongoing-lawsuit-ruling/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mike D.]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 18:50:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bill Morgan]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[John Deaton]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrp]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=530517</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bill Morgan has weighed in on discussions regarding the XRP lawsuit while the crypto community awaits the judge&#8217;s ruling. Morgan responded to a Twitter user, Marc Fagel, who’s been debating the XRP lawsuit with John Deaton. Morgan noted that Judge Torres was clear regarding her line of judgment on the Ripple case. Notably, the main issue in the case is whether or not Ripple sold XRP as a security. Related Reading: How Long Will Dogecoin Remain Sideways As Sellers Threaten Bearish Breakout? Bill Morgan on Judge Torres In Bill Morgan’s opinion, Judge Torres will base her judgment on facts regardless of the SEC&#8217;s broad and undefined position. Also, Ripple argues that it did not require registration since it didn’t sell XRP as an investment contract. Judge Torres made it very clear in the Daubert motion decision that the issue she must decide is whether Ripple sold XRP as a security despite the SEC taking broader positions at times in this litigation that seemed to suggest any sale of XRP was an investment contract or /1 https://t.co/HL1mclv8Xg pic.twitter.com/BrcHGAQlG9 &#8212; bill morgan (@Belisarius2020) May 8, 2023 However, the SEC took a broader stand that all XRP sales are securities, relying on the first allegation that Ripple distributed XRP through statutory underwriters. Morgan is unsure how Judge Torres will decide the case and why the SEC overstretches its positions towards XRP sales in the secondary market. Morgan noted that the SEC argues that Ripple’s XRP continuous offering in the secondary market violates securities law, stretching toward ODL customers who are not investors. In addition, he said that all XRP sales occur in the secondary market since Ripple has only offered XRP to ODL partners since 2020. Related Reading: Bitcoin Block 788695: The Day Transaction Fees Took The Crown He also responded to the founder of Crypto Capital, Justin Bons’ comment that Ripple’s defense hinges on XRP decentralization. According to Morgan, Ripple&#8217;s defense does not hinge on the XRP ledger&#8217;s decentralization but on the Howey test application.  However, the court is yet to decide the factual relevance of decentralization based on the Howey test. Congress Should Prohibit Regulators From Working At Firms They Regulated Recall that John Deaton called out the SEC on May 5 for its broad and undefined position on the XRP lawsuit. Deaton further noted the SEC couldn&#8217;t tag XRP as security since the sales do not meet the prongs in the Howey Test. The attorney weighed in again today, noting specific things that should change in the SEC. The US-based lawyer said Congress should pass a law prohibiting regulators from leaving to work at a firm they previously regulated for at least three years. Featured image from Pexels and chart from Tradingview]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bill Morgan has weighed in on discussions regarding the XRP lawsuit while the crypto community awaits the judge&#8217;s ruling. Morgan responded to a Twitter user, <a href="https://twitter.com/Marc_Fagel/status/1655344992255361024" rel="nofollow">Marc Fagel</a>, who’s been debating the XRP lawsuit with John Deaton.</p>
<p>Morgan noted that Judge Torres was clear regarding her line of judgment on the Ripple case. Notably, the main issue in the case is whether or not Ripple sold XRP as a security.</p>

<h2>Bill Morgan on Judge Torres</h2>
<p>In Bill Morgan’s opinion, Judge Torres will base her judgment on facts regardless of the SEC&#8217;s broad and undefined position. Also, Ripple argues that it did not require registration since it didn’t sell XRP as an investment contract.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Judge Torres made it very clear in the Daubert motion decision that the issue she must decide is whether Ripple sold XRP as a security despite the SEC taking broader positions at times in this litigation that seemed to suggest any sale of XRP was an investment contract or /1 <a href="https://t.co/HL1mclv8Xg" rel="nofollow">https://t.co/HL1mclv8Xg</a> <a href="https://t.co/BrcHGAQlG9" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/BrcHGAQlG9</a></p>
<p>&mdash; bill morgan (@Belisarius2020) <a href="https://twitter.com/Belisarius2020/status/1655404988934537216?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">May 8, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p></p>
<p>However, the SEC took a broader stand that all XRP sales are securities, relying on the first allegation that Ripple distributed XRP through statutory underwriters.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-530518 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSDT_2023-05-08_19-26-12-860x370.png" alt="Pro-XRP Lawyer Weighs In On The Ongoing Lawsuit Ruling" width="860" height="370" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSDT_2023-05-08_19-26-12-860x370.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSDT_2023-05-08_19-26-12-460x198.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSDT_2023-05-08_19-26-12-768x331.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSDT_2023-05-08_19-26-12-1536x661.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSDT_2023-05-08_19-26-12-750x323.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSDT_2023-05-08_19-26-12-1140x491.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSDT_2023-05-08_19-26-12.png 1714w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" />
<p>Morgan is unsure how Judge Torres will decide the case and why the SEC overstretches its positions towards XRP sales in the secondary market.</p>
<p>Morgan noted that the SEC argues that Ripple’s XRP continuous offering in the secondary market violates securities law, stretching toward ODL customers who are not investors. In addition, he <a href="https://twitter.com/Belisarius2020/status/1655439264614879232?cxt=HHwWgMDUqbDPpvktAAAA" rel="nofollow">said</a> that all XRP sales occur in the secondary market since Ripple has only offered XRP to ODL partners since 2020.</p>

<p>He also <a href="https://twitter.com/Belisarius2020/status/1655450136548610054?cxt=HHwWjMDQxZrIq_ktAAAA" rel="nofollow">responded</a> to the founder of Crypto Capital, Justin Bons’ <a href="https://twitter.com/Justin_Bons/status/1654916881403240449" rel="nofollow">comment</a> that Ripple’s defense hinges on XRP decentralization. According to Morgan, Ripple&#8217;s defense does not hinge on the XRP ledger&#8217;s decentralization but on the Howey test application. </p>
<p>However, the court is yet to decide the factual relevance of decentralization based on the Howey test.</p>
<h2>Congress Should Prohibit Regulators From Working At Firms They Regulated</h2>
<p>Recall that John Deaton <a href="https://twitter.com/JohnEDeaton1/status/1654370806045048832" rel="nofollow">called out</a> the SEC on May 5 for its broad and undefined position on the XRP lawsuit. Deaton further <a href="https://twitter.com/JohnEDeaton1/status/1654280863339651072" rel="nofollow">noted</a> the SEC couldn&#8217;t tag XRP as security since the sales do not meet the prongs in the Howey Test.</p>
<p>The attorney weighed in again today, noting specific things that should change in the SEC. The US-based lawyer <a href="https://twitter.com/JohnEDeaton1/status/1655338482670399488?cxt=HHwWgMDTqYzl-PgtAAAA" rel="nofollow">said</a> Congress should pass a law prohibiting regulators from leaving to work at a firm they previously regulated for at least three years.</p>
<p>Featured image from Pexels and chart from Tradingview</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ripple-XRP-460x276.jpeg" width="460" height="276" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance Records Highest BTC Outflows In its History; What&#8217;s the Catch?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/binance-records-highest-btc-outflows-in-its-history-whats-the-catch/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mike D.]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 18:00:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=530513</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The latest report by on-chain tracker Whalewire shows Binance is experiencing unusual Bitcoin outflows over the past 24 hours, the highest in its history. Whalewire reported that over 162,000 BTC, worth more than $4.5 billion, left the exchange in a day. The tracker believes something fishy is ongoing with Binance, as the crypto exchange has halted withdrawals three times today and has been offline for several hours. According to Whalewire, Bitcoin volume has plunged over 65% over the last 30 days. 162,000 BTC Moved In a Day, WhaleWire Reports Binance, the largest cryptocurrency exchange, has been relatively stable and resilient amid several ups and downs in the crypto industry. However, the recent observation leaves one speculating if something fishy is going on with the exchange. BREAKING: #Binance outflow data confirms largest withdrawal in it&#39;s history, over 162,000 $BTC has left the exchange, valued at over $4.6 Billion. Are Whales/Insiders jumping ship? 👀 pic.twitter.com/QSXYAEvHkt &#8212; WhaleWire (@WhaleWire) May 7, 2023 Whalewire has called attention to the latest on-chain data recorded on CryptoQuant. The data shows Bitcoin outflow on Binance reached an all-time high of 162,000 BTC worth over $4.5 billion following current prices. Related Reading: Bitcoin Block 788695: The Day Transaction Fees Took The Crown The data appear disturbing, as it could cause fear, uncertainty, and doubt, triggering massive price slumps across the market.  However, some respondents said Binance might be moving the coins to cold storage, while others blamed it on network congestion.  Binance Clarifies Reason Behind Massive Bitcoin Outflows Binance also confirmed this in a tweet posted about four (4) hours ago to reassure that it is aware of the large outflow recorded by some on-chain trackers. The exchange clarified that it moved Bitcoin from hot to cold wallets due to Bitcoin address adjustments. We’re aware that some data are showing a large volume of outflows from #Binance. This ‘outflow’ are actually movements between Binance hot and cold wallets due to the BTC address adjustments. &#8212; Binance (@binance) May 8, 2023 True to Binance’s reasons for the massive outflows, the Bitcoin network is experiencing issues, resulting in congestion and high fees.  According to a crypto enthusiast with a Twitter account @CryptoTea, Alexa, there are over 400,000 pending transactions on the Bitcoin network. Related Reading: How Long Will Dogecoin Remain Sideways As Sellers Threaten Bearish Breakout? Crypto Tea claimed the Bitcoin network witnessed an exploit that allowed people to upload useless data to the blockchain. According to Crypto Tea, one person alone uploaded 10,000 pictures of monkeys to the Bitcoin blockchain, increasing the number of nodes by 1.4 GB. Now, the network memory use has reached 1 GB above a 300 MB limit. However, another Bitcoin enthusiast has discounted the rumor that Bitcoin was the subject of an attack, saying that the increased usage due to the BRC-20 meme coins was the reason for the congestion. The discrepancy caused congestions that led Binance to move BTC into cold wallets, halting withdrawals while the issues get resolved. It&#8217;s still uncertain how this issue will affect Bitcoin, but its price is 3.29% down in the last 24 hours. Featured image from Pexels and chart from Tradingview.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The latest report by on-chain tracker Whalewire shows Binance is experiencing unusual Bitcoin outflows over the past 24 hours, the highest in its history. Whalewire reported that over 162,000 BTC, worth more than $4.5 billion, left the exchange in a day.</p>
<p>The tracker <a href="https://twitter.com/WhaleWire/status/1655396244678647809" rel="nofollow">believes</a> something fishy is ongoing with Binance, as the crypto exchange has halted withdrawals three times today and has been offline for several hours. According to Whalewire, Bitcoin volume has plunged over 65% over the last 30 days.</p>
<h2>162,000 BTC Moved In a Day, WhaleWire Reports</h2>
<p>Binance, the largest cryptocurrency exchange, has been relatively stable and resilient amid several ups and downs in the crypto industry. However, the recent observation leaves one speculating if something fishy is going on with the exchange.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">BREAKING: <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Binance?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#Binance</a> outflow data confirms largest withdrawal in it&#39;s history, over 162,000 <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24BTC&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$BTC</a> has left the exchange, valued at over $4.6 Billion.</p>
<p>Are Whales/Insiders jumping ship? <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f440.png" alt="👀" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> <a href="https://t.co/QSXYAEvHkt" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/QSXYAEvHkt</a></p>
<p>&mdash; WhaleWire (@WhaleWire) <a href="https://twitter.com/WhaleWire/status/1655339441416724482?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">May 7, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p></p>
<p>Whalewire has called attention to the latest on-chain data recorded on CryptoQuant. The data shows Bitcoin outflow on Binance reached an all-time high of 162,000 BTC worth over $4.5 billion following current prices.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-block-788695-the-day-transaction-fees-took-the-crown/?swcfpc=1">Bitcoin Block 788695: The Day Transaction Fees Took The Crown</a></p>
<p>The data appear disturbing, as it could cause fear, uncertainty, and doubt, triggering massive price slumps across the market. </p>
<p>However, some respondents <a href="https://twitter.com/briankizer9/status/1655342596632215553" rel="nofollow">said</a> Binance might be moving the coins to cold storage, while others blamed it on network congestion. </p>
<h2>Binance Clarifies Reason Behind Massive Bitcoin Outflows</h2>
<p>Binance also confirmed this in a tweet posted about four (4) hours ago to reassure that it is aware of the large outflow recorded by some on-chain trackers. The exchange clarified that it moved Bitcoin from hot to cold wallets due to Bitcoin address adjustments.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">We’re aware that some data are showing a large volume of outflows from <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Binance?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#Binance</a>. </p>
<p>This ‘outflow’ are actually movements between Binance hot and cold wallets due to the BTC address adjustments.</p>
<p>&mdash; Binance (@binance) <a href="https://twitter.com/binance/status/1655430207023747074?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">May 8, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p></p>
<p>True to Binance’s reasons for the massive outflows, the Bitcoin network is experiencing issues, resulting in congestion and high fees. </p>
<p>According to a crypto enthusiast with a Twitter account <a href="https://twitter.com/CryptoTea_/status/1655284474660151298" rel="nofollow">@CryptoTea</a>, Alexa, there are over 400,000 pending transactions on the Bitcoin network.</p>

<p>Crypto Tea claimed the Bitcoin network witnessed an exploit that allowed people to upload useless data to the blockchain. According to Crypto Tea, one person alone uploaded 10,000 pictures of monkeys to the Bitcoin blockchain, increasing the number of nodes by 1.4 GB. Now, the network memory use has reached 1 GB above a 300 MB limit.</p>
<p>However, another Bitcoin enthusiast has <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-maximalists-dismiss-dos-attack-claims/" rel="nofollow">discounted</a> the rumor that Bitcoin was the subject of an attack, saying that the increased usage due to the BRC-20 meme coins was the reason for the congestion.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-530514 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSDT_2023-05-08_19-02-21-860x371.png" alt="Bitcoin Binance" width="860" height="371" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSDT_2023-05-08_19-02-21-860x371.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSDT_2023-05-08_19-02-21-460x198.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSDT_2023-05-08_19-02-21-768x331.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSDT_2023-05-08_19-02-21-1536x662.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSDT_2023-05-08_19-02-21-750x323.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSDT_2023-05-08_19-02-21-1140x491.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSDT_2023-05-08_19-02-21.png 1713w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" />
<p>The discrepancy caused congestions that led Binance to move BTC into cold wallets, halting withdrawals while the issues get resolved. It&#8217;s still uncertain how this issue will affect <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/bitcoin/" rel="nofollow">Bitcoin,</a> but its price is 3.29% down in the last 24 hours.</p>
<p>Featured image from Pexels and chart from Tradingview.com</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/pexels-alesia-kozik-6765363-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Chainlink (LINK) Price Crumbles As The Bears Take Down Previous Gains</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/chainlink/chainlink-link-price-crumbles-as-the-bears-take-down-previous-gains/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Eli Dambel]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 17:20:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Chainlink]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bears]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[chainlink]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[linkusdt]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=530486</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The bullish trend that Chainlink (LINK) has enjoyed for much of its existence seems to have recently ended. The price of LINK has crumbled as the bears take down the bulls, leaving investors wondering what the future holds for the asset. There was a significant 24.55% decrease within the past weeks in the Chainlink (LINK) market. Notably, on April 18, 2023, LINK dropped from $8.795 to a low of $6.635, changing the trend to favor the bears. Chainlink (LINK) In A Consistent Bearish Trend LINK is trading in the red today, May 8, 2023. As of the time of writing, the price is $6.66, representing a decline of 3.31%. Also, its 7 days price gains have declined, sitting at a loss of 3.44%.  LINK price kickstarted a downtrend from April 19, when it lost grip on the $8 price mark to $7. It fell below $7 to $6.91 and $6.99 on May 1 and 2 before reclaiming the $7 price. However, it continued declining till the current price of $6.94 today. Related Reading: Shiba Inu: Whales Accumulate Yet Price Drops – What’s Going On? Currently, the chainlink Fear &#38; Greed Index is 55. This sentiment indicates that LINK’s market is presently neutral or slightly optimistic. One of the key factors contributing to the bearish sentiment around LINK is the general market trend. One of the key factors contributing to the bearish sentiment around LINK is the general market trend. The cryptocurrency market has been highly volatile over the last two weeks, with many assets, including Bitcoin and Ethereum, experiencing significant price drops.  However, it is still uncertain whether the bulls will retake power and drive the price of LINK upward or if the bears will continue to rule the market. LINK Technical Analysis The Chainlink trading chart for May 8, 2023, shows its market trend is bearish, and LINK shows negative momentum. Currently, the asset is trading below its 200-Day and 50-Day Simple Moving Averages (SMA). This indicates a bearish trend in the market. This also shows that both long-term and short-term trends are bearish. LINK price is lower than its average price over the past 50 days and 200 days, respectively, and the market&#8217;s selling pressure is high. The Relative Strength Index (RSI) is at 38.68; this shows that LINK is currently low selling pressure. An RSI below 50 indicates that the bears control the market. Lastly, the MACD line is trading below the signal line, indicating that the sellers have more control than the buyers. The MACD histogram also confirms the bearish sentiment as it is below the zero line. The momentum will continue if the bulls cannot maintain the selling pressure. Technical analysis/indicators are subjective and do not guarantee future performance. It should be used with other forms of analysis tools. Featured image from Pixabay and chart from Tradingview.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The bullish trend that Chainlink (LINK) has enjoyed for much of its existence seems to have recently ended. The price of LINK has crumbled as the bears take down the bulls, leaving investors wondering what the future holds for the asset.</p>
<p>There was a significant 24.55% decrease within the past weeks in the Chainlink (LINK) market. Notably, on April 18, 2023, LINK dropped from $8.795 to a low of $6.635, changing the trend to favor the bears.</p>
<h2>Chainlink (LINK) In A Consistent Bearish Trend</h2>
<p>LINK is trading <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/" rel="nofollow">in the red</a> today, May 8, 2023. As of the time of writing, the price is $6.66, representing a decline of 3.31%. Also, its 7 days price gains have declined, sitting at a loss of 3.44%. </p>
<p>LINK price kickstarted <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/chainlink/historical_data#panel" rel="nofollow">a downtrend </a>from April 19, when it lost grip on the $8 price mark to $7. It fell below $7 to $6.91 and $6.99 on May 1 and 2 before reclaiming the $7 price. However, it continued declining till the current price of $6.94 today.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/shiba-inu-whales-accumulate-price-drops/?swcfpc=1">Shiba Inu: Whales Accumulate Yet Price Drops – What’s Going On?</a></p>
<p>Currently, the chainlink <a href="https://cfgi.io/chainlink-fear-greed-index/" rel="nofollow">Fear &amp; Greed Index</a> is 55. This sentiment indicates that LINK’s market is presently neutral or slightly optimistic. One of the key factors contributing to the bearish sentiment around LINK is the general market trend.</p>
<p>One of the key factors contributing to the bearish sentiment around LINK is the general market trend. The cryptocurrency market has been highly volatile over the last two weeks, with many assets, including Bitcoin and Ethereum, experiencing significant price drops. </p>
<p>However, it is still uncertain whether the bulls will retake power and drive the price of LINK upward or if the bears will continue to rule the market.</p>
<h2>LINK Technical Analysis</h2>
<p>The Chainlink trading chart for May 8, 2023, shows its market trend is bearish, and LINK shows negative momentum.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-530492 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/LINKUSDT_2023-05-08_17-08-11-860x471.png" alt="Chainlink (LINK) Price Crumbles As The Bears Take Down Previous Gains" width="860" height="471" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/LINKUSDT_2023-05-08_17-08-11-860x471.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/LINKUSDT_2023-05-08_17-08-11-460x252.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/LINKUSDT_2023-05-08_17-08-11-768x420.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/LINKUSDT_2023-05-08_17-08-11-750x411.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/LINKUSDT_2023-05-08_17-08-11-1140x624.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/LINKUSDT_2023-05-08_17-08-11.png 1529w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" />
<p>Currently, the asset is trading below its 200-Day and 50-Day Simple Moving Averages (SMA). This indicates a bearish trend in the market. This also shows that both long-term and short-term trends are bearish.</p>
<p>LINK price is lower than its average price over the past 50 days and 200 days, respectively, and the market&#8217;s selling pressure is high.</p>
<p>The Relative Strength Index (RSI) is at 38.68; this shows that LINK is currently low selling pressure. An RSI below 50 indicates that the bears control the market.</p>
<p>Lastly, the MACD line is trading below the signal line, indicating that the sellers have more control than the buyers. The MACD histogram also confirms the bearish sentiment as it is below the zero line. The momentum will continue if the bulls cannot maintain the selling pressure.</p>
<p>Technical analysis/indicators are subjective and do not guarantee future performance. It should be used with other forms of analysis tools.</p>
<p>Featured image from Pixabay and chart from Tradingview.com</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/36916c121ba1402fbc496bf825c3052b-1-460x259.png" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>PEPE Token Futures Cast Gloom For Investors As Prices Plummet By 45%</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/pepe-prices-plummet-by-45/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 16:30:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[meme coin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PEPE price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PepeCoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price action]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=530498</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Pepecoin (PEPE) tokens were issued in mid-April and quickly gained popularity among investors, reaching a market capitalization of $1.8 billion in just over three weeks. However, the meme coin&#8217;s journey took a downward turn as the token dropped nearly 45% from their peak on Friday, causing a ripple of concern among investors. Some speculate that the sudden price drop was due to traders taking profits on their positions, while others point to the introduction of Pepe-tracked futures as a possible cause.  Either way, the Pepe token&#8217;s once-promising journey has hit a snag, leaving investors wondering whether this amphibian-inspired cryptocurrency can regain its footing and hop back into the limelight. Related Reading: Shiba Inu: Whales Accumulate Yet Price Drops – What’s Going On? PEPE Token&#8217;s Value Down After Short-Lived Rally As of writing, the PEPEUSD token&#8217;s price on CoinGecko stands at a mere $0.00000233, having fallen 10.6% in the past 24 hours. This comes as a disappointment to investors who had witnessed a remarkable seven-day rally, during which the token&#8217;s value had surged by a staggering 221.0%. The sudden downturn in the PEPEUSD&#8217;s value is a reminder of the volatility that characterizes the world of cryptocurrency. Despite the promising rally of the past week, the token&#8217;s current price suggests that caution is still warranted for those considering investing in this meme-inspired digital currency. Crypto total market cap weakens to $1.12 trillion. Chart: TradingView.com Related Reading: How Long Will Dogecoin Remain Sideways As Sellers Threaten Bearish Breakout? Following an unprecedented surge in value that saw PEPEUSD rise by almost 5,000,000% in just a few weeks, holders of the altcoin may be capitalizing on their gains by selling off their positions. This is reflected in the significant decline in the token&#8217;s value, which previously reached a peak of $0.00000431. Pepecoin had quickly taken the crypto market by storm, and in just over three weeks since its issuance in mid-April, it had achieved a market capitalization of $1.8 billion. However, the sudden drop in value indicates that the token&#8217;s meteoric rise may have been too good to last, and investors may be re-evaluating their positions accordingly. PEPEUSD Profits Converted To Ether As Deposits Hit New High Following the massive surge in Pepecoin&#8217;s value, investors are reportedly taking profits by converting their holdings into Ether (ETH), which recently hit an all-time high in deposits to exchanges since November 2021 when it reached a high of $4,500.  🚀 Updating our report on #Ethereum&#8216;s sky-high active deposits, exchange addresses interacting on the network is now at its highest level since November, 2021. As expected, $ETH is showing decoupling signs and on the cusp of breaking $2k once again. https://t.co/zYjY7669yj https://t.co/dQlKsTVyt2 pic.twitter.com/2nMXOUGgYC — Santiment (@santimentfeed) May 5, 2023 On Monday, Santiment, an on-chain analytics firm, suggested in a tweet that the rising number of Ether deposits could be a result of traders cashing out their Pepe positions. The Pepecoin rally has seen some investors turn small investments into significant profits within just a few days after the coin&#8217;s issuance. However, with the recent drop in the token&#8217;s value and the high volatility of cryptocurrency in general, investors should proceed with caution and conduct thorough research before investing in any digital currency.  (This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk) -Featured image from Alabama Cooperative Extension System ]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Pepecoin (PEPE) tokens were issued in mid-April and quickly gained popularity among investors, reaching a market capitalization of $1.8 billion in just over three weeks. However, the meme coin&#8217;s journey took a downward turn as the token dropped nearly 45% from their peak on Friday, causing a ripple of concern among investors.</p>
<p>Some speculate that the sudden price drop was due to traders taking profits on their positions, while others point to the introduction of Pepe-tracked futures as a possible cause. </p>
<p>Either way, the Pepe token&#8217;s once-promising journey has hit a snag, leaving investors wondering whether this amphibian-inspired cryptocurrency can regain its footing and hop back into the limelight.</p>

<h2><strong>PEPE Token&#8217;s Value Down After Short-Lived Rally</strong></h2>
<p>As of writing, the PEPEUSD token&#8217;s price on <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/pepe" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">CoinGecko</a> stands at a mere $0.00000233, having fallen 10.6% in the past 24 hours. This comes as a disappointment to investors who had witnessed a remarkable seven-day rally, during which the token&#8217;s value had surged by a staggering 221.0%.</p>
<p>The sudden downturn in the PEPEUSD&#8217;s value is a reminder of the volatility that characterizes the world of cryptocurrency. Despite the promising rally of the past week, the token&#8217;s current price suggests that caution is still warranted for those considering investing in this meme-inspired digital currency.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/tO3NVocP/" width="2047" height="979" /></p>


<p>Following an unprecedented surge in value that saw <a href="https://markets.businessinsider.com/news/currencies/pepecoins-bewildering-rise-turned-a-pittance-into-an-almost-5000000-meme-coin-profit-1032298533" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">PEPEUSD rise by almost 5,000,000%</a> in just a few weeks, holders of the altcoin may be capitalizing on their gains by selling off their positions. This is reflected in the significant decline in the token&#8217;s value, which previously reached a peak of $0.00000431.</p>
<p>Pepecoin had quickly taken the crypto market by storm, and in just over three weeks since its issuance in mid-April, it had achieved a market capitalization of $1.8 billion. However, the sudden drop in value indicates that the token&#8217;s meteoric rise may have been too good to last, and investors may be re-evaluating their positions accordingly.</p>
<h2><strong>PEPEUSD Profits Converted To Ether As Deposits Hit New High</strong></h2>
<p>Following the massive surge in Pepecoin&#8217;s value, investors are reportedly taking profits by converting their holdings into Ether (ETH), which recently hit an all-time high in deposits to exchanges since November 2021 when it reached a high of $4,500. </p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en"><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f680.png" alt="🚀" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> Updating our report on <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Ethereum?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#Ethereum</a>&#8216;s sky-high active deposits, exchange addresses interacting on the network is now at its highest level since November, 2021. As expected, <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24ETH&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$ETH</a> is showing decoupling signs and on the cusp of breaking $2k once again. <a href="https://t.co/zYjY7669yj" rel="nofollow">https://t.co/zYjY7669yj</a> <a href="https://t.co/dQlKsTVyt2" rel="nofollow">https://t.co/dQlKsTVyt2</a> <a href="https://t.co/2nMXOUGgYC" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/2nMXOUGgYC</a></p>
<p>— Santiment (@santimentfeed) <a href="https://twitter.com/santimentfeed/status/1654549272346628096?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">May 5, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p>On Monday, Santiment, an on-chain analytics firm, <a href="https://twitter.com/santimentfeed/status/1654549272346628096" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">suggested in a tweet</a> that the rising number of Ether deposits could be a result of traders cashing out their Pepe positions.</p>
<p>The Pepecoin rally has seen some investors turn small investments into significant profits within just a few days after the coin&#8217;s issuance. </p>
<p>However, with the recent drop in the token&#8217;s value and the high volatility of cryptocurrency in general, investors should proceed with caution and conduct thorough research before investing in any digital currency. </p>
<p><em>(This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk)</em></p>
<p><em>-Featured image from Alabama Cooperative Extension System </em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/a-25-460x321.png" width="460" height="321" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Stacks (STX) Surges 10% Due To Bitcoin Network Congestion</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/stacks-stx-surges-10-due-to-bitcoin-network-congestion/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jake Simmons]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 15:30:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stacks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[STX]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=530459</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[While the Bitcoin and crypto markets are deep in the red, one altcoin stands out today, posting a double-digit price increase: Stacks (STX). Along with the Lightning Network, the project is considered the most promising layer-2 technology for Bitcoin at the moment and is currently benefiting from the network congestion dilemma. There are currently over 425,000 unconfirmed transactions in the meme pool. Before being added to the Bitcoin blockchain, transactions are sent to the network&#8217;s meme pool, where they wait to be selected by a Bitcoin miner and inserted into the next Bitcoin block. At medium priority, a transaction currently costs an average of $19.04. The Case For Stacks The congestion is causing a heated debate: While one side calls it a DDoS attack on Bitcoin, the opposing side is calling the reason for the high fees, Bitcoin ordinals and BRC 20 tokens, a revolution. But no matter which side one takes, one thing becomes obvious. Layer-2 technologies are absolutely necessary and could emerge as a big winner. Revolution or DDoS? 🚀Market cap of BRC20 based #Bitcoin tokens reaches $1 billion. ⌛️Sh*tcoins are extremely congesting the network. There are still 425,000 unprocessed transactions piled up in the meme pool. &#8212; Jake Simmons (@realJakeSimmons) May 8, 2023 However, if the BTC price alone is to be the leading indicator, the current dilemma surrounding BRC20 tokens on the Bitcoin blockchain is not really doing the network any good. Binance hasn&#8217;t really done the market any favors either with the multiple withdrawal halts. Related Reading: Stacks (STX) Stumbles As Bulls Fail To Remain Intact But in the long run, higher fees are needed for the BTC network to replace the falling block reward. Co-inventor of Stacks, Muneeb Ali, therefore wrote today on Twitter that high fees are not an attack on Bitcoin, as they will be the norm when Bitcoin grows to a billion people. Rather, Ali says they are a wake-up call to developers to improve and grow Bitcoin L2s. Bitcoin fees just hit a new record. Up 500x from just a few months ago. Officially marks the start of the arms race to build the best Bitcoin L2s. Lightning, Stacks, and Rootstock have a head start. Time to build. Bitcoin expert Will Clemente also made the case for L2 today: If we are in a new regime of higher Bitcoin tx fees due to ordinals/brc-20s, think there’s a very compelling setup for the lightning network over the next few years. STX Rises 10% During the first days of May, the Stacks price has broken a downtrend that has lasted since March 20 (black line). Thanks to today&#8217;s 10% rise, the STX price now faces the 23.6% Fibonacci level at $0.82. At the price level, stronger resistance from the bears can be expected. Since April 19, STX has not managed to regain the mark. Related Reading: Stacks (STX) Price Defies Bears, Surges While The Market Bleeds If this succeeds, a rally to the region of $0.92, where the 38.2% Fibonacci is located, seems possible. Afterwards, the way to the psychologically important mark of $1 would be clear (50% Fibonacci). If the bulls also break through this level, $1.07 (61.8% Fibonacci) and $1.18 (78.6% Fibonacci) would be the next targets. Featured image from xVerse wallet, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>While the Bitcoin and crypto markets are <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/why-is-bitcoin-down-today-crypto-market-takes-hit/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">deep in the red</a>, one altcoin stands out today, posting a double-digit price increase: Stacks (STX). Along with the Lightning Network, the project is considered the most promising layer-2 technology for Bitcoin at the moment and is currently benefiting from the network congestion dilemma.</p>
<p>There are currently over 425,000 unconfirmed transactions in the meme pool. Before being added to the Bitcoin blockchain, transactions are sent to the network&#8217;s meme pool, where they wait to be selected by a Bitcoin miner and inserted into the next Bitcoin block. At medium priority, a transaction currently costs an average of $19.04.</p>
<h2>The Case For Stacks</h2>
<p>The congestion is causing a heated debate: While one side calls it a DDoS attack on Bitcoin, the opposing side is calling the reason for the high fees, Bitcoin ordinals and BRC 20 tokens, a revolution. But no matter which side one takes, one thing becomes obvious. Layer-2 technologies are absolutely necessary and could emerge as a big winner.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Revolution or DDoS?</p>
<p><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f680.png" alt="🚀" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />Market cap of BRC20 based <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Bitcoin?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#Bitcoin</a> tokens reaches $1 billion. </p>
<p><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/231b.png" alt="⌛" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />Sh*tcoins are extremely congesting the network. There are still 425,000 unprocessed transactions piled up in the meme pool.</p>
<p>&mdash; Jake Simmons (@realJakeSimmons) <a href="https://twitter.com/realJakeSimmons/status/1655526314114265088?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">May 8, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p></p>
<p>However, if the BTC price alone is to be the leading indicator, the current dilemma surrounding BRC20 tokens on the Bitcoin blockchain is not really doing the network any good. Binance hasn&#8217;t really done the market any favors either with the multiple withdrawal halts.</p>

<p>But in the long run, higher fees are needed for the BTC network to replace the falling block reward. Co-inventor of Stacks, Muneeb Ali, therefore <a href="https://twitter.com/muneeb/status/1655342436418310144" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">wrote</a> today on Twitter that high fees are not an attack on Bitcoin, as they will be the norm when Bitcoin grows to a billion people. Rather, Ali says they are a wake-up call to developers to improve and grow Bitcoin L2s.</p>
<blockquote><p><strong>Bitcoin fees just hit a new record. Up 500x from just a few months ago. Officially marks the start of the arms race to build the best Bitcoin L2s. Lightning, Stacks, and Rootstock have a head start. Time to build.</strong></p></blockquote>
<p>Bitcoin expert Will Clemente also <a href="https://twitter.com/WClementeIII/status/1655256488426852354" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">made</a> the case for L2 today:</p>
<blockquote><p><strong>If we are in a new regime of higher Bitcoin tx fees due to ordinals/brc-20s, think there’s a very compelling setup for the lightning network over the next few years.</strong></p></blockquote>
<h2>STX Rises 10%</h2>
<p>During the first days of May, the Stacks price has broken a downtrend that has lasted since March 20 (black line). Thanks to today&#8217;s 10% rise, the STX price now faces the 23.6% Fibonacci level at $0.82. At the price level, stronger resistance from the bears can be expected. Since April 19, STX has not managed to regain the mark.</p>

<p>If this succeeds, a rally to the region of $0.92, where the 38.2% Fibonacci is located, seems possible. Afterwards, the way to the psychologically important mark of $1 would be clear (50% Fibonacci). If the bulls also break through this level, $1.07 (61.8% Fibonacci) and $1.18 (78.6% Fibonacci) would be the next targets.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-530478 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/STXUSD_2023-05-08_13-46-29.png" alt="Stacks STX price" width="3625" height="1672" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/STXUSD_2023-05-08_13-46-29.png 3625w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/STXUSD_2023-05-08_13-46-29-460x212.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/STXUSD_2023-05-08_13-46-29-860x397.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/STXUSD_2023-05-08_13-46-29-768x354.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/STXUSD_2023-05-08_13-46-29-1536x708.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/STXUSD_2023-05-08_13-46-29-2048x945.png 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/STXUSD_2023-05-08_13-46-29-750x346.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/STXUSD_2023-05-08_13-46-29-1140x526.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 3625px) 100vw, 3625px" />

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/63d3f414697c542efdda61c9_stacksexplained_visual-460x222.jpg" width="460" height="222" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Shiba Inu Price Crash Persists Despite Trillions Of SHIB Tokens Being Bought Up</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/shiba-inu-price-crash-persists/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 15:01:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[meme coins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price action]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIB price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shiba Inu]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=530457</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Shiba Inu [SHIB] is facing a significant price drop despite trillions of the meme coins being purchased. However, this amount of purchase can&#8217;t seem to stop its price crash. What could be causing this downward trend, and will it continue in the coming months? Despite the large number of Shiba Inu tokens purchased, the cryptocurrency market remains highly speculative, and prices can be affected by a multitude of factors. Could it be that investors are losing faith in Shiba Inu&#8217;s long-term potential, or is this simply a temporary setback in a highly volatile market? As the Shiba Inu price continues to decline, many investors are left wondering whether they should hold on or cut their losses. Shiba Inu Token Volume Surges But Price Continues To Decline A recent report from cryptocurrency intelligence agency, IntoTheBlock, indicates that large buyers purchased over 10.25 trillion SHIB tokens in the past week, exceeding sales by 250 billion SHIB. Despite this volume surge, the price of SHIB has continued its downward trend for the third week in a row.  Interestingly, the week saw a spike in bullish sentiment, as large buyers seemed to dominate the market. However, this paradoxically did not translate to a rise in the token&#8217;s value. Although SHIB demonstrated growth from Monday to Wednesday, this trend was short-lived, and the token&#8217;s value fell during the next three days. This trend is in line with the recent bearish trend of the cryptocurrency market, which has been characterized by significant volatility and price declines.  Shiba Inu&#8217;s value on CoinGecko currently stands at a mere $0.00000899, having undergone a 4.2% slump in the past 24 hours and an 10.6% decline over the past seven days, leaving investors in a state of uncertainty about its future trajectory. Source: Coingecko Cryptocurrency Market Volatility And The Future Of SHIB The decline in SHIB&#8217;s price is not an isolated case but is instead reflective of the cryptocurrency market&#8217;s recent volatility. Both Bitcoin and Ethereum, the two largest cryptocurrencies by market capitalization, have also undergone significant price corrections in the past week, which has created uncertainty in the market. The fluctuation in prices can be attributed to several factors, including regulatory pressures, investor sentiment, and even environmental concerns around the energy consumption of mining cryptocurrencies.  Related Reading: Shiba Inu: Whales Accumulate Yet Price Drops – What’s Going On? SHIB total market cap at $5.3 billion on the daily chart at TradingView.com Related Reading: How Long Will Dogecoin Remain Sideways As Sellers Threaten Bearish Breakout? The recent slump in SHIB&#8217;s price can, therefore, be understood as part of a broader trend in the cryptocurrency market, which has been characterized by significant price declines and uncertainty. Moreover, with the growing popularity of alternative meme tokens like PEPE, investors may be exploring other options instead of SHIB, which could further contribute to the decline in SHIB&#8217;s price.  However, it is important to note that the cryptocurrency market is highly volatile and unpredictable, and it remains to be seen whether SHIB will recover from its recent slump or not. Investors need to exercise caution and undertake thorough research before making any investment decisions in the volatile cryptocurrency market. (This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk) -Featured image from iStock]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Shiba Inu [SHIB] is facing a significant price drop despite trillions of the meme coins being purchased. However, this amount of purchase can&#8217;t seem to stop its price crash. What could be causing this downward trend, and will it continue in the coming months?</p>
<p>Despite the large number of Shiba Inu tokens purchased, the cryptocurrency market remains highly speculative, and prices can be affected by a multitude of factors. </p>
<p>Could it be that investors are losing faith in Shiba Inu&#8217;s long-term potential, or is this simply a temporary setback in a highly volatile market?</p>
<p>As the Shiba Inu price continues to decline, many investors are left wondering whether they should hold on or cut their losses.</p>
<h2><strong>Shiba Inu Token Volume Surges But Price Continues To Decline</strong></h2>
<p>A recent report from cryptocurrency intelligence agency, <a href="https://app.intotheblock.com/coin/SHIB/deep-dive?group=all&amp;chart=all" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">IntoTheBlock</a>, indicates that large buyers purchased over 10.25 trillion SHIB tokens in the past week, exceeding sales by 250 billion SHIB. </p>
<p>Despite this volume surge, the price of SHIB has continued its downward trend for the third week in a row. </p>
<p>Interestingly, the week saw a spike in bullish sentiment, as large buyers seemed to dominate the market. However, this paradoxically did not translate to a rise in the token&#8217;s value.</p>
<p>Although SHIB demonstrated growth from Monday to Wednesday, this trend was short-lived, and the token&#8217;s value fell during the next three days. </p>
<p>This trend is in line with the recent bearish trend of the cryptocurrency market, which has been characterized by significant volatility and price declines. </p>
<p>Shiba Inu&#8217;s value on <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/shiba-inu" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">CoinGecko</a> currently stands at a mere $0.00000899, having undergone a 4.2% slump in the past 24 hours and an 10.6% decline over the past seven days, leaving investors in a state of uncertainty about its future trajectory.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-530491 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/a-24.png" alt="" width="1145" height="62" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/a-24.png 1145w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/a-24-460x25.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/a-24-860x47.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/a-24-768x42.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/a-24-1140x62.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/a-24-750x41.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 1145px) 100vw, 1145px" /></p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-530490 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/a-23.png" alt="" width="751" height="86" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/a-23.png 751w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/a-23-460x53.png 460w" sizes="(max-width: 751px) 100vw, 751px" /></p>

<h2><strong>Cryptocurrency Market Volatility And The Future Of SHIB</strong></h2>
<p>The decline in SHIB&#8217;s price is not an isolated case but is instead reflective of the cryptocurrency market&#8217;s recent volatility. Both Bitcoin and Ethereum, the two largest cryptocurrencies by market capitalization, have also undergone significant price corrections in the past week, which has created uncertainty in the market.</p>
<p>The fluctuation in prices can be attributed to several factors, including regulatory pressures, investor sentiment, and even environmental concerns around the energy consumption of mining cryptocurrencies. </p>

<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/gOWzlcBZ/" width="2047" height="979" /></p>


<p>The recent slump in SHIB&#8217;s price can, therefore, be understood as part of a broader trend in the cryptocurrency market, which has been characterized by significant price declines and uncertainty.</p>
<p>Moreover, with the <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-05-03/crypto-memecoin-mania-pepe-begins-to-cool-shortly-after-latest-renaissance" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">growing popularity</a> of alternative meme tokens like PEPE, investors may be exploring other options instead of SHIB, which could further contribute to the decline in SHIB&#8217;s price. </p>
<p>However, it is important to note that the cryptocurrency market is highly volatile and unpredictable, and it remains to be seen whether SHIB will recover from its recent slump or not. </p>
<p>Investors need to exercise caution and undertake thorough research before making any investment decisions in the volatile cryptocurrency market.</p>
<p><em>(This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk)</em></p>
<p><em>-Featured image from iStock</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/a-22-460x305.png" width="460" height="305" />	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
