<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
>

<channel>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.newsbtc.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<description>Bitcoin &#38; Cryptocurrency News Today</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 02:57:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Price Relatively Muted; Resistance Estimated Near $30,400</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-relatively-muted-30400/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 02:57:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xbtusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=543627</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin price is still consolidating above $29,500. BTC must settle above the $30,400 resistance zone to start a steady increase in the near term. Bitcoin is struggling to clear the $30,000 resistance level. The price is trading below $30,000 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average. There was a break below a key bullish trend line with support near $29,950 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Kraken). The pair could start a decent increase if there is a close above the $30,400 resistance. Bitcoin Price Remains In A Range Bitcoin price attempted a fresh increase above the $30,400 resistance zone. However, BTC struggled to settle above $30,400 and reacted to the downside. There was a break below a key bullish trend line with support near $29,950 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair. The pair declined below the $29,850 level but the downsides were limited. The price stayed above the $29,500 support. A low is formed near $29,591 and the price is now attempting a fresh increase. There was a move above the $29,650 level. Bitcoin price is now trading below $30,000 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average. Immediate resistance is near the $30,000 level and the 100 hourly Simple moving average. It is close to the 50% Fib retracement level of the recent decline from the $30,405 swing high to the $29,591 low. The first major resistance is near the $30,100 level. Source: BTCUSD on TradingView.com The 61.8% Fib retracement level of the recent decline from the $30,405 swing high to the $29,591 low is also near the $30,100 level. The next major resistance is near $30,400. A close above the $30,400 level might start a fresh increase. In the stated case, the price could rise toward the $30,800 level. Any more gains could open the doors for a move toward the $31,200 resistance zone. More Losses in BTC? If Bitcoin fails to clear the $30,000 resistance, it could continue to move down. Immediate support on the downside is near the $29,600 level. The next major support is near the $29,500 level, below which the price could accelerate lower. In the stated case, the price could drop toward the $29,200 support zone. Technical indicators: Hourly MACD – The MACD is now gaining pace in the bullish zone. Hourly RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BTC/USD is now near the 50 level. Major Support Levels – $29,600, followed by $29,500. Major Resistance Levels – $30,000, $30,100, and $31,400.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>Bitcoin price is still consolidating above $29,500. BTC must settle above the $30,400 resistance zone to start a steady increase in the near term.</em></p>
<ul>
<li>Bitcoin is struggling to clear the $30,000 resistance level.</li>
<li>The price is trading below $30,000 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average.</li>
<li>There was a break below a key bullish trend line with support near $29,950 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could start a decent increase if there is a close above the $30,400 resistance.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Bitcoin Price Remains In A Range</h2>
<p>Bitcoin price attempted a fresh increase above the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-increase-30200/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">$30,400 resistance zone</a>. However, BTC struggled to settle above $30,400 and reacted to the downside.</p>
<p>There was a break below a key bullish trend line with support near $29,950 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair. The pair declined below the $29,850 level but the downsides were limited. The price stayed above the $29,500 support.</p>
<p>A low is formed near $29,591 and the price is now attempting a fresh increase. There was a move above the $29,650 level. Bitcoin price is now trading below $30,000 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average.</p>
<p>Immediate resistance is near the $30,000 level and the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-bulls-pushing-31k/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">100 hourly Simple moving average</a>. It is close to the 50% Fib retracement level of the recent decline from the $30,405 swing high to the $29,591 low. The first major resistance is near the $30,100 level.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-543628" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-14.png" alt="Bitcoin Price" width="1835" height="845" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-14.png 1835w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-14-460x212.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-14-860x396.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-14-768x354.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-14-1536x707.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-14-750x345.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-14-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1835px) 100vw, 1835px"/></p>
<p>Source: <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BTCUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">BTCUSD on TradingView.com</a></p>
<p>The 61.8% Fib retracement level of the recent decline from the $30,405 swing high to the $29,591 low is also near the $30,100 level. The next major resistance is near $30,400. A close above the $30,400 level might start a fresh increase. In the stated case, the price could rise toward the $30,800 level. Any more gains could open the doors for a move toward the $31,200 resistance zone.</p>
<h2>More Losses in BTC?</h2>
<p>If Bitcoin fails to clear the $30,000 resistance, it could continue to move down. Immediate support on the downside is near the $29,600 level.</p>
<p>The next major support is near the $29,500 level, below which the price could accelerate lower. In the stated case, the price could drop toward the $29,200 support zone.</p>
<p>Technical indicators:</p>
<p>Hourly MACD – The MACD is now gaining pace in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>Hourly RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BTC/USD is now near the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Levels – $29,600, followed by $29,500.</p>
<p>Major Resistance Levels – $30,000, $30,100, and $31,400.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/shutterstock_1043982583-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Over 2 Million XRP Traded Every Minute, Path To Second Place After Bitcoin?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/ripple-2/2-million-xrp-traded-every-minute-second-place-bitcoin/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dalmas Ngetich]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 01:00:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrp]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=543607</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[On-chain data on July 19 shows that as much as 2 million XRP, the native currency of the XRP Ledger, were changing hands every minute on top cryptocurrency exchanges, including KuCoin and Poloniex. In a screen grab shared on Twitter, on-chain data reveals that more XRP was being traded in bulk, driving trading volumes higher across the board.  Accompanying the expansion, prices remain higher as of writing on July 20. The coin is up 72% from July 2023 lows, even though trading volumes in leading exchanges, including Binance, have since tapered slightly. Nonetheless, the resurgence in trading volumes this week suggests that the demand for the coin remains relatively higher. XRP And Its Spectacular Rally The token&#8217;s value experienced a surge following a recent court ruling declaring that the SEC could not provide evidence that it was a security. Per the Howey test, the judge concluded that XRP does not meet the legal definition of a security. Related Reading: SEC Allegedly Delays Assistance For US Crypto Market Bill Three years ago, in December 2020, the regulator filed a lawsuit alleging that Ripple, the blockchain company, and some of its executives, including Brad Garlinghouse, had raised over $1 billion through alleged illegal sales of XRP, an asset they claimed was an unregistered security. Ripple denied the allegations and fought the lawsuit, expending millions of dollars in legal expenses and eventually winning on this item.  Coinbase, Bitstamp, Crypto Exchanges Relisting The rally has also been boosted by the news that Coinbase Global, Kraken, and other top-tier cryptocurrency exchanges have relisted the token. Specifically, Coinbase delisted XRP in December 2020 following the SEC lawsuit, triggering a wave of delisting among cryptocurrency exchanges in the United States.  Relisting XRP across major exchanges could be a sign of confidence. It will likely boost the coin’s liquidity, increasing trading volumes in the coming months. Supporters find the listing a refreshing development, especially for clients in the United States who had been cut off from trading. Related Reading: Terraform Labs Appoints New CEO Following Do Kwon’s Sentencing In Montenegro Some predictions maintain that the token rally will likely continue in H2 2023. Judge Analisa Torres’ ruling in favor of Ripple Labs removed uncertainty around the coin&#8217;s status. This decision can also open more doors for institutional adoption.  Moreover, the rally and regulatory clarity cement the token&#8217;s position in the cryptocurrency market. This development may see it narrow its gap with Ethereum (ETH), perhaps even flipping it to become the second-largest coin after Bitcoin. In the last three years before the court ruling, the token shook off weakness and retained its slot in the top 10 cryptocurrencies by market capitalization amid the biting and extended crypto winter 2022. Feature image from Canva, chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On-chain data on July 19 <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://twitter.com/NCashOfficial/status/1681504537830457344" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">shows</a> that as much as 2 million XRP, the native currency of the XRP Ledger, were changing hands every minute on top cryptocurrency exchanges, including KuCoin and Poloniex. In a screen grab shared on Twitter, on-chain data reveals that more XRP was being traded in bulk, driving trading volumes higher across the board. </p>
<p>Accompanying the expansion, prices remain higher as of writing on July 20. The coin is up 72% from July 2023 lows, even though trading volumes in leading exchanges, including Binance, have since tapered slightly. Nonetheless, the resurgence in trading volumes this week suggests that the demand for the coin remains relatively higher.</p>
<a href="https://www.tradingview.com/x/KvwPSLE7/" rel="nofollow"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/KvwPSLE7/" alt="XRP price on July 20| Source: XRPUSDT on Binance, TradingView" width="1226" height="595"/></a>
<h2>XRP And Its Spectacular Rally</h2>
<p>The token&#8217;s value experienced a surge following a recent court ruling declaring that the SEC could not provide evidence that it was a security. Per the Howey test, the judge concluded that XRP does not meet the legal definition of a security.</p>

<p>Three years ago, in December 2020, the regulator filed a lawsuit alleging that Ripple, the blockchain company, and some of its executives, including Brad Garlinghouse, had raised over $1 billion through alleged illegal sales of XRP, an asset they claimed was an unregistered security. Ripple denied the allegations and fought the lawsuit, expending millions of dollars in legal expenses and eventually winning on this item. </p>
<h2>Coinbase, Bitstamp, Crypto Exchanges Relisting</h2>
<p>The rally has also been boosted by the news that Coinbase Global, <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://blog.bitstamp.net/post/xrp-is-back-in-the-us-start-trading-today/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Kraken</a>, and other top-tier cryptocurrency exchanges have relisted the token. Specifically, Coinbase delisted XRP in December 2020 following the SEC lawsuit, triggering a wave of delisting among cryptocurrency exchanges in the United States. </p>
<p>Relisting XRP across major exchanges could be a sign of confidence. It will likely boost the coin’s liquidity, increasing trading volumes in the coming months. Supporters find the listing a refreshing development, especially for clients in the United States who had been cut off from trading.</p>

<p>Some predictions <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.newsbtc.com/breaking-news-ticker/xrp-maintains-bullish-run/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">maintain</a> that the token rally will likely continue in H2 2023. Judge Analisa Torres’ ruling in favor of Ripple Labs removed uncertainty around the coin&#8217;s status. This decision can also open more doors for institutional adoption. </p>
<p>Moreover, the rally and regulatory clarity cement the token&#8217;s position in the cryptocurrency market. This development may see it narrow its gap with Ethereum (ETH), perhaps even flipping it to become the second-largest coin after Bitcoin. In the last three years before the court ruling, the token shook off weakness and retained its slot in the top 10 cryptocurrencies by market capitalization amid the biting and extended crypto winter 2022.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ripple-XRP-SEC-Bitcoin-Ethereum-460x260.jpg" width="460" height="260" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bullish Signal: Whales Accumulate Massive Amounts Of ARB</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/arb/bullish-signal-whales-accumulate-massive-amounts-of-arb/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Best Owie]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 23:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[ARB]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ARB whales]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Arbitrum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ARBUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ARBUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[whales]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=543529</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Through the bear market, Arbitrum (ARB) has been one of the tokens that have managed to hold on to a significant amount of its all-time high value. Along these same lines, the digital asset is one of the few tokens currently flashing a green bullish flag, and accumulation has ramped up as a result of this. ARB Whale Accumulation Ramps Up Transactions on the Arbitrum blockchain on Thursday, July 20, point to massive accumulation among large investors. These transactions were flagged by on-chain data tracker Lookonchain, going as far back as July 17 when the accumulation trend seemed to have begun. Related Reading: Why This Upcoming Event Is Bearish For Axie Infinity (AXS) On Monday, Lookonchain reported three transactions carrying 3.76 million ARB worth $5 million at the time from the Binance exchange to known whale wallets. While these transactions were significant, they did not stop there. The following day, July 18, the tracker spotted another transaction carrying 4 million ARB. The source of the transaction was the same, with the coins which were worth $5 million at the time being moved from Binance to a private wallet. The most recent whale accumulation happened on Wednesday, July 19, with the largest ARB withdrawals of the bunch. This time around, a whale identified as “0x6950” withdrew 4.6 million ARB worth $5.84 million at the time of the transaction, from Binance. Whale&#8221;0x6950&#8243; withdrew 4.6M $ARB ($5.84M) from #Binance again just now. The whale has withdrawn a total of 9M $ARB ($11.4M) from #Binance in the past 2 days.https://t.co/E9GCmJ7ftc pic.twitter.com/FNI1gBbxrd — Lookonchain (@lookonchain) July 19, 2023 All of these transactions point to a consistent accumulation trend among these large holders, which could suggest that they expect a price recovery to happen soon. Their withdrawals have also reduced the amount of selling pressure on the digital asset and this could also lend support to any rally from here on out. Arbitrum Continues To Dominate Layer 2 Blockchains Arbitrum has seen much success in the market and this contributes to the bullishness around its native ARB token. Arbitrum currently boasts the largest Total Value Locked (TVL) of all the Ethereum Layer 2 blockchains, including Polygon and Optimism. Related Reading: Back In The Game: Ripple Joins $54 Million Funding Round For Metaverse Startup While Polygon and Optimism TVLs are sitting at $1.027 billion and $926 million, respectively, the TVL of the Arbitrum network is at $2.68 billion. This figure makes the L2 the fourth-largest by TVL across all blockchains, coming up behind heavy hitters such as Ethereum, Tron, and BSC. With Arbitrum controlling a significant portion of the L2 TVL, expectations are that its native token will also surge alongside it. Currently, ARB is trading at $1.29 with a 3.33% price gain in the last 24 hours. However, the price could easily surge toward $1.5 if whale accumulations continue and sell pressure continues to decline. ARB price retests $1.3 resistance &#124; Source: ARBUSD on Tradingview.com Follow Best Owie on Twitter for market insights, updates, and the occasional funny tweet… Featured image from IQ.Wiki, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="p2">Through the bear market, Arbitrum (ARB) has been one of the tokens that have managed to hold on to a significant amount of its all-time high value. Along these same lines, the digital asset is one of the few tokens currently flashing a green bullish flag, and accumulation has ramped up as a result of this.</p>
<h2 class="p2">ARB Whale Accumulation Ramps Up</h2>
<p class="p2">Transactions on the Arbitrum blockchain on Thursday, July 20, point to massive accumulation among large investors. These transactions were flagged by on-chain data tracker Lookonchain, going as far back as July 17 when the accumulation trend seemed to have begun.</p>

<p class="p2">On Monday, Lookonchain <a href="https://twitter.com/lookonchain/status/1680829038020149250?s=20" rel="nofollow">reported</a> three transactions carrying 3.76 million ARB worth $5 million at the time from the Binance exchange to known whale wallets. While these transactions were significant, they did not stop there.</p>
<p class="p2">The following day, July 18, the tracker <a href="https://twitter.com/lookonchain/status/1681130243078365184?s=20" rel="nofollow">spotted</a> another transaction carrying 4 million ARB. The source of the transaction was the same, with the coins which were worth $5 million at the time being moved from Binance to a private wallet.</p>
<p class="p2">The most recent whale accumulation <a href="https://twitter.com/lookonchain/status/1681546063063425024?s=20" rel="nofollow">happened</a> on Wednesday, July 19, with the largest ARB withdrawals of the bunch. This time around, a whale identified as “0x6950” withdrew 4.6 million ARB worth $5.84 million at the time of the transaction, from Binance.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Whale&#8221;0x6950&#8243; withdrew 4.6M <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24ARB&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$ARB</a> ($5.84M) from <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Binance?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#Binance</a> again just now.</p>
<p>The whale has withdrawn a total of 9M <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24ARB&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$ARB</a> ($11.4M) from <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Binance?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#Binance</a> in the past 2 days.<a href="https://t.co/E9GCmJ7ftc" rel="nofollow">https://t.co/E9GCmJ7ftc</a> <a href="https://t.co/FNI1gBbxrd" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/FNI1gBbxrd</a></p>
<p>— Lookonchain (@lookonchain) <a href="https://twitter.com/lookonchain/status/1681546063063425024?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">July 19, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p class="p2">All of these transactions point to a consistent accumulation trend among these large holders, which could suggest that they expect a price recovery to happen soon. Their withdrawals have also reduced the amount of selling pressure on the digital asset and this could also lend support to any rally from here on out.</p>
<h2 class="p2">Arbitrum Continues To Dominate Layer 2 Blockchains</h2>
<p class="p2">Arbitrum has seen much success in the market and this contributes to the bullishness around its native ARB token. Arbitrum currently <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/arbitrum-could-be-the-best-layer-2-play/" rel="nofollow">boasts the largest Total Value Locked (TVL) of all the Ethereum Layer 2 blockchains</a>, including Polygon and Optimism.</p>

<p class="p2">While Polygon and Optimism TVLs are sitting at $1.027 billion and $926 million, respectively, the TVL of the Arbitrum network is at $2.68 billion. This figure makes the L2 the <a href="https://defillama.com/chains/Rollup" rel="nofollow">fourth-largest by TVL across all blockchains</a>, coming up behind heavy hitters such as Ethereum, Tron, and BSC.</p>
<p class="p2">With Arbitrum controlling a significant portion of the L2 TVL, expectations are that its native token will also surge alongside it. Currently, ARB is trading at $1.29 with a 3.33% price gain in the last 24 hours. However, the price could easily surge toward $1.5 if whale accumulations continue and sell pressure continues to decline.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/S5HzTCvc/" alt="Arbitrum (ARB) price chart from Tradingview.com" width="2884" height="1758"/></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Arbitrum-aRB-460x345.jpeg" width="460" height="345" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Did Justin Sun Use Fake Balance? Tron Founder&#8217;s $62 Million TUSD Minting Raises Eyebrows</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/trx/did-justin-sun-use-fake-balance-tron-founders-62-million-tusd-minting-raises-eyebrows/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 20:46:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[TRON]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Justin Sun]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=543615</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Crypto analyst Adam Cochran recently caused a stir in the cryptocurrency community when he called attention to a series of TrueUSD (TUSD) transactions made by Tron founder Justin Sun.  Cochran highlighted a series of transactions made by Sun&#8217;s address on the Tron blockchain, including minting $62 million worth of TUSD, withdrawing $50 million in USDT from Huobi, and depositing $50 million in USDT on Bitfinex. Justin Sun&#8217;s Dubious TUSD Transactions Perhaps most concerning, however, was Sun&#8217;s apparent burning of $50 million TUSD, which Cochran suggested could be an attempt to temporarily “snapshot or unwind” debt using a “fake” balance that was “unbacked”.  Cochran also pointed out that Sun appeared to be using Poloniex and Huobi as his own “piggy” banks to borrow against, with large amounts of Huobi assets being plowed into JustLend &#8211; an official lending platform on the TRON blockchain &#8211; for him to borrow against shitcoins. Related Reading: Bitcoin Bulls Rejoice: Blofin Forecasts $49,000 Price High With Potential Spot ETF Launch These transactions have raised questions about Sun&#8217;s motivations and the potential impact of his actions on the broader cryptocurrency market. In particular, Cochran expressed concern that Sun&#8217;s apparent “manipulation” of TUSD could create the appearance of greater liquidity in the market and potentially lead to price manipulation. Compounding these concerns is that Changpeng Zhao, the CEO of Binance, one of the world&#8217;s largest cryptocurrency exchanges, has reportedly offered voluntary termination packages to employees in multiple departments.  This move has raised questions about the financial stability of Binance and its potential exposure to Sun&#8217;s actions. Cochran concluded: CZ offered multiple departments &#8220;voluntary termination&#8221; offers where any staff member could apply to resign today, sign a new NDA and get a 3 month severance to quit. Totally normal thing to do after already big cuts&#8230;. The Uncertainty Of Justin Sun&#8217;s Cryptocurrency Moves The potential risks of Justin Sun&#8217;s transactions are unclear, as his motivations for these actions are unknown. However, several possible concerns have been raised in the crypto community.  One potential risk is the possibility of price manipulation. If Sun was attempting to manipulate the price of specific cryptocurrencies by creating the appearance of greater liquidity in the market, this could lead to price distortions that could harm investors and destabilize the market. Another risk is the possibility of a liquidity crisis. If Sun&#8217;s actions caused a sudden influx of TUSD or USDT into the market, this could lead to a sudden drop in the value of these cryptocurrencies, potentially causing a liquidity crisis and harming investors. There is also a risk that Sun&#8217;s actions could ripple throughout the broader cryptocurrency market, potentially causing other investors to panic or leading to a broader sell-off. Related Reading: SEC Allegedly Delays Assistance For US Crypto Market Bill Finally, there is a risk that Sun&#8217;s actions could trigger regulatory scrutiny or legal action, mainly if he is found to have engaged in illegal or unethical behavior. This could harm the reputation of the cryptocurrency industry as a whole and lead to increased regulatory oversight. Despite these concerns, it remains unclear precisely what Sun&#8217;s intentions were with the transactions highlighted by Cochran. Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Crypto analyst Adam Cochran recently caused a stir in the cryptocurrency community when he called attention to a series of TrueUSD (TUSD) transactions made by Tron founder Justin Sun. </p>
<p>Cochran <a href="https://twitter.com/adamscochran/status/1682097478491860998?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">highlighted </a>a series of transactions made by Sun&#8217;s address on the Tron blockchain, including minting $62 million worth of TUSD, withdrawing $50 million in USDT from Huobi, and depositing $50 million in USDT on Bitfinex.</p>
<h2>Justin Sun&#8217;s Dubious TUSD Transactions</h2>
<p>Perhaps most concerning, however, was Sun&#8217;s apparent burning of $50 million TUSD, which Cochran suggested could be an attempt to temporarily “snapshot or unwind” debt using a “fake” balance that was “unbacked”. </p>
<p>Cochran also pointed out that Sun appeared to be using Poloniex and Huobi as his own “piggy” banks to borrow against, with large amounts of Huobi assets being plowed into JustLend &#8211; an official lending platform on the TRON blockchain &#8211; for him to borrow against shitcoins.</p>

<p>These transactions have raised questions about Sun&#8217;s motivations and the potential impact of his actions on the broader cryptocurrency market. In particular, Cochran expressed concern that Sun&#8217;s apparent “manipulation” of TUSD could create the appearance of greater liquidity in the market and potentially lead to price manipulation.</p>
<p>Compounding these concerns is that Changpeng Zhao, the CEO of Binance, one of the world&#8217;s largest cryptocurrency exchanges, has reportedly offered voluntary termination packages to employees in multiple departments. </p>
<p>This move has raised questions about the financial stability of Binance and its potential exposure to Sun&#8217;s actions. Cochran concluded:</p>
<blockquote><p>CZ offered multiple departments &#8220;voluntary termination&#8221; offers where any staff member could apply to resign today, sign a new NDA and get a 3 month severance to quit. Totally normal thing to do after already big cuts&#8230;.</p></blockquote>
The Uncertainty Of Justin Sun&#8217;s Cryptocurrency Moves
<p>The potential risks of Justin Sun&#8217;s transactions are unclear, as his motivations for these actions are unknown. However, several possible concerns have been raised in the crypto community. </p>
<p>One potential risk is the possibility of price manipulation. If Sun was attempting to manipulate the price of specific cryptocurrencies by creating the appearance of greater liquidity in the market, this could lead to price distortions that could harm investors and destabilize the market.</p>
<p>Another risk is the possibility of a liquidity crisis. If Sun&#8217;s actions caused a sudden influx of TUSD or USDT into the market, this could lead to a sudden drop in the value of these cryptocurrencies, potentially causing a liquidity crisis and harming investors.</p>
<p>There is also a risk that Sun&#8217;s actions could ripple throughout the broader cryptocurrency market, potentially causing other investors to panic or leading to a broader sell-off.</p>

<p>Finally, there is a risk that Sun&#8217;s actions could trigger regulatory scrutiny or legal action, mainly if he is found to have engaged in illegal or unethical behavior. This could harm the reputation of the cryptocurrency industry as a whole and lead to increased regulatory oversight.</p>
<p>Despite these concerns, it remains unclear precisely what Sun&#8217;s intentions were with the transactions highlighted by Cochran.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/bCq2RehO/" alt="TUSD" width="1814" height="858"/>
<p>Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ali-hajian-LPylXWfMpgE-unsplash-306x460.jpg" width="306" height="460" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>SEC Allegedly Delays Assistance For US Crypto Market Bill</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/sec-allegedly-delays-assistance-for-us-crypto-market-bill/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Opeyemi Sule]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 19:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gary Gensler]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[U.S. Senate]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[US Congress]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=543556</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has allegedly held up assistance needed in a congressional bill to regulate the crypto markets. This has been considered a potential hurdle if the bill is to pass in Congress. Through multiple sources, the Block found that the SEC has yet to provide sufficient technical assistance for the bill after almost six weeks of request. The report stated that this appears to be the case despite the supposed commission’s good communication with the House.  SEC officials have recently provided briefings to the staff of Democratic members of the House Financial Services Committee. These briefings reportedly covered their opinions on digital asset regulation in light of the committee&#8217;s upcoming consideration of bills to establish a comprehensive framework for cryptocurrency markets in the United States. Related Reading: Arkansas Senator Calls For Reversal Of Controversial New Crypto Mining Law While the Securities and Exchange Commission seems to be dragging its feet in responding to the House’s request, the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) is said to have been receptive so far, providing the congressional staff with some technical assistance. Final Draft Of Crypto Market Bill To Be Unveiled  Various House committees have been working together for months to create a new bill for crypto markets in the country. This crypto market bill, led primarily by Republican members, is expected to direct the U.S. market regulators on how a digital asset can transition from a security to a commodity.  Additionally, it would temporarily confer the Commodity Futures Trading Commission superior power over crypto commodities markets &#8211; mainly Bitcoin trading. A final draft of this multi-committee bill will reportedly be introduced today, July 20, 2023. This is in anticipation of a committee debate and vote next week. Initially, a committee debate and amendment process for the Financial Services Committee part of the bill was scheduled on Wednesday, July 19. However, this “markup” has been rescheduled to the following week to allow enough time for additional review by committee members. Senators Urge SEC Chairman To Crack Down On Crypto Companies On Wednesday, July 19, two prominent figures in the U.S. Senate criticized the crypto industry, pressing the Securities and Exchange Commission to be more aggressive in its regulatory style.  Democrat Senator Dick Durbin D-III condemned the activities of crypto companies in the United States. The government official said: They spent billions on sports arena or stadium naming rights deals to gain misguided credibility with everyday Americans and manipulate prices with phony tokens of no underlying value. Related Reading: Terraform Labs Appoints New CEO Following Do Kwon’s Sentencing In Montenegro Senator John Kennedy, a Republican from Louisiana, asked Gensler why there was &#8220;no emergency injunction to force the bankrupt FTX exchange to halt its operations before collapsing last November.&#8221;  The SEC chairman responded, saying: We investigate by the book. You, I&#8217;m sure, and the American public, want us to follow the facts, follow the law, properly get people subpoenas. Although Gensler agreed with the Senators’ claims about the crypto industry and the need for more policies, he made a case for the underlying technology. Meanwhile, he took the opportunity to request more funding for his agency. Crypto Total Market Cap at $1.16 trillion &#124; Source: TOTAL chart from TradingView Featured image from Tekedia, chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has allegedly held up assistance needed in a congressional bill to regulate the crypto markets. This has been considered a potential hurdle if the bill is to pass in Congress.</p>
<p>Through multiple sources, the Block <a href="https://www.theblock.co/post/240688/sec-said-to-be-slow-walking-assistance-requested-for-us-crypto-market-bill" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">found</a> that the SEC has yet to provide sufficient technical assistance for the bill after almost six weeks of request. The report stated that this appears to be the case despite the supposed commission’s good communication with the House. </p>
<p>SEC officials have recently provided briefings to the staff of Democratic members of the House Financial Services Committee. These briefings reportedly covered their opinions on digital asset regulation in light of the committee&#8217;s upcoming consideration of bills to establish a comprehensive framework for cryptocurrency markets in the United States.</p>

<p>While the Securities and Exchange Commission seems to be dragging its feet in responding to the House’s request, the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) is said to have been receptive so far, providing the congressional staff with some technical assistance.</p>
<h2>Final Draft Of Crypto Market Bill To Be Unveiled </h2>
<p>Various House committees have been working together for months to create a new bill for crypto markets in the country. This crypto market bill, led primarily by Republican members, is expected to direct the U.S. market regulators on how a digital asset can transition from a security to a commodity. </p>
<p>Additionally, it would temporarily confer the Commodity Futures Trading Commission superior power over crypto commodities markets &#8211; mainly Bitcoin trading.</p>
<p>A final draft of this multi-committee bill will reportedly be introduced today, July 20, 2023. This is in anticipation of a committee debate and vote next week.</p>
<p>Initially, a committee debate and amendment process for the Financial Services Committee part of the bill was scheduled on Wednesday, July 19. However, this “markup” has been rescheduled to the following week to allow enough time for additional review by committee members.</p>
<h2>Senators Urge SEC Chairman To Crack Down On Crypto Companies</h2>
<p>On Wednesday, July 19, two prominent figures in the U.S. Senate criticized the crypto industry, pressing the Securities and Exchange Commission to be more aggressive in its regulatory style. </p>
<p>Democrat Senator Dick Durbin D-III condemned the activities of crypto companies in the United States. The government official said:</p>
<blockquote><p> They spent billions on sports arena or stadium naming rights deals to gain misguided credibility with everyday Americans and manipulate prices with phony tokens of no underlying value.</p></blockquote>

<p>Senator John Kennedy, a Republican from Louisiana, asked Gensler why there was &#8220;no emergency injunction to force the bankrupt FTX exchange to halt its operations before collapsing last November.&#8221; </p>
<p>The SEC chairman responded, saying:</p>
<blockquote><p>We investigate by the book. You, I&#8217;m sure, and the American public, want us to follow the facts, follow the law, properly get people subpoenas.</p></blockquote>
<p>Although Gensler agreed with the Senators’ claims about the crypto industry and the need for more policies, he made a case for the underlying technology. Meanwhile, he took the opportunity to request more funding for his agency.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/H7UflUBt/" alt="SEC" width="997" height="586"/></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/sec-956x450-1-460x217.jpg" width="460" height="217" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Bulls Rejoice: Blofin Forecasts $49,000 Price High With Potential Spot ETF Launch</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-bulls-rejoice-blofin-forecasts-49000-price-high-with-potential-spot-etf-launch/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 17:59:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=543565</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Digital asset management platform Blofin has released a report that explores the changing narrative of the cryptocurrency market, focusing on the diverging correlation between Bitcoin (BTC) and Ethereum (ETH).  The report suggests that BTC is becoming an increasingly prominent macro underlying asset, approaching the status of traditional assets such as foreign exchange and precious metals, while ETH&#8217;s narrative is shifting towards mega stocks. BTC Gaining Prominence As Macro Underlying Asset According to the report, the attractiveness of ETH for liquidity may continue to be weaker than that of BTC, especially in the current era of &#8220;lack of liquidity,&#8221; unless there is a grander narrative and widespread application.  Moreover, the report notes that a new Crypto 3.0 narrative has emerged, which combines macro trading, artificial intelligence (AI), and other factors. The report suggests that BTC&#8217;s macro attributes have been continuously strengthened by existing and external liquidity preferences, with the Bitcoin network becoming a natural macro underlying asset. Related Reading: Terraform Labs Appoints New CEO Following Do Kwon’s Sentencing In Montenegro The report also highlights the importance of BTC being a fully compliant asset, unlike ETH, which has not been recognized as a security by the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC).  This ambiguity around ETH&#8217;s status implies risk, while BTC has been identified as a commodity. Institutions are less likely to take risks on compliance, making BTC the preferred choice for many investors. Last but not least, the report also considers three scenarios for the future price of BTC, depending on changes in interest rates and market expectations.  The most optimistic scenario involves a Bitcoin spot exchange-traded fund (ETF) passing and pushing BTC&#8217;s market share up to 60%, resulting in a market cap of $960b and a unit price of over $49,400.  However, if investors have no better expectations and the crypto market capitalization is limited, the market capitalization of BTC will fluctuate between $600-$700b, and the price will fluctuate between $30,880-$36,026. Caution Until Bitcoin Can Sustain Above $32,000 Capriole Invest, a leading provider of Bitcoin and cryptocurrency investment strategies, has released its latest Bitcoin Macro Index report.  The report provides a comprehensive and data-driven analysis of the current state of the cryptocurrency market, combining over 40 powerful on-chain, macro market, and equity indicators into a single machine-learning model. The report reveals that Bitcoin is facing significant resistance at the $32,000 mark, despite a series of positive news stories for the industry in recent weeks.  While the Blackrock ETF announcement, XRP legal victory, and backing from presidential candidate Kennedy for backing the US Dollar with Bitcoin have all made headlines, they have not been able to sustain momentum above $31,000. Related Reading: Arkansas Senator Calls For Reversal Of Controversial New Crypto Mining Law According to the report, until Bitcoin can convincingly sustain price levels above $32,000, it is prudent to be conservative in the upper $30,000 region. On the high timeframe technicals, Bitcoin has failed to break out of weekly resistance at $32,000, suggesting a greater area of opportunity on a $32,000 break or reversion to the mid-$20,000s. The report concludes that while opportunities for trades may exist if the range lows can hold on to the lower time-frames at the end of the day, the risk-reward opportunity is not present for high-conviction investments. Despite a 50% increase in Bitcoin&#8217;s mining network in the last six months, long-term value remains, but now is probably not the time to go all-in. At present, Bitcoin is facing a challenge to maintain its position above the crucial $30,000 line, which is a fundamental psychological level for investors with a positive outlook for the cryptocurrency.  The leading digital asset in the market is currently trading at $29,750, indicating a 0.8% decline in the past 24 hours. Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Digital asset management platform Blofin has released a <a href="https://medium.com/@blofin_official/blofin-flow-insights-parting-ways-9bc1c6bd68b1" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">report </a>that explores the changing narrative of the cryptocurrency market, focusing on the diverging correlation between Bitcoin (BTC) and Ethereum (ETH). </p>
<p>The report suggests that BTC is becoming an increasingly prominent macro underlying asset, approaching the status of traditional assets such as foreign exchange and precious metals, while ETH&#8217;s narrative is shifting towards mega stocks.</p>
<h2>BTC Gaining Prominence As Macro Underlying Asset</h2>
<p>According to the report, the attractiveness of ETH for liquidity may continue to be weaker than that of BTC, especially in the current era of &#8220;lack of liquidity,&#8221; unless there is a grander narrative and widespread application. </p>
<p>Moreover, the report notes that a new Crypto 3.0 narrative has emerged, which combines macro trading, artificial intelligence (AI), and other factors. The report suggests that BTC&#8217;s macro attributes have been continuously strengthened by existing and external liquidity preferences, with the Bitcoin network becoming a natural macro underlying asset.</p>

<p>The report also highlights the importance of BTC being a fully compliant asset, unlike ETH, which has not been recognized as a security by the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). </p>
<p>This ambiguity around ETH&#8217;s status implies risk, while BTC has been identified as a commodity. Institutions are less likely to take risks on compliance, making BTC the preferred choice for many investors.</p>
<p>Last but not least, the report also considers three scenarios for the future price of BTC, depending on changes in interest rates and market expectations. </p>
<p>The most optimistic scenario involves a Bitcoin spot exchange-traded fund (ETF) passing and pushing BTC&#8217;s market share up to 60%, resulting in a market cap of $960b and a unit price of over $49,400. </p>
<p>However, if investors have no better expectations and the crypto market capitalization is limited, the market capitalization of BTC will fluctuate between $600-$700b, and the price will fluctuate between $30,880-$36,026.</p>
Caution Until Bitcoin Can Sustain Above $32,000
<p>Capriole Invest, a leading provider of Bitcoin and cryptocurrency investment strategies, has released its latest Bitcoin Macro Index <a href="https://capriole.com/update-1/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">report</a>. </p>
<p>The report provides a comprehensive and data-driven analysis of the current state of the cryptocurrency market, combining over 40 powerful on-chain, macro market, and equity indicators into a single machine-learning model.</p>
<p>The report reveals that Bitcoin is facing significant resistance at the $32,000 mark, despite a series of positive news stories for the industry in recent weeks. </p>
<p>While the Blackrock ETF announcement, XRP legal victory, and backing from presidential candidate Kennedy for backing the US Dollar with Bitcoin have all made headlines, they have not been able to sustain momentum above $31,000.</p>

<p>According to the report, until Bitcoin can convincingly sustain price levels above $32,000, it is prudent to be conservative in the upper $30,000 region. On the high timeframe technicals, Bitcoin has failed to break out of weekly resistance at $32,000, suggesting a greater area of opportunity on a $32,000 break or reversion to the mid-$20,000s.</p>
<p>The report concludes that while opportunities for trades may exist if the range lows can hold on to the lower time-frames at the end of the day, the risk-reward opportunity is not present for high-conviction investments. Despite a 50% increase in Bitcoin&#8217;s mining network in the last six months, long-term value remains, but now is probably not the time to go all-in.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/oOGh1vdf/" alt="Bitcoin " width="1814" height="858"/>
<p>At present, Bitcoin is facing a challenge to maintain its position above the crucial $30,000 line, which is a fundamental psychological level for investors with a positive outlook for the cryptocurrency. </p>
<p>The leading digital asset in the market is currently trading at $29,750, indicating a 0.8% decline in the past 24 hours.</p>
<p>Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/iStock-1322509303-1-460x259.jpg" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Terraform Labs Appoints New CEO Following Do Kwon&#8217;s Sentencing In Montenegro</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/terra-luna/terraform-labs-appoints-new-ceo/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 15:00:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Terra (LUNA)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Do Kwon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LUNA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Terra]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Terraform Labs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[TFL]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=543533</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Terraform Labs has announced the appointment of Chris Amani as the interim Chief Executive Officer (CEO), replacing co-founder Do Kwon.  Terraform Labs Elevates Former COO Chris Amani as Director and Interim CEO Chris Amani, an experienced leader with over two decades of experience in the technology industry, has been selected as the interim CEO for Terraform Labs. Having served as the Chief Operating Officer (COO) and Chief Financial Officer (CFO) since joining the company in 2021, Amani brings valuable insights and expertise to this new role.  Related Reading: Binance Burns $480 Million In BNB, Will Price Recover? Previously, Amani held leadership positions at prominent technology companies such as MongoDB, Electronic Arts, and Zynga. His deep understanding of TFL&#8217;s operations and strategy positions him to steer the company through its current challenges and drive its mission forward. This decision comes as Kwon faces potential extradition to South Korea or the United States from Montenegro, where he is currently serving a prison sentence. Navigating Through Troubled Waters: Terra&#8217;s Comeback Plan Terra, known for its TerraUSD and Luna cryptocurrencies, faced a significant setback in May 2022 when the collapse of its stablecoin caused a ripple effect across the crypto market.  Co-founder Do Kwon&#8217;s legal troubles further exacerbated the situation, with charges of misleading investors and alleged involvement in illicit transactions during the collapse. Amidst these challenges, Chris Amani expressed his commitment to reviving the Terra blockchain and focusing on developing applications that provide real utility.  LUNA price sitting at $0.65 &#124; Source: LUNAUSDT on Tradingview.com TFL&#8217;s comeback plan involves executing a clear vision for Terra&#8217;s role within the broader Web3 ecosystem, which Amani and the team are dedicated to implementing. The new CEO emphasized the importance of community collaboration and shared goals during this rebuilding phase. With approximately 40 employees, the company will continue to operate without Do Kwon&#8217;s leadership, as he focuses on addressing his legal affairs. The team is optimistic about its ability to salvage the situation and is actively working on plans to propel the company forward. Nevertheless, the legal issues surrounding Do Kwon&#8217;s involvement in the collapse have been a significant point of concern.  Related Reading: Ethereum Monthly Burn Surpasses 146,000 ETH As Total Clears $6.5 Billion Terra&#8217;s recovery plan is not without its complexities, but the team is determined to restore value to the Terra Classic ecosystem. Amain, in his statement, said,  &#8220;The process won&#8217;t be easy, but we have a clear vision of where Terra fits within the broader Web3 ecosystem and are hyper-focused on executing against that vision. We look forward to sharing more on this soon&#8221;  The plan involves reducing node syncing times, creating a TerraUSD testnet, developing yield-generating applications, and implementing a reward system for developers. Featured image from Binance Academy, chart from Tradingview.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Terraform Labs has <a href="https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/terraform-labs-appoints-former-coo-chris-amani-as-interim-ceo-301880860.html" rel="nofollow">announced</a> the appointment of Chris Amani as the interim Chief Executive Officer (CEO), replacing co-founder Do Kwon. </p>
<h2>Terraform Labs Elevates Former COO Chris Amani as Director and Interim CEO</h2>
<p>Chris Amani, an experienced leader with over two decades of experience in the technology industry, has been selected as the interim CEO for Terraform Labs. Having served as the Chief Operating Officer (COO) and Chief Financial Officer (CFO) since joining the company in 2021, Amani brings valuable insights and expertise to this new role. </p>

<p>Previously, Amani held leadership positions at prominent technology companies such as MongoDB, Electronic Arts, and Zynga. His deep understanding of TFL&#8217;s operations and strategy positions him to steer the company through its current challenges and drive its mission forward.</p>
<p>This decision comes as Kwon faces potential extradition to South Korea or the United States from Montenegro, where he is currently serving a prison sentence.</p>
<h2>Navigating Through Troubled Waters: Terra&#8217;s Comeback Plan</h2>
<p>Terra, known for its TerraUSD and Luna cryptocurrencies, faced a significant setback in May 2022 when the collapse of its stablecoin caused a ripple effect across the crypto market. </p>
<p>Co-founder Do Kwon&#8217;s legal troubles further exacerbated the situation, with charges of misleading investors and alleged involvement in illicit transactions during the collapse.</p>
<p>Amidst these challenges, Chris Amani expressed his commitment to reviving the Terra blockchain and focusing on developing applications that provide real utility. </p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/mziT0RfT/" alt="Terra LUNA price chart from Tradingview.com (Terraform Labs)" width="2884" height="1758"/></p>

<p>TFL&#8217;s comeback plan involves executing a clear vision for Terra&#8217;s role within the broader Web3 ecosystem, which Amani and the team are dedicated to implementing.</p>
<p>The new CEO emphasized the importance of community collaboration and shared goals during this rebuilding phase. With approximately 40 employees, the company will continue to operate without Do Kwon&#8217;s leadership, as he focuses on addressing his legal affairs.</p>
<p>The team is optimistic about its ability to salvage the situation and is actively working on plans to propel the company forward. Nevertheless, the legal issues surrounding Do Kwon&#8217;s involvement in the collapse have been a significant point of concern. </p>

<p>Terra&#8217;s recovery plan is not without its complexities, but the team is determined to restore value to the Terra Classic ecosystem.</p>
<p>Amain, in his statement, said,  &#8220;The process won&#8217;t be easy, but we have a clear vision of where Terra fits within the broader Web3 ecosystem and are hyper-focused on executing against that vision. We look forward to sharing more on this soon&#8221; </p>
<p>The plan involves reducing node syncing times, creating a TerraUSD testnet, developing yield-generating applications, and implementing a reward system for developers.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Terra-LUNA-460x259.png" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Arkansas Senator Calls For Reversal Of Controversial New Crypto Mining Law</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/arkansas-senator-calls-for-reversal-of-controversial-new-crypto-mining-law/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[anushsamal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 14:00:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Right to Mine]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=543492</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[In April 2023, Arkansas made history by becoming the first state to pass the &#8216;Right to Mine&#8217; Bitcoin bill in both the House and Senate. However, the &#8220;Right to Mine&#8221; law in Arkansas is encountering increasing opposition as it relaxes regulations on commercial crypto mining. Reports have suggested that loosening restrictions on commercial cryptocurrency mining has raised concerns. This is because after enacting the new law, large electricity-intensive crypto mines entered Arkansas. The legislation has sparked controversy by limiting the authority of city governments to regulate crypto mines. This has effectively stripped them of their ability to enforce local ordinances concerning such operations. During the 2023 legislative session, Arkansas Senator Bryan King (R) from District 28 expressed criticism of the bill&#8217;s introduction. And Senator King is reportedly planning to introduce another bill aimed at repealing the controversial &#8220;Right to Mine&#8221; law. Related Reading: Solana (SOL) Continues To Shine With Over 20% Surge – What’s Next? Reports indicate that residents have raised numerous concerns, including excessive noise, substantial power grid usage, and the fact that Green Digital LLC., the company behind the proposed crypto mines in their cities, is a subsidiary partially owned by the Chinese Communist Party. Some Towns Have Rejected Proposed Crypto-Mining Facilities Arkansas Senator Bryan King has taken proactive steps by drafting a bill aimed at repealing the controversial law related to crypto-mining. One of the major worries is the strain on the local power grid caused by the electricity-intensive nature of crypto-mining operations. Reports have surfaced that some areas are already facing warnings of potential brownouts or blackouts. This is because of the increased energy consumption from these facilities. As of the current moment, local reports indicate that Arkansas is home to approximately 10 crypto mines. Vilonia and Harrison, two towns in Arkansas, have prevented attempts to establish proposed crypto-mining facilities within their respective city limits. Related Reading: Stellar Makes Surprise 70% Rally – Start Of Something Big For XLM? Senator Bryan King has further contended that crypto mines do not serve as economic boons to the communities where they establish their operations. He specifically highlighted that facilities like those proposed by Green Digital only employ a limited number of people. As such, the mines fail to provide substantial job opportunities or significant economic growth to the areas they operate. Advocacy For The Mining Bill Senator Joshua Bryant (R) who sponsored the bill explained and supported that the bill aims to protect property rights and stop the unfair treatment of crypto entrepreneurs. He said that crypto miners are people living in Arkansas who invest money in the state&#8217;s infrastructure, help keep utility costs stable, and boost the local economy. Bryant points out that if crypto-mining facilities are treated similarly to other data centers, the law allows local governments to create their own regulations. Furthermore, he clarified, that regarding noise ordinances, local governments are free to regulate commercial facilities as they deem appropriate. Related Reading: XRP Maintains Bullish Run With Nearly 80% Rally – Is $1 Within Reach? However, the bill specifically focuses on home mining operations. In this regard, it suggests adhering to existing federal and state laws related to nuisances. It also includes the US EPA Noise Act or standard statutory language outlined in the Disturbance Act. Nevertheless, the Arkansas &#8220;Right to Mine&#8221; law is set to take effect next month. Featured image from UnSplash, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In April 2023, Arkansas made history by becoming the first state to<a href="https://www.nasdaq.com/articles/arkansas-house-and-senate-pass-bill-protecting-right-to-mine-bitcoin-goes-to-governor-for" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow"> pass</a> the &#8216;Right to Mine&#8217; Bitcoin bill in both the House and Senate. However, the &#8220;Right to Mine&#8221; law in Arkansas is encountering increasing opposition as it relaxes regulations on commercial crypto mining.</p>
<p><a href="https://katv.com/news/local/arkansas-senator-seeking-repeal-of-controversial-new-crypto-mining-law-bryan-king-joshua-bryant-rick-mcclure-city-of-harrison-act-851-cryptomine-green-digital-llc-arkansas-blockchain-council-vilonia-right-to-mine-bill-cryptocurrency-bitcoin-noise-2023" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Reports</a> have suggested that loosening restrictions on commercial cryptocurrency mining has raised concerns. This is because after enacting the new law, large electricity-intensive crypto mines entered Arkansas.</p>
<p>The legislation has sparked controversy by limiting the authority of city governments to regulate crypto mines. This has effectively stripped them of their ability to enforce local ordinances concerning such operations.</p>
<p>During the 2023 legislative session, Arkansas Senator Bryan King (R) from District 28 expressed criticism of the bill&#8217;s introduction. And Senator King is reportedly planning to introduce another bill aimed at repealing the controversial &#8220;Right to Mine&#8221; law.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/solana-sol-smashes-previous-high/">Solana (SOL) Continues To Shine With Over 20% Surge – What’s Next?</a></p>
<p>Reports indicate that residents have raised numerous concerns, including excessive noise, substantial power grid usage, and the fact that Green Digital LLC., the company behind the proposed crypto mines in their cities, is a subsidiary partially owned by the Chinese Communist Party.</p>
<h2>Some Towns Have Rejected Proposed Crypto-Mining Facilities</h2>
<p>Arkansas Senator Bryan King has taken proactive steps by drafting a bill aimed at repealing the controversial law related to crypto-mining. One of the major worries is the strain on the local power grid caused by the electricity-intensive nature of crypto-mining operations.</p>
<p>Reports have surfaced that some areas are already facing warnings of potential brownouts or blackouts. This is because of the increased energy consumption from these facilities.</p>
<p>As of the current moment, local reports indicate that Arkansas is home to approximately 10 crypto mines. Vilonia and Harrison, two towns in Arkansas, have prevented attempts to establish proposed crypto-mining facilities within their respective city limits.</p>

<p>Senator Bryan King has further contended that crypto mines do not serve as economic boons to the communities where they establish their operations.</p>
<p>He specifically highlighted that facilities like those proposed by Green Digital only employ a limited number of people. As such, the mines fail to provide substantial job opportunities or significant economic growth to the areas they operate.</p>
<h2>Advocacy For The Mining Bill</h2>
<p>Senator Joshua Bryant (R) who sponsored the bill explained and supported that the bill aims to protect property rights and stop the unfair treatment of crypto entrepreneurs.</p>
<p>He said that crypto miners are people living in Arkansas who invest money in the state&#8217;s infrastructure, help keep utility costs stable, and boost the local economy.</p>






<p>Bryant points out that if crypto-mining facilities are treated similarly to other data centers, the law allows local governments to create their own regulations.</p>
<p>Furthermore, he clarified, that regarding noise ordinances, local governments are free to regulate commercial facilities as they deem appropriate.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/breaking-news-ticker/xrp-maintains-bullish-run/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">XRP Maintains Bullish Run With Nearly 80% Rally – Is $1 Within Reach?</a></p>
<p>However, the bill specifically focuses on home mining operations. In this regard, it suggests adhering to existing federal and state laws related to nuisances. It also includes the US EPA Noise Act or standard statutory language outlined in the Disturbance Act.</p>
<p>Nevertheless, the Arkansas &#8220;Right to Mine&#8221; law is set to take effect next month.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-543515 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/TOTAL_2023-07-20_14-39-25-1.png" alt="Crypto" width="1818" height="743" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/TOTAL_2023-07-20_14-39-25-1.png 1818w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/TOTAL_2023-07-20_14-39-25-1-460x188.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/TOTAL_2023-07-20_14-39-25-1-860x351.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/TOTAL_2023-07-20_14-39-25-1-768x314.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/TOTAL_2023-07-20_14-39-25-1-1536x628.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/TOTAL_2023-07-20_14-39-25-1-750x307.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/TOTAL_2023-07-20_14-39-25-1-1140x466.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1818px) 100vw, 1818px"/>







]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/michael-fortsch-AA5sf7WTv10-unsplash-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Near Crucial Retest: Which Of These Historical Patterns Will Repeat?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-crucial-retest-which-historical-patterns-repeat/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hououin Kyouma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 13:00:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Pattern]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Retest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin SOPR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=543461</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[On-chain data shows a Bitcoin indicator is near a crucial retest currently that may decide where the cryptocurrency will go next from here. Which Pattern Will Bitcoin Follow Next: 2016 Or 2019? As pointed out by an analyst in a CryptoQuant post, the BTC SOPR for short-term holders is approaching the baseline. The &#8220;Spent Output Profit Ratio&#8221; (SOPR) is an indicator that tells us whether Bitcoin investors are selling/moving their coins at a profit or at a loss right now. When the value of this metric is greater than 1, it means that the average holder in the market is realizing some amount of profit with their selling currently. On the other hand, values below this threshold suggest loss taking is the dominant force in the market at the moment. Naturally, the SOPR being exactly equal to the 1 baseline implies the total amount of profits being realized are exactly canceling out the amount of losses as the market as a whole is neutral. This SOPR is for the entire Bitcoin market, but in the context of the current discussion, the relevant version of the metric is the one for just a single segment of the market: the &#8220;short-term holders&#8221; (STHs). The STH group includes all the investors who purchased their coins less than 155 days ago. This cohort generally includes the weak hands of the market, who may easily react to fluctuations in the market. Now, here is a chart that shows the trend in the 90-day and 365-day moving averages (MAs) of the Bitcoin STH SOPR over the last few years: Looks like both the metrics have been above the baseline in recent days: Source: CryptoQuant As displayed in the above graph, the 90-day MA of the Bitcoin STH SOPR (colored in yellow) broke out above the 1 baseline back when this rally first started around the beginning of the year. This breakout suggested a shift towards profit selling for these investors, something that has historically been observed in all previous major rallies in the cryptocurrency. With the latest leg in the Bitcoin rally above the $30,000 mark, the 365-day MA of the indicator (highlighted in blue) has also managed to climb up above this mark. Related Reading: Bitcoin Exchange Inflow Spikes, Is This Bearish? While this has been happening, though, the 90-day MA has actually been heading down and is now about to cross below the 365-day MA as it approaches the 1 baseline. In the chart, the quant has marked the two previous instances where a trend similar to this had formed for the asset. It looks like back in 2016 when the 90-day MA had retested the 1 mark after a similar structure had taken shape, the metric had found support at the break-even mark. This rebound kept Bitcoin going and the coin eventually built up into a bull market. In 2019, though, the retest of the 90-day MA STH SOPR failed and a bearish trend once again took over the coin. It wouldn&#8217;t be until 160 days later that bullish sentiment returned and the rally happened. Related Reading: Bitcoin Has Broken This Open Interest Pattern, Quant Explains As the current Bitcoin market looks to be in a similar spot as these two historical occurrences, it&#8217;s possible that it may follow the lead of one of these. It now remains to be seen, as to which of these patterns the asset might exhibit this time. BTC Price At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading around $30,300, down 1% in the last week. BTC has surged during the past day &#124; Source: BTCUSD on TradingView Featured image from Kanchanara on Unsplash.com, charts from TradingView.com, CryptoQuant.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On-chain data shows a Bitcoin indicator is near a crucial retest currently that may decide where the cryptocurrency will go next from here.</p>
<h2>Which Pattern Will Bitcoin Follow Next: 2016 Or 2019?</h2>
<p>As pointed out by an analyst in a CryptoQuant <a href="https://cryptoquant.com/insights/quicktake/64b8126241768f4ed318064b-The-market-is-waiting-for-short-term-holders" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">post</a>, the BTC SOPR for short-term holders is approaching the baseline. The &#8220;<a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-sopr-bounces-into-profit-zone-what-mean/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Spent Output Profit Ratio</a>&#8221; (SOPR) is an indicator that tells us whether Bitcoin investors are selling/moving their coins at a profit or at a loss right now.</p>
<p>When the value of this metric is greater than 1, it means that the average holder in the market is realizing some amount of profit with their selling currently. On the other hand, values below this threshold suggest loss taking is the dominant force in the market at the moment.</p>
<p>Naturally, the SOPR being exactly equal to the 1 baseline implies the total amount of profits being realized are exactly canceling out the amount of losses as the market as a whole is neutral.</p>
<p>This SOPR is for the entire Bitcoin market, but in the context of the current discussion, the relevant version of the metric is the one for just a single segment of the market: the &#8220;<a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-short-term-holders-exchange-inflows-price/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">short-term holders</a>&#8221; (STHs).</p>
<p>The STH group includes all the investors who purchased their coins less than 155 days ago. This cohort generally includes the weak hands of the market, who may easily react to fluctuations in the market.</p>
<p>Now, here is a chart that shows the trend in the 90-day and 365-day moving averages (MAs) of the Bitcoin STH SOPR over the last few years:</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone aligncenter" src="https://img.cryptoquant.com/333235/quicktake/2BGU4_9461eefa9b19f0a23b166f412d5d0825ea819237eca6f034e2b7bde43aa2b246.png" alt="Bitcoin STH SOPR" width="1280" height="584"/></p>

<p>As displayed in the above graph, the 90-day MA of the Bitcoin STH SOPR (colored in yellow) broke out above the 1 baseline back when this <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-rally-similar-genesis-points-uptrends-glassnode/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">rally</a> first started around the beginning of the year.</p>
<p>This breakout suggested a shift towards profit selling for these investors, something that has historically been observed in all previous major rallies in the cryptocurrency.</p>
<p>With the latest leg in the Bitcoin rally above the $30,000 mark, the 365-day MA of the indicator (highlighted in blue) has also managed to climb up above this mark.</p>

<p>While this has been happening, though, the 90-day MA has actually been heading down and is now about to cross below the 365-day MA as it approaches the 1 baseline.</p>
<p>In the chart, the quant has marked the two previous instances where a trend similar to this had formed for the asset. It looks like back in 2016 when the 90-day MA had retested the 1 mark after a similar structure had taken shape, the metric had found support at the break-even mark. This rebound kept Bitcoin going and the coin eventually built up into a bull market.</p>
<p>In 2019, though, the retest of the 90-day MA STH SOPR failed and a bearish trend once again took over the coin. It wouldn&#8217;t be until 160 days later that bullish sentiment returned and the rally happened.</p>

<p>As the current Bitcoin market looks to be in a similar spot as these two historical occurrences, it&#8217;s possible that it may follow the lead of one of these. It now remains to be seen, as to which of these patterns the asset might exhibit this time.</p>
<h2>BTC Price</h2>
<p>At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading around $30,300, down 1% in the last week.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium aligncenter" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/sEjnX5WK/" alt="Bitcoin Price Chart" width="1534" height="877"/></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/kanchanara-rhm7H8X5J98-unsplash-460x306.jpg" width="460" height="306" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Stellar Makes Surprise 70% Rally &#8211; Start Of Something Big For XLM?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/stellar-makes-surprise-70-rally-start-of-something-big-for-xlm/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 12:04:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price action]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[stellar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XLM Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=543488</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Stellar (XLM) has registered a surprise surge, catapulting itself into the forefront of the crypto market frenzy. Beginning July 18, this surge has taken the digital asset on a solid price rally, propelling its value to new heights. Currently, XLM is trading at $0.1617, representing a 22.1% increase over the past 24 hours. Even more remarkable is its exceptional performance over the previous week, which has soared by 68.8%, and dominating the top 100 roster of cryptocurrencies. Source: Coingecko Now, the question on everyone&#8217;s mind is: What is driving this surge? XLM Makes Waves: Catalysts For Price Surge XLM&#8217;s remarkable ascent is primarily attributed to a significant development in the crypto space – Ripple Labs&#8217;s legal victory against the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) &#8211; and the solid performance of XRP, which has likewise registered an impressive 72.3% climb at the time of writing. Related Reading: Solana (SOL) Continues To Shine With Over 20% Surge – What’s Next? A judge ruled that Ripple did not violate securities regulations when it sold its XRP token on public exchanges. This verdict sent XRP prices soaring and created a ripple effect (no pun intended), propelling other altcoins, including XLM and even Bitcoin (BTC), to surge in value. XLM market cap currently at $4.5 billion on the daily chart: TradingView.com Related Reading: BNB Chain Unveils Beacon Update – What’s Its Bearing On Price? Meanwhile, crypto exchange Coinbase has fully embraced the Stellar network, enabling seamless deposits and withdrawals of USD Coin (USDC). This integration bolstered Stellar&#8217;s status and expanded its reach, attracting more interest and investment to the platform. XLM seven-day price action. Source: CoinMarketCap Despite the initial upswing following US Judge Analisa Torres&#8217; favorable verdict for the Ripple coin, XLM was unable to retest its previous week&#8217;s highs at $0.20. But it looks like the bulls are still in charge, as XLM trade volumes are relatively high. CoinGecko reports that within the past 24 hours, almost $700 million worth of XLM has traded hands on key exchanges. What Lies Ahead For Stellar XLM? As the crypto market continues to evolve, all eyes are on XLM to see if it can sustain its current momentum. With the legal challenges surrounding Ripple and its XRP token seeing full closure, investors may view Stellar as a more stable alternative for their digital assets portfolio. Traders should closely monitor the price movement and whether XLM can break past the significant resistance level at $0.20. 350 million people in Africa don&#8217;t have access to bank accounts, and only 20% of families have formal bank accounts.@fonbnk1 provides a real-world solution to this problem by turning 8 billion active prepaid SIM cards globally into virtual debit cards with Stellar. (1/3) — Stellar (@StellarOrg) July 18, 2023 In related news, Stellar has just announced a partnership with Fonbnk to convert 8 billion active prepaid SIM cards into virtual debit cards. This development is anticipated to have a positive impact on XRP&#8217;s price over the coming weeks. (This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk). Featured image from Pxfuel]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Stellar (XLM) has registered a surprise surge, catapulting itself into the forefront of the crypto market frenzy. Beginning July 18, this surge has taken the digital asset on a solid price rally, propelling its value to new heights.</p>
<p>Currently, XLM is trading at $0.1617, representing a 22.1% increase over the past 24 hours. Even more remarkable is its exceptional performance over the previous week, which has soared by 68.8%, and dominating the top 100 roster of cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-543494" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-127.png" alt="" width="945" height="69" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-127.png 945w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-127-460x34.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-127-860x63.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-127-768x56.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-127-750x55.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 945px) 100vw, 945px"/></p>

<p>Now, the question on everyone&#8217;s mind is: What is driving this surge?</p>
<h2><strong>XLM Makes Waves: Catalysts For Price Surge</strong></h2>
<p>XLM&#8217;s remarkable ascent is primarily attributed to a significant development in the crypto space – <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.kitco.com/news/2023-07-18/Ripple-and-SEC-ordered-to-consider-settlement-in-landmark-case.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Ripple Labs&#8217;s legal victory</a> against the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) &#8211; and the solid performance of XRP, which has likewise registered an impressive 72.3% climb at the time of writing.</p>

<p>A judge ruled that Ripple did not violate securities regulations when it sold its XRP token on public exchanges. This verdict sent XRP prices soaring and created a ripple effect (no pun intended), propelling other altcoins, including XLM and even Bitcoin (BTC), to surge in value.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/YIcycUyZ/" width="2475" height="1187"/></p>


<p>Meanwhile, crypto exchange Coinbase has fully embraced the Stellar network, enabling seamless deposits and withdrawals of USD Coin (USDC). This integration bolstered Stellar&#8217;s status and expanded its reach, attracting more interest and investment to the platform.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-543500 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-129-860x386.png" alt="" width="860" height="386" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-129-860x386.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-129-460x206.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-129-768x344.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-129-750x336.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-129.png 1035w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/></p>

<p>Despite the initial upswing following US Judge Analisa Torres&#8217; favorable verdict for the Ripple coin, XLM was unable to retest its previous week&#8217;s highs at $0.20. But it looks like the bulls are still in charge, as XLM trade volumes are relatively high. CoinGecko reports that within the past 24 hours, almost $700 million worth of XLM has traded hands on key exchanges.</p>
<h2><strong>What Lies Ahead For Stellar XLM?</strong></h2>
<p>As the crypto market continues to evolve, all eyes are on XLM to see if it can sustain its current momentum. With the legal challenges surrounding Ripple and its XRP token seeing full closure, investors may view Stellar as a more stable alternative for their digital assets portfolio.</p>
<p>Traders should closely monitor the price movement and whether XLM can break past the significant resistance level at $0.20.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">350 million people in Africa don&#8217;t have access to bank accounts, and only 20% of families have formal bank accounts.<a href="https://twitter.com/fonbnk1?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">@fonbnk1</a> provides a real-world solution to this problem by turning 8 billion active prepaid SIM cards globally into virtual debit cards with Stellar. (1/3)</p>
<p>— Stellar (@StellarOrg) <a href="https://twitter.com/StellarOrg/status/1681396712756379648?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">July 18, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p>In related news, Stellar has just announced a partnership with Fonbnk to convert 8 billion active prepaid SIM cards into virtual debit cards. This development is anticipated to have a positive impact on XRP&#8217;s price over the coming weeks.</p>
<p><em>(This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk).</em></p>
<p><em>Featured image from Pxfuel</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-130-460x258.png" width="460" height="258" />	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
