<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"

	xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
	xmlns:geo="http://www.w3.org/2003/01/geo/wgs84_pos#"
	>

<channel>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.newsbtc.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<description>Bitcoin &#38; Cryptocurrency News Today</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 13:20:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-cropped-favicon.png?fit=32%2C32</url>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
<site xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">221170450</site>	<item>
		<title>Kraken Surges Ahead In Altcoin Liquidity To Overtake Coinbase In US: Kaiko</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/kraken-ahead-in-altcoin-liquidity/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samuel Edyme]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 15:00:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[kraken]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=546876</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The world of cryptocurrency exchanges, often clouded with volatility and competition, has recently been witnessing a distinct shift in dynamics, particularly as a Kraken is taking the lead in the US altcoin trading space. The latest data reveals Kraken, the California-based crypto exchange, is now dominating its rivals, specifically Coinbase, in the altcoin market. Dominating The Altcoin Trading Landscape Data analytics from crypto research firm Kaiko has highlighted Kraken&#8217;s emergence as the premier US crypto exchange for altcoin trading. With significant shifts in market depth percentages and a notable increase in market share, Kraken appears to be carving out a niche for itself in an otherwise volatile industry. 📈🤔In July, Kraken emerged as the most liquid platform for alts in the US. 👉 Its claiming almost half of the market depth for the top 10 alts. pic.twitter.com/2fumt7yi9a — Dessislava Ianeva (@DessislavaIane2) August 9, 2023 Related Reading: Gateway Issues Cause Withdrawal And Deposit Delays For Kraken Exchange Market depth is a crucial metric for crypto exchanges as it represents an exchange&#8217;s capability to manage large buy or sell orders without causing drastic price changes. And according to recent data from Kaiko, Kraken now commands roughly 47% of the market depth for the top 10 altcoins. This dominance, especially in the wake of the previous year&#8217;s price drop and the unfortunate collapse of FTX, underscores the resilience Kraken has brought to the altcoin trading sector. While the entire crypto trading industry has been grappling with declining trading volumes, Kraken has managed to hold its own. A steady uptick in its market share is evident as it jumped from 8.3% in August 2022 to 21.1% in July, according to data from The Block&#8217;s dashboard.  Behind Kraken Ascendancy Kraken reportedly attributes this upward trajectory to a few specific improvements in its offerings. Notably, the introduction of Kraken Pro, their advanced trading platform which rolled out in December, is believed to be a pivotal move. A spokesperson for the crypto exchange elaborated on the exchange&#8217;s recent performance, pointing out that their &#8220;share of total volumes has hit an 18-month high.&#8221; Furthermore, there&#8217;s been a significant surge in their share of EUR spot markets, rising from 35% to 53%, and the AUD spot markets have seen exponential growth, multiplying sixfold over the past year. Related Reading: Regulators Are To Blame For All The Crisis In Crypto, Says Kraken CEO Despite the laudable progress, it&#8217;s crucial to note that Kraken, like many others in the industry, has felt the effects of the industry-wide decline in trading volumes. Their monthly trading volumes have seen a dip from a high of $28.07 billion in March to $13.6 billion in the previous month. Featured image from Unsplash, Chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The world of cryptocurrency exchanges, often clouded with volatility and competition, has recently been witnessing a distinct shift in dynamics, particularly as a Kraken is taking the lead in the US altcoin trading space.</p>
<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w g0rxnol2" dir="ltr">The latest data <a href="https://twitter.com/DessislavaIane2/status/1689301335760363521?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">reveals</a> Kraken, the California-based crypto exchange, is now dominating its rivals, specifically Coinbase, in the altcoin market.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Dominating The Altcoin Trading Landscape</h2>
<p>Data analytics from crypto research firm Kaiko has highlighted Kraken&#8217;s emergence as the premier <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/crypto/gateway-issues-cause-withdrawal-and-deposit-delays-for-kraken-exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">US crypto exchange</a> for altcoin trading. With significant shifts in market depth percentages and a notable increase in market share, Kraken appears to be carving out a niche for itself in an otherwise volatile industry.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en"><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f4c8.png" alt="📈" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f914.png" alt="🤔" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />In July, Kraken emerged as the most liquid platform for alts in the US.
<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f449.png" alt="👉" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> Its claiming almost half of the market depth for the top 10 alts. <a href="https://t.co/2fumt7yi9a" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/2fumt7yi9a</a></p>
<p>— Dessislava Ianeva (@DessislavaIane2) <a href="https://twitter.com/DessislavaIane2/status/1689301335760363521?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">August 9, 2023</a></p></blockquote>

<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w g0rxnol2" dir="ltr">Market depth is a crucial metric for crypto exchanges as it represents an exchange&#8217;s capability to manage large buy or sell orders without causing drastic <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/light-speed-kraken-another-giant-exchange-integrates-the-lightning-network/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">price changes</a>. And according to recent data from Kaiko, Kraken now commands roughly 47% of the market depth for the top 10 altcoins.</p>
<p dir="ltr">This dominance, especially in the wake of the previous year&#8217;s price drop and the unfortunate collapse of FTX, underscores the resilience Kraken has brought to the altcoin trading sector.</p>
<p dir="ltr">While the entire crypto trading industry has been grappling with declining trading volumes, Kraken has managed to hold its own. A steady uptick in its <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/crypto-winter-pushes-kraken-out-of-japan/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">market share</a> is evident as it jumped from 8.3% in August 2022 to 21.1% in July, according to data from The Block&#8217;s dashboard. </p>
<img decoding="async" fetchpriority="high" class="size-medium wp-image-546878" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot-2023-08-11-at-13.22.16.png?w=460&#038;resize=460%2C241" alt="USD support exchange volume market share. | Source: The Block" width="460" height="241" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot-2023-08-11-at-13.22.16.png?w=1695 1695w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot-2023-08-11-at-13.22.16.png?w=460&#038;resize=460%2C241 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot-2023-08-11-at-13.22.16.png?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot-2023-08-11-at-13.22.16.png?w=860 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot-2023-08-11-at-13.22.16.png?w=1536 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot-2023-08-11-at-13.22.16.png?w=750 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot-2023-08-11-at-13.22.16.png?w=1140 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px" loading="lazy" data-recalc-dims="1"/>
<h2 dir="ltr">Behind Kraken Ascendancy</h2>
<p>Kraken reportedly attributes this upward trajectory to a few specific improvements in its offerings. Notably, the introduction of Kraken Pro, their advanced trading platform which rolled out in December, is believed to be a pivotal move.</p>
<p>A spokesperson for the crypto exchange <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/regulators-are-to-blame-for-all-the-crisis-in-crypto-says-kraken-ceo/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">elaborated</a> on the exchange&#8217;s recent performance, pointing out that their &#8220;share of total volumes has hit an 18-month high.&#8221; </p>
<p>Furthermore, there&#8217;s been a significant surge in their share of EUR spot markets, rising from 35% to 53%, and the AUD spot markets have seen exponential growth, multiplying sixfold over the past year.</p>

<p>Despite the laudable progress, it&#8217;s crucial to note that Kraken, like many others in the industry, has felt the effects of the industry-wide decline in trading volumes. Their monthly <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/kraken-ceo-says-bitcoin-below-40k-is-a-buying-opportunity/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">trading volumes</a> have seen a dip from a high of $28.07 billion in March to $13.6 billion in the previous month.</p>
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/xEFvvs4s/" alt="The global cryptocurrency market cap value on Tradingview amid Kraken news" width="2770" height="1408" loading="lazy"/>
<p>Featured image from Unsplash, Chart from TradingView</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/istockphoto-1430193192-170667a.jpg?fit=460%2C278" width="460" height="278" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">546876</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>San Francisco’s SoFi Bank Reveals Significant Holdings In BTC, ETH, And DOGE</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/sofi-bank-holdings-in-btc-eth-doge/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 14:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DOGE]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADACrypto holdings]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto bank]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto investments]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[doge]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SoFi Bank]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=546853</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[San Francisco’s SoFi Bank, a rising financial institution with 6.2 million customers, has unveiled its substantial cryptocurrency holdings, demonstrating a proactive embrace of the evolving digital asset landscape.  BTC, ETH, and DOGE Lead the Way A recent report shows that the bank&#8217;s second-quarter earnings totaled $170 million in various cryptocurrencies, including Bitcoin (BTC), Ethereum (ETH), and Dogecoin (DOGE). Related Reading: Bittrex, SEC Reach Settlement In Securities Violation Case Among its cryptocurrency investments, SoFi Bank boasts $82 million worth of Bitcoin, solidifying its position in ‘digital gold.’ Ethereum follows closely, with $55 million, showcasing the bank&#8217;s belief in the blockchain&#8217;s potential.  The meme-inspired Dogecoin takes the third spot with $5 million, while Cardano secures the fourth place with $4.5 million. The bank also diversifies with digital assets like Solana (SOL), Litecoin (LTC), and Ethereum Classic (ETC). SoFi Bank's crypto holdings &#124; Source: X SoFi Bank&#8217;s unique proposition lies in its commitment to fee-free cryptocurrency investments, allowing customers to allocate a portion of their direct deposits to digital assets.  The bank further incentivizes newcomers by offering a $100 crypto bonus upon registration. With a minimum investment threshold as low as $10, the platform fosters accessibility to a variety of cryptocurrencies beyond Bitcoin. While SoFi Bank&#8217;s innovative approach to cryptocurrency has garnered attention, it faces regulatory scrutiny, particularly from the United States Federal Reserve. The regulatory body has raised concerns over the bank&#8217;s involvement in crypto-related activities, requiring alignment with established policies. The bank has been given until January 2024 to ensure compliance, a process that involves navigating regulatory capital treatment intricacies. Founded in 2011, SoFi Bank transitioned from its status as a non-bank entity in 2019 to a fully-fledged financial institution the following year. BTC price falls to $29,300 &#124; Source: BTCUSD on Tradingview.com Strategic Growth And Financial Success The earnings report highlights SoFi Bank&#8217;s business acumen, reflected in its strong second-quarter performance. With a remarkable 37% surge in revenue ($498 million) compared to the previous year, the bank showcases its ability to thrive amidst a rapidly evolving financial landscape. SoFi Technology Stock also witnessed a 17% surge in July following its Q2 report. &#8220;As a result of this growth in high-quality deposits, we have benefited from a lower cost of funding for our loans,” SoFi CEO Anthony Noto said. Related Reading: New Milestone For Ethereum Could Spell Good News For ETH Price SoFi is not the only bank that has made its way into cryptocurrencies. Major US banks like Wells Fargo, JP Morgan, and Goldman Sachs, among others, have also taken the plunge to provide access to digital assets and cryptocurrencies for their clients. Other notable entrants into the industry include BlackRock and ARK Invest, which have filed applications for Spot Bitcoin ETFs with the SECs. On August 13, the first of these, the ARK Invest application, will be deliberated on to be approved or rejected by the SEC. However, the regulator could also end up extending the deadline. Featured image from BitIRA, chart from Tradingview.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>San Francisco’s <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/press-releases/is-sofi-a-good-bank-response-from-traders-union-analysts/">SoFi Bank</a>, a rising financial institution with 6.2 million customers, has unveiled its substantial cryptocurrency holdings, demonstrating a proactive embrace of the evolving digital asset landscape. </p>
<h2>BTC, ETH, and DOGE Lead the Way</h2>
<p>A recent report shows that the bank&#8217;s second-quarter earnings totaled $170 million in various cryptocurrencies, including Bitcoin (BTC), Ethereum (ETH), and Dogecoin (DOGE).</p>

<p>Among its cryptocurrency investments, SoFi Bank boasts $82 million worth of Bitcoin, solidifying its position in <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/blackrock-ceo-larry-fink-says-bitcoin-is-digital-gold-so-whats-the-digital-silver/">‘digital gold</a>.’ Ethereum follows closely, with $55 million, showcasing the bank&#8217;s belief in the blockchain&#8217;s potential. </p>
<p>The meme-inspired Dogecoin takes the third spot with $5 million, while <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/all/cardano-false-breakdown-could-it-set-the-stage-for-a-26-climb/">Cardano</a> secures the fourth place with $4.5 million. The bank also diversifies with digital assets like Solana (SOL), Litecoin (LTC), and Ethereum Classic (ETC).</p>
<p><img decoding="async" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-546854 aligncenter" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SoFi-Bank-BTC-ETH-DOGE.jpeg?w=460&#038;resize=460%2C157" alt="SoFi Bank BTC, ETH, DOGE" width="460" height="157" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SoFi-Bank-BTC-ETH-DOGE.jpeg?w=1024 1024w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SoFi-Bank-BTC-ETH-DOGE.jpeg?w=460&#038;resize=460%2C157 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SoFi-Bank-BTC-ETH-DOGE.jpeg?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SoFi-Bank-BTC-ETH-DOGE.jpeg?w=860 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SoFi-Bank-BTC-ETH-DOGE.jpeg?w=750 750w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px" loading="lazy" data-recalc-dims="1"/></p>

<p>SoFi Bank&#8217;s unique proposition lies in its commitment to fee-free cryptocurrency investments, allowing customers to allocate a portion of their direct deposits to digital assets. </p>
<p>The bank further incentivizes newcomers by offering a $100 crypto bonus upon registration. With a minimum investment threshold as low as $10, the platform fosters accessibility to a variety of cryptocurrencies beyond Bitcoin.</p>
<p>While SoFi Bank&#8217;s innovative approach to cryptocurrency has garnered attention, it faces regulatory scrutiny, particularly from the United States Federal Reserve. The regulatory body has raised concerns over the bank&#8217;s involvement in crypto-related activities, requiring alignment with established policies. The bank has been given until January 2024 to ensure compliance, a process that involves navigating regulatory capital treatment intricacies.</p>
<p>Founded in 2011, SoFi Bank transitioned from its status as a non-bank entity in 2019 to a fully-fledged financial institution the following year.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/ZSNW1kzy/" alt="Bitcoin (BTC) price chart from Tradingview.com (ETH, DOGE, SoFi Bank)" width="2884" height="1746"/></p>

<h2>Strategic Growth And Financial Success</h2>
<p>The earnings report highlights SoFi Bank&#8217;s business acumen, reflected in its strong second-quarter performance. With a remarkable 37% surge in revenue ($498 million) compared to the previous year, the bank showcases its ability to thrive amidst a rapidly evolving financial landscape.</p>
<p>SoFi Technology Stock also witnessed a 17% surge in July following its Q2 report. &#8220;As a result of this growth in high-quality deposits, we have benefited from a lower cost of funding for our loans,” SoFi CEO Anthony Noto said.</p>

<p>SoFi is not the only bank that has made its way into cryptocurrencies. Major US banks like <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/wells-fargo-offers-cryptocurrency-investment/">Wells Fargo</a>, <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-at-28600-first-republic-sold-to-jp-morgan/" rel="nofollow">JP Morgan</a>, and <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/goldman-bitcoin-is-world-best-performing/">Goldman Sachs</a>, among others, have also taken the plunge to provide access to digital assets and cryptocurrencies for their clients.</p>
<p>Other notable entrants into the industry include <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/blackrock-first-spot-bitcoin-etf/">BlackRock</a> and <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/sec-could-approve-multiple-bitcoin-etfs/">ARK Invest</a>, which have filed applications for Spot Bitcoin ETFs with the SECs. On August 13, the first of these, the ARK Invest application, <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/arks-bitcoin-etf-decision-sec-give-green-light/" rel="nofollow">will be deliberated on to be approved or rejected by the SEC</a>. However, the regulator could also end up extending the deadline.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SoFi-Bank-crypto.png?fit=460%2C243" width="460" height="243" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">546853</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Rollbit Coin Continues Supremacy Over Top 100 Cryptos In The Last Week</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/all/rollbit-coin-continues-supremacy-over-top-100-cryptos-in-the-last-week/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 13:05:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[All]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[RLB]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Rollbit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Token]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=546797</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Within the select group of the top 100 cryptocurrencies at the moment, Rollbit Coin (RLB) stands out as the best-performing project. The token has impressively increased by an astonishing 113% in the last week alone, and its daily performance charts also show an equally impressive gain of 30%. Recent statistics highlight Rollbit&#8217;s impressive financial accomplishments, with its income topping $2 million in the previous day. A wide range of services, such as cryptocurrency futures, sports betting, and casino games, are responsible for this remarkable financial achievement. Related Reading: Rising Star Hedera (HBAR) And Its 11% Climb – A Closer Look A significant amount of funds—net of related expenses—will be routinely and daily dedicated for the procurement of RLB as a direct result of this strong revenue stream. On A Roll &#8211; 94% Rally In The Weekly Timeframe At the time of writing, Rollbit was trading at $0.204, up a solid 30.3%, with an equally strong 94% increase in the last seven days, data from crypto market tracker Coingecko shows. The RLB token experienced a 7,850% increase year-to-date, rising from $0.002 to $0.159 in 2023. Although users should be aware of hazards, this performance emphasizes how technology and money have come together. RLB Revamped Tokenomics 🔥 ~1 month ago we publicly stated that our primary goal is to make RLB the cornerstone of Rollbit. Today we will deliver on that promise through launching the most impactful and highly anticipated feature to date: Buy &#38; Burn From today onwards, revenue… pic.twitter.com/tRzUWwBq1a — Lucky (@Lucky_Rollbit) August 8, 2023 The announcement of a big forthcoming change in the tokenomics of Rollbit&#8217;s native token, RLB, made by its pseudonymous co-founder &#8220;Lucky&#8221; on Tuesday raised interest and discussion in the community. As of today, the market cap of cryptocurrencies stood at $1.13 trillion. Chart: TradingView.com Rollbit has distinguished itself as one of the most quickly developing crypto protocols this year. This tremendous growth is attributable to the company&#8217;s strong alignment with market demands and the positive acceptance of its product by traders and gamblers alike. Thriving Over The Years Lucky claims that because of the variety of its products, Rollbit has thrived over the past few years, &#8220;independent of market situations. Whether it&#8217;s Bull or Bear, our hybrid offerings have enabled us to provide steady income.&#8221; Related Reading: Rising Star Hedera (HBAR) And Its 11% Climb – A Closer Look Since August 4, the RLB price had fallen below the $0.120 horizontal resistance zone. It attempted multiple unsuccessful breakouts throughout this time. On August 8, the price did, however, ultimately rise over the region. The breakout happened quickly, and the same day, RLB hit a new all-time high of $0.24. (This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk). Featured image from Pillai Center]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Within the select group of the top 100 cryptocurrencies at the moment, Rollbit Coin (RLB) stands out as the best-performing project. The token has impressively increased by an astonishing 113% in the last week alone, and its daily performance charts also show an equally impressive gain of 30%.</p>
<p>Recent statistics highlight Rollbit&#8217;s<a href="https://dailyhodl.com/2023/08/09/rollbit-coin-rlb-goes-parabolic-as-co-founder-reveals-revamped-tokenomics-system/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow"> impressive financial accomplishments</a>, with its income topping $2 million in the previous day. A wide range of services, such as cryptocurrency futures, sports betting, and casino games, are responsible for this remarkable financial achievement.</p>

<p>A significant amount of funds—net of related expenses—will be routinely and daily dedicated for the procurement of RLB as a direct result of this strong revenue stream.</p>
<h2><strong>On A Roll &#8211; 94% Rally In The Weekly Timeframe</strong></h2>
<p>At the time of writing, <a href="https://watcher.guru/news/rollbit-coin-takes-crypto-market-by-storm-rises-113" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Rollbit</a> was trading at $0.204, up a solid 30.3%, with an equally strong 94% increase in the last seven days, data from crypto market tracker Coingecko shows.</p>
<p>The RLB token experienced a 7,850% increase year-to-date, rising from $0.002 to $0.159 in 2023. Although users should be aware of hazards, this performance emphasizes how technology and money have come together.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">RLB Revamped Tokenomics <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f525.png" alt="🔥" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /></p>
<p>~1 month ago we publicly stated that our primary goal is to make RLB the cornerstone of Rollbit.</p>
<p>Today we will deliver on that promise through launching the most impactful and highly anticipated feature to date: Buy &amp; Burn</p>
<p>From today onwards, revenue… <a href="https://t.co/tRzUWwBq1a" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/tRzUWwBq1a</a></p>
<p>— Lucky (@Lucky_Rollbit) <a href="https://twitter.com/Lucky_Rollbit/status/1688965999695958022?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">August 8, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p>The announcement of a big forthcoming change in the tokenomics of Rollbit&#8217;s native token, RLB, made by its pseudonymous co-founder &#8220;Lucky&#8221; on Tuesday raised interest and discussion in the community.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/qXznmZPk/" width="1835" height="893"/></p>

<p>Rollbit has distinguished itself as one of the most quickly developing crypto protocols this year. This tremendous growth is attributable to the company&#8217;s strong alignment with market demands and the positive acceptance of its product by traders and gamblers alike.</p>
<h2><strong>Thriving Over The Years</strong></h2>
<p>Lucky claims that because of the variety of its products, Rollbit has thrived over the past few years, &#8220;independent of market situations. Whether it&#8217;s Bull or Bear, our hybrid offerings have enabled us to provide steady income.&#8221;</p>

<p>Since August 4, the RLB price had fallen below the $0.120 horizontal resistance zone. It attempted multiple unsuccessful breakouts throughout this time. On August 8, the price did, however, ultimately rise over the region. The breakout happened quickly, and the same day, RLB hit a new all-time high of $0.24.</p>
<p><em>(This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk).</em></p>
<p><em>Featured image from Pillai Center</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-56.png?fit=460%2C256" width="460" height="256" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">546797</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Solana Cuts Saga Price By 40%, But Case For New SOL Yearly High Increases</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/solana/solana-cuts-saga-price-40-sol-ytd-high/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jake Simmons]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 12:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Solana]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sage]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sol]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Solana smartphone]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SOLUSD]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=546847</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Solana Mobile, a subsidiary of Solana Labs, announced a significant 40% price reduction for its Saga smartphone, slashing the price from its initial $1,000 to a more affordable $599. This move comes just four months after the phone&#8217;s launch, sparking a flurry of reactions from the crypto community. The official statement from the company suggests that the price cut is a strategic move to foster wider adoption of mobile web3 and to enhance the user experience for the Solana mobile community. However, on-chain data paints a slightly different picture. According to data compiled by Flipside Crypto, sales of the Solana Saga have seen a sharp decline since their peak in April and May. This is evidenced by the number of Saga Genesis NFT mints, which are generated when a user sets up their Solana Saga smartphone and accesses the Solana app store. The chart below shows a clear downward trend of sales. Since June sales volume has been extremely flat after a successful May 2023. The price reduction has elicited mixed reactions on Twitter / X. While some early adopters expressed their frustration at purchasing the device at its original price, others defended the move, pointing out the benefits of being an early bird. Notably, early owners had the exclusive opportunity to mint Claynosaurz NFTs, which currently have a floor price of around 33 SOL on Magic Eden, translating to over $800. Related Reading: Solana (SOL) Leads Gains Among Top Coins, Is $30 Milestone Possible? Solana (SOL) Price Analysis On the flip side, the Solana (SOL) token is in bullish territory. At the time of writing, SOL was trading at $24.38. A look at the daily chart shows that SOL was able to confirm the breakout from its downtrend channel on Monday after the price found support at both the channel&#8217;s trend line and the 200-day Exponential Moving Average (EMA). As a result of this bullish confirmation, SOL broke above the 50% Fibonacci retracement level at $23.94. For now, it looks like SOL can defend the level and make a new run towards the 61.8% Fibonacci retracement level at $27.42. Related Reading: Solana Beats Out Ethereum To Emerge As Best Performer In Terms Of TVL Remarkably, on July 14, SOL reached its year-to-date peak of $32.36 and recoiled from the 78.6% Fibonacci retracement level. Subsequently, SOL dipped below the 61.8% Fibonacci level and couldn&#8217;t sustain a daily close above it. Given this context, the $27.42 price point emerges as the most pivotal resistance currently. Should a breakout occur, a clear path to the year&#8217;s high would be established. In this case, a bullish breakout seems imminent. However, strong profit taking can be expected around $32.36. If the yearly high falls, though, the bulls could target the 1.618 Fibonacci extension level at $56.86. Featured image from Disruption Banking, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Solana Mobile, a subsidiary of Solana Labs, announced a significant 40% price reduction for its Saga smartphone, slashing the price from its initial $1,000 to a more affordable $599. This move comes just four months after the phone&#8217;s launch, sparking a flurry of reactions from the crypto community.</p>
<p>The official <a href="https://twitter.com/solanamobile/status/1689305794049634304" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">statement</a> from the company suggests that the price cut is a strategic move to foster wider adoption of mobile web3 and to enhance the user experience for the Solana mobile community. However, on-chain data paints a slightly different picture.</p>
<p>According to data compiled by Flipside Crypto, sales of the Solana Saga have seen a sharp decline since their peak in April and May. This is evidenced by the number of Saga Genesis NFT mints, which are generated when a user sets up their Solana Saga smartphone and accesses the Solana app store. The chart below shows a clear downward trend of sales. Since June sales volume has been extremely flat after a successful May 2023.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-546856 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot-2023-08-11-121611.png?resize=3742%2C1027" alt="Solana Saga sales " width="3742" height="1027" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot-2023-08-11-121611.png?resize=3742%2C1027?w=3742 3742w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot-2023-08-11-121611.png?resize=3742%2C1027?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot-2023-08-11-121611.png?resize=3742%2C1027?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot-2023-08-11-121611.png?resize=3742%2C1027?w=860 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot-2023-08-11-121611.png?resize=3742%2C1027?w=1536 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot-2023-08-11-121611.png?resize=3742%2C1027?w=2048 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot-2023-08-11-121611.png?resize=3742%2C1027?w=750 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot-2023-08-11-121611.png?resize=3742%2C1027?w=1140 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot-2023-08-11-121611.png?resize=3742%2C1027?w=3000 3000w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" data-recalc-dims="1"/>
<p>The price reduction has elicited mixed reactions on Twitter / X. While some early adopters expressed their frustration at purchasing the device at its original price, others defended the move, pointing out the benefits of being an early bird. Notably, early owners had the exclusive opportunity to mint Claynosaurz NFTs, which currently have a floor price of around 33 SOL on Magic Eden, translating to over $800.</p>

<h2>Solana (SOL) Price Analysis</h2>
<p>On the flip side, the Solana (SOL) token is in bullish territory. At the time of writing, SOL was trading at $24.38. A look at the daily chart shows that SOL was able to confirm the breakout from its downtrend channel on Monday after the price found support at both the channel&#8217;s trend line and the 200-day Exponential Moving Average (EMA).</p>
<p>As a result of this bullish confirmation, SOL broke above the 50% Fibonacci retracement level at $23.94. For now, it looks like SOL can defend the level and make a new run towards the 61.8% Fibonacci retracement level at $27.42.</p>

<p>Remarkably, on July 14, SOL reached its year-to-date peak of $32.36 and recoiled from the 78.6% Fibonacci retracement level. Subsequently, SOL dipped below the 61.8% Fibonacci level and couldn&#8217;t sustain a daily close above it.</p>
<p>Given this context, the $27.42 price point emerges as the most pivotal resistance currently. Should a breakout occur, a clear path to the year&#8217;s high would be established. In this case, a bullish breakout seems imminent. However, strong profit taking can be expected around $32.36. If the yearly high falls, though, the bulls could target the 1.618 Fibonacci extension level at $56.86.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-546858 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SOLUSD_2023-08-11_12-23-34.png?resize=3628%2C1672" alt="Solana SOL price" width="3628" height="1672" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SOLUSD_2023-08-11_12-23-34.png?resize=3628%2C1672?w=3628 3628w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SOLUSD_2023-08-11_12-23-34.png?resize=3628%2C1672?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SOLUSD_2023-08-11_12-23-34.png?resize=3628%2C1672?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SOLUSD_2023-08-11_12-23-34.png?resize=3628%2C1672?w=860 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SOLUSD_2023-08-11_12-23-34.png?resize=3628%2C1672?w=1536 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SOLUSD_2023-08-11_12-23-34.png?resize=3628%2C1672?w=2048 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SOLUSD_2023-08-11_12-23-34.png?resize=3628%2C1672?w=750 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SOLUSD_2023-08-11_12-23-34.png?resize=3628%2C1672?w=1140 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SOLUSD_2023-08-11_12-23-34.png?resize=3628%2C1672?w=3000 3000w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" data-recalc-dims="1"/>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/solana.jpg?fit=460%2C255" width="460" height="255" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">546847</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cardano (ADA) Tests Psychological Support &#8211; What&#8217;s The Next Move?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/all/cardano-tests-psychological-support/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 11:05:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[All]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADA price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price action]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=546820</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Cardano (ADA) recently made waves as it brushed against the critical $0.30 resistance level. The significance of such resistance levels in the world of cryptocurrencies cannot be underestimated, as they often mark crucial junctures in the price trajectory of digital assets. Resistance levels serve as key markers on the price charts, indicating levels at which an asset faces heightened selling pressure. These levels are points where a substantial number of traders historically have chosen to sell their holdings, causing the price to temporarily stall or reverse its upward trajectory. Such zones are closely monitored by market participants and analysts alike, as they offer insights into the sentiments and actions of traders.  A successful breach of a resistance level often signifies a potential continuation of the upward trend, while a failure to overcome this obstacle may lead to a period of consolidation or even a reversal. Cardano Recent Performance And Market Landscape As of the latest data from CoinGecko, Cardano (ADA) stands at a price of approximately $0.300341, reflecting a 1.5% decline over the past 24 hours. However, the past seven days have seen a modest 0.9% surge, indicating a relatively stable performance. Related Reading: Turbulent AVAX Price Trends And Fading Trading Activity – What To Expect Notably, ADA&#8217;s recent touch of the $0.30 resistance level has sparked interest among traders and investors, highlighting the psychological significance of this price point. People believe in the long-term potential of #Cardano. According to Morning Consult, people sold $ADA (and Solana) the least often over the past month. Only 22% of holders. $BTC was sold by 46% and $ETH by 33% of holders. pic.twitter.com/UVGDrEasJ0 — Cardanians &#124; stake with CRDN3 (@Cardanians_io) August 11, 2023 Interestingly, ADA&#8217;s current reversal mode should not be seen as an unequivocal bearish signal. The broader crypto market is exhibiting signs of recovery, with several major cryptocurrencies showing renewed potential. Moreover, the absence of intense selling pressure suggests that the recent resistance encounter might not translate into an extended downturn. Sideways Trading In The Near Future Despite the intriguing movement around the $0.30 resistance level, it is plausible that ADA might engage in ongoing sideways trading within the wide range of $0.29 to $0.31, according to a recent price analysis. This is a typical pattern observed in the cryptocurrency market, especially during periods of uncertainty. Such a scenario could persist until the end of the month, with traders cautiously navigating the price fluctuations. Cardano market cap currently at $10.3 billion. Chart: TradingView.com Cardano&#8217;s journey to the $0.30 resistance level is a captivating development in the crypto world. While ADA currently grapples with a reversal mode, the overall market sentiment leans towards recovery. Related Reading: XRP Price: Breaking This Key Resistance Could Propel Crypto To $21 By 2025 – Analyst Understanding the dynamics of resistance levels and their implications is crucial for traders aiming to decipher ADA&#8217;s future price action. As the month unfolds, all eyes will remain on ADA and the wider crypto market to discern whether the sideways trading will give way to a more definitive trend. (This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk). Featured image from CryptoGlobe]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Cardano (ADA) recently made waves as it brushed against the critical $0.30 resistance level. The significance of such resistance levels in the world of cryptocurrencies cannot be underestimated, as they often mark crucial junctures in the price trajectory of digital assets.</p>
<p>Resistance levels serve as key markers on the price charts, indicating levels at which an asset faces heightened selling pressure. </p>
<p>These levels are points where a substantial number of traders historically have chosen to sell their holdings, causing the price to temporarily stall or reverse its upward trajectory. </p>
<p>Such zones are closely monitored by market participants and analysts alike, as they offer insights into the sentiments and actions of traders. </p>
<p>A successful breach of a resistance level often signifies a potential continuation of the upward trend, while a failure to overcome this obstacle may lead to a period of consolidation or even a reversal.</p>
<h2><strong>Cardano Recent Performance And Market Landscape</strong></h2>
<p>As of the latest data from <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/cardano" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">CoinGecko</a>, Cardano (ADA) stands at a price of approximately $0.300341, reflecting a 1.5% decline over the past 24 hours. </p>
<p>However, the past seven days have seen a modest 0.9% surge, indicating a relatively stable performance.</p>

<p>Notably, ADA&#8217;s recent touch of the $0.30 resistance level has sparked interest among traders and investors, highlighting the psychological significance of this price point.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">People believe in the long-term potential of <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Cardano?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#Cardano</a>. According to Morning Consult, people sold <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24ADA&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$ADA</a> (and Solana) the least often over the past month. Only 22% of holders. <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24BTC&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$BTC</a> was sold by 46% and <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24ETH&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$ETH</a> by 33% of holders. <a href="https://t.co/UVGDrEasJ0" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/UVGDrEasJ0</a></p>
<p>— Cardanians | stake with CRDN3 (@Cardanians_io) <a href="https://twitter.com/Cardanians_io/status/1689890826824855552?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">August 11, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p>Interestingly, ADA&#8217;s current reversal mode should not be seen as an unequivocal bearish signal. The broader crypto market is exhibiting signs of recovery, with several major cryptocurrencies showing <a href="https://twitter.com/Cardanians_io/status/1689890826824855552" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">renewed potential</a>. </p>
<p>Moreover, the absence of intense selling pressure suggests that the recent resistance encounter might not translate into an extended downturn.</p>
<h2><strong>Sideways Trading In The Near Future</strong></h2>
<p>Despite the intriguing movement around the $0.30 resistance level, it is plausible that ADA might engage in ongoing sideways trading within the wide range of $0.29 to $0.31, according to a recent <a href="https://u.today/cardano-ada-price-analysis-for-august-10" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">price analysis</a>. </p>
<p>This is a typical pattern observed in the cryptocurrency market, especially during periods of uncertainty. Such a scenario could persist until the end of the month, with traders cautiously navigating the price fluctuations.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/I2kGULpl/" width="2475" height="1179"/></p>

<p>Cardano&#8217;s journey to the $0.30 resistance level is a captivating development in the crypto world. While ADA currently grapples with a reversal mode, the overall market sentiment leans towards recovery.</p>

<p>Understanding the dynamics of resistance levels and their implications is crucial for traders aiming to decipher ADA&#8217;s future price action. </p>
<p>As the month unfolds, all eyes will remain on ADA and the wider crypto market to discern whether the sideways trading will give way to a more definitive trend.</p>
<p><em>(This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk).</em></p>
<p><em>Featured image from CryptoGlobe</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-55.png?fit=460%2C230" width="460" height="230" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">546820</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bittrex, SEC Reach Settlement In Securities Violation Case</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/crypto/bittrex-sec-reach-settlement/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 10:00:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bittrex]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto lawsuit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto settlement]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=546842</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Another crypto firm, Bittrex, bites the dust in the SEC’s continued clampdown on major players in the crypto industry amidst regulatory uncertainty. The regulator has been known to come hard at these crypto firms because it believes they aren’t toeing an almost non-existent regulatory framework.  Bittrex Succumbs To SEC In a press release dated August 10, the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) announced that crypto exchange Bittrex and its former CEO William Shihara have agreed to a $24 million monetary settlement with the regulator. According to the statement, Bittrex’s international affiliate company Bittrex Global GmbH also agreed to settle the charge of failing to register as a national securities exchange. Related Reading: New Milestone For Ethereum Could Spell Good News For ETH Price The SEC had alleged that the crypto exchange and its former CEO operated an “unregistered national securities exchange, broker, and clearing agency.” It argued that the exchange violated securities laws when it offered and allowed US investors to invest in crypto assets, which it deems as securities (The SEC has continued to allege that tokens like MATIC, SOL, ADA, and XRP are securities).  Furthermore, the agency accused the firm and its former CEO of going as far as to cover their tracks in order to escape regulatory scrutiny. The SEC’s complaint stated Shihara directed token issuers, who wanted their tokens listed on the exchange, to remove “problematic statements,” which could lead any regulator to investigate whether or not the company offered and sold securities on the platform. The settlement news may come as a surprise considering many thought the SEC was going to experience a pushback from the crypto exchange. This is because Bittrex had earlier argued that the SEC had no authority to regulate tokens traded on its platform due to a lack of clear-cut law by Congress authorizing the regulator to do so.  SEC Might Be Killing The Crypto Economy Besides Bittrex, the SEC is currently embroiled in legal battles against the world’s biggest cryptocurrency exchanges, Binance and Coinbase. Similarly, it accuses these exchanges of offering and selling securities on their platform without registering with the agency. While many may argue that the SEC is simply doing its job of protecting the interests of US investors, others may take a different point of view by arguing that the SEC is simply killing the Web3 economy in the country. For instance, Bittrex, before filing bankruptcy in the US, had earlier shut down its US operations due to “continued regulatory uncertainty.”  Related Reading: The Spoils Of Victory: XRP Daily Transactions Surpass Ethereum This unfavorable regulatory environment is undoubtedly one of the reasons why some other crypto firms have also chosen to take their operations abroad instead of being domiciled in the US, especially with the fact that other countries are putting crypto-friendly guidelines in place on how crypto exchanges should conduct their operations.  For this reason, Congress needs to step in and pass clear-cut laws that stipulate whether or not crypto exchanges fall under the purview of the SEC, and if yes, it needs to also address whether crypto assets are securities or not.  Total market cap down to $1.133 trillion amid regulatory concerns &#124; Source: Crypto Total Market Cap on Tradingview.com Featured image from Business Insider, chart from Tradingview.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Another crypto firm, Bittrex, bites the dust in the SEC’s continued clampdown on major players in the crypto industry amidst regulatory uncertainty. The regulator has been known to come hard at these crypto firms because it believes they aren’t toeing an almost non-existent regulatory framework. </p>
<h2>Bittrex Succumbs To SEC</h2>
<p>In a press release dated August 10, the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) <a href="https://www.sec.gov/news/press-release/2023-150" rel="nofollow">announced</a> that crypto exchange Bittrex and its former CEO William Shihara have agreed to a $24 million monetary settlement with the regulator. According to the statement, Bittrex’s international affiliate company Bittrex Global GmbH also agreed to settle the charge of failing to register as a national securities exchange.</p>

<p>The SEC had alleged that the crypto exchange and its former CEO operated an “unregistered national securities exchange, broker, and clearing agency.” It argued that the exchange violated securities laws when it offered and allowed US investors to invest in crypto assets, which it deems as securities (The SEC has continued to allege that tokens like MATIC, SOL, ADA, and XRP are securities). </p>
<p>Furthermore, the agency accused the firm and its former CEO of going as far as to cover their tracks in order to escape regulatory scrutiny. The SEC’s complaint stated Shihara directed token issuers, who wanted their tokens listed on the exchange, to remove “problematic statements,” which could lead any regulator to investigate whether or not the company offered and sold securities on the platform.</p>
<p>The settlement news may come as a surprise considering many thought the SEC was going to experience a pushback from the crypto exchange. This is because Bittrex had earlier <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/sec-authority-in-question-bittrex-challenges-court/" rel="nofollow">argued</a> that the SEC had no authority to regulate tokens traded on its platform due to a lack of clear-cut law by Congress authorizing the regulator to do so. </p>
<h2>SEC Might Be Killing The Crypto Economy</h2>
<p>Besides Bittrex, the SEC is currently embroiled in legal battles against the world’s biggest cryptocurrency exchanges, Binance and Coinbase. Similarly, it accuses these exchanges of offering and selling securities on their platform without registering with the agency.</p>
<p>While many may argue that the SEC is simply doing its job of protecting the interests of US investors, others may take a different point of view by arguing that the SEC is simply killing the Web3 economy in the country. For instance, Bittrex, before <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/cryptocurrency-exchange-bittrex-files-for-bankruptcy-amid-sec-probe/">filing</a> bankruptcy in the US, had earlier shut down its US operations due to “continued regulatory uncertainty.” </p>

<p>This unfavorable regulatory environment is undoubtedly one of the reasons why some other crypto firms have also chosen to take their operations abroad instead of being domiciled in the US, especially with the fact that other countries are putting crypto-friendly guidelines in place on how crypto exchanges should conduct their operations. </p>
<p>For this reason, Congress needs to step in and pass clear-cut laws that stipulate whether or not crypto exchanges fall under the purview of the SEC, and if yes, it needs to also address whether crypto assets are securities or not. </p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/0MefFYhF/" alt="Crypto total market cap chart from Tradingview.com (Bittrex)" width="2884" height="1746"/></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bittrex-SEC.jpeg?fit=318%2C159" width="318" height="159" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">546842</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Price Prediction 2024/25: 4-Year Cycle And Elliot Wave Can Coexist</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-price-prediction-2024-25-4-year-cycle-elliot-wave/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jake Simmons]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 08:20:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[4-Year Cycle]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin prediction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elliot Wave]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=546802</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Bitcoin landscape is no stranger to debates and predictions. Two dominant theories are currently at the forefront: the 4-Year Cycle and the Elliot Impulse Wave. However, a comprehensive analysis by the esteemed crypto analyst CryptoCon, suggests a fascinating intersection of these two theories. The Dueling Bitcoin Price Prediction Theories At the heart of the debate are two camps. The first, the 4-Year Cycle proponents, believe in Bitcoin&#8217;s 4-year journey from cycle tops to bottoms, with a predicted zenith in 2025. The second camp, the Elliot Impulse Wave advocates, are forecasting a powerful parabolic top either this year or by early 2024. CryptoCon&#8217;s meticulous analysis, which encompasses TA, on-chain data, market psychology, and more, offers a fresh perspective. &#8220;I believe it may be possible to see the best of both worlds for each group of thinkers,&#8221; he posited. Related Reading: Bitcoin Bears Ran Out Of Coins? What This Analyst Forecast For BTC At Around $30,000 A significant portion of the 4-Year Cycle theory hinges on the halving&#8217;s impact on Bitcoin&#8217;s price. &#8220;When the Bitcoin supply is reduced approximately every 4 years, this should trigger a supply decrease which causes price to rise,&#8221; CryptoCon elucidated. However, he also raised a counterpoint, noting the diminishing influence of miner supply output on Bitcoin&#8217;s price, especially given its current market size. Historical Parallels, Signals And Indicators CryptoCon drew attention to the 2011-2013 cycle, a period that didn&#8217;t adhere to traditional patterns. This cycle experienced both an early and a later top. Could this be a precedent for the current cycle? &#8220;Both of these groups of people seem to forget one particular cycle that seemingly defied all of the rules. 2011 &#8211; 2013,&#8221; he recalled. Two compelling signals were central to his analysis: the DXY Correlation Coefficient and the Vigor Signal. Historically, these have been precursors to a price parabola. &#8220;The parabola signal has triggered. This has been the start of every price parabola by definition,&#8221; he emphasized, underscoring their reliability. Historically, when Bitcoin has shown a low correlation with the US dollar, significant price movements have been observed. Related Reading: Bitcoin Futures Fakeout: The Price Divergence That Predicts A Phony The November 28th Cycles Theory, rooted in the date of Bitcoin&#8217;s first halving, has also been a consistent predictor of Bitcoin&#8217;s price movements for a decade. It segments the Bitcoin price journey into four distinct phases: Green, Blue, Red, and Orange years (see chart below), each with its own characteristic price behavior. &#8220;With its level of accuracy, there&#8217;s no reason to expect it to fail this cycle. Telling us the true cycle top will come late 2025,&#8221; CryptoCon confidently stated. CryptoCon&#8217;s Trend Pattern Price Model, which uses patterns in angles degrees from cycle highs and lows to predict future ones, projects a price of $130,000 by the end of the November 28th Cycle&#8217;s Theory timeframe. He was quick to caution against over-reliance on fundamentals, stating, &#8220;Although many would say there is no limit to price with fundamentals, I think this is an absolutely ridiculous argument.&#8221; Converging BTC Predictions Synthesizing all this data, CryptoCon envisions a scenario where both the 4-Year Cycle and the Elliot Impulse Wave theories might harmoniously coexist. He anticipates an early top around April 2024, potentially reaching $90,000, followed by a mid-cycle bear market. The final top, he predicts, could touch $130k by late 2025. CryptoCon&#8217;s analysis, while detailed and comprehensive, also comes with a dose of humility. &#8220;This is what I believe is possible. Absolute? Hardly,&#8221; he remarked. As the Bitcoin community continues its fervent discussions, one thing remains clear: Only time will truly reveal the course Bitcoin&#8217;s price will take. At press time, the BTC price stood at $29,466. Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Bitcoin landscape is no stranger to debates and predictions. Two dominant theories are currently at the forefront: the 4-Year Cycle and the Elliot Impulse Wave. However, a comprehensive <a href="https://twitter.com/CryptoCon_/status/1689686289379991585" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">analysis</a> by the esteemed crypto analyst CryptoCon, suggests a fascinating intersection of these two theories.</p>
<h2>The Dueling Bitcoin Price Prediction Theories</h2>
<p>At the heart of the debate are two camps. The first, the 4-Year Cycle proponents, believe in Bitcoin&#8217;s 4-year journey from cycle tops to bottoms, with a predicted zenith in 2025. The second camp, the Elliot Impulse Wave advocates, are forecasting a powerful parabolic top either this year or by early 2024.</p>
<p>CryptoCon&#8217;s meticulous analysis, which encompasses TA, on-chain data, market psychology, and more, offers a fresh perspective. &#8220;I believe it may be possible to see the best of both worlds for each group of thinkers,&#8221; he posited.</p>

<p>A significant portion of the 4-Year Cycle theory hinges on the halving&#8217;s impact on Bitcoin&#8217;s price. &#8220;When the Bitcoin supply is reduced approximately every 4 years, this should trigger a supply decrease which causes price to rise,&#8221; CryptoCon elucidated. However, he also raised a counterpoint, noting the diminishing influence of miner supply output on Bitcoin&#8217;s price, especially given its current market size.</p>
<h2>Historical Parallels, Signals And Indicators</h2>
<p>CryptoCon drew attention to the 2011-2013 cycle, a period that didn&#8217;t adhere to traditional patterns. This cycle experienced both an early and a later top. Could this be a precedent for the current cycle? &#8220;Both of these groups of people seem to forget one particular cycle that seemingly defied all of the rules. 2011 &#8211; 2013,&#8221; he recalled.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-546811 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-2011-2013-cycle.png?resize=1920%2C1080" alt="Bitcoin 2011-2013 cycle" width="1920" height="1080" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-2011-2013-cycle.png?resize=1920%2C1080?w=1920 1920w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-2011-2013-cycle.png?resize=1920%2C1080?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-2011-2013-cycle.png?resize=1920%2C1080?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-2011-2013-cycle.png?resize=1920%2C1080?w=860 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-2011-2013-cycle.png?resize=1920%2C1080?w=1536 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-2011-2013-cycle.png?resize=1920%2C1080?w=750 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-2011-2013-cycle.png?resize=1920%2C1080?w=1140 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" data-recalc-dims="1"/>
<p>Two compelling signals were central to his analysis: the DXY Correlation Coefficient and the Vigor Signal. Historically, these have been precursors to a price parabola. &#8220;The parabola signal has triggered. This has been the start of every price parabola by definition,&#8221; he emphasized, underscoring their reliability. Historically, when Bitcoin has shown a low correlation with the US dollar, significant price movements have been observed.</p>

<p>The November 28th Cycles Theory, rooted in the date of Bitcoin&#8217;s first halving, has also been a consistent predictor of Bitcoin&#8217;s price movements for a decade. It segments the Bitcoin price journey into four distinct phases: Green, Blue, Red, and Orange years (see chart below), each with its own characteristic price behavior. &#8220;With its level of accuracy, there&#8217;s no reason to expect it to fail this cycle. Telling us the true cycle top will come late 2025,&#8221; CryptoCon confidently stated.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-546812 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/November-28th-Cycles-Theory.png?resize=1914%2C1135" alt="November 28th Cycles Theory" width="1914" height="1135" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/November-28th-Cycles-Theory.png?resize=1914%2C1135?w=1914 1914w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/November-28th-Cycles-Theory.png?resize=1914%2C1135?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/November-28th-Cycles-Theory.png?resize=1914%2C1135?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/November-28th-Cycles-Theory.png?resize=1914%2C1135?w=860 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/November-28th-Cycles-Theory.png?resize=1914%2C1135?w=1536 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/November-28th-Cycles-Theory.png?resize=1914%2C1135?w=750 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/November-28th-Cycles-Theory.png?resize=1914%2C1135?w=1140 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" data-recalc-dims="1"/>
<p>CryptoCon&#8217;s Trend Pattern Price Model, which uses patterns in angles degrees from cycle highs and lows to predict future ones, projects a price of $130,000 by the end of the November 28th Cycle&#8217;s Theory timeframe. He was quick to caution against over-reliance on fundamentals, stating, &#8220;Although many would say there is no limit to price with fundamentals, I think this is an absolutely ridiculous argument.&#8221;</p>
<h2>Converging BTC Predictions</h2>
<p>Synthesizing all this data, CryptoCon envisions a scenario where both the 4-Year Cycle and the Elliot Impulse Wave theories might harmoniously coexist. He anticipates an early top around April 2024, potentially reaching $90,000, followed by a mid-cycle bear market. The final top, he predicts, could touch $130k by late 2025.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-546809 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-cycle-possibilies.jpg?resize=1920%2C1077" alt="Bitcoin cycle possibilities" width="1920" height="1077" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-cycle-possibilies.jpg?resize=1920%2C1077?w=1920 1920w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-cycle-possibilies.jpg?resize=1920%2C1077?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-cycle-possibilies.jpg?resize=1920%2C1077?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-cycle-possibilies.jpg?resize=1920%2C1077?w=860 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-cycle-possibilies.jpg?resize=1920%2C1077?w=1536 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-cycle-possibilies.jpg?resize=1920%2C1077?w=750 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-cycle-possibilies.jpg?resize=1920%2C1077?w=1140 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" data-recalc-dims="1"/>
<p>CryptoCon&#8217;s analysis, while detailed and comprehensive, also comes with a dose of humility. &#8220;This is what I believe is possible. Absolute? Hardly,&#8221; he remarked. As the Bitcoin community continues its fervent discussions, one thing remains clear: Only time will truly reveal the course Bitcoin&#8217;s price will take.</p>
<p>At press time, the BTC price stood at $29,466.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-546814 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD_2023-08-11_09-12-35.png?resize=3628%2C1672" alt="Bitcoin price" width="3628" height="1672" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD_2023-08-11_09-12-35.png?resize=3628%2C1672?w=3628 3628w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD_2023-08-11_09-12-35.png?resize=3628%2C1672?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD_2023-08-11_09-12-35.png?resize=3628%2C1672?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD_2023-08-11_09-12-35.png?resize=3628%2C1672?w=860 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD_2023-08-11_09-12-35.png?resize=3628%2C1672?w=1536 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD_2023-08-11_09-12-35.png?resize=3628%2C1672?w=2048 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD_2023-08-11_09-12-35.png?resize=3628%2C1672?w=750 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD_2023-08-11_09-12-35.png?resize=3628%2C1672?w=1140 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD_2023-08-11_09-12-35.png?resize=3628%2C1672?w=3000 3000w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" data-recalc-dims="1"/>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/iStock-1296910866.jpg?fit=460%2C283" width="460" height="283" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">546802</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Turbulent AVAX Price Trends And Fading Trading Activity &#8211; What To Expect</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/all/turbulent-avax-price-trends-and-fading-trading-activity-what-to-expect/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 07:19:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[All]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Avalanche]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AVAX Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price action]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=546801</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Avalanche (AVAX) has found itself ensnared within a critical price zone, grappling with a lackluster trading volume that has hindered its price action. The coin&#8217;s journey has been fraught with challenges as market sentiment takes a bearish stance, casting shadows over its potential upward trajectory. The recent attempt at a bullish surge, stemming from the $11 support level, encountered a formidable obstacle at the $15.8 resistance level. This pivotal juncture proved to be an insurmountable barrier, leading to an abrupt price rejection.  The consequence of this rejection has been instrumental in preserving AVAX&#8217;s bearish market structure, leaving traders and investors grappling with uncertainty. AVAX Long/Short Ratio Signals Predominance Of Sellers On closer examination of the trading landscape, the long/short ratio in the four-hour timeframe reveals a striking imbalance in favor of sellers. Data sourced from Coinglass paints a telling picture, with a staggering 56.5% of open contracts adopting short positions. &#160; Source: Coinglass This lopsided ratio serves as a clear indication that a significant cohort of market participants anticipates AVAX&#8217;s downward trajectory to persist, amplifying the prevailing bearish sentiment. The culmination of these factors has translated into AVAX&#8217;s current price of $12.46, as reported by CoinGecko. Over the past 24 hours, the cryptocurrency has experienced a modest decline of 0.6%, reflective of the prevailing market volatility. AVAX price today. Source: Coingecko Furthermore, the seven-day trend highlights a marginal contraction of 0.2%, further underscoring the turbulent nature of AVAX&#8217;s recent price movements. Uncertainty Looms As Sellers Maintain Grip As AVAX navigates this challenging phase, uncertainty looms large over its immediate future. The lack of trading volume has left the cryptocurrency vulnerable to sudden and sharp price fluctuations, while the prevailing bearish sentiment continues to deter potential investors from entering the market. Related Reading: XRP Price: Breaking This Key Resistance Could Propel Crypto To $21 By 2025 – Analyst In this climate of uncertainty, all eyes remain fixated on the interplay between support and resistance levels., According to a recent price analysis, the token&#8217;s ability to transcend the $15.8 resistance level will likely dictate its trajectory moving forward. AVAX market cap at $4.2 billion today. Chart: TradingView.com Should this barrier be breached, it could instill newfound confidence among traders, potentially mitigating the bearish grip that currently envelopes the market sentiment. AVAX finds itself at a critical crossroads, grappling with a lack of trading volume and a prevailing bearish sentiment. The recent price rejection has sustained the cryptocurrency&#8217;s bearish market structure, with the long/short ratio skewing significantly towards sellers. Related Reading: Rising Star Hedera (HBAR) And Its 11% Climb – A Closer Look As AVAX treads cautiously through this uncertain terrain, the cryptocurrency community watches, eager to discern whether the current challenges will pave the way for a resurgence or further deepen its bearish trajectory. (This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk). Featured image from Token Gamer]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Avalanche (AVAX) has found itself ensnared within a critical price zone, grappling with a lackluster trading volume that has hindered its price action. The coin&#8217;s journey has been fraught with challenges as market sentiment takes a bearish stance, casting shadows over its potential upward trajectory.</p>
<p>The recent attempt at a bullish surge, stemming from the $11 support level, encountered a formidable obstacle at the $15.8 resistance level. This pivotal juncture proved to be an insurmountable barrier, leading to an abrupt price rejection. </p>
<p>The consequence of this rejection has been instrumental in preserving AVAX&#8217;s bearish market structure, leaving traders and investors grappling with uncertainty.</p>
<h2><strong>AVAX Long/Short Ratio Signals Predominance Of Sellers</strong></h2>
<p>On closer examination of the trading landscape, the long/short ratio in the four-hour timeframe reveals a striking imbalance in favor of sellers. Data sourced from <a href="https://www.coinglass.com/LongShortRatio" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Coinglass</a> paints a telling picture, with a staggering 56.5% of open contracts adopting short positions.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-546816 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-54.png?resize=625%2C386" alt="" width="625" height="386" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-54.png?resize=625%2C386?w=625 625w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-54.png?resize=625%2C386?w=460 460w" sizes="(max-width: 625px) 100vw, 625px" data-recalc-dims="1"/></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>

<p>This lopsided ratio serves as a clear indication that a significant cohort of market participants anticipates AVAX&#8217;s downward trajectory to persist, amplifying the prevailing bearish sentiment.</p>
<p>The culmination of these factors has translated into AVAX&#8217;s current price of $12.46, as reported by <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/avalanche" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">CoinGecko</a>. Over the past 24 hours, the cryptocurrency has experienced a modest decline of 0.6%, reflective of the prevailing market volatility. </p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-546806" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-52.png?resize=1024%2C52" alt="" width="1024" height="52" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-52.png?resize=1024%2C52?w=1136 1136w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-52.png?resize=1024%2C52?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-52.png?resize=1024%2C52?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-52.png?resize=1024%2C52?w=860 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-52.png?resize=1024%2C52?w=750 750w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" data-recalc-dims="1"/></p>

<p>Furthermore, the seven-day trend highlights a marginal contraction of 0.2%, further underscoring the turbulent nature of AVAX&#8217;s recent price movements.</p>
<h2><strong>Uncertainty Looms As Sellers Maintain Grip</strong></h2>
<p>As AVAX navigates this challenging phase, uncertainty looms large over its immediate future. The lack of trading volume has left the cryptocurrency vulnerable to sudden and sharp price fluctuations, while the prevailing bearish sentiment continues to deter potential investors from entering the market.</p>

<p>In this climate of uncertainty, all eyes remain fixated on the interplay between support and resistance levels., According to a recent <a href="https://ambcrypto.com/sloppy-price-action-declining-volume-whats-next-for-avax/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">price analysis</a>, the token&#8217;s ability to transcend the $15.8 resistance level will likely dictate its trajectory moving forward.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/8VZphxJx/" width="2475" height="1179"/></p>

<p>Should this barrier be breached, it could instill newfound confidence among traders, potentially mitigating the bearish grip that currently envelopes the market sentiment.</p>
<p>AVAX finds itself at a critical crossroads, grappling with a lack of trading volume and a prevailing bearish sentiment. The recent price rejection has sustained the cryptocurrency&#8217;s bearish market structure, with the long/short ratio skewing significantly towards sellers.</p>

<p>As AVAX treads cautiously through this uncertain terrain, the cryptocurrency community watches, eager to discern whether the current challenges will pave the way for a resurgence or further deepen its bearish trajectory.</p>
<p><em>(This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk).</em></p>
<p><em>Featured image from Token Gamer</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-53.png?fit=460%2C208" width="460" height="208" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">546801</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>SOL Price Prediction: Solana Could Soon Surge Past $25</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/sol-price-prediction-solana-surge-25/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 06:19:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Technical analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sol]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Solana]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SOLUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SOLUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=546793</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Solana is attempting a fresh increase above the $25 resistance against the US Dollar. SOL price rally toward $30 if there is a close above $25.65. SOL price is showing positive signs above the $23.80 level against the US Dollar. The price is now trading above $24 and the 100 simple moving average (4 hours). There was a break above a major bearish trend line with resistance near $23.10 on the 4-hour chart of the SOL/USD pair (data source from Kraken). The pair could continue to move up if it clears the $25.65 resistance zone. Solana Price Starts Fresh Increase After a steady decline, Solana’s price found support near the $22.20 zone. SOL traded as low as $22.22 and recently started a fresh increase, unlike Bitcoin and Ethereum. The price climbed above the $23.20 and $24.00 resistance levels. There was a break above a major bearish trend line with resistance near $23.10 on the 4-hour chart of the SOL/USD pair. The pair climbed above the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $25.65 swing high to the $22.22 low. SOL is now trading above $24 and the 100 simple moving average (4 hours). On the upside, immediate resistance is near the $24.85 level. It is near the 76.4% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $25.65 swing high to the $22.22 low. Source: SOLUSD on TradingView.com The first major resistance is near the $25.65 level. A clear move above the $25.65 resistance might send the price toward the $28.80 resistance. Any more gains might send the price toward the $30 level. Are Dips Limited in SOL? If SOL fails to clear the $25.65 resistance, it could start a fresh decline. Initial support on the downside is near the $24.00 level and the 100 SMA. The first major support is near the $23.50 level. If there is a close below the $23.50 support, the price could decline toward the $22.50 support. In the stated case, there is a risk of more downsides toward the $21.20 support in the near term. Technical Indicators 4-Hours MACD – The MACD for SOL/USD is gaining pace in the bullish zone. 4-Hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for SOL/USD is above the 50 level. Major Support Levels – $24.00, and $23.50. Major Resistance Levels – $24.85, $25.65, and $30.00.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>Solana is attempting a fresh increase above the $25 resistance against the US Dollar. SOL price rally toward $30 if there is a close above $25.65.</em></p>
<ul>
<li>SOL price is showing positive signs above the $23.80 level against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>The price is now trading above $24 and the 100 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There was a break above a major bearish trend line with resistance near $23.10 on the 4-hour chart of the SOL/USD pair (data source from Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could continue to move up if it clears the $25.65 resistance zone.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Solana Price Starts Fresh Increase</h2>
<p>After a steady decline, Solana’s price found support near the $22.20 zone. SOL traded as low as $22.22 and recently started a fresh increase, unlike <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-next-leg-lower-28800/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Bitcoin</a> and <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-thrust-1820/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Ethereum</a>.</p>
<p>The price climbed above the $23.20 and $24.00 resistance levels. There was a break above a major bearish trend line with resistance near $23.10 on the 4-hour chart of the SOL/USD pair. The pair climbed above the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $25.65 swing high to the $22.22 low.</p>
<p>SOL is now trading above $24 and the 100 simple moving average (4 hours). On the upside, immediate resistance is near the $24.85 level. It is near the 76.4% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $25.65 swing high to the $22.22 low.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-546794" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Solana.png?resize=1024%2C468" alt="SOL Price Prediction" width="1024" height="468" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Solana.png?resize=1024%2C468?w=1835 1835w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Solana.png?resize=1024%2C468?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Solana.png?resize=1024%2C468?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Solana.png?resize=1024%2C468?w=860 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Solana.png?resize=1024%2C468?w=1536 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Solana.png?resize=1024%2C468?w=750 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Solana.png?resize=1024%2C468?w=1140 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" data-recalc-dims="1"/></p>
<p>Source: <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/SOLUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">SOLUSD on TradingView.com</a></p>
<p>The first major resistance is near the $25.65 level. A clear move above the $25.65 resistance might send the price toward the $28.80 resistance. Any more gains might send the price toward the $30 level.</p>
<h2>Are Dips Limited in SOL?</h2>
<p>If SOL fails to clear the $25.65 resistance, it could start a fresh decline. Initial support on the downside is near the $24.00 level and the 100 SMA.</p>
<p>The first major support is near the $23.50 level. If there is a close below the $23.50 support, the price could decline toward the $22.50 support. In the stated case, there is a risk of more downsides toward the $21.20 support in the near term.</p>
<p>Technical Indicators</p>
<p>4-Hours MACD – The MACD for SOL/USD is gaining pace in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>4-Hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for SOL/USD is above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Levels – $24.00, and $23.50.</p>
<p>Major Resistance Levels – $24.85, $25.65, and $30.00.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/shutterstock_589406480.jpg?fit=460%2C304" width="460" height="304" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">546793</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum Price Could See Downside Thrust Before Fresh Increase</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-thrust-1820/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 05:34:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=546787</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Ethereum price is correcting gains from the $1,880 zone against the US Dollar. ETH could spike toward $1,820 before the bulls attempt a fresh increase. Ethereum is moving lower from the $1,875 and $1,880 resistance levels. The price is trading below $1,850 and the 100-hourly Simple Moving Average. There is a bullish flag pattern forming with resistance near $1,855 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD (data feed via Kraken). The pair could drop toward the $1,820 support where the bulls might take a stand. Ethereum Price Dips Again Ethereum’s price struggled to clear the $1,880 resistance zone and started a downside correction. ETH slowly moved lower below the $1,850 pivot level, similar to Bitcoin. There was a drop below the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the key increase from the $1,800 swing low to the $1,876 high. The bears even pushed the price below the 100-hourly Simple Moving Average. Besides, there is a bullish flag pattern forming with resistance near $1,855 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD. Ether is now trading below $1,850 and the 100-hourly Simple Moving Average. On the upside, immediate resistance is near the $1,855 level and the channel zone. Source: ETHUSD on TradingView.com The first major resistance is near the $1,872 level. The next key resistance is near the $1,880 level. A close above the $1,880 level could increase the chances of a steady increase toward $1,920. Any more gains might send the price toward the $2,000 hurdle, above which the price could rise toward the $2,040 level or even $2,120. Downside Break in ETH? If Ethereum fails to clear the $1,855 resistance, it could continue to move down. Initial support on the downside is near the $1,840 level or the 50% Fib retracement level of the key increase from the $1,800 swing low to the $1,876 high. The first major support is near the $1,830 zone or the channel lower trend line. If the bulls fail to protect the $1,820 support, there could be a sharp decline. The next major support is near the $1,800 support level. Any more losses might send the price toward the $1,720 level in the near term. Technical Indicators Hourly MACD – The MACD for ETH/USD is losing momentum in the bullish zone. Hourly RSI &#8211; The RSI for ETH/USD is now below the 50 level. Major Support Level – $1,820 Major Resistance Level – $1,880]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>Ethereum price is correcting gains from the $1,880 zone against the US Dollar. ETH could spike toward $1,820 before the bulls attempt a fresh increase.</em></p>
<ul>
<li>Ethereum is moving lower from the $1,875 and $1,880 resistance levels.</li>
<li>The price is trading below $1,850 and the 100-hourly Simple Moving Average.</li>
<li>There is a bullish flag pattern forming with resistance near $1,855 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD (data feed via Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could drop toward the $1,820 support where the bulls might take a stand.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Ethereum Price Dips Again</h2>
<p>Ethereum’s price struggled to clear the $1,880 resistance zone and started a downside correction. ETH slowly moved lower below the $1,850 pivot level, similar to <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-next-leg-lower-28800/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Bitcoin</a>.</p>
<p>There was a drop below the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the key increase from the $1,800 swing low to the $1,876 high. The bears even pushed the price below the 100-hourly Simple Moving Average. Besides, there is a bullish flag pattern forming with resistance near $1,855 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD.</p>
<p>Ether is now trading below $1,850 and the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-bullish-1880/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">100-hourly Simple Moving Average</a>. On the upside, immediate resistance is near the $1,855 level and the channel zone.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-546788" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Ethereum-1.png?resize=1024%2C468" alt="Ethereum Price" width="1024" height="468" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Ethereum-1.png?resize=1024%2C468?w=1835 1835w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Ethereum-1.png?resize=1024%2C468?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Ethereum-1.png?resize=1024%2C468?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Ethereum-1.png?resize=1024%2C468?w=860 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Ethereum-1.png?resize=1024%2C468?w=1536 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Ethereum-1.png?resize=1024%2C468?w=750 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Ethereum-1.png?resize=1024%2C468?w=1140 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" data-recalc-dims="1"/></p>
<p>Source: <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/ETHUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">ETHUSD on TradingView.com</a></p>
<p>The first major resistance is near the $1,872 level. The next key resistance is near the $1,880 level. A close above the $1,880 level could increase the chances of a steady increase toward $1,920. Any more gains might send the price toward the $2,000 hurdle, above which the price could rise toward the $2,040 level or even $2,120.</p>
<h2>Downside Break in ETH?</h2>
<p>If Ethereum fails to clear the $1,855 resistance, it could continue to move down. Initial support on the downside is near the $1,840 level or the 50% Fib retracement level of the key increase from the $1,800 swing low to the $1,876 high.</p>
<p>The first major support is near the $1,830 zone or the channel lower trend line. If the bulls fail to protect the $1,820 support, there could be a sharp decline. The next major support is near the $1,800 support level. Any more losses might send the price toward the $1,720 level in the near term.</p>
<p>Technical Indicators</p>
<p>Hourly MACD<strong> – </strong>The MACD for ETH/USD is losing momentum in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>Hourly RSI<strong> &#8211; </strong>The RSI for ETH/USD is now below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Level – $1,820</p>
<p>Major Resistance Level – $1,880</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/shutterstock_1100038610.jpg?fit=460%2C272" width="460" height="272" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">546787</post-id>	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
