<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"

	xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
	xmlns:geo="http://www.w3.org/2003/01/geo/wgs84_pos#"
	>

<channel>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.newsbtc.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<description>Bitcoin &#38; Cryptocurrency News Today</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 23:02:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-cropped-favicon.png?fit=32%2C32</url>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
<site xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">221170450</site>	<item>
		<title>Key On-Chain Metric Points to Stagnation, Will Ethereum Ever Break $2,000?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/ethereum/on-chain-metric-stagnation-ethereum-break-2000/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dalmas Ngetich]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 03:00:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DeFi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum bulls]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=545575</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[According to Etherscan data, the number of active ERC-20 addresses has not changed much in 2023. It has stayed between 200,000 and 300,000 while Ethereum prices stagnate below July 2023 highs. As of August 2, there were about 275,000 active ERC-20 addresses, up from 156,000 on June 18. Although activity has been low overall, there was a significant increase on June 11, with over 446,000 active ERC-20 addresses. Ethereum&#8217;s price trajectory has been tumultuous in tandem with this activity pattern, looking at the charts. For instance, Ethereum bulls have failed to breach the $2,100 liquidation level posted in the latter stages of H1 2023.  Ethereum Prices Volatile, Few Coins Burned At the moment, ETH prices hover around the $1,800 range, teetering precariously and likely to drop, looking at candlestick arrangements in the daily chart. Although Ethereum has been bullish in the past two months, bulls have been tamed, and a drop below the $1,800 level may signal a shift from bullish to bearish in the medium term. With ETH under pressure, the number of active ERC-20 addresses remains constant and relatively lower than the 2021 peaks. This means there is less demand for ETH, which is used to pay transaction fees. As a result, gas fees are lower because there is less competition for block space. Typically, this would encourage more people to participate and even deploy complex contracts in decentralized finance (DeFi).  Related Reading: Ethereum ETFs Heat Up As Filings With SEC Climbs To Six With EIP-1559 in the equation, low activity means fewer coins are taken out of circulation. Despite low network activity, the protocol continues to issue 2 ETH after each validated block, watering down deflationary effects enforced by EIP-1559.  DeFi Activities Falling Falling activity could be attributed to the waning interest in decentralized finance (DeFi) activities over recent months. As of August 2, the total value locked (TVL) remains below $50 billion, with a significant portion of assets tied in Ethereum. DeFi projects like LidoDAO, Curve, and Uniswap facilitate the trading of ERC-20 tokens. Furthermore, on-chain data highlights USDT as the most actively transacted token. Given its position as the third-largest coin by market cap, with substantial circulation in Ethereum and Tron networks, such a trend is expected. Looking back at ERC-20 transactions from June and July, it is evident that transfers stayed constant despite temporary price increases. Ethereum prices rose from $1,630 to $2,000 between mid-June and mid-July 2023, but ETH is now lower.  Related Reading: BNB Nears $250 Level As Market Suffers Volatility; What’s Driving It? On-chain ERC-20 activity has remained stable despite price volatility. It&#8217;s unclear whether there will be a change in activity as prices continue to drop. However, lower prices may force token holders to wait and see, leading to less activity. Feature image from Canva, chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>According to Etherscan <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://etherscan.io/chart/erc20-active-address" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">data</a>, the number of active ERC-20 addresses has not changed much in 2023. It has stayed between 200,000 and 300,000 while Ethereum prices stagnate below July 2023 highs. As of August 2, there were about 275,000 active ERC-20 addresses, up from 156,000 on June 18. Although activity has been low overall, there was a significant increase on June 11, with over 446,000 active ERC-20 addresses.</p>
<img decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-545577" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/active-erc20-addresses.jpeg?resize=1024%2C939" alt="Active ERC-20 Addresses: Etherscan" width="1024" height="939" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/active-erc20-addresses.jpeg?resize=1024%2C939?w=1200 1200w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/active-erc20-addresses.jpeg?resize=1024%2C939?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/active-erc20-addresses.jpeg?resize=1024%2C939?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/active-erc20-addresses.jpeg?resize=1024%2C939?w=860 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/active-erc20-addresses.jpeg?resize=1024%2C939?w=750 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/active-erc20-addresses.jpeg?resize=1024%2C939?w=1140 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" loading="lazy" data-recalc-dims="1"/>
<p>Ethereum&#8217;s price trajectory has been tumultuous in tandem with this activity pattern, looking at the charts. For instance, Ethereum bulls have failed to breach the $2,100 liquidation level posted in the latter stages of H1 2023. </p>
<h2>Ethereum Prices Volatile, Few Coins Burned</h2>
<p>At the moment, ETH prices hover around the $1,800 range, teetering precariously and likely to drop, looking at candlestick arrangements in the daily chart. Although Ethereum has been bullish in the past two months, bulls have been tamed, and a drop below the $1,800 level may signal a shift from bullish to bearish in the medium term.</p>
<a href="https://www.tradingview.com/x/DZsgN32I/" rel="nofollow"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/DZsgN32I/" alt="ETH price on August 2| Source: ETHUSDT on Binance, TradingView" width="1226" height="595"/></a>
<p>With ETH under pressure, the number of active ERC-20 addresses remains constant and relatively lower than the 2021 peaks. This means there is less demand for ETH, which is used to pay transaction fees. As a result, gas fees are lower because there is less competition for block space. Typically, this would encourage more people to participate and even deploy complex contracts in decentralized finance (DeFi). </p>

<p>With <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://ultrasound.money/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">EIP-1559</a> in the equation, low activity means fewer coins are taken out of circulation. Despite low network activity, the protocol continues to issue 2 ETH after each validated block, watering down deflationary effects enforced by EIP-1559. </p>
<h2>DeFi Activities Falling</h2>
<p>Falling activity could be attributed to the waning interest in decentralized finance (DeFi) activities over recent months. As of August 2, the total value locked (TVL) <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://defillama.com/home" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">remains</a> below $50 billion, with a significant portion of assets tied in Ethereum. DeFi projects like LidoDAO, Curve, and Uniswap facilitate the trading of ERC-20 tokens.</p>
<p>Furthermore, on-chain data <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.coinlore.com/coin/tether" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">highlights</a> USDT as the most actively transacted token. Given its position as the third-largest coin by market cap, with substantial circulation in Ethereum and Tron networks, such a trend is expected.</p>
<p>Looking back at ERC-20 transactions from June and July, it is evident that transfers stayed constant despite temporary price increases. Ethereum prices rose from $1,630 to $2,000 between mid-June and mid-July 2023, but ETH is now lower. </p>

<p>On-chain ERC-20 activity has remained stable despite price volatility. It&#8217;s unclear whether there will be a change in activity as prices continue to drop. However, lower prices may force token holders to wait and see, leading to less activity.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Ethereum-ERC-20-Addresses.jpg?fit=460%2C260" width="460" height="260" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">545575</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Whale Activity Spikes As Shiba Inu Preps For Shibarium Launch</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/whale-activity-spikes-as-shiba-inu-preps-for-shibarium-launch/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samuel Edyme]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 02:00:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Shiba Inu]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[memecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIB]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIBUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=545557</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Shiba Inu, a cryptocurrency that originated as a meme but has now solidified its market presence, is making waves with the &#8216;Shibarium&#8217; launch on the horizon. Data from IntoTheBlock reveals that the crypto&#8217;s whales &#8211; entities holding large quantities &#8211; have shifted billions of SHIB tokens in the past 24 hours. This vast movement of funds coincides with an increase in Shiba Inu&#8217;s large transaction volume, reaching roughly 1.13 trillion SHIB. It appears that large-scale investors are making their moves in anticipation of the cryptocurrency&#8217;s next big announcement, which is likely to be the Shibarium launch. Related Reading: Shiba Inu Price Prediction: Is Shibarium The Key To A Trend Reversal? Whales And Burn Rates &#8211; Shiba Inu Active Market The metric of large transaction volumes serves as a key indicator, offering a snapshot of the activities carried out by prominent players, often called &#8216;whales,&#8217; within the crypto ecosystem during a specific timeframe. This measure mainly provides valuable insights into the magnitude of transactions made by these influential participants on any given day, reflecting their potential impact on the market dynamics. IntoTheBlock defines large transactions as transfers exceeding $100,000. And as it stands, the recent activity shows increasing movements on the Shiba Inu market, with whales adjusting their holdings. Simultaneously, there has been a significant uptick in the burning of SHIB tokens, doubling in the past 24 hours. According to data from Shibburn, a platform solely for tracking Shiba Inu burn activities, over 62 million SHIB tokens have been eliminated from circulation in the past day, increasing the total SHIB burn rate by 220% over the same period. Notably, this deliberate reduction of available tokens is a strategy often used in the crypto sphere to create scarcity and potentially drive up the value of the remaining tokens in the long, in this case, the price of SHIB. The Shibarium Anticipation The recent activity among SHIB&#8217;s largest holders may be connected to the upcoming Shibarium launch. Bitcoin advocate Davinci Jeremie has recently expressed his bullish sentiment on X (formerly known as Twitter), stating, &#8220;Big things are happening for Shib looking forward to [seeing] what happens.&#8221; Related Reading: Shibarium Hype: Shiba Inu Whales Boost Appetite, Snag 1 Trillion SHIB Tokens Further fuelling the anticipation, the official SHIB account on X also hinted at the community with a post featuring a cheerful expression of a Shiba Inu dog. However, the specifics of what these &#8220;big things&#8221; could be remain uncertain, further stoking the fires of curiosity and excitement among the Shiba Inu investors. GM #SHIBARMY pic.twitter.com/bC60SaRx4L — Shib (@Shibtoken) August 2, 2023 However, as the curtain rises on the next chapter for Shiba Inu, the recent flurry of whale activity and the increased burn rate underline a market bracing for impact. Whether the coming changes propel SHIB to new heights or steer it down another path is a story that remains to be written. Meanwhile, Shiba Inu token SHIB has seen quite a retrace in the past 24 hours following a more than 5% increase over the past 7 days. At the time of writing, SHIB trades for $0.00000817 down by 1.1% in the past 24 hours. Featured image from Unsplash, Chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Shiba Inu, a cryptocurrency that originated as a meme but has now solidified its market presence, is making waves with the &#8216;Shibarium&#8217; launch on the horizon. <a href="https://app.intotheblock.com/coin/SHIB/deep-dive?group=all&amp;chart=all" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Data </a>from IntoTheBlock reveals that the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/shiba-inu-whales-snag-1-trillion-tokens/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">crypto&#8217;s whales</a> &#8211; entities holding large quantities &#8211; have shifted billions of SHIB tokens in the past 24 hours.</p>
<p>This vast movement of funds coincides with an increase in Shiba Inu&#8217;s large transaction volume, reaching roughly 1.13 trillion SHIB. It appears that large-scale investors are making their moves in anticipation of the cryptocurrency&#8217;s next big announcement, which is likely to be the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/shiba-inu-price-prediction-shibarium-trend-reversal/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Shibarium launch.</a></p>

<h2>Whales And Burn Rates &#8211; Shiba Inu Active Market</h2>
<p>The metric of large transaction volumes serves as a key indicator, offering a snapshot of the activities carried out by prominent players, often called &#8216;whales,&#8217; within the crypto ecosystem during a specific timeframe. </p>
<p>This measure mainly provides valuable insights into the magnitude of transactions made by these influential participants on any given day, reflecting their potential impact on the market dynamics.</p>
<p>IntoTheBlock defines large transactions as transfers exceeding $100,000. And as it stands, the recent activity shows increasing movements on the Shiba Inu market, with whales adjusting their holdings. Simultaneously, there has been a significant uptick in the burning of SHIB tokens, doubling in the past 24 hours. </p>
<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w" dir="ltr">According to data from <a href="https://www.shibburn.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Shibburn</a>, a platform solely for tracking Shiba Inu burn activities, over 62 million SHIB tokens have been eliminated from circulation in the past day, increasing the total SHIB burn rate by 220% over the same period.</p>
<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w" dir="ltr">Notably, this deliberate reduction of available tokens is a strategy often used in the crypto sphere to create scarcity and potentially drive up the value of the remaining tokens in the long, in this case, <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/why-shiba-inu-burns-do-not-impact-shib-price/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">the price of SHIB</a>.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">The Shibarium Anticipation</h2>
<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w" dir="ltr">The recent activity among SHIB&#8217;s largest holders may be connected to the upcoming Shibarium launch. Bitcoin advocate Davinci Jeremie has recently expressed his bullish sentiment on X (formerly known as Twitter), <a href="https://twitter.com/Davincij15/status/1686365776511426560?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">stating</a>, &#8220;Big things are happening for Shib looking forward to [seeing] what happens.&#8221;</p>

<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w" dir="ltr">Further fuelling the anticipation, the official SHIB account on X also hinted at the community with a <a href="https://twitter.com/Shibtoken/status/1686692934698119168?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">post</a> featuring a cheerful expression of a Shiba Inu dog. However, the specifics of what these &#8220;big things&#8221; could be remain uncertain, further stoking the fires of curiosity and excitement among the Shiba Inu investors.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="und">GM <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/SHIBARMY?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#SHIBARMY</a> <a href="https://t.co/bC60SaRx4L" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/bC60SaRx4L</a></p>
<p>— Shib (@Shibtoken) <a href="https://twitter.com/Shibtoken/status/1686692934698119168?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">August 2, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w" dir="ltr">However, as the curtain rises on the next chapter for Shiba Inu, the recent flurry of whale activity and the increased burn rate underline a <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/shiba-inu-will-this-bullish-formation-lead-to-a-25-upsurge/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">market bracing for impact</a>. Whether the coming changes propel SHIB to new heights or steer it down another path is a story that remains to be written.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/P3q87jT1/" alt="Shiba Inu (SHIB)’s price chart on TradingView" width="2770" height="1556"/>
<p dir="ltr">Meanwhile, <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/shiba-inu-reclaims-14th-spot/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Shiba Inu token</a> SHIB has seen quite a retrace in the past 24 hours following a more than 5% increase over the past 7 days. At the time of writing, SHIB trades for $0.00000817 down by 1.1% in the past 24 hours.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Featured image from Unsplash, Chart from TradingView</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/todd-cravens-QnBrjY-nFUs-unsplash-2.jpg?fit=460%2C305" width="460" height="305" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">545557</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Litecoin Completes Halving, But Price Plunges 6%</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/litecoin/litecoin-completes-halving-but-price-plunges-6/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hououin Kyouma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 01:00:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Litecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Litecoin Halving]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ltc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ltc/usd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=545562</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Litecoin has completed its much-anticipated halving event today, but it seems the investors have reacted by participating in a selloff. Litecoin Has Completed Its Third Halving, Block Rewards Now Down To 6.25 LTC The &#8220;halving&#8221; event is where LTC&#8217;s block rewards are permanently cut in half. This event is periodic, occurring approximately every four years or roughly every 840,000 blocks miners hash. Today&#8217;s halving was Litecoin&#8217;s third, meaning its block rewards have been cut three times since its genesis. In the first halving, the cryptocurrency saw its block rewards go from an initial 50 LTC to 25 LTC, and with the second, the tips dropped further to 12.5 LTC. With the latest halving event, miners&#8217; rewards for solving blocks have been cut down further to 6.25 LTC. The reason that halvings even exist is because they serve as a measure for controlling the asset&#8217;s inflation. These block rewards that miners receive are the only way to introduce fresh tokens into the circulating supply, so cutting them down repeatedly makes sure that the cryptocurrency&#8217;s supply goes up slower and slower. Eventually, when the halvings would keep on happening, the block rewards would approach zero. This would occur approximately in 2142. After this point, the asset&#8217;s supply will hit the maximum cap, and the miners will have to rely on transaction fees to pay off their running costs. As halvings are important events, it&#8217;s natural that there has been a lot of discussion around this latest event as it has approached. During the start of July, the asset had observed a sharp rally towards the $114 mark, as the market had perhaps become hopeful for the halving, which was only one month away. Related Reading: Bitcoin Funding Rates Most Positive Since Feb, Long Squeeze Soon? This rally, however, ran out of steam soon enough, and since then, LTC has struggled to put together any significant bullish momentum. LTC has plunged during the past day &#124; Source: LTCUSD on TradingView Today&#8217;s halving hasn&#8217;t been able to change anything in this matter, either, as Litecoin has only plummeted further instead. It would appear that the event has indeed been a buy the rumor, sell the news type of scenario. Following the latest plummet, Litecoin has gone below the $87 level and is down almost 7% during the past 24 hours. These high losses mean that LTC has been the poorest-performing coin out of the top cryptocurrencies by market cap in this period. Related Reading: BlackRock CEO Larry Fink Is The Best Thing To Happen To Bitcoin, Mike Novogratz Says While the price performance of the asset might have been poor, LTC supporters may take solace in the fact that the asset has come forward a lot in terms of other network-related metrics since the previous halving, as data from IntoTheBlock shows: The growth of the LTC network &#124; Source: IntoTheBlock on X Interestingly, the price at which both halvings happened was approximately the same. The cryptocurrency seems to have done well in terms of userbase and utility-related growth. This impressive rise in adoption may be because Litecoin offers cheap and fast transactions compared to some other networks like Bitcoin. LTC investors can only hope, however, that this growth may also show up in the price. Featured image from Kanchanara on Unsplash.com, charts from TradingView.com, IntoTheBlock.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Litecoin has completed its much-anticipated halving event today, but it seems the investors have reacted by participating in a selloff.</p>
<h2>Litecoin Has Completed Its Third Halving, Block Rewards Now Down To 6.25 LTC</h2>
<p>The &#8220;<a href="https://bitcoinist.com/280-days-bitcoin-halving-how-previous-cycles-here/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">halving</a>&#8221; event is where LTC&#8217;s block rewards are permanently cut in half. This event is periodic, occurring approximately every four years or roughly every 840,000 blocks miners hash.</p>
<p>Today&#8217;s halving was Litecoin&#8217;s third, meaning its block rewards have been cut three times since its genesis. In the first halving, the cryptocurrency saw its block rewards go from an initial 50 LTC to 25 LTC, and with the second, the tips dropped further to 12.5 LTC.</p>
<p>With the latest halving event, miners&#8217; rewards for solving blocks have been cut down further to 6.25 LTC. The reason that halvings even exist is because they serve as a measure for controlling the asset&#8217;s inflation.</p>
<p>These block rewards that miners receive are the only way to introduce fresh tokens into the circulating supply, so cutting them down repeatedly makes sure that the cryptocurrency&#8217;s supply goes up slower and slower.</p>
<p>Eventually, when the halvings would keep on happening, the block rewards would approach zero. This would occur approximately in 2142. After this point, the asset&#8217;s supply will hit the maximum cap, and the miners will have to rely on <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-block-788695-the-day-transaction-fees-took-the-crown/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">transaction fees</a> to pay off their running costs.</p>
<p>As halvings are important events, it&#8217;s natural that there has been a lot of discussion around this latest event as it has approached. During the start of July, the asset had observed a sharp rally towards the $114 mark, as the market had perhaps become hopeful for the halving, which was only one month away.</p>

<p>This rally, however, ran out of steam soon enough, and since then, LTC has struggled to put together any significant bullish momentum.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium aligncenter" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/2KFXYIrw/" alt="Litecoin Price Chart" width="1534" height="877"/></p>

<p>Today&#8217;s halving hasn&#8217;t been able to change anything in this matter, either, as Litecoin has only plummeted further instead. It would appear that the event has indeed been a <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/litecoin/sell-the-news-litecoin-traders-capitulate-ahead-halving/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">buy the rumor, sell the news</a> type of scenario.</p>
<p>Following the latest plummet, Litecoin has gone below the $87 level and is down almost 7% during the past 24 hours. These high losses mean that LTC has been the poorest-performing coin out of the top cryptocurrencies by market cap in this period.</p>

<p>While the price performance of the asset might have been poor, LTC supporters may take solace in the fact that the asset has come forward a lot in terms of other network-related metrics since the previous halving, as data from <a href="https://twitter.com/intotheblock/status/1686735190297600000" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">IntoTheBlock</a> shows:</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter" src="https://pbs.twimg.com/media/F2h8YnJW4AEERf_?format=jpg&amp;name=4096x4096" alt="Litecoin Comparison" width="3216" height="1816"/></p>

<p>Interestingly, the price at which both halvings happened was approximately the same. The cryptocurrency seems to have done well in terms of userbase and utility-related growth.</p>
<p>This impressive rise in adoption may be because Litecoin offers cheap and fast transactions compared to some other networks like Bitcoin. LTC investors can only hope, however, that this growth may also show up in the price.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/kanchanara-_m8pHtTykMs-unsplash.jpg?fit=460%2C306" width="460" height="306" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">545562</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Why Isn&#8217;t Bitcoin Outperforming Most Risk Assets? A Market Conundrum</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/why-isnt-bitcoin-outperforming-most-risk-assets-a-market-conundrum/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 00:00:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=545558</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Mike McGlone, Senior Commodity Strategist at Bloomberg Intelligence, has recently suggested that Bitcoin&#8217;s (BTC) underperformance compared to the stock market may be a warning sign for investors.  BTC’s Failure To Outshine In A Bull Market McGlone notes that Bitcoin has declined compared to the Nasdaq 100 stock index since its 2021 peak and April bounce. This waning performance may presage rising headwinds not only for Bitcoin but also for the broader crypto market. McGlone stated: If Bitcoin truly is the &#8220;fastest-horse-in-the-race,&#8221; as some consider it to be, then it should logically be outperforming in an everything bull market. However, that is not the case.  Notably, McGlone points to the most aggressive liquidity pull from central banks in history, which may be a significant factor in Bitcoin&#8217;s underperformance. Related Reading: Buying Pressure Incoming? MicroStrategy Files Notice With SEC To Sell $750 Million In Stocks The Federal Reserve (Fed) is still sighting in 3Q, despite the producer price index finished-goods gauge at minus 3.1% and dropping from 2022’s 18.3% peak at its fastest pace since 1948, which may be part of what underperforming Bitcoin is “sniffing out,” according to McGlone.  On a one-year basis to August 1st, Bitcoin is up just over 20%, similar to the Nasdaq, yet the crypto’s volatility is about two times greater. McGlone believes Bitcoin&#8217;s underperformance may be a warning sign for the broader market. The fact that Bitcoin is not outperforming as it should be in an everything-bull market could indicate that more significant market issues are at play, particularly in the face of aggressive liquidity pulls from central banks. Bitcoin And Ethereum Volatility At Historic Lows In a statement shared with NewsBTC Luuk Strijers, the Chief Commercial Officer at Deribit, a prominent cryptocurrency derivatives exchange, has recently stated that the Deribit Volatility Index (DVOL) for both Bitcoin and Ethereum is currently trading at an all-time low.  This is a significant development, especially since the DVOL for ETH is trading below the DVOL for BTC, which is a rare occurrence and may have been caused by the activity of a single large trader, commonly known as a whale. Despite the current low levels of volatility, Luuk Strijers highlights that the market is anticipating a considerable upswing in volatility shortly. This expectation is driven by several factors, including the upcoming ruling on the Blackrock spot Exchange-Traded Fund (ETF) and the approaching Bitcoin Halving. Strijers notes that Deribit has been observing signs of these expectations in the market, such as the significant steepness of the term structure, with June &#8217;24 trades at approximately 50, and the enduring call skew.  These indicators suggest that the market is anticipating increased volatility and potential price movements shortly, despite the current low levels of volatility. The Blackrock spot ETF ruling is anticipated to impact the cryptocurrency market significantly. If approved, the ETF will allow investors to gain exposure to Bitcoin without directly holding the cryptocurrency, potentially increasing demand and driving up prices.  Related Reading: Shiba Inu Price Prediction: Is Shibarium The Key To A Trend Reversal? On the other hand, if the ruling is not approved, it may lead to a temporary drop in prices and increased volatility. The approaching Bitcoin Halvening, which is expected to occur in 2024, is another factor contributing to the anticipation of increased volatility, according to Strijers.  The Halvening is a significant event in the Bitcoin network that occurs roughly every four years, where the block reward for Bitcoin miners is cut in half. This tends to reduce the supply of Bitcoin on the market, potentially driving up prices and increasing volatility. Despite the current low levels of volatility, Strijers suggests that investors and traders should remain vigilant and prepare for potential price movements and increased volatility in the cryptocurrency market. At the time of writing, BTC is trading at $29,100, representing a slight increase of 0.8% in the past 24 hours. Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Mike McGlone, Senior Commodity Strategist at Bloomberg Intelligence, has recently <a href="https://twitter.com/mikemcglone11/status/1686694332189773824?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">suggested </a>that Bitcoin&#8217;s (BTC) underperformance compared to the stock market may be a warning sign for investors. </p>
<h2>BTC’s Failure To Outshine In A Bull Market</h2>
<p>McGlone notes that Bitcoin has declined compared to the Nasdaq 100 stock index since its 2021 peak and April bounce. This waning performance may presage rising headwinds not only for Bitcoin but also for the broader crypto market. McGlone stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>If Bitcoin truly is the &#8220;fastest-horse-in-the-race,&#8221; as some consider it to be, then it should logically be outperforming in an everything bull market. However, that is not the case. </p></blockquote>
<p>Notably, McGlone points to the most aggressive liquidity pull from central banks in history, which may be a significant factor in Bitcoin&#8217;s underperformance.</p>

<p>The Federal Reserve (Fed) is still sighting in 3Q, despite the producer price index finished-goods gauge at minus 3.1% and dropping from 2022’s 18.3% peak at its fastest pace since 1948, which may be part of what underperforming Bitcoin is “sniffing out,” according to McGlone. </p>
<p>On a one-year basis to August 1st, Bitcoin is up just over 20%, similar to the Nasdaq, yet the crypto’s volatility is about two times greater.</p>
<p>McGlone believes Bitcoin&#8217;s underperformance may be a warning sign for the broader market. The fact that Bitcoin is not outperforming as it should be in an everything-bull market could indicate that more significant market issues are at play, particularly in the face of aggressive liquidity pulls from central banks.</p>
Bitcoin And Ethereum Volatility At Historic Lows
<p>In a statement shared with NewsBTC Luuk Strijers, the Chief Commercial Officer at Deribit, a prominent cryptocurrency derivatives exchange, has recently stated that the Deribit Volatility Index (DVOL) for both Bitcoin and Ethereum is currently trading at an all-time low. </p>
<p>This is a significant development, especially since the DVOL for ETH is trading below the DVOL for BTC, which is a rare occurrence and may have been caused by the activity of a single large trader, commonly known as a whale.</p>
<p>Despite the current low levels of volatility, Luuk Strijers highlights that the market is anticipating a considerable upswing in volatility shortly. This expectation is driven by several factors, including the upcoming ruling on the Blackrock spot Exchange-Traded Fund (ETF) and the approaching Bitcoin Halving.</p>
<p>Strijers notes that Deribit has been observing signs of these expectations in the market, such as the significant steepness of the term structure, with June &#8217;24 trades at approximately 50, and the enduring call skew. </p>
<p>These indicators suggest that the market is anticipating increased volatility and potential price movements shortly, despite the current low levels of volatility.</p>
<p>The Blackrock spot ETF ruling is anticipated to impact the cryptocurrency market significantly. If approved, the ETF will allow investors to gain exposure to Bitcoin without directly holding the cryptocurrency, potentially increasing demand and driving up prices. </p>

<p>On the other hand, if the ruling is not approved, it may lead to a temporary drop in prices and increased volatility. The approaching Bitcoin Halvening, which is expected to occur in 2024, is another factor contributing to the anticipation of increased volatility, according to Strijers. </p>
<p>The Halvening is a significant event in the Bitcoin network that occurs roughly every four years, where the block reward for Bitcoin miners is cut in half. This tends to reduce the supply of Bitcoin on the market, potentially driving up prices and increasing volatility.</p>
<p>Despite the current low levels of volatility, Strijers suggests that investors and traders should remain vigilant and prepare for potential price movements and increased volatility in the cryptocurrency market.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/HVO1p4O3/" alt="Bitcoin " width="1814" height="858"/>
<p>At the time of writing, BTC is trading at $29,100, representing a slight increase of 0.8% in the past 24 hours.</p>
<p>Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/iStock-1294303261.jpg?fit=460%2C345" width="460" height="345" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">545558</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>This Long-Term Bitcoin Price Average Is Setting ATHs</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/this-long-term-bitcoin-price-average-is-setting-aths/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tony "The Bull"]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 23:02:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=545580</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin price is nowhere near setting new all-time highs, but an important long-term price average is doing so, day after day, month after month. What is this moving average being referenced, and what does it setting new highs potentially mean? The 50-month moving average at the highest point ever&#124; BTCUSD on TradingView.com Meet The Moving Train: The 50-Month Moving Average As Bitcoin and the rest of the crypto market grind painfully sideways, a key measure using a moving average of BTCUSD price action is rising steadily, now at its highest point ever historically. The moving average in reference is the 50-month moving average (50MA). To calculate the span, simply take the last 50 months worth of BTCUSD closing prices, add them together, then divide them by the 50 (the number of months worth of data in the period). Related Reading: Bitcoin Bollinger Bands Are The Tightest Ever, What Happens Next? Traders use moving averages for a variety of reasons. This includes as trend-following tool, as trend lines, and for timing entries and exits. Such signals trigger when price passes above or below the span, or if two moving averages crossover one another in a two-moving average system. These are called a golden cross or death cross. #Bitcoin’s 50-month moving average continues to set new record highs Without all the noise, the primary trend points upward pic.twitter.com/HG8gjO3Gn6 &#8212; Tony &#34;The Bull&#34; (@tonythebullBTC) August 2, 2023 What The 50MA Hitting ATHs Means For Bitcoin The 50-month moving average making new all-time highs, general means the primary trend is still up. The chart above shows the long-term uptrend clearly without the noise of candlesticks or price action. With the candlesticks turned back on, Bitcoin is above the span — another bullish sign. Related Reading: Don’t Change The Channel! Why Bitcoin Could Target $42K If Uptrend Holds BTCUSD closed above the 50MA back in March 2023 and has since held above it for several months. Notably, Bitcoin lost this level for the first time back in June 2022. Meanwhile, the top cryptocurrency bottomed precisely at the 50MA in 2018 and again in 2020. The 50MA is currently at $26,353 and could act as support of retested. If lost, it could be a sign the longer-term trend is turning bearish. The 200-week moving average, another similar high timeframe price indicator that is used widely in technical analysis, is also at a similar level and trending upwards. This chart originally appeared in Issue #14 of CoinChartist (VIP). Subscribe for free. Tony is the author of the CoinChartist (VIP) newsletter. Sign up for free. Follow @TonyTheBullBTC &#38; @coinchartist_io on Twitter. Or join the TonyTradesBTC Telegram for daily market insights and technical analysis education. Please note: Content is educational and should not be considered investment advice. Featured image from iStockPhoto, Charts from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin price is nowhere near setting new all-time highs, but an important long-term price average is doing so, day after day, month after month.</p>
<p>What is this moving average being referenced, and what does it setting new highs potentially mean?</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-545581 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/CF9F3687-CD1F-404A-834C-27319A1DE5BA.jpeg?w=860&#038;resize=860%2C535" alt="Bitcoin moving average " width="860" height="535" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/CF9F3687-CD1F-404A-834C-27319A1DE5BA.jpeg?w=1272 1272w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/CF9F3687-CD1F-404A-834C-27319A1DE5BA.jpeg?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/CF9F3687-CD1F-404A-834C-27319A1DE5BA.jpeg?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/CF9F3687-CD1F-404A-834C-27319A1DE5BA.jpeg?w=860&#038;resize=860%2C535 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/CF9F3687-CD1F-404A-834C-27319A1DE5BA.jpeg?w=750 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/CF9F3687-CD1F-404A-834C-27319A1DE5BA.jpeg?w=1140 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" data-recalc-dims="1"/></p>

<h2>Meet The Moving Train: The 50-Month Moving Average</h2>
<p>As Bitcoin and the rest of the crypto market grind painfully sideways, a key measure using a moving average of BTCUSD price action is rising steadily, now at its highest point ever historically.</p>
<p>The moving average in reference is the 50-month moving average (50MA). To calculate the span, simply take the last 50 months worth of BTCUSD closing prices, add them together, then divide them by the 50 (the number of months worth of data in the period).</p>

<p>Traders use moving averages for a variety of reasons. This includes as trend-following tool, as trend lines, and for timing entries and exits. Such signals trigger when price passes above or below the span, or if two moving averages crossover one another in a two-moving average system. These are called a golden cross or death cross.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr"><a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Bitcoin?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#Bitcoin</a>’s 50-month moving average continues to set new record highs</p>
<p>Without all the noise, the primary trend points upward <a href="https://t.co/HG8gjO3Gn6" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/HG8gjO3Gn6</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Tony &quot;The Bull&quot; (@tonythebullBTC) <a href="https://twitter.com/tonythebullBTC/status/1686873819074404352?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">August 2, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<h2>What The 50MA Hitting ATHs Means For Bitcoin</h2>
<p>The 50-month moving average making new all-time highs, general means the primary trend is still up. The chart above shows the long-term uptrend clearly without the noise of candlesticks or price action. With the candlesticks turned back on, Bitcoin is above the span — another bullish sign.</p>

<p>BTCUSD closed above the 50MA back in March 2023 and has since held above it for several months. Notably, Bitcoin lost this level for the first time back in June 2022. Meanwhile, the top cryptocurrency bottomed precisely at the 50MA in 2018 and again in 2020.</p>
<p>The 50MA is currently at $26,353 and could act as support of retested. If lost, it could be a sign the longer-term trend is turning bearish. The 200-week moving average, another similar high timeframe price indicator that is used widely in technical analysis, is also at a similar level and trending upwards.</p>
<p>This chart originally appeared in <a href="https://coinchartist.substack.com/p/issue-14-refuting-the-impact-of-the" rel="nofollow">Issue #14 of CoinChartist (VIP)</a>. Subscribe for <a href="https://coinchartist.substack.com/p/issue-14-refuting-the-impact-of-the" rel="nofollow">free</a>.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/48DBC9EC-77A2-4A19-9884-CCAF3D343671.jpeg?fit=460%2C259" width="460" height="259" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">545580</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>KuCoin Shuts Down Bitcoin And Litecoin Mining Pools Amid Market Turmoil</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/kucoin-shuts-down-bitcoin-and-litecoin-mining-pools-amid-market-turmoil/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 22:00:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[KuCoin exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Litecoin (LTC)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Litecoin Halving]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LTCUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=545551</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[KuCoin, one of the world&#8217;s largest cryptocurrency exchanges, has temporarily halted its KuCoin Pool service, effective August 15, 2023, until further notice. The move is part of KuCoin&#8217;s business strategy and aims to ensure the security and integrity of users&#8217; assets. KuCoin Urges Users To Backup Mining Records During the suspension, users will retain complete access and control over their assets, and all other KuCoin offerings will remain operational as usual.  However, users who are involved in cryptocurrency mining are advised to transition their Bitcoin (BTC) and Litecoin (LTC) miners to alternative mining pools before the deadline to ensure uninterrupted earnings. KuCoin has also advised users to back up and preserve their mining records and associated data before August 27, 2023, as failure to migrate to alternative mining pools within the specified timeline could affect their mining revenue.  Related Reading: Sell The News? Litecoin Traders Capitulate Ahead Of Today’s Halving Nevertheless, KuCoin Pool will not be held accountable for any potential earnings lapses resulting from users&#8217; failure to migrate to alternative pools. The temporary suspension of KuCoin&#8217;s mining pools may cause some disruption in the crypto market, as mining plays an important role in the ecosystem. Despite this, it is worth noting that KuCoin is just one exchange, and its suspension may not have a significant impact on the overall market. KuCoin has assured its users that the suspension is temporary, and the company is working on a new strategy for its mining pool service. The company has also emphasized that the security and integrity of users&#8217; assets remain its top priority, and it will take all necessary steps to ensure the safety of users&#8217; funds. Litecoin Halving Triggers Price Drop Litecoin, one of the oldest and most popular cryptocurrencies, has completed its third block reward halving at a block height of 2,520,000, as reported by Colin Wu. The halving event has cut the mining reward in half, from 12.5 LTC to 6.25 LTC, as part of the cryptocurrency&#8217;s deflationary monetary policy. The halving is a regular event that occurs approximately every four years and is designed to control the rate at which new coins are minted. By reducing the reward for mining new blocks, the halving helps to prevent inflation and maintain the scarcity of the cryptocurrency. The current price of Litecoin is $89.12, which represents a 3.8% decline over the past 24 hours and a 10% decline over the past six months. The price drop may be related to market uncertainty surrounding the halving event, as well as broader market conditions. Despite the short-term price decline, many analysts remain optimistic about the long-term prospects for Litecoin and the cryptocurrency market as a whole. The halving event is seen as a positive development that highlights the ongoing maturation of the industry and the growing recognition of cryptocurrencies as a legitimate asset class. Related Reading: Uniswap Delists HEX Token After SEC Deems It An “Unregistered Security” Litecoin has a strong community and a dedicated development team, which continue to work on improving the technology and expanding the use cases for the cryptocurrency. The halving event is expected to further strengthen Litecoin&#8217;s position as a leading cryptocurrency and contribute to its long-term growth and success. Overall, the completion of Litecoin&#8217;s third block reward halving is a significant milestone for the cryptocurrency and the broader industry. While short-term price volatility is to be expected, the long-term outlook for Litecoin and cryptocurrencies, in general, remains positive, with many experts predicting continued growth and adoption in the years to come. Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>KuCoin, one of the world&#8217;s largest cryptocurrency exchanges, has temporarily <a href="https://www.kucoin.com/announcement/zh-announcement-kucoin-pool-to-temporarily-suspend-operations" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">halted</a> its KuCoin Pool service, effective August 15, 2023, until further notice. The move is part of KuCoin&#8217;s business strategy and aims to ensure the security and integrity of users&#8217; assets.</p>
<h2>KuCoin Urges Users To Backup Mining Records</h2>
<p>During the suspension, users will retain complete access and control over their assets, and all other KuCoin offerings will remain operational as usual. </p>
<p>However, users who are involved in cryptocurrency mining are advised to transition their Bitcoin (BTC) and Litecoin (LTC) miners to alternative mining pools before the deadline to ensure uninterrupted earnings.</p>
<p>KuCoin has also advised users to back up and preserve their mining records and associated data before August 27, 2023, as failure to migrate to alternative mining pools within the specified timeline could affect their mining revenue. </p>

<p>Nevertheless, KuCoin Pool will not be held accountable for any potential earnings lapses resulting from users&#8217; failure to migrate to alternative pools.</p>
<p>The temporary suspension of KuCoin&#8217;s mining pools may cause some disruption in the crypto market, as mining plays an important role in the ecosystem. Despite this, it is worth noting that KuCoin is just one exchange, and its suspension may not have a significant impact on the overall market.</p>
<p>KuCoin has assured its users that the suspension is temporary, and the company is working on a new strategy for its mining pool service. The company has also emphasized that the security and integrity of users&#8217; assets remain its top priority, and it will take all necessary steps to ensure the safety of users&#8217; funds.</p>
Litecoin Halving Triggers Price Drop
<p>Litecoin, one of the oldest and most popular cryptocurrencies, has completed its third block reward halving at a block height of 2,520,000, as <a href="https://twitter.com/WuBlockchain/status/1686759576572514305?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">reported </a>by Colin Wu. The halving event has cut the mining reward in half, from 12.5 LTC to 6.25 LTC, as part of the cryptocurrency&#8217;s deflationary monetary policy.</p>
<p>The halving is a regular event that occurs approximately every four years and is designed to control the rate at which new coins are minted. By reducing the reward for mining new blocks, the halving helps to prevent inflation and maintain the scarcity of the cryptocurrency.</p>
<p>The current price of Litecoin is $89.12, which represents a 3.8% decline over the past 24 hours and a 10% decline over the past six months. The price drop may be related to market uncertainty surrounding the halving event, as well as broader market conditions.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/6cbabnK7/" alt="KuCoin" width="1815" height="858"/>
<p>Despite the short-term price decline, many analysts remain optimistic about the long-term prospects for Litecoin and the cryptocurrency market as a whole. The halving event is seen as a positive development that highlights the ongoing maturation of the industry and the growing recognition of cryptocurrencies as a legitimate asset class.</p>

<p>Litecoin has a strong community and a dedicated development team, which continue to work on improving the technology and expanding the use cases for the cryptocurrency. </p>
<p>The halving event is expected to further strengthen Litecoin&#8217;s position as a leading cryptocurrency and contribute to its long-term growth and success.</p>
<p>Overall, the completion of Litecoin&#8217;s third block reward halving is a significant milestone for the cryptocurrency and the broader industry. </p>
<p>While short-term price volatility is to be expected, the long-term outlook for Litecoin and cryptocurrencies, in general, remains positive, with many experts predicting continued growth and adoption in the years to come.</p>
<p>Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/giulia-may-aDaxUHo2Dz8-unsplash.jpg?fit=345%2C460" width="345" height="460" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">545551</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>BNB Nears $250 Level As Market Suffers Volatility; What&#8217;s Driving It?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/binance-coin/bnb-nears-250-level-as-market-suffers-volatility-whats-driving-it/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Kent Glory]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 21:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Binance Coin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance Japan]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BNB analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BNB Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BNBUSD]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=545541</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Binance’s utility coin BNB has posted significant gains, surprising investors as the broader crypto market slumps. Bitcoin and Ethereum, including most altcoins, have gone on recess while BNB surges amid rapid expansion plans on the Binance ecosystem. BNB’s spike on Tuesday, August 1, hinged on Binance&#8217;s announcement about the asset&#8217;s debut in the Japanese market through its newly launched subsidiary, Binance Japan. BNB jumped dramatically from $236.8555 to $246.0655, a nearly 4% increase, immediately after the news circulated the market.  BNB Price Bullish Amid Japanese Debut It is noteworthy that BNB is launching on Binance Japan for the first time since the history of Binance. Moreover, Binance Japan is the only Japanese exchange offering the token on its platform. Therefore, venturing into a new market is like achieving a major milestone for BNB and could guarantee a wider user base and increased daily transactions for the token. Alongside the announcement for the launch of Binance Japan, Binance is offering spot and leverage crypto trading on 34 cryptocurrencies. This vast list potentially entails more transactions on Binance, leading to more BNB spending as the platform&#8217;s utility token. Related Reading: Sell The News? Litecoin Traders Capitulate Ahead Of Today’s Halving But surprisingly, the price increase is not reflected in BNB&#8217;s trading volume, down over 47% in a 24-hour period. CoinMarketCap data shows BNB recorded over $1 billion in trading volume toward the close of Monday’s trading session.  The token saw an over 253% surge in trading volume on July 31, which didn&#8217;t reflect its nearly 1% price decline during the same period. After the sudden surge in trading activity and price, BNB&#8217;s movement has stalled as 24-hour trading volume stands at $734 million, with a 0.6% price increase in the last 24 hours. As of the time of writing, BNB trades at $242.9, inching closer to the $250 level as traders accumulate the token in anticipation of major rallies as it trades live on Binance Japan in the coming days.  BNB Vies For More Rallies As It Prepares To Conquer Key Resistance Levels Binance Coin (BNB) trades above three key support levels: $240.4, $242.0, and $243.3. The bulls found strength at $242.0 and $243.3 price levels, facilitating the sharp spike to $246.065 in the early hours of August 1. The chart demonstrates heated strife between the bulls and the bears as they struggle to prevail over the market. However, the stiff resistance at the $246.5 price level allowed the sellers to trigger a trend reversal. The bears have formed bearish candle sticks above the $243.3 price level and are striving to press the token further below. Related Reading: Weeks of Prosperity: MKR Holders See Wealth Grow By Over 100% Amidst Price Boom BNB is in a critical conjecture as the next few hours determine whether a move to the $250 target is possible. A break above the $246.5 level will facilitate more rallies. Conversely, if the bulls relent, BNB could retrace to the $241.3 level, allowing the bears an opportunity to soar. Featured image from Pixabay and chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Binance’s utility coin BNB has posted significant gains, surprising investors as the broader crypto market slumps. Bitcoin and Ethereum, including most altcoins, have gone on recess while BNB surges amid rapid expansion plans on the Binance ecosystem.</p>
<p>BNB’s spike on Tuesday, August 1, hinged on Binance&#8217;s <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/binance/binance-to-enter-japan-with-a-bang/">announcement</a> about the asset&#8217;s debut in the Japanese market through its newly launched subsidiary, Binance Japan. BNB jumped dramatically from $236.8555 to $246.0655, a nearly 4% increase, immediately after the news circulated the market. </p>
<h2>BNB Price Bullish Amid Japanese Debut</h2>
<p>It is noteworthy that BNB is launching on Binance Japan for the first time since the history of Binance. Moreover, Binance Japan is the only Japanese exchange offering the token on its platform. Therefore, venturing into a new market is like achieving a major milestone for BNB and could guarantee a wider user base and increased daily transactions for the token.</p>
<p>Alongside the announcement for the launch of Binance Japan, Binance is offering spot and leverage crypto trading on 34 cryptocurrencies. This vast list potentially entails more transactions on Binance, leading to more BNB spending as the platform&#8217;s utility token.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/litecoin/sell-the-news-litecoin-traders-capitulate-ahead-halving/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Sell The News? Litecoin Traders Capitulate Ahead Of Today’s Halving</a></p>
<p>But surprisingly, the price increase is not reflected in BNB&#8217;s trading volume, down over 47% in a 24-hour period. CoinMarketCap <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/bnb/" rel="nofollow">data</a> shows BNB recorded over $1 billion in trading volume toward the close of Monday’s trading session. </p>
<p>The token saw an over 253% surge in trading volume on July 31, which didn&#8217;t reflect its nearly 1% price decline during the same period. After the sudden surge in trading activity and price, BNB&#8217;s movement has stalled as 24-hour trading volume stands at $734 million, with a 0.6% price increase in the last 24 hours.</p>
<p>As of the time of writing, BNB trades at $242.9, inching closer to the $250 level as traders accumulate the token in anticipation of major rallies as it trades live on Binance Japan in the coming days. </p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/7qZ8E8hG/" alt="BNBUSD price chart " width="980" height="532"/>
<h2>BNB Vies For More Rallies As It Prepares To Conquer Key Resistance Levels</h2>
<p>Binance Coin (BNB) trades above three key support levels: $240.4, $242.0, and $243.3. The bulls found strength at $242.0 and $243.3 price levels, facilitating the sharp spike to $246.065 in the early hours of August 1.</p>
<p>The <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/x/o3FyNLja/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">chart</a> demonstrates heated strife between the bulls and the bears as they struggle to prevail over the market. However, the stiff resistance at the $246.5 price level allowed the sellers to trigger a trend reversal.</p>
<p>The bears have formed bearish candle sticks above the $243.3 price level and are striving to press the token further below.</p>

<p>BNB is in a critical conjecture as the next few hours determine whether a move to the $250 target is possible. A break above the $246.5 level will facilitate more rallies. Conversely, if the bulls relent, BNB could retrace to the $241.3 level, allowing the bears an opportunity to soar.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BNB.jpg?fit=460%2C332" width="460" height="332" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">545541</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum ETFs Heat Up As Filings With SEC Climbs To Six</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/ethereum/ethereum-etfs-heat-up/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 20:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[etf]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETFs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH ETFs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum ETFs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=545540</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The latest sign of crypto going mainstream among traditional investors is the race heating up to launch the first exchange-traded fund (ETF) tied to Ethereum futures. In recent weeks, six companies have filed proposals with the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) to launch Ethereum futures ETFs.  The Race To Launch An Ethereum Futures ETF Cryptocurrency ETFs track the price of the digital currencies they are tied to and they are not a new thing in the crypto industry. Bitcoin futures have gained popularity in recent years and are already being offered by popular investment companies.  However, with bitcoin futures ETFs now established, it is only natural for the next hot product to be an Ethereum futures ETF. So far, more than 10 Ethereum futures ETFs have been filed in the past, but none have been approved by the SEC. Related Reading: BlackRock CEO Larry Fink Is The Best Thing To Happen To Bitcoin, Mike Novogratz Says Volatility Shares Ether Strategy ETF was the first to be filed on July 28. Since then, Bitwise Ethereum Strategy ETF, Roundhill Ether Strategy ETF, VanEck&#8217;s Ethereum Strategy ETF, and Proshares Short Ether Strategy ETF have been filed and are awaiting clearance, as reported by Bloomberg Intelligence.  Now, Grayscale Investments is also looking to join the pack with its new Ethereum Futures ETF filing. After withdrawing its filing earlier due to SEC concerns, the digital currency asset management company is now back with a better application. Bitwise, another crypto index fund manager, also withdrew its previous filing at the same time.  ETH price jumps to $1,839 &#124; Source: ETHUSD on Tradingview.com According to the filing, the majority of the Grayscale Investments fund&#8217;s assets would be placed in Ether futures contracts with &#8220;front-month&#8221; maturities, which have &#8220;the shortest time to maturity.&#8221;  The company also intends to diversify into other Ethereum contracts in the coming future.  Why Ethereum Futures ETFs Are Gaining Traction The buzz around crypto ETFs was recently ignited by the news of BlackRock and other investment companies filing applications with the SEC for Spot Bitcoin ETFs. However, the SEC is still yet to give the go-ahead, citing failure to meet anti-fraud and investor protection standards in past applications.  Analysts report that BlackRock&#8217;s Bitcoin ETF could unlock $30 trillion worth of wealth. Of course, there’s no guarantee if or when they may get the green light. Related Reading: Here’s The Total Number Of XRP That Ripple Currently Holds For crypto investors and the industry, an Ethereum futures ETF would no doubt be a game changer. If approved, Ethereum futures would become available to investors 75 days after the application date. It would provide an easy, low-cost way for investors of these investment companies to gain exposure to the second-largest cryptocurrency by market cap.  As for ETH’s spot price, it has been struggling to break above $2,000 this year. At the time of writing, ETH is trading at $1,843.96. But if the filings are approved by the SEC, it may signal the beginning of the next Ethereum bull run. Featured image from iStock, chart from Tradingview.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The latest sign of crypto going mainstream among traditional investors is the race heating up to launch the first exchange-traded fund (ETF) tied to Ethereum futures. In recent weeks, six companies have filed proposals with the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) to launch Ethereum futures ETFs. </p>
<h2>The Race To Launch An Ethereum Futures ETF</h2>
<p>Cryptocurrency ETFs track the price of the digital currencies they are tied to and they are not a new thing in the crypto industry. Bitcoin futures have gained popularity in recent years and are already being offered by popular investment companies. </p>
<p>However, with <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/valkyrie-follows-in-blackrocks-footsteps-refiles-for-spot-bitcoin-etf/">bitcoin futures ETFs now established</a>, it is only natural for the next hot product to be an Ethereum futures ETF. So far, more than 10 Ethereum futures ETFs have been filed in the past, but none have been approved by the SEC.</p>

<p>Volatility Shares Ether Strategy ETF was the first to be filed on July 28. Since then, Bitwise Ethereum Strategy ETF, Roundhill Ether Strategy ETF, <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/ethereum/vaneck-ethereum-etf-price-staggers/">VanEck&#8217;s Ethereum Strategy ETF</a>, and Proshares Short Ether Strategy ETF have been filed and are awaiting clearance, as <a href="https://twitter.com/JSeyff/status/1686499879495852032?s=20" rel="nofollow">reported </a>by Bloomberg Intelligence. </p>
<p>Now, Grayscale Investments is also looking to join the pack with its new Ethereum Futures ETF filing. After withdrawing its filing earlier due to SEC concerns, the digital currency asset management company is now back with a better application. Bitwise, another crypto index fund manager, also withdrew its previous filing at the same time. </p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/ha9xVrGg/" alt="Ethereum price chart from Tradingview.com (Ethereum ETFs)" width="2884" height="1746"/></p>

<p>According to the filing, the majority of the Grayscale Investments fund&#8217;s assets would be placed in Ether futures contracts with &#8220;front-month&#8221; maturities, which have &#8220;the shortest time to maturity.&#8221;  The company also intends to diversify into other Ethereum contracts in the coming future. </p>
<h2>Why Ethereum Futures ETFs Are Gaining Traction</h2>
<p>The buzz around crypto ETFs was recently ignited by the news of <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/blackrock-larry-fink-best-thing-to-happen-to-bitcoin/">BlackRock and other investment companies filing applications with the SEC for Spot Bitcoin ETFs</a>. However, the SEC is still yet to give the go-ahead, citing failure to meet anti-fraud and investor protection standards in past applications. </p>
<p>Analysts report that BlackRock&#8217;s Bitcoin ETF could unlock $30 trillion worth of wealth. Of course, there’s no guarantee if or when they may get the green light.</p>

<p>For crypto investors and the industry, an Ethereum <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/canada-marks-launch-of-first-bitcoin-ethereum-etfs-with-monthly-payouts/">futures ETF</a> would no doubt be a game changer. If approved, Ethereum futures would become available to investors 75 days after the application date. It would provide an easy, low-cost way for investors of these investment companies to gain exposure to the second-largest cryptocurrency by market cap. </p>
<p>As for ETH’s spot price, it has been struggling to break above $2,000 this year. At the time of writing, ETH is trading at $1,843.96. But if the filings are approved by the SEC, it may signal the beginning of the next Ethereum bull run.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/iStock-1370585933.jpg?fit=460%2C345" width="460" height="345" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">545540</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Optimism (OP) Climbs Over 10% On Weekly Chart, Will The Rally Last?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/optimism/optimism-op-climbs-over-10-on-weekly-chart-will-the-rally-last/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Kent Glory]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 19:00:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Optimism]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=545535</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Following a slight improvement in the broader cryptocurrency market, Optimism (OP) has posted positive gains today, August 2. The token is now over 10% higher than seven days ago. Optimism’s gain has placed it among the top-gaining coins today, with a nearly 3% gain in the last 24 hours.  Optimism Price Action as Bulls Struggle to Prevail According to CoinMarketCap data, Optimism peaked at $1.6712 on Wednesday morning, an over 5% increase from its past-day price. However, due to the intense struggle between the buyers and sellers, OP has receded from the day peak and is now traded at $1.63, with a 3.08% price increase. Related Reading: Shiba Inu Price Prediction: Is Shibarium The Key To A Trend Reversal? Optimism maintained a fairly bullish momentum from July 13 to August 2, reflected in its over 22% 30-day price increase. While the uncertainty about its next price action remains high, speculations suggest the following developments might influence the OP’s market outlook in the coming days. Optimism Could Face Backlash Due To The Recent BASE Exploit Coinbase’s newly launched BASE network built on the Optimism Stack reportedly witnessed a backdoor contract exploit, leading to the loss of 597 Ether worth approximately $1 million.  According to on-chain investigations, the exploiters infiltrated a BASE Chain&#8217;s backdoor contract, continuously minted tokens, and sold them for profit. Data shows that the perpetrator address already minted 40 different tokens, generating approximately 597 Ether in profit, which has been moved out. Speculations are that the exploit might impact all protocols linked to it, including the Optimism network, since BASE anchors the OP Stack. Also, the BASE hype attracted several new crypto addresses to the Optimism network. The recent hack may depress investor sentiment, potentially impacting OP&#8217;s price. The number of active addresses on the Optimism network grew significantly over the last few months after BASE&#8217;s launch in late February. However, this growth could be stalled due to the unfortunate event on the BASE network. OP Price Outlook; Will the Bulls Sustain the Rally? The OP/USD daily chart demonstrates OP’s bullish momentum as the bulls fight to secure higher market positions for the coin. OP has surpassed its two critical support levels, and the bulls show no sign of stopping, evident in the short green candlesticks formed above the $1.631 support level. The Moving Average Convergence/Divergence is above the signal line with green histogram bars that reflect the asset’s bullish momentum. In addition, the RSI has crossed the overbought region and now sits at 75, demonstrating increased buying pressure on OP.  Related Reading: Here’s The Total Number Of XRP That Ripple Currently Holds However, a bearish trend reversal is possible since the buyers have reached saturation and may recede due to a decline in momentum.  As of the time of writing, OP trades at $1.63. But the next few hours are critical as the price could decline to $1.61 if the bears reclaim control. Featured image from Pixabay and chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Following a slight improvement in the broader cryptocurrency market, Optimism (OP) has posted positive gains today, August 2. The token is now over 10% higher than seven days ago. Optimism’s gain has placed it among the top-gaining coins today, with a nearly 3% gain in the last 24 hours. </p>
<h2>Optimism Price Action as Bulls Struggle to Prevail</h2>
<p>According to CoinMarketCap <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/optimism-ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">data</a>, Optimism peaked at $1.6712 on Wednesday morning, an over 5% increase from its past-day price. However, due to the intense struggle between the buyers and sellers, OP has receded from the day peak and is now traded at $1.63, with a 3.08% price increase.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/shiba-inu-price-prediction-shibarium-trend-reversal/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Shiba Inu Price Prediction: Is Shibarium The Key To A Trend Reversal?</a></p>
<p>Optimism maintained a fairly bullish momentum from July 13 to August 2, reflected in its over 22% 30-day price increase. While the uncertainty about its next price action remains high, speculations suggest the following developments might influence the OP’s market outlook in the coming days.</p>
<h2>Optimism Could Face Backlash Due To The Recent BASE Exploit</h2>
<p>Coinbase’s newly launched BASE network built on the Optimism Stack reportedly <a href="https://twitter.com/AegisWeb3/status/1686558956569903104" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">witnessed</a> a backdoor contract exploit, leading to the loss of 597 Ether worth approximately $1 million. </p>
<p>According to on-chain investigations, the exploiters infiltrated a BASE Chain&#8217;s backdoor contract, continuously minted tokens, and sold them for profit. Data shows that the perpetrator address already minted 40 different tokens, generating approximately 597 Ether in profit, which has been moved out.</p>
<p>Speculations are that the exploit might impact all protocols linked to it, including the Optimism network, since BASE anchors the OP Stack. Also, the BASE hype attracted several new crypto addresses to the Optimism network. The recent hack may depress investor sentiment, potentially impacting OP&#8217;s price.</p>
<p>The number of active addresses on the Optimism network grew significantly over the last few months after BASE&#8217;s launch in late February. However, this growth could be stalled due to the unfortunate event on the BASE network.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/uxIcLIVk/" alt="OPUSD" width="980" height="532"/>
OP Price Outlook; Will the Bulls Sustain the Rally?
<p>The OP/USD daily <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/x/rSzu7jFj/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">chart</a> demonstrates OP’s bullish momentum as the bulls fight to secure higher market positions for the coin. OP has surpassed its two critical support levels, and the bulls show no sign of stopping, evident in the short green candlesticks formed above the $1.631 support level.</p>
<p>The Moving Average Convergence/Divergence is above the signal line with green histogram bars that reflect the asset’s bullish momentum. In addition, the RSI has crossed the overbought region and now sits at 75, demonstrating increased buying pressure on OP. </p>

<p>However, a bearish trend reversal is possible since the buyers have reached saturation and may recede due to a decline in momentum. </p>
<p>As of the time of writing, OP trades at $1.63. But the next few hours are critical as the price could decline to $1.61 if the bears reclaim control.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">545535</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Abracadabra Protocol To Counter CRV Risk With 200% Interest Rate Hike</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/defi/abracadabra-protocol-to-counter-crv-risk-with-200-interest-rate-hike/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Semilore Faleti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 18:00:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[DeFi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Abracadabra]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Collateral-based interest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CRV]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Curve Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MIM]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=545524</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[DeFi lending protocol, Abracadabra Money, is currently debating a proposal to boost the interest rate in its CRV lending markets as it looks to mitigate its exposure to the DeFi token.  In the last few days, CRV  has seen its value decline significantly due to the recent Curve Finance exploit on Sunday, which resulted in a total loss of over $60 million. According to data from CoinMarketCap, CRV is currently trading at $0.56, with an 8.28% loss in the last 24 hours. Abracadabra Exposed To Significant CRV Risk Levels In a governance proposal submitted on Aug 1, DAO contributor and community manager Romy highlighted that Abracadabra was currently exposed to a substantial level of CRV risk. To address this situation, the proposal contains a strategy that introduces collateral-based interest to both CRV cauldrons &#8211; lending markets &#8211; on Abracadabra. Related Reading: Ethereum DeFi Coins Plunge As Curve Concerns Threaten Major Market Crash Romy stated that Curve Finance, the underlying platform of CRV, has seen its TVL negatively affected over the last month by several events, including the Conic Finance Hack, the JPEG’d exploit, and the attack on Curve itself.  In particular, Romy noted that the theft of $25 million from Curve’s CRV/ETH pool had impacted the on-chain liquidity for CRV, altering the conditions that led to the adoption of the token as a collateral asset on Abracadabra.  In addition, the proposal also noted that Abracadabra had recorded CRV outflows toward markets with lower Loan-to-Value (LTV) ratios and higher interest rates. Together, all these factors have affected CRV’s price and liquidity, prompting the need for Abracadabra to reduce its exposure to the token. &#160; CRV trading at $0.558 on the daily chart: Source: CRVUSD chart on Tradingview.com Abracadabra’s Proposed Strategy To Introduce 200% Interest Hike As earlier stated, Romy’s governance proposal aims to cover Abracadabra CRV’s risk by applying collateral-based interest to the two CRV lending markets on the platform. It was stated that this strategy had been previously implemented with the WBTC and WETH cauldrons.  This introduction of collateral-based interests would allow Abracadabra to levy interest directly on each CRV cauldron’s collateral which is directly transferred to the protocol’s treasury and converted to Abracardra’s native stablecoin MIM, either via on-chain or off-chain transactions.  Related Reading: Is It A Good Idea To Buy Curve Now? Here’s What This Founder Thinks Based on projections, Romy stated that this strategy would allow Abracadabra to boost its treasury reserve and cut potential losses due to CRV exposure to about $5M borrowed MIM.  Under the new proposed interest structure, the interest rates will be determined based on two factors: the combined outstanding principal of the CRV cauldrons and the collateral ratio of each cauldron.  The base interest rate will vary depending on the total borrowed amount, classified into three ranges: $0M-$5M, $5M-$10M, and $10M-$18M. For instance, as the current outstanding principal stands at $18M, the base interest rate would be set at 200%.  Using this rate, it is estimated that the loan would be completely covered in six months&#8217; time. Furthermore, the collateral ratio would influence the interest multiplier, with ratios ranging from &#60;= 40% to &#60;= 70% correlating to multipliers of 1x, 5x, 10x, and 25x, respectively.   According to the proposal, this interest rate structure ensures the maximum chances of “full principal recovery” for Abracadabra. The voting session for this proposal commenced on Aug. 1. and will run for only 46 hours due to the supposed urgency of the matter. As of the time of writing, 51 members of the Abracadabra DAO have placed their votes, with 99.74% supporting the proposal.  Source: Snapshot Featured image from Ceqoa, chart from Tradingview]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>DeFi lending protocol, Abracadabra Money, is currently debating a proposal to boost the interest rate in its CRV lending markets as it looks to mitigate its exposure to the DeFi token. </p>
<p>In the last few days, CRV  has seen its value decline significantly due to the recent Curve Finance exploit on Sunday, which resulted in a total loss of over $60 million. According to<a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/curve-dao-token/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow"> data from CoinMarketCap,</a> CRV is currently trading at $0.56, with an 8.28% loss in the last 24 hours.</p>
<h2>Abracadabra Exposed To Significant CRV Risk Levels</h2>
<p>In a<a href="https://forum.abracadabra.money/t/aip-13-5-interest-rate-adjustment-for-the-crv-cauldrons/4320" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow"> governance proposal</a> submitted on Aug 1, DAO contributor and community manager Romy highlighted that Abracadabra was currently exposed to a substantial level of CRV risk.</p>
<p>To address this situation, the proposal contains a strategy that introduces collateral-based interest to both CRV cauldrons &#8211; lending markets &#8211; on Abracadabra.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/ethereum-defi-coins-plunge-curve-concerns-crash/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Ethereum DeFi Coins Plunge As Curve Concerns Threaten Major Market Crash</a></p>
<p>Romy stated that Curve Finance, the underlying platform of CRV, has seen its TVL negatively affected over the last month by several events, including the Conic Finance Hack, the JPEG’d exploit, and the attack on Curve itself. </p>
<p>In particular, Romy noted that the theft of $25 million from Curve’s CRV/ETH pool had impacted the on-chain liquidity for CRV, altering the conditions that led to the adoption of the token as a collateral asset on Abracadabra. </p>
<p style="text-align: left">In addition, the proposal also noted that Abracadabra had recorded CRV outflows toward markets with lower Loan-to-Value (LTV) ratios and higher interest rates. Together, all these factors have affected CRV’s price and liquidity, prompting the need for Abracadabra to reduce its exposure to the token.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>

<h2>Abracadabra’s Proposed Strategy To Introduce 200% Interest Hike</h2>
<p>As earlier stated, Romy’s governance proposal aims to cover Abracadabra CRV’s risk by applying collateral-based interest to the two CRV lending markets on the platform. It was stated that this strategy had been<a href="https://forum.abracadabra.money/t/aip-12-increase-weth-and-wbtc-cauldrons-interest/3992" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow"> previously implemented</a> with the WBTC and WETH cauldrons. </p>
<p>This introduction of collateral-based interests would allow Abracadabra to levy interest directly on each CRV cauldron’s collateral which is directly transferred to the protocol’s treasury and converted to Abracardra’s native stablecoin MIM, either via on-chain or off-chain transactions. </p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/defi/is-it-a-good-idea-to-buy-curve-now/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Is It A Good Idea To Buy Curve Now? Here’s What This Founder Thinks</a></p>
<p>Based on projections, Romy stated that this strategy would allow Abracadabra to boost its treasury reserve and cut potential losses due to CRV exposure to about $5M borrowed MIM. </p>
<p>Under the new proposed interest structure, the interest rates will be determined based on two factors: the combined outstanding principal of the CRV cauldrons and the collateral ratio of each cauldron. </p>
<p>The base interest rate will vary depending on the total borrowed amount, classified into three ranges: $0M-$5M, $5M-$10M, and $10M-$18M. For instance, as the current outstanding principal stands at $18M, the base interest rate would be set at 200%. </p>
<p>Using this rate, it is estimated that the loan would be completely covered in six months&#8217; time. Furthermore, the collateral ratio would influence the interest multiplier, with ratios ranging from &lt;= 40% to &lt;= 70% correlating to multipliers of 1x, 5x, 10x, and 25x, respectively.  </p>
<p>According to the proposal, this interest rate structure ensures the maximum chances of “full principal recovery” for Abracadabra.
</p>
<p>The <a href="https://snapshot.org/#/abracadabrabymerlinthemagician.eth/proposal/0xf5722a42dfdb3fe73a689936e9d2c094a56e140200ae08321b5b20c7001ee338" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">voting session</a> for this proposal commenced on Aug. 1. and will run for only 46 hours due to the supposed urgency of the matter. As of the time of writing, 51 members of the Abracadabra DAO have placed their votes, with 99.74% supporting the proposal.  </p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/News-Why-the-Feds-rate-hike-probably-wont-stop-the-stock-market-rally.jpg?fit=460%2C307" width="460" height="307" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">545524</post-id>	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
