<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
>

<channel>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.newsbtc.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<description>Bitcoin &#38; Cryptocurrency News Today</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 06:38:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Solana (SOL) Price Climbs 15% &#8211; A Positive Outlook For Investors?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/solana-sol-price-climbs-15-a-positive-outlook-for-investors/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 06:38:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price action]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SOL Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Solana]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=542295</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Solana (SOL) has recently made a significant breakthrough, successfully shattering both long-term and short-term resistance lines and marking a pivotal moment for the cryptocurrency&#8217;s future. Resistance lines are an essential concept in technical analysis that represent price levels where selling pressure historically outweighed buying pressure, resulting in a temporary halt or reversal in an asset&#8217;s price movement. In the case of SOL, the breakthrough of both long-term and short-term resistance lines signifies a significant shift in the market dynamics. Breakout Signals A Shift In SOL Price Movement Analyzing the weekly time frame reveals an important development for Solana. Last week, SOL managed to break out from a long-term descending resistance line. Remarkably, this resistance line had been in place for a staggering 600 days, originating from the all-time high reached back in November 2021.  Related Reading: Dogecoin (DOGE) Price Downtrend Set To Persist – What To Expect Breakouts from such extended structures often serve as a significant indication that the preceding trend has concluded and a new one has commenced, but in the opposite direction. SOL market cap nearing the $9 billion mark. Chart: TradingView.com Considering SOL&#8217;s recent breakout from the long-term descending resistance line, it is highly likely that the cryptocurrency has initiated a new bullish trend reversal. Related Reading: Cardano Price Momentum Bid Fizzles Out Despite New Payment Feature This breakthrough represents a major shift in the market dynamics for SOL, suggesting that the selling pressure that previously impeded its progress has weakened or been overcome by increasing buying pressure.  As a result, the stage is set for SOL to potentially experience an upward surge in value and embark on a new bullish trajectory. Source: Benzinga Meanwhile, over the previous week, Solana has experienced a notable 98.0% surge in trading volume, accompanied by a 0.91% rise in the coin&#8217;s circulating supply. Current SOL Price And Recent Performance At present, the SOL price listed on CoinGecko stands at $22.07, highlighting a notable 1.7% rally within the past 24 hours. Over the course of the last seven days, SOL has exhibited an impressive climb of 14.7%. These recent price movements further support the notion of a potential bullish trend reversal, as SOL continues to gather positive momentum. Source: Coingecko While the current analysis suggests a bullish outlook for Solana, it is essential to acknowledge the possibility of a price correction. If SOL loses its current momentum, there is a chance that it could retrace to the descending resistance line. However, it is worth noting that there are no immediate indications or signals in the short term to suggest such a decline is likely to occur. (This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk). Featured image from POSITRAN]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Solana (SOL) has recently made a significant breakthrough, successfully shattering both long-term and short-term resistance lines and marking a pivotal moment for the cryptocurrency&#8217;s future.</p>
<p>Resistance lines are an essential concept in technical analysis that represent price levels where selling pressure historically outweighed buying pressure, resulting in a temporary halt or reversal in an asset&#8217;s price movement.</p>
<p>In the case of SOL, the breakthrough of both long-term and short-term resistance lines signifies a significant shift in the market dynamics.</p>
<h2><strong>Breakout Signals A Shift In SOL Price Movement</strong></h2>
<p>Analyzing the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/SOLUSDT/?exchange=BINANCE" rel="nofollow">weekly time frame</a> reveals an important development for Solana. Last week, SOL managed to break out from a long-term descending resistance line. Remarkably, this resistance line had been in place for a staggering 600 days, originating from the all-time high reached back in November 2021. </p>

<p>Breakouts from such extended structures often serve as a significant indication that the preceding trend has concluded and a new one has commenced, but in the opposite direction.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/Fx24OI8P/" width="2475" height="1187"/></p>

<p>Considering <a href="https://www.benzinga.com/markets/cryptocurrency/23/07/33186956/solanas-price-increased-more-than-4-within-24-hours" rel="nofollow">SOL&#8217;s recent breakout</a> from the long-term descending resistance line, it is highly likely that the cryptocurrency has initiated a new bullish trend reversal. </p>

<p>This breakthrough represents a major shift in the market dynamics for SOL, suggesting that the selling pressure that previously impeded its progress has weakened or been overcome by increasing buying pressure. </p>
<p>As a result, the stage is set for SOL to potentially experience an upward surge in value and embark on a new bullish trajectory.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-542309" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-68.png" alt="" width="575" height="305" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-68.png 575w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-68-460x244.png 460w" sizes="(max-width: 575px) 100vw, 575px"/></p>

<p>Meanwhile, over the previous week, Solana has experienced a notable 98.0% surge in trading volume, accompanied by a 0.91% rise in the coin&#8217;s circulating supply.</p>
<h2><strong>Current SOL Price And Recent Performance</strong></h2>
<p>At present, the <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/solana" rel="nofollow">SOL price listed on CoinGecko</a> stands at $22.07, highlighting a notable 1.7% rally within the past 24 hours. Over the course of the last seven days, SOL has exhibited an impressive climb of 14.7%. </p>
<p>These recent price movements further support the notion of a potential bullish trend reversal, as SOL continues to gather positive momentum.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-542298" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-66.png" alt="Solana" width="1029" height="75" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-66.png 1029w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-66-460x34.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-66-860x63.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-66-768x56.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-66-750x55.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 1029px) 100vw, 1029px"/></p>

<p>While the current analysis suggests a bullish outlook for Solana, it is essential to acknowledge the possibility of a price correction. If SOL loses its current momentum, there is a chance that it could retrace to the descending resistance line. </p>
<p>However, it is worth noting that there are no immediate indications or signals in the short term to suggest such a decline is likely to occur.</p>
<p><em>(This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk).</em></p>
<p><em>Featured image from POSITRAN</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-67-460x229.png" width="460" height="229" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>DOT Price (Polkadot) Key Indicators Suggest Strong Case For Rally To $6</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/dot/dot-price-polkadot-rally-to-6/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 04:38:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[DOT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DOTUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DOTUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[polkadot]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=542288</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Polkadot’s DOT is moving higher from the $5.0 support against the US Dollar. The price could rally if it clears the $5.30 and $5.40 resistance levels. DOT is slowly moving higher above the $5.15 resistance zone against the US Dollar. The price is trading above the $5.20 zone and the 100 simple moving average (4 hours). There is a key bullish trend line forming with support near $5.10 on the 4-hour chart of the DOT/USD pair (data source from Kraken). The pair could gain bullish momentum if there is a close above the $5.30 resistance. Polkadot’s DOT Price Aims Higher After a sharp decline, DOT price found support near the $5.0 zone. A low is formed near $4.98 and the price is now attempting a fresh increase, similar to Bitcoin and Ethereum. There was a break above the $5.15 and $5.20 resistance levels. There is also a key bullish trend line forming with support near $5.10 on the 4-hours chart of the DOT/USD pair. The pair is now trading above the $5.20 zone and the 100 simple moving average (4 hours). Immediate resistance is near the $5.30 level. It is near the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $5.62 swing high to the $4.98 low. Source: DOTUSD on TradingView.com The next major resistance is near $5.40 or the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $5.62 swing high to the $4.98 low. A successful break above $5.40 could start a strong rally. In the stated case, the price could easily rally toward $5.60 in the coming sessions. The next major resistance is seen near the $6.0 zone. Dips Limited? If DOT price fails to continue higher above $5.30 or $5.40, it could start a downside correction. The first key support is near the $5.15 level and the 100 simple moving average (4 hours). The next major support is near the $5.10 level and the trend line, below which the price might decline to $5.00. Any more losses may perhaps open the doors for a move toward the $4.80 support zone in the coming sessions. Technical Indicators 4-Hours MACD – The MACD for DOT/USD is now gaining momentum in the bullish zone. 4-Hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for DOT/USD is now above the 50 level. Major Support Levels – $5.15, $5.10 and $5.00. Major Resistance Levels – $5.30, $5.40, and $5.60.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>Polkadot’s DOT is moving higher from the $5.0 support against the US Dollar. The price could rally if it clears the $5.30 and $5.40 resistance levels.</em></p>
<ul>
<li>DOT is slowly moving higher above the $5.15 resistance zone against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>The price is trading above the $5.20 zone and the 100 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There is a key bullish trend line forming with support near $5.10 on the 4-hour chart of the DOT/USD pair (data source from Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could gain bullish momentum if there is a close above the $5.30 resistance.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Polkadot’s DOT Price Aims Higher</h2>
<p>After a sharp decline, DOT price found support near the $5.0 zone. A low is formed near $4.98 and the price is now attempting a fresh increase, similar to <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-bulls-keep-pushing-31k/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Bitcoin</a> and <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-lacks-momentum-1900/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Ethereum</a>.</p>
<p>There was a break above the $5.15 and $5.20 resistance levels. There is also a key bullish trend line forming with support near $5.10 on the 4-hours chart of the DOT/USD pair. The pair is now trading above the $5.20 zone and the 100 simple moving average (4 hours).</p>
<p>Immediate resistance is near the $5.30 level. It is near the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $5.62 swing high to the $4.98 low.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-542289" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Polkadot-DOT.png" alt="DOT Price (Polkadot)" width="1835" height="845" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Polkadot-DOT.png 1835w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Polkadot-DOT-460x212.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Polkadot-DOT-860x396.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Polkadot-DOT-768x354.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Polkadot-DOT-1536x707.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Polkadot-DOT-750x345.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Polkadot-DOT-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1835px) 100vw, 1835px"/></p>
<p>Source: <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/DOTUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">DOTUSD on TradingView.com</a></p>
<p>The next major resistance is near $5.40 or the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $5.62 swing high to the $4.98 low. A successful break above $5.40 could start a strong rally. In the stated case, the price could easily rally toward $5.60 in the coming sessions. The next major resistance is seen near the $6.0 zone.</p>
<h2>Dips Limited?</h2>
<p>If DOT price fails to continue higher above $5.30 or $5.40, it could start a downside correction. The first key support is near the $5.15 level and the 100 simple moving average (4 hours).</p>
<p>The next major support is near the $5.10 level and the trend line, below which the price might decline to $5.00. Any more losses may perhaps open the doors for a move toward the $4.80 support zone in the coming sessions.</p>
<p>Technical Indicators</p>
<p>4-Hours MACD – The MACD for DOT/USD is now gaining momentum in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>4-Hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for DOT/USD is now above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Levels – $5.15, $5.10 and $5.00.</p>
<p>Major Resistance Levels – $5.30, $5.40, and $5.60.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Depositphotos_78872860_s-2019-460x293.jpg" width="460" height="293" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum Price Lacks Momentum But ETH Holders Are Safe: Here&#8217;s Why</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-lacks-momentum-1900/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 04:10:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=542285</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Ethereum price is consolidating below the $1,900 resistance against the US Dollar. ETH could attempt another increase unless there is a close below $1,825. Ethereum is trading in a range above the $1,850 level. The price is trading above $1,870 and the 100-hourly Simple Moving Average. There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $1,890 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD (data feed via Kraken). The pair could start a decent increase if it clears $1,890 and $1,900. Ethereum Price Holds Support Ethereum’s price made another attempt to gain strength above $1,900. However, ETH failed to settle above the $1,900 resistance and remained in a range, similar to Bitcoin. There was a bearish reaction below $1,880. A low is formed near $1,862 and the price is now moving higher. There was a break above the $1,880 level. The price climbed above the 50% Fib retracement level of the recent drop from the $1,905 swing high to the $1,862 low. Ether is now trading above $1,870 and the 100-hourly Simple Moving Average. Immediate resistance is near the $1,890 level. There is also a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $1,890 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD. Source: ETHUSD on TradingView.com The trend line is close to the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the recent drop from the $1,905 swing high to the $1,862 low. The first major resistance is near the $1,900 zone. A close above the $1,900 resistance could start a decent increase toward $1,955. The next major resistance is near the $1,975 level. Any more gains could send Ether toward the $2,050 resistance. Another Decline in ETH? If Ethereum fails to clear the $1,900 resistance, it could start another decline. Initial support on the downside is near the $1,870 level or the 100-hourly Simple Moving Average. There is also a connecting bullish trend line at $1,870. The first major support is near the $1,845 level, below which the price might revisit the key support at $1,825. The next major support is near the $1,770 level. Any more losses could send Ether toward the $1,720 support level in the near term. Technical Indicators Hourly MACD – The MACD for ETH/USD is losing momentum in the bullish zone. Hourly RSI &#8211; The RSI for ETH/USD is now above the 50 level. Major Support Level – $1,845 Major Resistance Level – $1,900]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>Ethereum price is consolidating below the $1,900 resistance against the US Dollar. ETH could attempt another increase unless there is a close below $1,825.</em></p>
<ul>
<li>Ethereum is trading in a range above the $1,850 level.</li>
<li>The price is trading above $1,870 and the 100-hourly Simple Moving Average.</li>
<li>There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $1,890 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD (data feed via Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could start a decent increase if it clears $1,890 and $1,900.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Ethereum Price Holds Support</h2>
<p>Ethereum’s price made another attempt to gain strength above $1,900. However, ETH failed to settle above the $1,900 resistance and remained in a range, similar to <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-bulls-keep-pushing-31k/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Bitcoin</a>.</p>
<p>There was a bearish reaction below $1,880. A low is formed near $1,862 and the price is now moving higher. There was a break above the $1,880 level. The price climbed above the 50% Fib retracement level of the recent drop from the $1,905 swing high to the $1,862 low.</p>
<p>Ether is now trading above $1,870 and the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-turning-point-1900/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">100-hourly Simple Moving Average</a>. Immediate resistance is near the $1,890 level. There is also a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $1,890 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-542286" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ethereum-7.png" alt="Ethereum Price" width="1835" height="845" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ethereum-7.png 1835w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ethereum-7-460x212.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ethereum-7-860x396.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ethereum-7-768x354.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ethereum-7-1536x707.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ethereum-7-750x345.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ethereum-7-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1835px) 100vw, 1835px"/></p>
<p>Source: <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/ETHUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">ETHUSD on TradingView.com</a></p>
<p>The trend line is close to the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the recent drop from the $1,905 swing high to the $1,862 low. The first major resistance is near the $1,900 zone. A close above the $1,900 resistance could start a decent increase toward $1,955. The next major resistance is near the $1,975 level. Any more gains could send Ether toward the $2,050 resistance.</p>
<h2>Another Decline in ETH?</h2>
<p>If Ethereum fails to clear the $1,900 resistance, it could start another decline. Initial support on the downside is near the $1,870 level or the 100-hourly Simple Moving Average.</p>
<p>There is also a connecting bullish trend line at $1,870. The first major support is near the $1,845 level, below which the price might revisit the key support at $1,825. The next major support is near the $1,770 level. Any more losses could send Ether toward the $1,720 support level in the near term.</p>
<p>Technical Indicators</p>
<p>Hourly MACD<strong> – </strong>The MACD for ETH/USD is losing momentum in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>Hourly RSI<strong> &#8211; </strong>The RSI for ETH/USD is now above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Level – $1,845</p>
<p>Major Resistance Level – $1,900</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/iStock-1150291277-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Bulls Keep Pushing, Why BTC Could Soon Attempt To Surpass $31K</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-bulls-keep-pushing-31k/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 03:09:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xbtusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=542282</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin price is moving higher above the $30,500 level. BTC is showing signs of a fresh move toward the $31,000 resistance zone. Bitcoin is slowly moving higher above the $30,500 support zone. The price is trading above $30,400 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average. There is a key bullish trend line forming with support near $30,500 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Kraken). The pair could rise further toward the $31,000 resistance and then $31,400. Bitcoin Price Holds Ground Bitcoin price remained stable above the $30,000 support zone. A base was formed and BTC started a decent increase above the $30,200 level. The price was able to spike a couple of times above the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $31,020 high to the $30,215 low. However, the bears seem to be active near the $30,700 resistance zone. There is also a key bullish trend line forming with support near $30,500 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair. Bitcoin price is now trading above $30,400 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average. Immediate resistance on the upside is seen near the $30,720 level. It is close to the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $31,020 high to the $30,215 low. Source: BTCUSD on TradingView.com The next resistance is near the $31,000 zone, above which the price could gain bullish momentum. In the stated case, BTC might rise toward the $31,400 resistance. The next major resistance is near the $32,000 level. Any more gains could open the doors for a move toward the $32,500 resistance zone. Another Decline in BTC? If Bitcoin’s price fails to clear the $30,700 resistance, it could start another decline. Immediate support on the downside is near the $30,500 level and the trend line. The next major support is near the $30,300 level and the 100 hourly Simple moving average, below which there could be a drop toward the $30,000 support zone. Any more losses might send the price toward the $29,850 level in the near term. Technical indicators: Hourly MACD – The MACD is now gaining pace in the bullish zone. Hourly RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BTC/USD is now above the 50 level. Major Support Levels – $30,500, followed by $30,300. Major Resistance Levels – $30,700, $31,000, and $31,400.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>Bitcoin price is moving higher above the $30,500 level. BTC is showing signs of a fresh move toward the $31,000 resistance zone.</em></p>
<ul>
<li>Bitcoin is slowly moving higher above the $30,500 support zone.</li>
<li>The price is trading above $30,400 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average.</li>
<li>There is a key bullish trend line forming with support near $30,500 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could rise further toward the $31,000 resistance and then $31,400.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Bitcoin Price Holds Ground</h2>
<p>Bitcoin price remained stable above the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-holds-ground-30k-2/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">$30,000 support zone</a>. A base was formed and BTC started a decent increase above the $30,200 level.</p>
<p>The price was able to spike a couple of times above the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $31,020 high to the $30,215 low. However, the bears seem to be active near the $30,700 resistance zone. There is also a key bullish trend line forming with support near $30,500 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair.</p>
<p>Bitcoin price is now trading above $30,400 and the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-could-nosedive-30k/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">100 hourly Simple moving average</a>. Immediate resistance on the upside is seen near the $30,720 level. It is close to the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $31,020 high to the $30,215 low.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-542283" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-7.png" alt="Bitcoin Price" width="1835" height="845" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-7.png 1835w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-7-460x212.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-7-860x396.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-7-768x354.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-7-1536x707.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-7-750x345.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-7-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1835px) 100vw, 1835px"/></p>
<p>Source: <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BTCUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">BTCUSD on TradingView.com</a></p>
<p>The next resistance is near the $31,000 zone, above which the price could gain bullish momentum. In the stated case, BTC might rise toward the $31,400 resistance. The next major resistance is near the $32,000 level. Any more gains could open the doors for a move toward the $32,500 resistance zone.</p>
<h2>Another Decline in BTC?</h2>
<p>If Bitcoin’s price fails to clear the $30,700 resistance, it could start another decline. Immediate support on the downside is near the $30,500 level and the trend line.</p>
<p>The next major support is near the $30,300 level and the 100 hourly Simple moving average, below which there could be a drop toward the $30,000 support zone. Any more losses might send the price toward the $29,850 level in the near term.</p>
<p>Technical indicators:</p>
<p>Hourly MACD – The MACD is now gaining pace in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>Hourly RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BTC/USD is now above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Levels – $30,500, followed by $30,300.</p>
<p>Major Resistance Levels – $30,700, $31,000, and $31,400.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/shutterstock_555674926-460x313.jpg" width="460" height="313" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Unmoved Bitcoin Supply Hits New all time high as BTC rally resumes</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/unmoved-bitcoin-supply-hits-new-ath/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 03:00:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin unmoved supply]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC supply]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=542261</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin continues to dominate the market as it struggles to find a continued surge in price. In its latest weekly report, crypto exchange Bitfinex highlighted a key part of Ark Invest&#8217;s report to show growing support from strong holders and improved institutional sentiment toward Bitcoin.  As of early July, 70% of the existing Bitcoin supply of 19.4 million BTC has remained unmoved for at least 12 months. This means that Bitcoin’s unmoved supply, that is, the amount of BTC that hasn’t been transferred in over a year, just reached an all-time high.  Bitcoin Sees Growing Institutional Interest Institutional investors are taking interest in Bitcoin as a hedge against inflation. When major players put serious money into an asset, it signals they believe in its future value.  Related Reading: Bitcoin Hash Rate Retakes All-Time High As Miners Continue To Expand Capacity According to the report, several factors have contributed to the increase in long-term confidence of Bitcoin investors. One major influence is the news of major investment companies filing for Bitcoin spot ETFs which seemed to have fueled more interest.  Over-the-counter (OTC) trading reached a one-year high in June, surging by 60% in the past quarter alone. These OTC trading deals are now more popular with institutional investors, indicating BTC is becoming a preferred investment option. BTC price recovers above $30,500 resistance &#124; Source: BTCUSD on TradingView.com This surge in Bitcoin’s unmoved supply definitely means positive things for the price of Bitcoin. As more of the supply becomes locked up by long-term holders, the available supply in circulation decreases. According to the law of supply and demand, when supply goes down but demand remains the same or increases, the price goes up. It’s not all bullish for the asset though because, according to Bitfinex&#8217;s report, news of the spot ETF filing by BlackRock and other investment companies led to a surge of more than 38% in Bitcoin Open Interest. This suggests that derivatives traders may be dominating the current market momentum, which might negatively affect the price of BTC in the short term. Percent of Supply Last Active 5+ Years Ago Reaches All-Time High Following in the same vein as the Bitfinex report, on-chain data from Glassnode alerts also show that Bitcoin’s supply which has remained unmoved for more than 5 years recently reached an all-time high of 29.070%. Clearly, this shows that more people are holding Bitcoin as a long-term investment rather than trading or spending it. Related Reading: BNB Whale Moves $35 Million To Binance Ahead Of Arkham (ARKM) Sale With Bitcoin having a fixed supply, the unmoved supply of the cryptocurrency is expected to continue to rise as long as investment institutions such as MicroStrategy continue to accumulate more of the cryptocurrency. Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin continues to dominate the market as it struggles to find a continued surge in price. In its latest weekly <a href="https://blog.bitfinex.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitfinex-Alpha-62.pdf" rel="nofollow">report</a>, crypto exchange Bitfinex highlighted a key part of Ark Invest&#8217;s <a href="https://ark-invest.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/The-Bitcoin-Monthly-June-2023.pdf" rel="nofollow">report </a>to show growing support from strong holders and improved institutional sentiment toward Bitcoin. </p>
<p>As of early July, 70% of the existing Bitcoin supply of 19.4 million BTC has remained unmoved for at least 12 months. This means that Bitcoin’s unmoved supply, that is, the amount of BTC that hasn’t been transferred in over a year, just reached an all-time high. </p>
<h2>Bitcoin Sees Growing Institutional Interest</h2>
<p>Institutional investors are taking interest in Bitcoin as a hedge against inflation. When major players put serious money into an asset, it signals they believe in its future value. </p>

<p>According to the report, several factors have contributed to the increase in long-term confidence of Bitcoin investors. One major influence is the news of major investment companies filing for Bitcoin spot ETFs which seemed to have fueled more interest. </p>
<p>Over-the-counter (OTC) trading reached a one-year high in June, surging by 60% in the past quarter alone. These OTC trading deals are now more popular with institutional investors, indicating BTC is becoming a preferred investment option.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/otdIr5ix/" alt="Bitcoin (BTC) price chart from TradingView.com" width="2884" height="1758"/></p>

<p>This surge in Bitcoin’s unmoved supply definitely means positive things for the price of Bitcoin. As more of the supply becomes locked up by long-term holders, the available supply in circulation decreases. According to the law of supply and demand, when supply goes down but demand remains the same or increases, the price goes up.</p>
<p>It’s not all bullish for the asset though because, according to Bitfinex&#8217;s report, news of the spot ETF filing by BlackRock and other investment companies led to a surge of more than 38% in Bitcoin Open Interest. This suggests that derivatives traders may be dominating the current market momentum, which might negatively affect the price of BTC in the short term.</p>
<h2>Percent of Supply Last Active 5+ Years Ago Reaches All-Time High</h2>
<p>Following in the same vein as the Bitfinex report, on-chain <a href="https://twitter.com/glassnodealerts/status/1678810454770974738" rel="nofollow">data </a>from Glassnode alerts also show that Bitcoin’s supply which has remained unmoved for more than 5 years recently reached an all-time high of 29.070%. Clearly, this shows that more people are holding Bitcoin as a long-term investment rather than trading or spending it.</p>

<p>With Bitcoin having a fixed supply, the unmoved supply of the cryptocurrency is expected to continue to rise as long as investment institutions such as MicroStrategy continue to accumulate more of the cryptocurrency.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/iStock-471085352-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Thief Busted: DOJ Files Charges Against 25-Year-Old For OpenSea NFT Heist</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/crypto-thief-busted-doj-files-charges-against-25-year-old-for-opensea-nft-heist/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 02:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cybercriminals]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DeFi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[OpenSea]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=542254</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The United States Department of Justice (DOJ) announced on July 10 the unsealing of a four-count indictment against Soufiane Oulahyane for a scheme to impersonate the OpenSea marketplace to obtain unauthorized access to cryptocurrency and non-fungible tokens (NFTs).  Oulahyane, currently in custody in Morocco for foreign charges, allegedly has stolen approximately $450,000 worth of cryptocurrency and NFTs. OpenSea NFT Theft According to the indictment filed by the US Department of Justice, Soufiane Oulahyane, the alleged hacker who stole $450,000 worth of cryptocurrency NFTs from a victim in Manhattan, sold several NFTs that belonged to the victim.  The NFTs sold by Oulahyane included pieces from popular series like &#8220;Bored Ape Yacht Club,&#8221; &#8220;Meebit,&#8221; &#8220;Bored Ape Kennel Club,&#8221; and &#8220;CryptoDad.&#8221; Per the press release, Oulahyane allegedly used a scheme to &#8220;spoof&#8221; the login page to the OpenSea marketplace by creating a fake website that looked like the real one. He used paid advertisements on a popular search engine to direct users to his fake website, where he tricked them into entering their login credentials or other private information.  Related Reading: BNB Whale Moves $35 Million To Binance Ahead Of Arkham (ARKM) Sale The information was automatically sent to an email account controlled by Oulahyane, who used it to gain unauthorized access to the victims&#8217; cryptocurrency wallets. Oulahyane is charged with wire fraud, use of an unauthorized access device, affecting transactions with an access device to receive something of value equal to or greater than $1,000, and aggravated identity theft.  If convicted, Oulahyane could face up to 20 years in prison for wire fraud, 10 years for using an unauthorized access device, 15 years for affecting transactions with an access device, and a mandatory consecutive sentence of two years for aggravated identity theft. Moreover, according to the press release, the DOJ emphasizes that digital assets, such as cryptocurrency and NFTs, are not immune from cyber fraudsters.  The charges against Oulahyane serve as a reminder that cybercrime techniques such as &#8220;spoofing&#8221; are still in use and can be adapted for use in the cryptocurrency space. The DOJ is committed to prosecuting these fraudsters in the US and abroad. Related Reading: ConsenSys To Launch Linea, Its ZK-Rollup Network, On Main Ethereum Network This indictment shows that law enforcement agencies are taking cybercrime in the cryptocurrency space seriously and are prepared to pursue individuals who engage in fraudulent activities. It is essential for users to exercise caution when dealing with digital assets and to take necessary security measures to protect their cryptocurrency wallets and NFTs from cyber criminals. Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com ]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The United States Department of Justice (DOJ) <a href="https://www.justice.gov/usao-sdny/pr/defendant-charged-theft-cryptocurrency-and-nfts-through-spoofing-opensea-marketplace" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">announced</a> on July 10 the unsealing of a four-count indictment against Soufiane Oulahyane for a scheme to impersonate the OpenSea marketplace to obtain unauthorized access to cryptocurrency and non-fungible tokens (NFTs). </p>
<p>Oulahyane, currently in custody in Morocco for foreign charges, allegedly has stolen approximately $450,000 worth of cryptocurrency and NFTs.</p>
<h2>OpenSea NFT Theft</h2>
<p>According to the indictment filed by the US Department of Justice, Soufiane Oulahyane, the alleged hacker who stole $450,000 worth of cryptocurrency NFTs from a victim in Manhattan, sold several NFTs that belonged to the victim. </p>
<p>The NFTs sold by Oulahyane included pieces from popular series like &#8220;Bored Ape Yacht Club,&#8221; &#8220;Meebit,&#8221; &#8220;Bored Ape Kennel Club,&#8221; and &#8220;CryptoDad.&#8221;</p>
<p>Per the press release, Oulahyane allegedly used a scheme to &#8220;spoof&#8221; the login page to the OpenSea marketplace by creating a fake website that looked like the real one. He used paid advertisements on a popular search engine to direct users to his fake website, where he tricked them into entering their login credentials or other private information. </p>

<p>The information was automatically sent to an email account controlled by Oulahyane, who used it to gain unauthorized access to the victims&#8217; cryptocurrency wallets.</p>
<p>Oulahyane is charged with wire fraud, use of an unauthorized access device, affecting transactions with an access device to receive something of value equal to or greater than $1,000, and aggravated identity theft. </p>
<p>If convicted, Oulahyane could face up to 20 years in prison for wire fraud, 10 years for using an unauthorized access device, 15 years for affecting transactions with an access device, and a mandatory consecutive sentence of two years for aggravated identity theft.</p>
<p>Moreover, according to the press release, the DOJ emphasizes that digital assets, such as cryptocurrency and NFTs, are not immune from cyber fraudsters. </p>
<p>The charges against Oulahyane serve as a reminder that cybercrime techniques such as &#8220;spoofing&#8221; are still in use and can be adapted for use in the cryptocurrency space. The DOJ is committed to prosecuting these fraudsters in the US and abroad.</p>

<p>This indictment shows that law enforcement agencies are taking cybercrime in the cryptocurrency space seriously and are prepared to pursue individuals who engage in fraudulent activities. It is essential for users to exercise caution when dealing with digital assets and to take necessary security measures to protect their cryptocurrency wallets and NFTs from cyber criminals.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/q9duHC1H/" alt="OpenSea" width="1814" height="858"/>
<p>Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/oxana-melis-smXo5DGHXNc-unsplash-307x460.jpg" width="307" height="460" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum Price On The Verge Of Rectangle Pattern Breakout: Is $2000 Within Reach?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/ethereum/ethereum-price-on-the-verge-of-rectangle-pattern-breakout-is-2000-within-reach/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[anushsamal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 01:00:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=542229</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Over the past few days, the Ethereum price has remained relatively stable, with minor gains seen on the daily chart. Meanwhile, Bitcoin&#8217;s indecisiveness has resulted in slower movement for altcoins. Related Reading: ConsenSys To Launch Linea, Its ZK-Rollup Network, On Main Ethereum Network Despite this, Ethereum has risen on its chart, although the technical outlook suggests low demand and accumulation due to reduced buying strength. Despite the fall in buying strength, buyers still hold an advantage over sellers in the market. However, if Ethereum fails to move above its immediate resistance, the coin may retrace on its chart, potentially falling below its local support level and activating bearish sentiment. Investors are now looking ahead to the release of US CPI data, which analysts predict will significantly impact the market in the coming weeks. The market capitalization of Ethereum has fallen slightly, indicating slow demand for the altcoin. Ethereum Price Analysis: One-Day Chart At the time of writing, ETH was priced at $1,870. The daily chart indicated a potential breakout as the price approached the upper boundary of a rectangle pattern. The crucial overhead resistance for Ethereum was identified at $1,880. If the price managed to surpass this level, it could potentially exceed $1,900 and ultimately reach the milestone of $2,000. However, it was essential for ETH to surpass the $1,880 mark in the upcoming trading sessions. On the downside, there was a local support level of $1,820. A dip below this point could lead to a decline towards $1,770. Technical Analysis The inability to break through the $1,900 level had a detrimental impact on investor confidence, resulting in ongoing challenges for Ethereum regarding demand on the daily chart. The Relative Strength Index (RSI) remained positive, although it suggested a relatively low level of demand. Furthermore, Ethereum&#8217;s current position below the 20-Simple Moving Average line indicated a decline in buying strength, indicating that buyers were gradually losing control of the price momentum. In addition to the low buying strength, ETH also experienced a decline on capital inflows. This indicated a decline in investor interest, as evidenced by the Chaikin Money Flow indicator. Conversely, the Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD) formed declining red histograms, suggesting a potential breakout in the upcoming trading sessions. The MACD is a useful tool for identifying price momentum and trend changes. Related Reading: This Bitcoin Rally Is Similar To Genesis Points Of Historical Uptrends: Glassnode The next trading sessions will be critical for ETH. It will determine whether the market will be driven by bears or bulls, ultimately influencing the price. Featured image from UnSplash, charts from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Over the past few days, the Ethereum price has remained relatively stable, with minor gains seen on the daily chart. Meanwhile, Bitcoin&#8217;s indecisiveness has resulted in slower movement for altcoins.</p>

<p>Despite this, Ethereum has risen on its chart, although the technical outlook suggests low demand and accumulation due to reduced buying strength.</p>
<p>Despite the fall in buying strength, buyers still hold an advantage over sellers in the market. However, if Ethereum fails to move above its immediate resistance, the coin may retrace on its chart, potentially falling below its local support level and activating bearish sentiment.</p>
<p>Investors are now looking ahead to the release of US CPI data, which analysts predict will significantly impact the market in the coming weeks. The market capitalization of Ethereum has fallen slightly, indicating slow demand for the altcoin.</p>
<h2>Ethereum Price Analysis: One-Day Chart</h2>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-542233 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETHUSDT_2023-07-11_21-32-30.png" alt="Ethereum" width="1817" height="830" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETHUSDT_2023-07-11_21-32-30.png 1817w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETHUSDT_2023-07-11_21-32-30-460x210.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETHUSDT_2023-07-11_21-32-30-860x393.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETHUSDT_2023-07-11_21-32-30-768x351.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETHUSDT_2023-07-11_21-32-30-1536x702.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETHUSDT_2023-07-11_21-32-30-750x343.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETHUSDT_2023-07-11_21-32-30-1140x521.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1817px) 100vw, 1817px"/>






<p>At the time of writing, ETH was priced at $1,870. The daily chart indicated a potential breakout as the price approached the upper boundary of a rectangle pattern. The crucial overhead resistance for Ethereum was identified at $1,880.</p>
<p>If the price managed to surpass this level, it could potentially exceed $1,900 and ultimately reach the milestone of $2,000.</p>
<p>However, it was essential for ETH to surpass the $1,880 mark in the upcoming trading sessions. On the downside, there was a local support level of $1,820. A dip below this point could lead to a decline towards $1,770.</p>
<h2>Technical Analysis</h2>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-542257 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETHUSDT_2023-07-11_21-33-12.png" alt="Ethereum" width="1817" height="743" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETHUSDT_2023-07-11_21-33-12.png 1817w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETHUSDT_2023-07-11_21-33-12-460x188.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETHUSDT_2023-07-11_21-33-12-860x352.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETHUSDT_2023-07-11_21-33-12-768x314.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETHUSDT_2023-07-11_21-33-12-1536x628.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETHUSDT_2023-07-11_21-33-12-750x307.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETHUSDT_2023-07-11_21-33-12-1140x466.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1817px) 100vw, 1817px"/>
<p>The inability to break through the $1,900 level had a detrimental impact on investor confidence, resulting in ongoing challenges for Ethereum regarding demand on the daily chart. The Relative Strength Index (RSI) remained positive, although it suggested a relatively low level of demand.</p>
<p>Furthermore, Ethereum&#8217;s current position below the 20-Simple Moving Average line indicated a decline in buying strength, indicating that buyers were gradually losing control of the price momentum.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-542258 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETHUSDT_2023-07-11_21-34-01.png" alt="Ethereum" width="1817" height="743" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETHUSDT_2023-07-11_21-34-01.png 1817w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETHUSDT_2023-07-11_21-34-01-460x188.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETHUSDT_2023-07-11_21-34-01-860x352.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETHUSDT_2023-07-11_21-34-01-768x314.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETHUSDT_2023-07-11_21-34-01-1536x628.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETHUSDT_2023-07-11_21-34-01-750x307.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETHUSDT_2023-07-11_21-34-01-1140x466.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1817px) 100vw, 1817px"/>
<p>In addition to the low buying strength, ETH also experienced a decline on capital inflows. This indicated a decline in investor interest, as evidenced by the Chaikin Money Flow indicator.</p>
<p>Conversely, the Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD) formed declining red histograms, suggesting a potential breakout in the upcoming trading sessions. The MACD is a useful tool for identifying price momentum and trend changes.</p>

<p>The next trading sessions will be critical for ETH. It will determine whether the market will be driven by bears or bulls, ultimately influencing the price.</p>







]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/kanchanara-VcoXL-xP9I0-unsplash-460x306.jpg" width="460" height="306" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Insider Job? Chainalysis Report Suggests Multichain Attacker Had Inside Connections</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/insider-job-chainalysis-report-suggests-multichain-attacker-had-inside-connections/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 00:00:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exploit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantom (FTM)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[multichain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MULTIUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=542243</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[On July 6, 2023, the Multichain Protocol was hit by a massive hack, resulting in the loss of over $125 million worth of cryptocurrency. The attack targeted the protocol&#8217;s Fantom bridge, resulting in the theft of valuable crypto assets like WBTC, USDC, DAI, wETH, and Link.  The stolen funds amounted to a staggering $126 million, with WBTC accounting for $30.9 million, wETH for $13.6 million, and USDC for $57 million. This exploit is one of the biggest crypto hacks on record. Multichain Attack And Insider Threats According to a recent report by the analysis and data company Chainalysis, the attack is suspected to be an inside job since Multichain has recently experienced some notable issues unrelated to its protocol design, prompting public suspicions that insiders may have carried out this recent exploit.  The disappearance of Multichain&#8217;s CEO, who is known by the alias Zhaojun, and the subsequent suspension of services for more than 10 chains, including DynoChain, Redlight Chain, and Public Mint has added fuel to this suspicion. Related Reading: ConsenSys To Launch Linea, Its ZK-Rollup Network, On Main Ethereum Network Multichain&#8217;s smart contracts are secured by a multi-party computation (MPC) system, which functions similarly to a multi-signature wallet system. However, like multi-signature wallets, these systems are still vulnerable if an attacker possesses sufficient MPC keys. It is possible that the attacker gained control of Multichain&#8217;s MPC keys to pull off this exploit. Interestingly, the attacker did not swap out centrally controlled assets like USDC, which can be frozen by the issuing company (Circle, in the case of USDC), along with the addresses holding those assets.  Most hackers typically seek to quickly swap funds for those not vulnerable to those security measures. In total, addresses frozen by Circle and Tether hold approximately $65 million in assets stolen from Multichain. What’s Next For The Protocol? After the attack, the Multichain team tweeted that they were beginning an investigation and urged users to pause transactions. A day later, on July 7, the team tweeted that the protocol would be stopping service indefinitely. Unfortunately, scammers also went on Twitter to spread a “phishing” link and impersonate the Fantom Foundation to trick affected users into claiming an &#8220;emergency FTM distribution.&#8221; Cross-chain bridge protocols have proven lucrative targets for hackers due to their experimental designs and the fact that they generally have large, centralized repositories of assets bridged by users to other blockchains. However, there may be several methods to mitigate risk and prevent similar exploits from occurring.  According to Chainalysis, one way is through rigorous code audits to help developers standardize projects and investors evaluate protocol viability.  While the Multichain hack appears to have resulted from compromised keys rather than faulty code, reputable audit reports often explicitly identify which parts of protocols are vulnerable to private key theft, which may help users better assess risk. Additionally, users of any protocol can research before they transact. Related Reading: Bitcoin And Crypto Investors Must Monitor The DXY: 6x Rally Ahead? The exploit suffered has left the blockchain community on edge, with many waiting for an official statement from the Multichain team. The team has not made any public pronouncements on the matter, leaving users and investors in the dark about the protocol&#8217;s future. Multichain&#8217;s native token, MULTI, has experienced a significant decline over the past 7 days, with a drop of over 27% in this timeframe. Currently, the token is trading at $2.387, representing a further decline of 3% in the last 24 hours. Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On July 6, 2023, the Multichain Protocol was hit by a massive hack, resulting in the loss of over $125 million worth of cryptocurrency. The attack targeted the protocol&#8217;s Fantom bridge, resulting in the theft of valuable crypto assets like WBTC, USDC, DAI, wETH, and Link. </p>
<p>The stolen funds amounted to a staggering $126 million, with WBTC accounting for $30.9 million, wETH for $13.6 million, and USDC for $57 million. This exploit is one of the biggest crypto hacks on record.</p>
<h2>Multichain Attack And Insider Threats</h2>
<p>According to a recent <a href="https://blog.chainalysis.com/reports/multichain-exploit-july-2023/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">report </a>by the analysis and data company Chainalysis, the attack is suspected to be an inside job since Multichain has recently experienced some notable issues unrelated to its protocol design, prompting public suspicions that insiders may have carried out this recent exploit. </p>
<p>The disappearance of Multichain&#8217;s CEO, who is known by the alias Zhaojun, and the subsequent suspension of services for more than 10 chains, including DynoChain, Redlight Chain, and Public Mint has added fuel to this suspicion.</p>

<p>Multichain&#8217;s smart contracts are secured by a multi-party computation (MPC) system, which functions similarly to a multi-signature wallet system. However, like multi-signature wallets, these systems are still vulnerable if an attacker possesses sufficient MPC keys. </p>
<p>It is possible that the attacker gained control of Multichain&#8217;s MPC keys to pull off this exploit. Interestingly, the attacker did not swap out centrally controlled assets like USDC, which can be frozen by the issuing company (Circle, in the case of USDC), along with the addresses holding those assets. </p>
<p>Most hackers typically seek to quickly swap funds for those not vulnerable to those security measures. In total, addresses frozen by Circle and Tether hold approximately $65 million in assets stolen from Multichain.</p>
What’s Next For The Protocol?
<p>After the attack, the Multichain team tweeted that they were beginning an investigation and urged users to pause transactions. A day later, on July 7, the team tweeted that the protocol would be stopping service indefinitely. </p>
<p>Unfortunately, scammers also went on Twitter to spread a “phishing” link and impersonate the Fantom Foundation to trick affected users into claiming an &#8220;emergency FTM distribution.&#8221;</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-542245" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot_18.jpg" alt="Multichain " width="723" height="496" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot_18.jpg 723w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot_18-460x316.jpg 460w" sizes="(max-width: 723px) 100vw, 723px"/>
<p>Cross-chain bridge protocols have proven lucrative targets for hackers due to their experimental designs and the fact that they generally have large, centralized repositories of assets bridged by users to other blockchains. However, there may be several methods to mitigate risk and prevent similar exploits from occurring. </p>
<p>According to Chainalysis, one way is through rigorous code audits to help developers standardize projects and investors evaluate protocol viability. </p>
<p>While the Multichain hack appears to have resulted from compromised keys rather than faulty code, reputable audit reports often explicitly identify which parts of protocols are vulnerable to private key theft, which may help users better assess risk. Additionally, users of any protocol can research before they transact.</p>

<p>The exploit suffered has left the blockchain community on edge, with many waiting for an official statement from the Multichain team. The team has not made any public pronouncements on the matter, leaving users and investors in the dark about the protocol&#8217;s future.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/p8krCE6O/" alt="Multichain " width="1815" height="858"/>
<p>Multichain&#8217;s native token, MULTI, has experienced a significant decline over the past 7 days, with a drop of over 27% in this timeframe. Currently, the token is trading at $2.387, representing a further decline of 3% in the last 24 hours.</p>
<p>Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/israel-palacio-ImcUkZ72oUs-unsplash-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Pre-100X Litecoin Signal Returns After Six-Year Slump</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/litecoin/pre-100x-litecoin-signal-returns-six-year-slump/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tony "The Bull"]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 23:29:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Litecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ltc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ltc/usd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=542277</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Litecoin price is now back under $100, locked within an ever tightening trading range. The lack of notorious cryptocurrency market volatility in LTCUSD in recent weeks is reminiscent of late 2016 and early 2017 — right before an epic 100x rally. With the signal back, does this mean that another sizable surge is ahead? A Pre-100x Litecoin Signal Is Back Past performance is never a guarantee of future results, but technical analysis seeks out various signals and historical patterns in hopes of increasing the probability of success. What can be guaranteed, however, is that after a long period of low volatility, it ends with a bang and a breakout back into a highly volatile state. Combine this behavior with the more volatile crypto asset class, and you’ve got a recipe for some serious moves. So large in fact, that the lowest volatility that Litecoin ever reached, concluded with a breakout into a 100x rally. In less than a year’s time, LTCUSD grew from $3 to over $300. Now that signal is back again, and it could once again lead to a huge move in Litecoin. But it doesn’t necessarily mean up. It’s been a long time since bulls had a turn &#124; LTCUSD on TradingView.com Why Low Volatility Ends With A Bang The pre-100x signal in LTCUSD we are talking about is the 9-day Bollinger Bands, and Bollinger Band Width. The Bollinger Bands are the second-tightest in Litecoin history. The Bollinger Bands are a volatility-measuring tool using a simple moving average and two bands set at two standard deviations. They expand with high volatility and contract with low volatility. A low volatility state, called a squeeze, always ends with a significant move and turn to shocking volatility. But volatility is only the measure of price dispersion over a time period. This means a that the large move, when it finally arrives, could be down. However, several other technicals support price appreciation in the future so up is also an option. What isn’t an option, is remaining in this low volatility state for much longer, so buckle up, it’s about to get interesting soon enough. Furthermore, Bollinger Band Width has been contracting with lower highs for six full years. If the downtrend pattern breaks, the largest movement in half a decade might arrive. #Litecoin volatility is compressing for six years now Lowest volatility since $LTC went from $3 to $300 (100x) in 2017 Patience will be rewarded. The longer it takes, the larger the move. When it begins, it will be a sight to behold pic.twitter.com/YTtbB0TrJz — Tony &#8220;The Bull&#8221; (@tonythebullBTC) July 9, 2023 Tony is the author of the CoinChartist (VIP) newsletter. Follow @TonyTheBullBTC &#38; @coinchartist_io on Twitter. Or join the TonyTradesBTC Telegram for daily market insights and technical analysis education. Please note: Content is educational and should not be considered investment advice. Featured image from iStockPhoto, Charts from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Litecoin price is now back under $100, locked within an ever tightening trading range. The lack of notorious cryptocurrency market volatility in LTCUSD in recent weeks is reminiscent of late 2016 and early 2017 — right before an epic 100x rally.</p>
<p>With the signal back, does this mean that another sizable surge is ahead?</p>
<h2>A Pre-100x Litecoin Signal Is Back</h2>
<p>Past performance is never a guarantee of future results, but technical analysis seeks out various signals and historical patterns in hopes of increasing the probability of success.</p>
<p>What can be guaranteed, however, is that after a long period of low volatility, it ends with a bang and a breakout back into a highly volatile state. Combine this behavior with the more volatile crypto asset class, and you’ve got a recipe for some serious moves.</p>
<p>So large in fact, that the lowest volatility that Litecoin ever reached, concluded with a breakout into a 100x rally. In less than a year’s time, LTCUSD grew from $3 to over $300.</p>
<p>Now that signal is back again, and it could once again lead to a huge move in Litecoin. But it doesn’t necessarily mean up.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large wp-image-542278 aligncenter" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/AF74A8CC-B0FD-4DF6-B663-636D715E2B5F-860x535.png" alt="Litecoin LTCUSD" width="860" height="535" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/AF74A8CC-B0FD-4DF6-B663-636D715E2B5F-860x535.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/AF74A8CC-B0FD-4DF6-B663-636D715E2B5F-460x286.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/AF74A8CC-B0FD-4DF6-B663-636D715E2B5F-768x478.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/AF74A8CC-B0FD-4DF6-B663-636D715E2B5F-1536x955.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/AF74A8CC-B0FD-4DF6-B663-636D715E2B5F-2048x1274.png 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/AF74A8CC-B0FD-4DF6-B663-636D715E2B5F-750x466.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/AF74A8CC-B0FD-4DF6-B663-636D715E2B5F-1140x709.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/></p>

<h2>Why Low Volatility Ends With A Bang</h2>
<p>The pre-100x signal in LTCUSD we are talking about is the 9-day Bollinger Bands, and Bollinger Band Width. The Bollinger Bands are the second-tightest in Litecoin history.</p>
<p>The Bollinger Bands are a volatility-measuring tool using a simple moving average and two bands set at two standard deviations. They expand with high volatility and contract with low volatility. A low volatility state, called a squeeze, always ends with a significant move and turn to shocking volatility. But volatility is only the measure of price dispersion over a time period.</p>
<p>This means a that the large move, when it finally arrives, could be down. However, several other technicals support price appreciation in the future so up is also an option. What isn’t an option, is remaining in this low volatility state for much longer, so buckle up, it’s about to get interesting soon enough.</p>
<p>Furthermore, Bollinger Band Width has been contracting with lower highs for six full years. If the downtrend pattern breaks, the largest movement in half a decade might arrive.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en"><a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Litecoin?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#Litecoin</a> volatility is compressing for six years now</p>
<p>Lowest volatility since <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24LTC&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$LTC</a> went from $3 to $300 (100x) in 2017</p>
<p>Patience will be rewarded. The longer it takes, the larger the move. When it begins, it will be a sight to behold <a href="https://t.co/YTtbB0TrJz" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/YTtbB0TrJz</a></p>
<p>— Tony &#8220;The Bull&#8221; (@tonythebullBTC) <a href="https://twitter.com/tonythebullBTC/status/1678157447167451136?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">July 9, 2023</a></p></blockquote>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/7A0438FF-588E-4C63-9102-2F15FB563E9C-460x345.jpeg" width="460" height="345" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin And NASDAQ Composite Index Correlation Drops To A 2-Year Low</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-nasdaq-correlation-2-year-low/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dalmas Ngetich]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 23:00:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin prices]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[federal reserve]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NASDAQ]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=542215</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[New data from Kaiko on July 11 indicates that the correlation between Bitcoin and the Nasdaq Composite Index is at a two-year low. The correlation coefficient between these two assets dropped to less than 1% in early July. At this level, it is at July 2021 lows. The NASDAQ Composite Index tracks the performance of all stocks listed on the NASDAQ stock exchange. Among stocks listed on this bourse include Coinbase’s COIN. Dropping Correlation Between Bitcoin And NASDAQ A correlation coefficient of around 0% signifies a weak negative relationship between Bitcoin and the NASDAQ. This implies that Bitcoin prices moved in the opposite direction or are unrelated to the NASDAQ Composite Index action.  Related Reading: Bitcoin Google Search Interest Stands At Critical Level, What This Forecast For BTC As of July 10, Bitcoin prices were relatively firm, oscillating around the $30,000 level and generally in an uptrend looking at price performance in Q2 2023. For context, Bitcoin is less than $2,000 away from 2023 highs of $31,400 registered in June 2023. Meanwhile, market data shows that the NASDAQ Composite Index is also at multi-month highs and firm, reflecting the broader market recovery in the United States. The dwindling correlation between Bitcoin and the NASDAQ may be attributed to several factors. One potential explanation is that investors are becoming more discerning in their investment choices. As the cryptocurrency market matures and regulations are drafted, investors might seek assets with low correlation with traditional finance instruments like stocks and indices. The other reason could stem from the recent action of the cryptocurrency market. In 2022, cryptocurrencies, including Bitcoin, fell from highs registered in 2021. After peaking at over $69,000, Bitcoin prices crashed in 2022. This was fast-tracked by the solvency of several centralized finance platforms offering crypto services, including Celsius. The collapse of FTX, a popular cryptocurrency exchange, forced prices even low. In November 2022, BTC prices crashed below $16,000.  Like crypto assets, technology stocks like COIN listed on NASDAQ are relatively volatile and were also impacted by rising interest rates in 2021. Subsequently, the dump in asset prices might have forced investors to be more risk-averse and diversify their holdings, forcing the correlation between NASDAQ and Bitcoin even lower.  Watching The US Federal Reserve Whether this correlation will fall in the months ahead remains to be seen. However, at the moment, the cryptocurrency market seems fragile. Bitcoin bulls have failed to break above June 2023 highs in continuation of bullish pressure in the past few weeks.  Related Reading: Bulls Remain Resilient Despite Litecoin’s Fall Below $100, Key Levels To Watch At the same time, market participants closely track how the United States Federal Reserve will proceed with its monetary policy.  After steadily increasing interest rates to tame rising inflation, the central bank paused rate hikes in Q2 2023. Whether they will slash rates in the coming months remains to be seen. Feature image from Canva, chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>New data from Kaiko on July 11 <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://twitter.com/KaikoData/status/1678673860818792451" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">indicates</a> that the correlation between Bitcoin and the Nasdaq Composite Index is at a two-year low. The correlation coefficient between these two assets dropped to less than 1% in early July. </p>
<p>At this level, it is at July 2021 lows. The NASDAQ Composite Index tracks the performance of all stocks listed on the NASDAQ stock exchange. Among stocks listed on this bourse include Coinbase’s COIN.</p>
<h2>Dropping Correlation Between Bitcoin And NASDAQ
</h2>
<p>A correlation coefficient of around 0% signifies a weak negative relationship between Bitcoin and the NASDAQ. This implies that Bitcoin prices moved in the opposite direction or are unrelated to the NASDAQ Composite Index action. </p>

<p>As of July 10, Bitcoin prices were relatively firm, oscillating around the $30,000 level and generally in an uptrend looking at price performance in Q2 2023. For context, Bitcoin is less than $2,000 away from 2023 highs of $31,400 registered in June 2023. </p>
<p>Meanwhile, market data <a href="https://finance.yahoo.com/quote/%5EIXIC/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">shows</a> that the NASDAQ Composite Index is also at multi-month highs and firm, reflecting the broader market recovery in the United States.</p>
<a href="https://www.tradingview.com/x/uQ3K7iX6/" rel="nofollow"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/uQ3K7iX6/" alt="Bitcoin price on July 11| Source: BTCUSDT on Binance, TradingView" width="1226" height="595"/></a>
<p>The dwindling correlation between Bitcoin and the NASDAQ may be attributed to several factors. One potential explanation is that investors are becoming more discerning in their investment choices. </p>
<p>As the cryptocurrency market matures and regulations are drafted, investors might seek assets with low correlation with traditional finance instruments like stocks and indices.</p>
<p>The other reason could stem from the recent action of the cryptocurrency market. In 2022, cryptocurrencies, including Bitcoin, fell from highs registered in 2021. After peaking at over $69,000, Bitcoin prices crashed in 2022. </p>
<p>This was fast-tracked by the solvency of several centralized finance platforms offering crypto services, including Celsius. The collapse of FTX, a popular cryptocurrency exchange, forced prices even low. In November 2022, BTC prices crashed below $16,000. </p>
<p>Like crypto assets, technology stocks like COIN listed on NASDAQ are relatively volatile and were also impacted by rising interest rates in 2021. Subsequently, the dump in asset prices might have forced investors to be more risk-averse and diversify their holdings, forcing the correlation between NASDAQ and Bitcoin even lower. </p>
<h2>Watching The US Federal Reserve</h2>
<p>Whether this correlation will fall in the months ahead remains to be seen. However, at the moment, the cryptocurrency market seems fragile. Bitcoin bulls have failed to break above June 2023 highs in continuation of bullish pressure in the past few weeks. </p>

<p>At the same time, market participants closely track how the United States Federal Reserve will proceed with its monetary policy. </p>
<p>After steadily increasing interest rates to tame rising inflation, the central bank paused rate hikes in Q2 2023. Whether they will slash rates in the coming months remains to be seen.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-Nasdaq-460x260.jpg" width="460" height="260" />	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
