<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
>

<channel>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.newsbtc.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<description>Bitcoin &#38; Cryptocurrency News Today</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 17:10:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>29% Of Bitcoin’s Circulating Supply Is Now Presumed Lost Forever</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-presumed-lost-forever/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 19:00:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dormant BTC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=542992</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[According to recent findings from blockchain analytics company IntoTheBlock, around 29% of the total Bitcoin circulating supply is now presumed lost forever after remaining stagnant for over five years. Bitcoin was designed to be scarce, with only 21 million coins ever to be mined, but the very features that make the cryptocurrency so attractive to investors can sometimes lead to investors losing their assets forever, especially in cases where private keys are forgotten.  Related Reading: Why Ripple’s Victory Against The SEC May Be Short-Lived: Legal Expert Stagnant BTC Addresses Are Growing Over Time In a recent tweet by IntoTheBlock, the company called attention to the high number of dormant bitcoin addresses. &#8220;Our data shows that 29% of $BTC hasn&#8217;t moved in over 5 years. It&#8217;s possible that a large part of this concerns lost coins,&#8221; the tweet said.  BTC presumed lost crosses 7.7 million &#124; Source: Glassnode Similar data has been supplied by Glassnode Alerts, an on-chain metrics monitor. According to Glassnode, on-chain data shows that the total quantity of HODLed or lost bitcoins just hit a new all-time high of 7,781,224.168 BTC. Given that the price of a single Bitcoin is currently about $30,000, this equates to more than $235 billion in BTC that has now been lost.  What Does This Mean For Bitcoin? Institutional interest in Bitcoin has grown in the past year, with companies like MicroStrategy doubling down on their bitcoin holdings. Hence, the increase in dormant addresses can show more people are holding Bitcoin as a long-term investment rather than trading or spending it. However, it can also signal the amount of BTC lost forever, especially by early investors.  BTC price trending at $30,100 &#124; Source: BTCUSD on TradingView.com Taking into account that early investors are more likely to cash out on the huge gains made by the price of bitcoin, the latter is more likely. The price of Bitcoin has skyrocketed over the years and small amounts of Bitcoin from the early days are now worth a fortune. So if investors still had access to these dormant BTC, then they would likely have been moved already.  As Bitcoin gained mainstream popularity, many people have also bought in without fully understanding how to secure their private keys properly. A good example is the case of Stefan Thomas, a San Francisco-based programmer who is unable to asses his holdings of about 7,002 bitcoins. Thomas&#8217; holdings are currently worth $216 million, but he can&#8217;t remember the password containing the private keys to his digital wallet.  Related Reading: Ark Invest Sells Over $50 Million Worth of Coinbase Shares Amidst Stock Rally With bitcoin having a fixed supply, its increasing scarcity due to lost coins can also enhance its appeal as a store of value. This could drive the price up due to increasing demand for the fewer bitcoins in circulation.  Bitcoin has seen a surge in price in recent months fueled by spot ETF applications filed by major investment companies like BlackRock and Valkyrie. The cryptocurrency is up by 43% this year and is currently ranging around $30,000 for the past few weeks. Featured image from Futurism, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p style="font-weight: 400">According to recent findings from blockchain analytics company IntoTheBlock, around 29% of the total Bitcoin circulating supply is now presumed lost forever after remaining stagnant for over five years. </p>
<p style="font-weight: 400">Bitcoin was designed to be scarce, with only 21 million coins ever to be mined, but the very features that make the cryptocurrency so attractive to investors can sometimes lead to investors losing their assets forever, especially in cases where private keys are forgotten. </p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="Legal Expert" rel="nofollow">Why Ripple’s Victory Against The SEC May Be Short-Lived: Legal Expert</a></p>
<h2 style="font-weight: 400">Stagnant BTC Addresses Are Growing Over Time</h2>
<p style="font-weight: 400">In a recent <a href="https://twitter.com/intotheblock/status/1680834832601939968?s=20" rel="nofollow">tweet </a>by IntoTheBlock, the company called attention to the high number of dormant bitcoin addresses. &#8220;Our data shows that 29% of $BTC hasn&#8217;t moved in over 5 years. It&#8217;s possible that a large part of this concerns lost coins,&#8221; the tweet said. </p>


<p style="font-weight: 400">Similar <a href="https://twitter.com/glassnodealerts/status/1680823505976279041?s=20" rel="nofollow">data </a>has been supplied by Glassnode Alerts, an on-chain metrics monitor. According to Glassnode, on-chain data shows that the total quantity of HODLed or lost bitcoins just hit a new all-time high of 7,781,224.168 BTC. Given that the price of a single Bitcoin is currently about $30,000, this equates to more than $235 billion in BTC that has now been lost. </p>
<h2 style="font-weight: 400">What Does This Mean For Bitcoin?</h2>
<p style="font-weight: 400">Institutional interest in Bitcoin has grown in the past year, with companies like MicroStrategy doubling down on their bitcoin holdings. Hence, the increase in dormant addresses can show more people are holding Bitcoin as a long-term investment rather than trading or spending it. However, it can also signal the amount of BTC lost forever, especially by early investors. </p>
<p style="text-align: center"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/XcF1QvUE/" alt="Bitcoin (BTC) price chart from TradingView.com" width="2160" height="1686"/></p>

<p style="font-weight: 400">Taking into account that early investors are more likely to cash out on the huge gains made by the price of bitcoin, the latter is more likely. The price of Bitcoin has skyrocketed over the years and small amounts of Bitcoin from the early days are now worth a fortune. So if investors still had access to these dormant BTC, then they would likely have been moved already. </p>
<p style="font-weight: 400">As Bitcoin gained mainstream popularity, many people have also bought in without fully understanding how to secure their private keys properly. A good example is the case of Stefan Thomas, a San Francisco-based programmer who is unable to asses his holdings of about 7,002 bitcoins. Thomas&#8217; holdings are currently worth $216 million, but he can&#8217;t remember the password containing the private keys to his digital wallet. </p>

<p style="font-weight: 400">With bitcoin having a fixed supply, its increasing scarcity due to lost coins can also enhance its appeal as a store of value. This could drive the price up due to increasing demand for the fewer bitcoins in circulation. </p>
<p style="font-weight: 400">Bitcoin has seen a surge in price in recent months fueled by spot ETF applications filed by major investment companies like BlackRock and Valkyrie. The cryptocurrency is up by 43% this year and is currently ranging around $30,000 for the past few weeks.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/IMG_0018-460x265.jpeg" width="460" height="265" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>XRP Crosses 1 Million Trades Per Minute Following Court Ruling</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/xrp-crosses-1-million-trades/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 17:30:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrp]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP volume]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrpusdt]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=542979</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[In the wake of a favorable court ruling in the Ripple vs. SEC case, XRP has witnessed an extraordinary surge in demand and trading activity. With over 1 million trades per minute globally, XRP has become the center of attention for investors worldwide.  This unprecedented growth comes after a period of legal uncertainty and trading restrictions, positioning XRP for potential success in the cryptocurrency market. XRP&#8217;s Milestone: Over 1 Million Trades Per Minute Sparks Growth Visionary entrepreneur and self-proclaimed &#8220;Crypto Crusader,&#8221; known as Nick on Twitter,  swiftly recognized the unparalleled growth potential inherent in XRP. Related Reading: Why Ripple’s Victory Against The SEC May Be Short-Lived: Legal Expert Taking to social media, Nick expressed his awe at the surging demand for XRP, emphasizing its relentless upward trajectory in a tweet. With unwavering confidence, Nick firmly believes that this remarkable milestone is merely the inception of XRP&#8217;s extraordinary journey. Also, XRP experienced a significant surge in trading volume, reaching $10.4 billion on July 13. However, while this figure appears impressive, it is worth noting that it only ranks as the 76th largest volume in XRP&#8217;s history.  This observation highlights the immense potential that XRP possesses, suggesting that the recent surge in volume may be just the beginning. A tweet from Leonidas, the host of the popular crypto YouTube channel XRPArcade, underscores this point, stating, &#8220;On July 13th, XRP&#8217;s volume spiked to $10.4 billion. Even though this seems like a big number, historically, this was XRP&#8217;s 76th largest daily trading volume recorded on CoinMarketCap (CMC). The highest was almost $37 billion on April 6th, 2021.&#8221;  This historical context emphasizes that XRP has achieved even higher trading volumes in the past, indicating the potential for further growth.  XRP price sitting at $0.73 &#124; Source: XRPUSD on TradingView.com Daily Volume Surges 18-Fold Following Court Ruling And Exchange Relisting The court ruling that declared XRP as not a Security favored the altcoin as XRP witnessed a dramatic surge in trading volume, increasing from $613 million to $11.2 billion within a single day.  The ruling by the Southern District Court of New York has reignited investor interest in XRP, leading major exchange platforms such as Coinbase, Kraken, and Crypto.com to relist the asset.  The market responded with XRP&#8217;s value soaring by 85% from $0.47 to $0.87, with the token currently trading at $0.78 despite the market drawdown. Related Reading: Ark Invest Sells Over $50 Million Worth of Coinbase Shares Amidst Stock Rally Moreover, XRP&#8217;s market capitalization also experienced a substantial boost, reaching $40.8 billion within the past 24 hours. This surge propelled XRP to become the fourth largest cryptocurrency in terms of market capitalization, trailing only Bitcoin (BTC), Ether (ETH), and Tether USD (USDT).  The derivatives market also witnessed increased interest, with funding rates and open interest for XRP derivatives reaching the highest levels of the year, indicating growing confidence among traders. Featured image from Outlook India, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In the wake of a favorable court ruling in the Ripple vs. SEC case, XRP has witnessed an extraordinary surge in demand and trading activity. With over 1 million trades per minute globally, XRP has become the center of attention for investors worldwide. </p>
<p>This unprecedented growth comes after a period of legal uncertainty and trading restrictions, positioning XRP for potential success in the cryptocurrency market.</p>
<h2>XRP&#8217;s Milestone: Over 1 Million Trades Per Minute Sparks Growth</h2>
<p>Visionary entrepreneur and self-proclaimed &#8220;Crypto Crusader,&#8221; known as Nick on Twitter,  swiftly recognized the unparalleled growth potential inherent in XRP.</p>

<p>Taking to social media, Nick expressed his awe at the surging demand for XRP, emphasizing its relentless upward trajectory in a <a href="https://twitter.com/NCashOfficial/status/1680633846822236161?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw%7Ctwcamp%5Etweetembed%7Ctwterm%5E1680633846822236161%7Ctwgr%5Eb8abeb7f9c7535c558c4eff033e21dbf31f5dbb1%7Ctwcon%5Es1_c10&amp;ref_url=https%3A%2F%2Fthecryptobasic.com%2F2023%2F07%2F17%2Fxrp-demand-skyrockets-with-over-1-million-trades-per-minute-globally%2F" rel="nofollow">tweet</a>. With unwavering confidence, Nick firmly believes that this remarkable milestone is merely the inception of XRP&#8217;s extraordinary journey.</p>
<p>Also, XRP experienced a significant surge in trading volume, reaching $10.4 billion on July 13. However, while this figure appears impressive, it is worth noting that it only ranks as the 76th largest volume in XRP&#8217;s history. </p>
<p>This observation highlights the immense potential that XRP possesses, suggesting that the recent surge in volume may be just the beginning.</p>
<p>A <a href="https://twitter.com/LeoHadjiloizou/status/1680595490185023488?s=20" rel="nofollow">tweet</a> from Leonidas, the host of the popular crypto YouTube channel XRPArcade, underscores this point, stating, &#8220;On July 13th, XRP&#8217;s volume spiked to $10.4 billion. Even though this seems like a big number, historically, this was XRP&#8217;s 76th largest daily trading volume recorded on CoinMarketCap (CMC). The highest was almost $37 billion on April 6th, 2021.&#8221; </p>
<p>This historical context emphasizes that XRP has achieved even higher trading volumes in the past, indicating the potential for further growth. </p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/xOptrzwf/" alt="Ripple (XRP) price chart on TradingView.com" width="2884" height="1758"/></p>

<h2>Daily Volume Surges 18-Fold Following Court Ruling And Exchange Relisting</h2>
<p>The court ruling that declared XRP as not a Security favored the altcoin as XRP witnessed a dramatic surge in trading volume, increasing from $613 million to $11.2 billion within a single day. </p>
<p>The ruling by the Southern District Court of New York has reignited investor interest in XRP, leading major exchange platforms such as Coinbase, Kraken, and Crypto.com to <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/large-exchanges-relist-xrp/?swcfpc=1">relist the asset</a>. </p>
<p>The market responded with XRP&#8217;s value soaring by 85% from $0.47 to $0.87, with the token currently trading at $0.78 despite the market drawdown.</p>

<p>Moreover, XRP&#8217;s market capitalization also experienced a substantial boost, reaching $40.8 billion within the past 24 hours. This surge propelled XRP to become the fourth largest cryptocurrency in terms of market capitalization, trailing only Bitcoin (BTC), Ether (ETH), and Tether USD (USDT). </p>
<p>The derivatives market also witnessed increased interest, with funding rates and open interest for XRP derivatives reaching the highest levels of the year, indicating growing confidence among traders.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRP-460x259.jpeg" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>zkSync Unveils Boojum Upgrade: The Ultimate Solution For Scalability And Security?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/blockchain/zksync-unveils-boojum-upgrade-the-ultimate-solution-for-scalability-and-security/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 16:30:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blockchain technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DeFi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[zkSync]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=542973</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[zkSync, a blockchain network that aims to make digital self-ownership universally accessible, has announced a major cryptographic upgrade to its proof system.  The upgrade involves transitioning to a new STARK-based proof system called Boojum, which, according to the announcement, offers world-class proving performance and reduces hardware requirements for decentralization. zkSync Era Moves To Boojum Boojum is a Rust-based arithmetization and constraint library that implements the upgraded version of the ZK circuits for zkSync Era and the ZK Stack. The library offers several compelling properties, including PLONK-style arithmetization. PLONK-style arithmetization refers to the use of PLONK (Permutation-based Linear-based SNARKs for transparent, universal, and upgradable proofs) as the underlying zero-knowledge proof system.  PLONK is a relatively new proof system that provides several advantages over previous systems, such as Sonic and Halo. Specifically, PLONK is designed to be more transparent, universal, and upgradeable, making it a good choice for zkSync&#8217;s upgraded proof system. Related Reading: Celsius Is Selling, More Pain For BNB, LINK, And SNX? According to the announcement, the move to a STARK-based proof system represents a dramatic performance improvement and will help ensure low latency for finality and support for increased levels of activity on zkSync Era and other ZK Stack-based systems.  The GPU provers used for Boojum require just 16 GB (GygaByte) of RAM, a significant reduction from the hundreds of GBs of RAM needed by prevalent proof systems.  By reducing the amount of RAM required to run the GPU provers from hundreds of GBs to just 16 GB, zkSync will be able to use cheaper machines for increased horizontal scalability. This will likely have a positive impact on the cost of using zkSync. This means that more people will be able to participate in the network and contribute to its decentralization, ultimately leading to a healthier and more robust network. Furthermore, to ensure a smooth transition, zkSync is running the new proof system alongside the existing one in a testing phase called mainnet shadow mode.  The network is generating and verifying &#8220;shadow proofs&#8221; for Mainnet blocks to further test and optimize the system with real production data from zkSync Era&#8217;s user activity. This testing is being done off-chain to find edge cases and bugs, and to continue reviewing the implementation. zkSync is also open-sourcing the Boojum codebase to allow anyone to use the new proofs and verify them using a command-line interface (CLI) tool.  Related Reading: Polkadot (DOT) Price Momentum Builds As Open Interest Climbs – Details The network is confident that Boojum and its commitment to innovation and user-first design are the next steps forward for a more secure, scalable, and efficient zkEVM. However, according to the announcement, the migration to the new proof system will only happen after further audits and security reviews are completed. Overall, the move to Boojum is a significant step towards a future of user-powered, decentralized proof generation. The increased performance and reduced hardware requirements will help zkSync and other ZK Stack-based systems achieve greater scalability and accessibility, making digital self-ownership more accessible to everyone. Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com ]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>zkSync, a blockchain network that aims to make digital self-ownership universally accessible, has <a href="https://zksync.mirror.xyz/HJ2Pj45EJkRdt5Pau-ZXwkV2ctPx8qFL19STM5jdYhc" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">announced </a>a major cryptographic upgrade to its proof system. </p>
<p>The upgrade involves transitioning to a new STARK-based proof system called Boojum, which, according to the announcement, offers world-class proving performance and reduces hardware requirements for decentralization.</p>
<h2>zkSync Era Moves To Boojum</h2>
<p>Boojum is a Rust-based arithmetization and constraint library that implements the upgraded version of the ZK circuits for zkSync Era and the ZK Stack. The library offers several compelling properties, including PLONK-style arithmetization.</p>
<p>PLONK-style arithmetization refers to the use of PLONK (Permutation-based Linear-based SNARKs for transparent, universal, and upgradable proofs) as the underlying zero-knowledge proof system. </p>
<p>PLONK is a relatively new proof system that provides several advantages over previous systems, such as Sonic and Halo. Specifically, PLONK is designed to be more transparent, universal, and upgradeable, making it a good choice for zkSync&#8217;s upgraded proof system.</p>

<p>According to the announcement, the move to a STARK-based proof system represents a dramatic performance improvement and will help ensure low latency for finality and support for increased levels of activity on zkSync Era and other ZK Stack-based systems. </p>
<p>The GPU provers used for Boojum require just 16 GB (GygaByte) of RAM, a significant reduction from the hundreds of GBs of RAM needed by prevalent proof systems. </p>
<p>By reducing the amount of RAM required to run the GPU provers from hundreds of GBs to just 16 GB, zkSync will be able to use cheaper machines for increased horizontal scalability. This will likely have a positive impact on the cost of using zkSync.</p>
<p>This means that more people will be able to participate in the network and contribute to its decentralization, ultimately leading to a healthier and more robust network.</p>
<p>Furthermore, to ensure a smooth transition, zkSync is running the new proof system alongside the existing one in a testing phase called mainnet shadow mode. </p>
<p>The network is generating and verifying &#8220;shadow proofs&#8221; for Mainnet blocks to further test and optimize the system with real production data from zkSync Era&#8217;s user activity. This testing is being done off-chain to find edge cases and bugs, and to continue reviewing the implementation.</p>
<p>zkSync is also open-sourcing the Boojum codebase to allow anyone to use the new proofs and verify them using a command-line interface (CLI) tool. </p>

<p>The network is confident that Boojum and its commitment to innovation and user-first design are the next steps forward for a more secure, scalable, and efficient zkEVM. </p>
<p>However, according to the announcement, the migration to the new proof system will only happen after further audits and security reviews are completed.</p>
<p>Overall, the move to Boojum is a significant step towards a future of user-powered, decentralized proof generation. The increased performance and reduced hardware requirements will help zkSync and other ZK Stack-based systems achieve greater scalability and accessibility, making digital self-ownership more accessible to everyone.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/8QtCNAZV/" alt="zkSync" width="1814" height="858"/>
<p>Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/hitesh-choudhary-JNxTZzpHmsI-unsplash-460x259.jpg" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Miners Selling Again, Will Price Crash Again?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-miners-selling-again-will-price-crash-again/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hououin Kyouma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 15:30:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin bearish]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Miner Selling]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin miners]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=542955</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[On-chain data shows that Bitcoin miners may have once again been participating in selling recently, something that could lead to the asset declining. Bitcoin Miner Reserve Has Been Declining In The Last Two Weeks As pointed out by an analyst in a CryptoQuant post, the BTC miner reserve has been observing outflows recently. The &#8220;miner reserve&#8221; here refers to the total amount of Bitcoin that the miners as a whole are holding in their wallets right now. When the value of this metric goes up, it means that these chain validators are transferring coins into their addresses currently. This kind of trend can be a sign that the miners are accumulating, and hence, can be bullish for the price of the asset. On the other hand, the indicator trending down suggests the miners are taking BTC out of their wallets at the moment. Generally, these investors withdraw coins from their reserve for selling-related purposes, so such a trend can have bearish consequences for the cryptocurrency&#8217;s value. In the context of the current discussion, the miner reserve itself isn&#8217;t of interest, but rather its &#8220;rate of change&#8221; (ROC) is. This metric keeps track of the percentage changes in the miner reserve over a specific period. Here, the relevant period is the 14-day one. Related Reading: Bitcoin MVRV At Critical Level: Will A Break Happen? Now, below is a chart that shows the trend in the 14-day ROC of the Bitcoin miner reserves over the last few months: Looks like the value of the metric seems to have been negative in recent days &#124; Source: CryptoQuant As shown in the above graph, the 14-day ROC of the miner reserve had been green last month as Bitcoin had rallied above the $30,000 level. These positive values of the indicator imply that the miner reserve had been rapidly going up. The timing of these positive ROC values could suggest that the accumulation from the miners might have provided support for the surge in the cryptocurrency&#8217;s price. Related Reading: Stablecoin Exchange Deposits Remain Low, What Does It Mean For Bitcoin? In the first week of this month, though, the metric turned negative, implying that the miner reserve started to decline. The miners look to have continued to withdraw coins from their wallets since then, as the indicator&#8217;s value has remained red. The Bitcoin price has been struggling in this period, as it hasn&#8217;t been able to mount up any significant moves. It would appear that this selling from the miners (if the withdrawals are indeed happening for selling) might be one of the factors behind the asset stalling in the past couple of weeks. Since the 14-day ROC of the miner reserve has continued to be at notable red values recently, it&#8217;s possible that these chain validators aren&#8217;t letting up their selling just yet. So far, the price has continued to hold on above the $30,000 level, implying that there may be enough demand in the market to absorb any selling from the miners for now. However, if the miners continue to sell into the near future, it&#8217;s possible the asset may buckle and the price could face a drawdown. BTC Price At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading around $30,000, down 1% in the last week. BTC has been moving sideways recently &#124; Source: BTCUSD on TradingView Featured image from Kanchanara on Unsplash.com, charts from TradingView.com, CryptoQuant.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On-chain data shows that Bitcoin miners may have once again been participating in selling recently, something that could lead to the asset declining.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Miner Reserve Has Been Declining In The Last Two Weeks</h2>
<p>As pointed out by an analyst in a CryptoQuant <a href="https://cryptoquant.com/insights/quicktake/64b522b041768f4ed3151978-Bitcoin-is-under-pressure-from-miners-again" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">post</a>, the BTC miner reserve has been observing outflows recently. The &#8220;<a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-miner-reserve-plunges-bearish-price/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">miner reserve</a>&#8221; here refers to the total amount of Bitcoin that the miners as a whole are holding in their wallets right now.</p>
<p>When the value of this metric goes up, it means that these chain validators are transferring coins into their addresses currently. This kind of trend can be a sign that the miners are accumulating, and hence, can be bullish for the price of the asset.</p>
<p>On the other hand, the indicator trending down suggests the miners are taking BTC out of their wallets at the moment. Generally, these investors withdraw coins from their reserve for selling-related purposes, so such a trend can have bearish consequences for the cryptocurrency&#8217;s value.</p>
<p>In the context of the current discussion, the miner reserve itself isn&#8217;t of interest, but rather its &#8220;rate of change&#8221; (ROC) is. This metric keeps track of the percentage changes in the miner reserve over a specific period. Here, the relevant period is the 14-day one.</p>

<p>Now, below is a chart that shows the trend in the 14-day ROC of the Bitcoin miner reserves over the last few months:</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone aligncenter" src="https://img.cryptoquant.com/35304/quicktake/smjvSB0_4efb40142bc6206cb55ba68e973cbd24b17b4ed0819ff240e22350e3083b56e5.png" alt="Bitcoin miner reserve ROC" width="1192" height="505"/></p>

<p>As shown in the above graph, the 14-day ROC of the miner reserve had been green last month as Bitcoin had rallied above the $30,000 level. These positive values of the indicator imply that the miner reserve had been rapidly going up.</p>
<p>The timing of these positive ROC values could suggest that the accumulation from the miners might have provided support for the surge in the cryptocurrency&#8217;s price.</p>

<p>In the first week of this month, though, the metric turned negative, implying that the miner reserve started to decline. The miners look to have continued to withdraw coins from their wallets since then, as the indicator&#8217;s value has remained red.</p>
<p>The Bitcoin price has been <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/big-bitcoin-move-ahead-bollinger-bands-see-extreme-squeeze/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">struggling</a> in this period, as it hasn&#8217;t been able to mount up any significant moves. It would appear that this selling from the miners (if the withdrawals are indeed happening for selling) might be one of the factors behind the asset stalling in the past couple of weeks.</p>
<p>Since the 14-day ROC of the miner reserve has continued to be at notable red values recently, it&#8217;s possible that these chain validators aren&#8217;t letting up their selling just yet.</p>
<p>So far, the price has continued to hold on above the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/520000-bitcoin-accumulated-at-30000-btc-bull-run/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">$30,000 level</a>, implying that there may be enough demand in the market to absorb any selling from the miners for now. However, if the miners continue to sell into the near future, it&#8217;s possible the asset may buckle and the price could face a drawdown.</p>
<h2>BTC Price</h2>
<p>At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading around $30,000, down 1% in the last week.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium aligncenter" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/ipieXj6U/" alt="Bitcoin Price Chart" width="1534" height="877"/></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/iStock-906872048-460x319.jpg" width="460" height="319" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Stablecoin Exchange Deposits Remain Low, What Does It Mean For Bitcoin?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/stablecoin/stablecoin-exchange-deposits-remain-low-mean-bitcoin/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hououin Kyouma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 14:30:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Stablecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[stablecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stablecoin Exchange Deposits]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stablecoin Exchange Withdrawals]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=542899</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[On-chain data shows the stablecoin exchange deposits have remained low recently. Here&#8217;s what this may mean for Bitcoin. Stablecoin Exchange Deposits Stay Low, While Withdrawals Jump As pointed out by an analyst in a CryptoQuant post, the fact that the stablecoin exchange withdrawals have spiked while deposits have stayed low may be slightly alarming for BTC. There are two indicators of relevance here: the &#8220;stablecoin exchange withdrawing transactions&#8221; and the &#8220;stablecoin exchange depositing transactions.&#8221; As their names already imply, these metrics track the total number of withdrawals and deposit transfers, respectively, that investors of the ERC-20 stables are making right now. Generally, investors seek the safety of these fiat-tied tokens whenever they want to escape the volatility associated with the other assets in the sector. Eventually, when these holders think that the prices are right to jump back into the volatile markets, they swap their stables back for their desired cryptocurrency. These investors usually make use of centralized exchanges for this purpose. So, when the exchange withdrawing transactions are high, it can be a sign that holders are exchanging coins like Bitcoin for stablecoins right now. Related Reading: Here’s What On-Chain Data Reveals About XRP Rally On the other hand, the deposits being high can imply these investors are looking to buy volatile assets using their stables. Naturally, in the former case, Bitcoin and others may feel a bearish effect from the selling, while in the latter case, the prices might see a bullish boost. Now, here is a chart that shows the trend in the stablecoin exchange withdrawing and depositing transactions over the past couple of years: Looks like only one of these two metrics has had a high value recently &#124; Source: CryptoQuant As displayed in the above graph, the stablecoin exchange depositing transactions metric has been relatively low for a while now. This would suggest that there may not be enough demand for converting stables into other assets right now. From the graph, it&#8217;s visible that the last time the indicator spiked was back in March of this year. Following the deposits back then, Bitcoin observed a sharp rebound in its price as the rally saw a revival. The timing of these inflows might mean that it was the buying from these stablecoin holders that had provided the fuel for the BTC surge. Related Reading: Bitcoin MVRV At Critical Level: Will A Break Happen? In the graph, the quant has marked other similar past instances as well. It looks like the BTC price generally observes a rise after stablecoin deposits spike, given that the withdrawals are low at the same time. Recently, however, only the stablecoin withdrawals have observed a spike, implying that investors are taking these tokens away from exchanges, likely to hold onto them for extended periods in self-custody. As there aren&#8217;t any deposits happening to counteract this, the BTC price has been struggling recently. If the trend continues and more stablecoin withdrawals continue to take place, it&#8217;s possible that the cryptocurrency could take a hit in the short term. Bitcoin Price At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading around $30,200, up 1% in the last week. BTC has taken a hit recently &#124; Source: BTCUSD on TradingView Featured image from iStock.com, charts from TradingView.com, CryptoQuant.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On-chain data shows the stablecoin exchange deposits have remained low recently. Here&#8217;s what this may mean for Bitcoin.</p>
<h2>Stablecoin Exchange Deposits Stay Low, While Withdrawals Jump</h2>
<p>As pointed out by an analyst in a CryptoQuant <a href="https://cryptoquant.com/insights/quicktake/64b48531d3b74754036d682e-Retail-Demand-Weakening" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">post</a>, the fact that the stablecoin exchange withdrawals have spiked while deposits have stayed low may be slightly alarming for BTC.</p>
<p>There are two indicators of relevance here: the &#8220;stablecoin exchange withdrawing transactions&#8221; and the &#8220;stablecoin exchange depositing transactions.&#8221; As their names already imply, these metrics track the total number of withdrawals and deposit transfers, respectively, that investors of the ERC-20 stables are making right now.</p>
<p>Generally, investors seek the safety of these <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/stablecoin/stablecoins-market-cap-shows-rise-why-bullish-bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">fiat-tied tokens</a> whenever they want to escape the volatility associated with the other assets in the sector. Eventually, when these holders think that the prices are right to jump back into the volatile markets, they swap their stables back for their desired cryptocurrency.</p>
<p>These investors usually make use of centralized exchanges for this purpose. So, when the exchange withdrawing transactions are high, it can be a sign that holders are exchanging coins like Bitcoin for stablecoins right now.</p>

<p>On the other hand, the deposits being high can imply these investors are looking to buy volatile assets using their stables. Naturally, in the former case, Bitcoin and others may feel a bearish effect from the selling, while in the latter case, the prices might see a <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/exchanges-large-stablecoin-inflows-what-bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">bullish boost</a>.</p>
<p>Now, here is a chart that shows the trend in the stablecoin exchange withdrawing and depositing transactions over the past couple of years:</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone aligncenter" src="https://img.cryptoquant.com/148277/quicktake/QNL53ERXk_3be09f44191d25a3cc63140518c3bd97943329e7792b60a59df90872cbddb6a8.png" alt="Stablecoin Deposits And Bitcoin" width="1280" height="527"/></p>

<p>As displayed in the above graph, the stablecoin exchange depositing transactions metric has been relatively low for a while now. This would suggest that there may not be enough demand for converting stables into other assets right now.</p>
<p>From the graph, it&#8217;s visible that the last time the indicator spiked was back in March of this year. Following the deposits back then, Bitcoin observed a sharp rebound in its price as the rally saw a revival. The timing of these inflows might mean that it was the buying from these stablecoin holders that had provided the fuel for the BTC surge.</p>

<p>In the graph, the quant has marked other similar past instances as well. It looks like the BTC price generally observes a rise after stablecoin deposits spike, given that the withdrawals are low at the same time.</p>
<p>Recently, however, only the stablecoin withdrawals have observed a spike, implying that investors are taking these tokens away from exchanges, likely to hold onto them for extended periods in self-custody.</p>
<p>As there aren&#8217;t any deposits happening to counteract this, the BTC price has been <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-stuck-tight-range-btc-decompress-big-move/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">struggling</a> recently. If the trend continues and more stablecoin withdrawals continue to take place, it&#8217;s possible that the cryptocurrency could take a hit in the short term.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Price</h2>
<p>At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading around $30,200, up 1% in the last week.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium aligncenter" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/pbJn5tNc/" alt="Bitcoin Price Chart" width="1534" height="877"/></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/iStock-1359416693-460x259.jpg" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Celsius Is Selling, More Pain For BNB, LINK, And SNX?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/celsius-is-selling-more-pain-for-bnb-link-and-snx/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dalmas Ngetich]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 13:30:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BNB]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BONE]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[celsius]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FalconX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[OKX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ZRX]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=542947</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Celsius, the bankrupt crypto lender, has started selling its non-Bitcoin and non-Ethereum crypto assets, records on July 17 indicate. According to on-chain data from Lookonchain, Celsius has transferred approximately $23.5 million of various cryptocurrencies, including BNB, ZRX, LINK, BONE, and SNX, to FalconX and OKX, respectively. Different amounts of these tokens were transferred by Celsius, a move that, while it could be positive for creditors, may impact the token valuations of those projects. Celsius Selling Altcoins  Lookonchain revealed that Celsius moved $8.5 million worth of LINK, the native currency of Chainlink, a middleware protocol linking on-chain smart contracts to external but verified data. At the same time, it also moved $7.84 million worth of SNX, the native token of Synthetix, a protocol allowing users to trade derivatives called synths, was transferred. Celsius also went on to move $3 million worth of BNB, the coin behind the sprawling Binance ecosystem, $2.26 million worth of 1INCH, the token aggregator, and $1.9 million worth of ZRX, the token behind one of the first decentralized finance platforms, Ox Protocol. The bankrupt lender also moved $709,678 worth of FTT, the token behind the collapsed FTX exchange, to FalconX. In response, FalconX has started depositing these tokens to Binance for selling. Related Reading: $18 Billion Worth Of Bitcoin Accumulated At $30,200 – BTC Bull Run Incoming? The only token moved to a different exchange was BONE, where Celsius moved $235,000 of the meme token to the popular cryptocurrency exchange, OKX. While OKX caters to retail and institutional investors, FalconX serves institutional investors, offering diverse services, including liquidity provision and risk management. So far, a large tranche of tokens held by Celsius has moved through FalconX. In late June, Judge Martin Glenn of the Southern District of New York allowed Celsius to start converting all their tokens to either Bitcoin or Ethereum, the two currencies that would be allowed to pay back creditors. All conversions were set to begin on July 1. Altcoins Taking A Hit The transfer also comes amid a favorable ruling that saw a US Judge say XRP, one of the major altcoins, is not a security and can be traded like a commodity, just like Bitcoin. However, even though news pumped altcoins, mostly XRP, momentum tapered during the weekend, and most altcoins fell back from last week&#8217;s highs. Related Reading: XRP Whales Ride The Crypto Surge, As Ripple Token Notches 62% Price Spike Among the impacted tokens included BNB, the native currency behind Binance, the world&#8217;s largest ecosystem. The coin currently oscillates within a $30 range as bears dominate price action. From the daily chart, BNB has resistance at $260 and is down over 30% from April 2023 highs.  LINK and SNX are seeing similar price actions, both recording losses on the 24-hour chart. LINK is down 2.97% to be trading at $6.63, while SNX is nursing 3.94% losses, bringing its price to $2.64. Feature image from Canva, chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Celsius, the bankrupt crypto lender, has started selling its non-Bitcoin and non-Ethereum crypto assets, records on July 17 indicate. According to on-chain data from Lookonchain, Celsius has transferred approximately $23.5 million of various cryptocurrencies, including BNB, ZRX, LINK, BONE, and SNX, to FalconX and OKX, respectively. </p>
<p>Different amounts of these tokens were transferred by Celsius, a move that, while it could be positive for creditors, may impact the token valuations of those projects.</p>
<h2>Celsius Selling Altcoins </h2>
<p>Lookonchain <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://twitter.com/lookonchain/status/1680790940842340357?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">revealed</a> that Celsius moved $8.5 million worth of LINK, the native currency of Chainlink, a middleware protocol linking on-chain smart contracts to external but verified data. At the same time, it also moved $7.84 million worth of SNX, the native token of Synthetix, a protocol allowing users to trade derivatives called synths, was transferred. </p>
<p>Celsius also went on to move $3 million worth of BNB, the coin behind the sprawling Binance ecosystem, $2.26 million worth of 1INCH, the token aggregator, and $1.9 million worth of ZRX, the token behind one of the first decentralized finance platforms, Ox Protocol. </p>
<p>The bankrupt lender also moved $709,678 worth of FTT, the token behind the collapsed FTX exchange, to FalconX. In response, FalconX has <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://twitter.com/lookonchain/status/1680793493701292033" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">started</a> depositing these tokens to Binance for selling.</p>

<p>The only token moved to a different exchange was BONE, where Celsius moved $235,000 of the meme token to the popular cryptocurrency exchange, OKX. </p>
<p>While OKX caters to retail and institutional investors, FalconX serves institutional investors, offering diverse services, including liquidity provision and risk management. So far, a large tranche of tokens held by Celsius has moved through FalconX.</p>
<p>In late June, Judge Martin Glenn of the Southern District of New York <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cases.stretto.com/public/x191/11749/PLEADINGS/1174906302380000000027.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">allowed</a> Celsius to start converting all their tokens to either Bitcoin or Ethereum, the two currencies that would be allowed to pay back creditors. All conversions were set to begin on July 1.</p>
<h2>Altcoins Taking A Hit</h2>
<p>The transfer also comes amid a favorable ruling that saw a US Judge say XRP, one of the major altcoins, is not a security and can be traded like a commodity, just like Bitcoin. However, even though news pumped altcoins, mostly XRP, momentum tapered during the weekend, and most altcoins fell back from last week&#8217;s highs.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/xrp-whales-ride-the-crypto-surge-as-ripple-token-notches-62-price-spike/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">XRP Whales Ride The Crypto Surge, As Ripple Token Notches 62% Price Spike</a></p>
<p>Among the impacted tokens included BNB, the native currency behind Binance, the world&#8217;s largest ecosystem. The coin currently oscillates within a $30 range as bears dominate price action. From the daily chart, BNB has resistance at $260 and is down over 30% from April 2023 highs. </p>
<p>LINK and SNX are seeing similar price actions, both recording losses on the 24-hour chart. LINK is down 2.97% to be trading at $6.63, while SNX is nursing 3.94% losses, bringing its price to $2.64.</p>
<a href="https://www.tradingview.com/x/DdcSOCjJ/" rel="nofollow"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/DdcSOCjJ/" alt="BNB price on July 17| Source: BNBUSDT on Binance, TradingView" width="1226" height="595"/></a>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Celsius-BNB-Bitcoin-Ethereum-460x260.jpg" width="460" height="260" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Polkadot (DOT) Price Momentum Builds As Open Interest Climbs &#8211; Details</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/polkadot-dot-price-momentum-builds-as-open-interest-climbs-details/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 12:30:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DOT Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[polkadot]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price action]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=542923</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Polkadot (DOT) has enjoyed a successful three-week period, with bullish investors maintaining their position at the forefront despite fluctuations in the market. In addition, the recent legal victory of Ripple against the US Securities and Exchange Commission triggered a positive response across the entire market, benefiting not only significant cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin (BTC) and Ethereum (ETH) but also altcoins in general. Nevertheless, it is essential to note that Bitcoin and Ether experienced notable downward corrections in the short term after they attempted to surge higher last week. As a result, there might be some selling pressure soon for these leading cryptocurrencies, which could potentially harm the price of DOT. Given this scenario, how can DOT bulls regain control and overcome a potential market correction? DOT Price Update: Minor Dip, But Open Interest Improves The latest update on DOT&#8217;s price from CoinGecko shows that it currently stands at $5.30. While the cryptocurrency experienced a slight decline of 1.7% over the past 24 hours, it still managed to maintain a seven-day rally of 4.8%. However, a closer analysis of the DOT price report shows some concerning indicators. Source: Coingecko According to a report, by mid-June, the Open Interest had significantly diminished compared to its April levels, signaling a bearish sentiment. However, as the month advanced, a reversal in this trend emerged. Related Reading: Shiba Inu Encounters Familiar Resistance, Prompting Concerns About Bull Run Source: Coinglass/AMBCrypto The declining Open Interest in April, which refers to the number of open contracts in the market, served as an early indicator that hinted at the forthcoming bearish sentiment. As traders and investors reduced their positions and interest waned, it reflected a growing caution and skepticism in the market. This downward trend in Open Interest implied a decrease in market participation and a potential lack of confidence in the prevailing bullish trends. Related Reading: USTC Surprises With Nearly 60% Rally – What’s Going On? However, as June unfolded, a gradual and encouraging shift in market sentiment began to take shape. Market participants started to exhibit a more optimistic outlook, which was reflected in the increasing Open Interest. This surge in OI suggested renewed interest and activity, as traders and investors re-entered the market and established new positions. DOT market cap currently at $6.3 billion. Chart: TradingView.com Polkadot Potential Rebound Tied To Bitcoin&#8217;s Resilience On the other hand, if BTC can stabilize or even climb back above $31,000, DOT will likely follow suit. The correlation between BTC and altcoins like DOT has been a well-established trend in the cryptocurrency market. BTC, the dominant cryptocurrency and a significant influencer of market sentiment, often sets the tone for the overall market direction. If Bitcoin regains stability and exhibits a bullish move, it tends to ignite a favorable view among traders and investors. This positive sentiment, in turn, could extend to altcoins like DOT. DOT seven-day price movement. Source: CoinMarketCap Therefore, for DOT bulls looking to reclaim their yard and counteract the potential negative impact of a market correction, monitoring BTC&#8217;s performance closely becomes crucial. If Bitcoin can stabilize or, ideally, recover above the significant resistance level of $31k, it would likely create a favorable environment for DOT to regain momentum. (This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk). Featured image from VOA News]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Polkadot (DOT) has enjoyed a successful three-week period, with bullish investors maintaining their position at the forefront despite fluctuations in the market. </p>
<p>In addition, the recent legal victory of Ripple against the US Securities and Exchange Commission triggered a positive response across the entire market, benefiting not only significant cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin (BTC) and Ethereum (ETH) but also altcoins in general.</p>
<p>Nevertheless, it is essential to note that Bitcoin and Ether experienced notable downward corrections in the short term after they attempted to surge higher last week. As a result, there might be some selling pressure soon for these leading cryptocurrencies, which could potentially harm the price of DOT.</p>
<p>Given this scenario, how can DOT bulls regain control and overcome a potential market correction?</p>
<h2><strong>DOT Price Update: Minor Dip, But Open Interest Improves</strong></h2>
<p>The latest update on <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/polkadot" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">DOT&#8217;s price from CoinGecko</a> shows that it currently stands at $5.30. While the cryptocurrency experienced a slight decline of 1.7% over the past 24 hours, it still managed to maintain a seven-day rally of 4.8%. However, a closer analysis of the DOT price report shows some concerning indicators.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-542936" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-106.png" alt="" width="1139" height="62" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-106.png 1139w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-106-460x25.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-106-860x47.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-106-768x42.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-106-750x41.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 1139px) 100vw, 1139px"/></p>

<p><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://ambcrypto.com/polkadot-on-the-verge-of-initiating-another-rally-as/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">According to a report</a>, by mid-June, the Open Interest had significantly diminished compared to its April levels, signaling a bearish sentiment. However, as the month advanced, a reversal in this trend emerged.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/shiba-inu-encounters-familiar-resistance/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Shiba Inu Encounters Familiar Resistance, Prompting Concerns About Bull Run</a></p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-542951 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-109-860x259.png" alt="" width="860" height="259" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-109-860x259.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-109-460x139.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-109-768x232.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-109-750x226.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-109-1140x344.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-109.png 1453w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/></p>

<p>The declining Open Interest in April, which refers to the number of open contracts in the market, served as an early indicator that hinted at the forthcoming bearish sentiment.</p>
<p>As traders and investors reduced their positions and interest waned, it reflected a growing caution and skepticism in the market. This downward trend in Open Interest implied a decrease in market participation and a potential lack of confidence in the prevailing bullish trends.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/ustc-surprises-with-nearly-60-rally-whats-going-on/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">USTC Surprises With Nearly 60% Rally – What’s Going On?</a></p>
<p>However, as June unfolded, a gradual and encouraging shift in market sentiment began to take shape. Market participants started to exhibit a more optimistic outlook, which was reflected in the increasing Open Interest. This surge in OI suggested renewed interest and activity, as traders and investors re-entered the market and established new positions.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/r0mjpf8c/" width="2475" height="1187"/></p>

<h2><strong>Polkadot Potential Rebound Tied To Bitcoin&#8217;s Resilience</strong></h2>
<p>On the other hand, if <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bitcoin-dips-over-weekend-other-013056846.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">BTC can stabilize</a> or even climb back above $31,000, DOT will likely follow suit. The correlation between BTC and altcoins like DOT has been a well-established trend in the cryptocurrency market.</p>
<p>BTC, the dominant cryptocurrency and a significant influencer of market sentiment, often sets the tone for the overall market direction. If Bitcoin regains stability and exhibits a bullish move, it tends to ignite a favorable view among traders and investors. This positive sentiment, in turn, could extend to altcoins like DOT.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-542940 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-107-860x378.png" alt="" width="860" height="378" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-107-860x378.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-107-460x202.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-107-768x338.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-107-750x330.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-107.png 1034w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/></p>

<p>Therefore, for DOT bulls looking to reclaim their yard and counteract the potential negative impact of a market correction, monitoring BTC&#8217;s performance closely becomes crucial. If Bitcoin can stabilize or, ideally, recover above the significant resistance level of $31k, it would likely create a favorable environment for DOT to regain momentum.</p>
<p><em>(This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk).</em></p>
<p><em>Featured image from VOA News</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-108-460x310.png" width="460" height="310" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Big Bitcoin Move Ahead: Bollinger Bands See Extreme Squeeze</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/big-bitcoin-move-ahead-bollinger-bands-see-extreme-squeeze/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jake Simmons]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 11:30:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bollinger bands]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=542925</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Since the Bitcoin price reached a new yearly high of $31,840 last week, only to invalidate the bullish breakout within a few hours and fall towards $30,000, there has been a strange tranquility in the market. Already since June 23, BTC has been in the trading range between $29,800 and $31,300, with every breakout attempt to the upside and downside having failed within a very short period of time. However, one of the most prominent technical indicators, the Bollinger Bands, predict that this calm may soon be over. Created by the esteemed trader John Bollinger, these bands provide invaluable insights into market volatility and potential price levels. Bollinger Bands Predict Big Move For Bitcoin The Bollinger Bands consist of three distinct lines on a price chart: the middle band, the upper band, and the lower band. The middle band is a simple moving average (SMA) that represents the average price over a specified period. The upper and lower bands are derived from the middle band, with the upper band usually set two standard deviations above the SMA, and the lower band set two standard deviations below it. Related Reading: $18 Billion Worth Of Bitcoin Accumulated At $30,200 – BTC Bull Run Incoming? The primary purpose of the Bollinger Bands is to measure market volatility. When the price of an asset experiences significant fluctuations, the bands widen, indicating increased volatility. Conversely, during periods of reduced price movement, the bands contract, indicating lower volatility. This contraction is commonly referred to as a &#8220;squeeze,&#8221; where the upper and lower bands come closer together, forming a narrowing price channel. When the Bollinger Bands squeeze, the potential for a significant price movement looms. The squeeze suggests that the market is in a state of temporary equilibrium, akin to a coiled spring ready to release its stored energy. The direction of the breakout determines whether it&#8217;s a bullish or bearish signal. Up Or Down? Glassnode, a respected on-chain data provider, highlighted today the current state of the Bitcoin market, noting a remarkably low volatility environment. The 20-day Bollinger Bands are experiencing an extreme squeeze, with a mere 4.2% price range separating the upper and lower bands. This suggests that Bitcoin is currently in a period of limited price movement, “making this the quietest Bitcoin market since the lull in early January.” As Bitcoin investors may remember, the Bollinger Bands squeeze in January marked the end of a lengthy downtrend. After the FTX collapse, the BTC market was in a state of shock paralysis, which was ultimately resolved by Bollinger Bands squeeze, leading to a 42% price increase in 26 days. Related Reading: Perfect Storm: Why Bitcoin &#38; Crypto Are Poised For A Dramatic Recovery The Bollinger Bands&#8217; squeeze, combined with diminishing trading volumes, creates a scenario of mounting pressure in the Bitcoin market. As trading volume declines, the potential energy stored in this coiled spring intensifies. According to the analysts at CryptoCon, the bullish scenario is the one to be favored at the moment. &#8220;When Bitcoin volatility gets low in a bear market, it&#8217;s very bearish. When volatility gets low in a bull market, it&#8217;s insanely bullish,&#8221; the analysts say. As Bitcoin is unanimously seen to be at the start of a new bull market, a strong move to the upside could be in store. Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Since the Bitcoin price reached a new yearly high of $31,840 last week, only to invalidate the bullish breakout within a few hours and fall towards $30,000, there has been a strange tranquility in the market. Already since June 23, BTC has been in the trading range between $29,800 and $31,300, with every breakout attempt to the upside and downside having failed within a very short period of time.</p>
<p>However, one of the most prominent technical indicators, the Bollinger Bands, predict that this calm may soon be over. Created by the esteemed trader John Bollinger, these bands provide invaluable insights into market volatility and potential price levels.</p>
<h2>Bollinger Bands Predict Big Move For Bitcoin</h2>
<p>The Bollinger Bands consist of three distinct lines on a price chart: the middle band, the upper band, and the lower band. The middle band is a simple moving average (SMA) that represents the average price over a specified period. The upper and lower bands are derived from the middle band, with the upper band usually set two standard deviations above the SMA, and the lower band set two standard deviations below it.</p>

<p>The primary purpose of the Bollinger Bands is to measure market volatility. When the price of an asset experiences significant fluctuations, the bands widen, indicating increased volatility. Conversely, during periods of reduced price movement, the bands contract, indicating lower volatility. This contraction is commonly referred to as a &#8220;squeeze,&#8221; where the upper and lower bands come closer together, forming a narrowing price channel.</p>
<p>When the Bollinger Bands squeeze, the potential for a significant price movement looms. The squeeze suggests that the market is in a state of temporary equilibrium, akin to a coiled spring ready to release its stored energy. The direction of the breakout determines whether it&#8217;s a bullish or bearish signal.</p>
<h2>Up Or Down?</h2>
<p>Glassnode, a respected on-chain data provider, highlighted today the current state of the Bitcoin market, <a href="https://twitter.com/glassnode/status/1680875530244042752" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">noting</a> a remarkably low volatility environment. The 20-day Bollinger Bands are experiencing an extreme squeeze, with a mere 4.2% price range separating the upper and lower bands. This suggests that Bitcoin is currently in a period of limited price movement, “making this the quietest Bitcoin market since the lull in early January.”</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-542937 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/F1OrNtyX0AMroPu-scaled.jpg" alt="Bitcoin Bollinger Bands" width="2560" height="1475" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/F1OrNtyX0AMroPu-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/F1OrNtyX0AMroPu-460x265.jpg 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/F1OrNtyX0AMroPu-860x496.jpg 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/F1OrNtyX0AMroPu-768x443.jpg 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/F1OrNtyX0AMroPu-1536x885.jpg 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/F1OrNtyX0AMroPu-2048x1180.jpg 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/F1OrNtyX0AMroPu-750x432.jpg 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/F1OrNtyX0AMroPu-1140x657.jpg 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px"/>
<p>As Bitcoin investors may remember, the Bollinger Bands squeeze in January marked the end of a lengthy downtrend. After the FTX collapse, the BTC market was in a state of shock paralysis, which was ultimately resolved by Bollinger Bands squeeze, leading to a 42% price increase in 26 days.</p>

<p>The Bollinger Bands&#8217; squeeze, combined with diminishing trading volumes, creates a scenario of mounting pressure in the Bitcoin market. As trading volume declines, the potential energy stored in this coiled spring intensifies.</p>
<p>According to the analysts at CryptoCon, the bullish scenario is the one to be <a href="https://twitter.com/CryptoCon_/status/1677692883627831296" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">favored</a> at the moment. &#8220;When Bitcoin volatility gets low in a bear market, it&#8217;s very bearish. When volatility gets low in a bull market, it&#8217;s insanely bullish,&#8221; the analysts say. As Bitcoin is unanimously seen to be at the start of a new bull market, a strong move to the upside could be in store.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-542939 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD_2023-07-17_12-53-24.png" alt="Bitcoin price" width="3628" height="1672" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD_2023-07-17_12-53-24.png 3628w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD_2023-07-17_12-53-24-460x212.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD_2023-07-17_12-53-24-860x396.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD_2023-07-17_12-53-24-768x354.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD_2023-07-17_12-53-24-1536x708.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD_2023-07-17_12-53-24-2048x944.png 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD_2023-07-17_12-53-24-750x346.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD_2023-07-17_12-53-24-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 3628px) 100vw, 3628px"/>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/iStock-1305769484-1-460x272.jpg" width="460" height="272" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>XRP Whales Ride The Crypto Surge, As Ripple Token Notches 62% Price Spike</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/xrp-whales-ride-the-crypto-surge-as-ripple-token-notches-62-price-spike/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 10:30:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price action]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=542912</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[XRP is now witnessing a surge in network activity as prominent holders of the cryptocurrency make their moves.  The latest findings from Lookonchain, a renowned data analytics firm, shed light on the purchase and sale patterns of XRP whales on the Binance Smart Chain (BSC), signaling a potential rise in selling activity within the market. Ripple&#8217;s triumph over the SEC has undoubtedly injected a fresh wave of confidence into the XRP community. With the regulatory cloud dissipating, investors and holders are now eager to capitalize on the newfound clarity surrounding the token&#8217;s status. As a result, the actions of these notable whales have become a focal point of interest for market observers and enthusiasts alike. Related Reading: USTC Surprises With Nearly 60% Rally – What’s Going On? XRP Whales&#8217; Purchasing Habits Revealed: Insight From Lookonchain Based on analysis by Lookonchain, the transactional behavior of four influential whales has come to light. Each of these whales demonstrates distinct patterns in their purchasing habits, shedding light on their strategies within the crypto market. 1/ Did whales sell $XRP as the price of $XRP rises? Let&#8217;s check the top 4 whales of $XRP on the #BSC.👇 pic.twitter.com/cwkXIcK6s2 — Lookonchain (@lookonchain) July 15, 2023 One of the whales, known as &#8220;0xf522,&#8221; has amassed a staggering 25 million XRP, equivalent to $18 million, between April 22 and November 24, 2022. Interestingly, this particular whale has refrained from selling any of their holdings thus far.  Source: Lookonchain Another notable participant, identified as &#8220;0x513d,&#8221; acquired 10 million units of the coin at an average price of $0.45 per token. Following the recent surge in XRP&#8217;s value, this whale has deposited 5.4 million XRP, worth around $4.3 million, into Binance. Related Reading: Shiba Inu Encounters Familiar Resistance, Prompting Concerns About Bull Run By taking advantage of the recent price rally, &#8220;0x513d&#8221; demonstrates a more proactive approach, capitalizing on the upward momentum of XRP. Source: Coingecko At present, Coingecko displays XRP&#8217;s price at $0.7412, reflecting a 2.9% rally within the past 24 hours alone. Over the course of the previous seven days, XRP has experienced a remarkable surge of 58.6%.  Ex-Ripple Chief Affirms Company&#8217;s Limited Market Influence Amid XRP&#8217;s Surge Meanwhile, Matt Hamilton, the former Director of Developer Relations at Ripple, clarified on Twitter that Ripple&#8217;s influence on the market is relatively constrained when considering the global daily sales volume of XRP. Ripple are the single largest holder of XRP with something like 48B XRP. Most of it is held in escrow contracts that release each month. Ripple sell a small portion of that and put the rest back in new escrow contracts. — Matt Hamilton (@HammerToe) July 16, 2023 This assertion holds true even in light of the recent surge in XRP&#8217;s value following the resolution of the Ripple-SEC case.  He stressed that the price movements of XRP are primarily governed by market forces and the performance of Bitcoin (BTC), underscoring the interplay between these factors in shaping the cryptocurrency&#8217;s trajectory. XRP market cap closing in to the $39 billion level. Chart: TradingView.com Hamilton explicitly stated that Ripple does not have authority over either XRP or the XRP Ledger (XRPL), ensuring any misunderstandings are clarified. In order to stress this notion further, he proposed the potential scenario where Ripple&#8217;s complete XRP holdings could be eradicated if the XRP community deemed it appropriate. (This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk). Featured image from Blockchain News]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>XRP is now witnessing a surge in network activity as prominent holders of the cryptocurrency make their moves. </p>
<p>The latest findings from Lookonchain, a renowned data analytics firm, shed light on the purchase and <a href="https://u.today/xrp-whales-in-spotlight-as-cryptocurrency-prices-soar" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">sale patterns of XRP whales</a> on the Binance Smart Chain (BSC), signaling a potential rise in selling activity within the market.</p>
<p>Ripple&#8217;s triumph over the SEC has undoubtedly injected a fresh wave of confidence into the XRP community. With the regulatory cloud dissipating, investors and holders are now eager to capitalize on the newfound clarity surrounding the token&#8217;s status. </p>
<p>As a result, the actions of these notable whales have become a focal point of interest for market observers and enthusiasts alike.</p>

<h2><strong>XRP Whales&#8217; Purchasing Habits Revealed: Insight From Lookonchain</strong></h2>
<p>Based on analysis by <a href="https://twitter.com/lookonchain/status/1680240044261670913" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Lookonchain</a>, the transactional behavior of four influential whales has come to light. Each of these whales demonstrates distinct patterns in their purchasing habits, shedding light on their strategies within the crypto market.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">1/ Did whales sell <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24XRP&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$XRP</a> as the price of <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24XRP&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$XRP</a> rises?</p>
<p>Let&#8217;s check the top 4 whales of <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24XRP&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$XRP</a> on the <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/BSC?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#BSC</a>.<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f447.png" alt="👇" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> <a href="https://t.co/cwkXIcK6s2" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/cwkXIcK6s2</a></p>
<p>— Lookonchain (@lookonchain) <a href="https://twitter.com/lookonchain/status/1680240044261670913?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">July 15, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p>One of the whales, known as &#8220;0xf522,&#8221; has amassed a staggering 25 million XRP, equivalent to $18 million, between April 22 and November 24, 2022. Interestingly, this particular whale has refrained from selling any of their holdings thus far. </p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-542920 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-104-860x443.png" alt="" width="860" height="443" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-104-860x443.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-104-460x237.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-104-768x396.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-104-1536x791.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-104-750x386.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-104-1140x587.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-104.png 1598w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/></p>

<p>Another notable participant, identified as &#8220;0x513d,&#8221; acquired 10 million units of the coin at an average price of $0.45 per token. Following the recent surge in XRP&#8217;s value, this whale has deposited 5.4 million XRP, worth around $4.3 million, into Binance.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/shiba-inu-encounters-familiar-resistance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Shiba Inu Encounters Familiar Resistance, Prompting Concerns About Bull Run</a></p>
<p>By taking advantage of the recent price rally, &#8220;0x513d&#8221; demonstrates a more proactive approach, capitalizing on the upward momentum of XRP.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-542917" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-103.png" alt="" width="1156" height="59" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-103.png 1156w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-103-460x23.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-103-860x44.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-103-768x39.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-103-1140x58.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-103-750x38.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 1156px) 100vw, 1156px"/></p>

<p>At present, <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/xrp" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Coingecko</a> displays XRP&#8217;s price at $0.7412, reflecting a 2.9% rally within the past 24 hours alone. Over the course of the previous seven days, XRP has experienced a remarkable surge of 58.6%. </p>
<h2><strong>Ex-Ripple Chief Affirms Company&#8217;s Limited Market Influence Amid XRP&#8217;s Surge</strong></h2>
<p>Meanwhile, Matt Hamilton, the former Director of Developer Relations at Ripple, <a href="https://twitter.com/HammerToe/status/1680418001500110848" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">clarified on Twitter</a> that Ripple&#8217;s influence on the market is relatively constrained when considering the global daily sales volume of XRP. </p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Ripple are the single largest holder of XRP with something like 48B XRP. Most of it is held in escrow contracts that release each month. Ripple sell a small portion of that and put the rest back in new escrow contracts.</p>
<p>— Matt Hamilton (@HammerToe) <a href="https://twitter.com/HammerToe/status/1680418001500110848?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">July 16, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p>This assertion holds true even in light of the recent surge in XRP&#8217;s value following the resolution of the Ripple-SEC case. </p>
<p>He stressed that the price movements of XRP are primarily governed by market forces and the performance of Bitcoin (BTC), underscoring the interplay between these factors in shaping the cryptocurrency&#8217;s trajectory.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/OwgYMs1w/" width="2475" height="1187"/></p>

<p>Hamilton explicitly stated that Ripple does not have authority over either XRP or the XRP Ledger (XRPL), ensuring any misunderstandings are clarified. In order to stress this notion further, he proposed the potential scenario where Ripple&#8217;s complete XRP holdings could be eradicated if the XRP community deemed it appropriate.</p>
<p><em>(This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk).</em></p>
<p><em>Featured image from Blockchain News</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-105-460x241.png" width="460" height="241" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>$18 Billion Worth Of Bitcoin Accumulated At $30,200 &#8211; BTC Bull Run Incoming?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/520000-bitcoin-accumulated-at-30000-btc-bull-run/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dalmas Ngetich]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 09:19:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin bulls]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ERPD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NVT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=542858</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A record 592,000 Bitcoin, or roughly $17.8 billion, was accumulated when the coin was trading at $30,200, recent Glassnode data indicates. At this accumulation rate, suggesting possible demand, more entities bought more coins at the second fastest pace in the network&#8217;s history. This record was only broken when 637,000 BTC were bought at an average price of $16,500. 592,000 Bitcoin Bought At $30,200 The spike in Bitcoin accumulated at this price point preceded the decision by a United States court to rule that XRP, an altcoin issued from the XRP Ledger (XRPL), is a commodity, just like Bitcoin. The ruling on Friday, July 14, was received positively by the crypto community and temporarily lifted prices, sustaining Bitcoin above the psychological $30,000 mark. According to Glassnode, the Bitcoin Entity-Adjusted Economic Ratio Per Day (ERPD) is a metric designed to assess economic activity within the network, considering the number of entities participating. This metric is calculated by dividing the Network Value to Transactions (NVT) ratio by the entity-adjusted on-chain volume. In on-chain analysis, the NVT ratio represents the relationship between the market capitalization and the recorded on-chain trading volumes at a specific price point. A higher NVT ratio indicates a greater value than recorded trading volumes. Related Reading: Synthetix (SNX) Up By 35% In Anticipation Of New Decentralized Exchange While the NVT reading can be useful, it can also be misleading if the entities, or clustered addresses, involved in transactions are not accounted for. To correct this error, the ERPD integrates addresses involved at that price point, used in taking account of the market cap. This way, it can be easy to gauge the entities and total coins involved. Shifting Sentiment? The surge in Bitcoin ERPD development will also likely impact altcoins. Considering its liquidity and support across the board, Bitcoin sets the tone for other altcoins in crypto. Its performance and transactions can gauge market-wide sentiment, which might, in turn, change how altcoins are perceived in the current market conditions. Related Reading: Stablecoin TrueUSD To Be Fully Controlled By Asian Owner Still, some commentators on Twitter were unsure if the metric was a positive development or a position for further price crashes. One believes that most such transactions are conducted by &#8220;paper hands&#8221; who buy Bitcoin when the price increases and are set to sell at any moment of negative news. The spike in ERPD is also ahead of the Bitcoin halving event in 2024, which, reading on historical performances, may impact prices positively, even triggering a bull run. After halving, miners would receive fewer coins, releasing even fewer for circulation, a supply shock that may support prices. Feature image from Canva, chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A record 592,000 Bitcoin, or roughly $17.8 billion, was accumulated when the coin was trading at $30,200, recent Glassnode <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://twitter.com/glassnode/status/1678357739905400832" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">data</a> indicates. At this accumulation rate, suggesting possible demand, more entities bought more coins at the second fastest pace in the network&#8217;s history. This record was only broken when 637,000 BTC were bought at an average price of $16,500.</p>
<h2><strong>592,000 Bitcoin Bought At $30,200</strong></h2>
<p>The spike in Bitcoin accumulated at this price point preceded the decision by a United States court to rule that XRP, an altcoin issued from the XRP Ledger (XRPL), is a commodity, just like Bitcoin. The ruling on Friday, July 14, was received positively by the crypto community and temporarily lifted prices, sustaining Bitcoin above the psychological $30,000 mark.</p>
<a href="https://www.tradingview.com/x/1oocVkq3/" rel="nofollow"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/1oocVkq3/" alt="Bitcoin price on July 16| Source: BTCUSDT on Binance, TradingView" width="1226" height="595"/></a>
<p>According to Glassnode, the Bitcoin Entity-Adjusted Economic Ratio Per Day (ERPD) is a metric designed to assess economic activity within the network, considering the number of entities participating. This metric is calculated by dividing the Network Value to Transactions (NVT) ratio by the entity-adjusted on-chain volume. </p>
<p>In on-chain analysis, the NVT ratio represents the relationship between the market capitalization and the recorded on-chain trading volumes at a specific price point. A higher NVT ratio indicates a greater value than recorded trading volumes.</p>

<p>While the NVT reading can be useful, it can also be misleading if the entities, or clustered addresses, involved in transactions are not accounted for. To correct this error, the ERPD integrates addresses involved at that price point, used in taking account of the market cap. This way, it can be easy to gauge the entities and total coins involved.</p>
<h2><strong>Shifting Sentiment?</strong></h2>
<p>The surge in Bitcoin ERPD development will also likely impact altcoins. Considering its liquidity and support across the board, Bitcoin sets the tone for other altcoins in crypto. Its performance and transactions can gauge market-wide sentiment, which might, in turn, change how altcoins are perceived in the current market conditions.</p>

<p>Still, some commentators on Twitter were unsure if the metric was a positive development or a position for further price crashes. One <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://twitter.com/HamzaAa68799909/status/1680230591458066432" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">believes</a> that most such transactions are conducted by &#8220;paper hands&#8221; who buy Bitcoin when the price increases and are set to sell at any moment of negative news.</p>
<p>The spike in ERPD is also ahead of the Bitcoin halving event in 2024, which, reading on historical performances, may impact prices positively, even triggering a bull run. After halving, miners would receive fewer coins, releasing even fewer for circulation, a supply shock that may support prices.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Crypto-news-Template25-460x260.jpg" width="460" height="260" />	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
