<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
>

<channel>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.newsbtc.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<description>Bitcoin &#38; cryptocurrency news today, price &#38; technical analysis</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 03:00:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Ethereum Price Signals Recovery But 100 SMA Is The Key</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-recovery-1875/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 03:00:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=530833</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Ethereum price is slowly moving higher from $1,840 against the US Dollar. ETH is still facing strong resistance near the $1,875 level and the 100 hourly SMA. Ethereum is currently consolidating losses above the $1,820 support zone. The price is trading below $1,875 and the 100-hourly Simple Moving Average. There was a break above a major bearish trend line with resistance near $1,850 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD (data feed via Kraken). The pair could struggle to clear the $1,875 and $1,880 resistance levels. Ethereum Price Starts Consolidation Ethereum’s price remained in a bearish zone the $1,875 support zone. ETH tested the $1,810 zone and recently started a consolidation phase, similar to Bitcoin. A low is formed near $1,812 and the price is slowly moving higher in a range. It traded above the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the swing move from the $1,935 high to the $1,812 low. Besides, there was a break above a major bearish trend line with resistance near $1,850 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD. However, Ether is still trading below $1,875 and the 100-hourly Simple Moving Average. Immediate resistance is near the $1,860 level. The next resistance sits near $1,875 or the 100-hourly Simple Moving Average or the 50% Fib retracement level of the swing move from the $1,935 high to the $1,812 low. Source: ETHUSD on TradingView.com The next key resistance might be near the $1,920 level. A close above the $1,920 resistance zone could start a decent increase in Ethereum and the price might rise toward the $1,975 resistance. Any more gains might send the price toward the $1,950 resistance. Fresh Decline in ETH? If Ethereum fails to clear the $1,875 resistance, it could start another decline. Initial support on the downside is near the $1,820 level or the recent low. The next major support is near the $1,800 zone. If there is a downside break and a close below $1,800, the bears could gain strength. In the stated case, the price might drop toward the $1,720 support zone. Any more losses may perhaps take the price toward the $1,650 level in the near term. Technical Indicators Hourly MACD – The MACD for ETH/USD is now losing momentum in the bearish zone. Hourly RSI &#8211; The RSI for ETH/USD is still below the 50 level. Major Support Level – $1,800 Major Resistance Level – $1,875]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>Ethereum price is slowly moving higher from $1,840 against the US Dollar. ETH is still facing strong resistance near the $1,875 level and the 100 hourly SMA.</em></p>
<ul>
<li>Ethereum is currently consolidating losses above the $1,820 support zone.</li>
<li>The price is trading below $1,875 and the 100-hourly Simple Moving Average.</li>
<li>There was a break above a major bearish trend line with resistance near $1,850 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD (data feed via Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could struggle to clear the $1,875 and $1,880 resistance levels.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Ethereum Price Starts Consolidation</h2>
<p>Ethereum’s price remained in a bearish zone the $1,875 support zone. ETH tested the $1,810 zone and recently started a consolidation phase, similar to <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-consolidates-27k/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a>.</p>
<p>A low is formed near $1,812 and the price is slowly moving higher in a range. It traded above the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the swing move from the $1,935 high to the $1,812 low. Besides, there was a break above a major bearish trend line with resistance near $1,850 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD.</p>
<p>However, Ether is still trading below $1,875 and the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-takes-drop-to-1650/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener">100-hourly Simple Moving Average</a>. Immediate resistance is near the $1,860 level. The next resistance sits near $1,875 or the 100-hourly Simple Moving Average or the 50% Fib retracement level of the swing move from the $1,935 high to the $1,812 low.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ethereum-7.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-530834" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ethereum-7.png" alt="Ethereum Price" width="1834" height="845" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ethereum-7.png 1834w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ethereum-7-460x212.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ethereum-7-860x396.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ethereum-7-768x354.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ethereum-7-1536x708.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ethereum-7-750x346.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ethereum-7-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1834px) 100vw, 1834px" /></a></p>
<p>Source: <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/ETHUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">ETHUSD on TradingView.com</a></p>
<p>The next key resistance might be near the $1,920 level. A close above the $1,920 resistance zone could start a decent increase in Ethereum and the price might rise toward the $1,975 resistance. Any more gains might send the price toward the $1,950 resistance.</p>
<h2>Fresh Decline in ETH?</h2>
<p>If Ethereum fails to clear the $1,875 resistance, it could start another decline. Initial support on the downside is near the $1,820 level or the recent low.</p>
<p>The next major support is near the $1,800 zone. If there is a downside break and a close below $1,800, the bears could gain strength. In the stated case, the price might drop toward the $1,720 support zone. Any more losses may perhaps take the price toward the $1,650 level in the near term.</p>
<p>Technical Indicators</p>
<p>Hourly MACD<strong> – </strong>The MACD for ETH/USD is now losing momentum in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>Hourly RSI<strong> &#8211; </strong>The RSI for ETH/USD is still below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Level – $1,800</p>
<p>Major Resistance Level – $1,875</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/iStock-1329407939-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Price Consolidates Losses, This Resistance Might Trigger Another Drop</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-consolidates-27k/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 02:29:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xbtusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=530829</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin price is consolidating losses below $28,200. BTC could start another decline unless there is a clear move above the $28,500 resistance. Bitcoin is consolidating losses and trading above the $27,000 support. The price is trading below $28,200 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average. There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $28,040 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Kraken). The pair could continue to move down if stays below $28,200 and $28,500. Bitcoin Price Stable Above $27K Bitcoin price remained in a bearish zone below the $28,200 support zone. BTC tested the $27,200 support zone and now seems to be consolidating above the $27,400 level. A low is formed near $27,282 and the price is now slowly moving higher. It is consolidating near the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the swing move from the $29,129 high to the $27,282 low. However, it is still trading below $28,200 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average. Bitcoin price is now facing resistance near the $28,000 zone. Besides, there is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $28,040 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair. The next major resistance is near the $28,200 level or the 50% Fib retracement level of the swing move from the $29,129 high to the $27,282 low. The main resistance is now forming near the $28,500 level and the 100 hourly Simple moving average. Source: BTCUSD on TradingView.com A close above the $28,500 resistance might spark a decent increase. The next key resistance is near $29,125, above which the price might climb toward the $29,500 resistance. Any more gains could open the doors for a decent move toward the $30,000 resistance. More Losses in BTC? If Bitcoin’s price fails to clear the $28,200 resistance, it could continue to move down. Immediate support on the downside is near the $27,250 level. The next major support is near the $27,000 zone, below which the price might accelerate losses and drop to the $26,000 support zone. Any more losses might take Bitcoin toward the $25,500 level in the near term. Technical indicators: Hourly MACD – The MACD is now losing pace in the bearish zone. Hourly RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BTC/USD is now above the 50 level. Major Support Levels – $27,250, followed by $27,000. Major Resistance Levels – $28,050, $28,200, and $28,500.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>Bitcoin price is consolidating losses below $28,200. BTC could start another decline unless there is a clear move above the $28,500 resistance.</em></p>
<ul>
<li>Bitcoin is consolidating losses and trading above the $27,000 support.</li>
<li>The price is trading below $28,200 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average.</li>
<li>There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $28,040 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could continue to move down if stays below $28,200 and $28,500.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Bitcoin Price Stable Above $27K</h2>
<p>Bitcoin price remained in a <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-bears-gains-strength-28k/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener">bearish zone</a> below the $28,200 support zone. BTC tested the $27,200 support zone and now seems to be consolidating above the $27,400 level.</p>
<p>A low is formed near $27,282 and the price is now slowly moving higher. It is consolidating near the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the swing move from the $29,129 high to the $27,282 low. However, it is still trading below $28,200 and the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-rejection-30k/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener">100 hourly Simple moving average</a>.</p>
<p>Bitcoin price is now facing resistance near the $28,000 zone. Besides, there is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $28,040 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair.</p>
<p>The next major resistance is near the $28,200 level or the 50% Fib retracement level of the swing move from the $29,129 high to the $27,282 low. The main resistance is now forming near the $28,500 level and the 100 hourly Simple moving average.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-7.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-530830" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-7.png" alt="Bitcoin Price" width="1834" height="845" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-7.png 1834w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-7-460x212.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-7-860x396.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-7-768x354.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-7-1536x708.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-7-750x346.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-7-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1834px) 100vw, 1834px" /></a></p>
<p>Source: <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BTCUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">BTCUSD on TradingView.com</a></p>
<p>A close above the $28,500 resistance might spark a decent increase. The next key resistance is near $29,125, above which the price might climb toward the $29,500 resistance. Any more gains could open the doors for a decent move toward the $30,000 resistance.</p>
<h2>More Losses in BTC?</h2>
<p>If Bitcoin’s price fails to clear the $28,200 resistance, it could continue to move down. Immediate support on the downside is near the $27,250 level.</p>
<p>The next major support is near the $27,000 zone, below which the price might accelerate losses and drop to the $26,000 support zone. Any more losses might take Bitcoin toward the $25,500 level in the near term.</p>
<p>Technical indicators:</p>
<p>Hourly MACD – The MACD is now losing pace in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>Hourly RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BTC/USD is now above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Levels – $27,250, followed by $27,000.</p>
<p>Major Resistance Levels – $28,050, $28,200, and $28,500.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/shutterstock_608669048-460x306.jpg" width="460" height="306" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>PEPE Whale Who Earned $14.5M Turns To Turbo, Is This The Next Big Thing?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/pepe-whale-who-earned-14-5m-turns-to-turbo-is-this-the-next-big-thing/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dalmas Ngetich]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 00:00:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[meme token]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PEPE]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[TURBO]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=530823</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A whale recently transferred $14.5 million of PEPE to Binance and is now buying TURBO, Lookonchain data on May 9 shows. Pepe coin (PEPE) is a meme token and one of the top-performing assets after rallying by over 10x in recent days pushing its market capitalization to over $1 billion. PEPE&#8217;s performance and trading activity saw it flip mainstream coins, including Bitcoin. Whale Exiting PEPE Trackers on May 9 now indicate that the PEPE whale is actively accumulating TURBO, doubling down on the token. Because of the address&#8217; past success, traders are closely watching his actions, with some speculating that TURBO might be the next &#8220;big thing&#8221; after PEPE&#8217;s success. Related Reading: PEPE Price Prediction: Can Pepe Coin Flip Dogecoin? On-chain records show that between April 24 and 27, the whale bought 4.23 trillion PEPE from 422 ETH and 200K USDC. On May 5, the whale transferred all tokens to Binance, a cryptocurrency exchange, possibly earning a profit of approximately $14.5 million. This giant whale who bought 4.23T $PEPE ($15.6M) with 422 $ETH ($871K) and 200K $USDC deposited all $PEPE to #Binance 30 mins ago. His average buying cost is $0.0000002535, and the profit is ~$14.5M now! He may sell after opening trading, watching out for the price change.⚠️ pic.twitter.com/7UoNYG9PJb &#8212; Lookonchain (@lookonchain) May 5, 2023 By exiting at PEPE peaks, observers suspect the whale could be an experienced trader or entity. Nonetheless, though PEPE surged in the first part of last week, the meme token&#8217;s price has been cooling off days after listing on Binance&#8217;s Innovation Zone and derivatives exchange. PEPE is ranked 57 on the market cap leaderboard, according to CoinMarketCap data. The meme token has gained significant traction at this valuation, attracting interest from speculators and traders. Focus on TURBO With PEPE looking fragile, dropping 55% from May&#8217;s high, the whale seems to have identified an opportunity in TURBO. Related Reading: PEPE, FLOKI, SHIB: Insiders Spill The Beans On Meme Coin Investing The whale bought 1.38 billion TURBO with $977,000, worth $1.1M at the time of writing. The last time the whale bought TURBO was on May 8. A smart whale who earned ~$14.5M on $PEPE has been buying $TURBO since May 3. He bought a total of 1.38B $TURBO ($1.1M currently) with $977K, the average buying price is $0.0007055. The last time he bought $TURBO was 7 hours ago. pic.twitter.com/eawQWEivKq &#8212; Lookonchain (@lookonchain) May 9, 2023 The Turbo meme coin is created entirely using artificial intelligence (AI) with Chat GPT-4, the generative AI protocol, taking charge, building the project from scratch and issuing the token. Fueled by the current rage of AI projects and platforms, the TURBO community is expanding, further propping prices. As of writing, TURBO is up 45% in the last 24 hours, with trading volumes exceeding $140 million. The founder has meticulously recorded the entire process from the project&#8217;s documentation while strictly adhering to the AI&#8217;s guidance. Still, it is not clear whether TURBO will replicate PEPE&#8217;s success and soar to record highs. Bitcoin prices are relatively lower at spot rates, which could be a hurdle for the token&#8217;s price action. Despite recent double-digit gains, TURBO has resisted selling pressure and separated from the broader market. However, the success of meme tokens relies heavily on hype and FOMO-driven demand, as they generally lack any practical utility. Consequently, their prices tend to collapse rapidly once the hype subsides. Feature Image From Canva, Chart From TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A whale recently transferred $14.5 million of PEPE to Binance and is now buying TURBO, Lookonchain data on May 9 shows.</p>
<p>Pepe coin (PEPE) is a meme token and one of the top-performing assets after rallying by over 10x in recent days pushing its market capitalization to over $1 billion. PEPE&#8217;s performance and trading activity saw it flip mainstream coins, including Bitcoin.</p>
<h2>Whale Exiting PEPE</h2>
<p>Trackers on May 9 now indicate that the PEPE whale is actively accumulating TURBO, doubling down on the token.</p>
<p>Because of the address&#8217; past success, traders are closely watching his actions, with some speculating that TURBO might be the next &#8220;big thing&#8221; after PEPE&#8217;s success.</p>

<p>On-chain records show that between April 24 and 27, the whale bought 4.23 trillion PEPE from 422 ETH and 200K USDC.</p>
<p>On May 5, the whale transferred all tokens to Binance, a cryptocurrency exchange, possibly earning a profit of approximately $14.5 million.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">This giant whale who bought 4.23T <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24PEPE&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$PEPE</a> ($15.6M) with 422 <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24ETH&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$ETH</a> ($871K) and 200K <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24USDC&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$USDC</a> deposited all <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24PEPE&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$PEPE</a> to <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Binance?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#Binance</a> 30 mins ago.</p>
<p>His average buying cost is $0.0000002535, and the profit is ~$14.5M now!</p>
<p>He may sell after opening trading, watching out for the price change.<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/26a0.png" alt="⚠" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> <a href="https://t.co/7UoNYG9PJb" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/7UoNYG9PJb</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Lookonchain (@lookonchain) <a href="https://twitter.com/lookonchain/status/1654546602449862656?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">May 5, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p></p>
<p>By exiting at PEPE peaks, observers suspect the whale could be an experienced trader or entity.</p>
<p>Nonetheless, though PEPE surged in the first part of last week, the meme token&#8217;s price has been cooling off days after listing on Binance&#8217;s Innovation Zone and derivatives exchange.</p>
<p>PEPE is ranked 57 on the market cap leaderboard, according to CoinMarketCap <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/pepe/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">data</a>. The meme token has gained significant traction at this valuation, attracting interest from speculators and traders.</p>
<h2>Focus on TURBO</h2>
<p>With PEPE looking fragile, dropping 55% from May&#8217;s high, the whale seems to have identified an opportunity in TURBO.</p>

<p>The whale bought 1.38 billion TURBO with $977,000, worth $1.1M at the time of writing. The last time the whale bought TURBO was on May 8.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">A smart whale who earned ~$14.5M on <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24PEPE&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$PEPE</a> has been buying <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24TURBO&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$TURBO</a> since May 3.</p>
<p>He bought a total of 1.38B <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24TURBO&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$TURBO</a> ($1.1M currently) with $977K, the average buying price is $0.0007055.</p>
<p>The last time he bought <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24TURBO&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$TURBO</a> was 7 hours ago. <a href="https://t.co/eawQWEivKq" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/eawQWEivKq</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Lookonchain (@lookonchain) <a href="https://twitter.com/lookonchain/status/1655787862951088128?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">May 9, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p></p>
<p>The <a href="http://turbotoadtoken.com/" rel="nofollow">Turbo</a> meme coin is created entirely using artificial intelligence (AI) with Chat GPT-4, the generative AI protocol, taking charge, building the project from scratch and issuing the token.</p>
<p>Fueled by the current rage of AI projects and platforms, the TURBO community is expanding, further propping prices.</p>
<p>As of writing, TURBO is <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/turbo/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">up</a> 45% in the last 24 hours, with trading volumes exceeding $140 million. The founder has meticulously recorded the entire process from the project&#8217;s documentation while strictly adhering to the AI&#8217;s guidance.</p>
<p>Still, it is not clear whether TURBO will replicate PEPE&#8217;s success and soar to record highs. Bitcoin prices are relatively lower at spot rates, which could be a hurdle for the token&#8217;s price action.</p>
<p>Despite recent double-digit gains, TURBO has resisted selling pressure and separated from the broader market. However, the success of meme tokens relies heavily on hype and FOMO-driven demand, as they generally lack any practical utility. Consequently, their prices tend to collapse rapidly once the hype subsides.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/PEPE-Coin-1-460x260.jpg" width="460" height="260" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Matrixport Report: Here’s What Happens To Bitcoin If Inflation Continues To Fall</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/matrixport-report-heres-what-happens-to-bitcoin-if-inflation-continues-to-fall/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Best Owie]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 23:00:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CPI]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[inflation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=530652</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[As Bitcoin became a more mainstream asset, its correlation with the stock market rose which meant it has been impacted by world events to a higher degree than it did before. This is evident with the asset’s reaction to the rising inflation and the Fed’s continuous hiking of interest rates. However, there seems to be a reversal in this trend as inflation is starting to ease. This means the Fed could change its stance on interest rates soon. If this happens, what does it mean for Bitcoin? Looking Toward The CPI Data Release In the Matrixport Daily Insights report released on Tuesday, Head of Research Markus Thielen outlines a bullish case for Bitcoin as inflation slows down. He starts out by explaining the expectation that inflation is going to fall further which would be a good thing for risk assets such as BTC. Related Reading: PEPE Market Cap Crosses $1 Billion As Gemini Listing Rumors Spread The inflation Matrixport forecast for the year 2023 puts it below 2% before year’s end, which would be an over 50% reduction. Such low CPIs would no doubt see the Fed reverse interest rates, dropping them significantly. In fact, the report projects interest rate cuts of up to 100 bps. “Hedge Funds remain massively hedged equities. The CFTC data for S&#38;P500 positions is equivalent to levels only seen during the 2008 financial crisis and the European Debt crisis in 2011,” the report said. “While this does not necessarily mean that Hedge Funds are short, it indicates that hedge funds have sold those contracts and will have to cover them at some point. This buying will squeeze prices higher.” Matrixport predicts sub-2% inflation by end of year &#124; Source: Matrixport If inflation were to fall as low as predicted, then the price of BTC would rally toward the $40,000 level before the end of 2023. As for the current Bitcoin price and how to play the market, the report further adds that “A stop loss of $27,000(-3%) could offer great risk/reward with the macro data being released soon,” pointing to the CPI data being released on Wednesday, May 10. Bitcoin Sellers Hold Market Hostage Ahead Of CPI Release With less than one day left to the CPI data release for May, Bitcoin sellers are currently dominating the market. As a result, the digital asset fell to the mid-$27,000 level where it currently trending. This is also understandable as investors tend to move their holdings into stables leading up to important events like this as it can trigger high volatility in the market. Related Reading: PEPE, WOJAK, TURBO Take A Nosedive As Meme Coin Euphoria Dies Down This decline in price has driven BTC below its 20-day simple moving average (SMA) and puts it dangerously close to its 50-day moving average. If the digital asset were to fall below the latter, it could be disastrous as it would solidify the bears’ hold on the market, further driving down the price. BTC price returns to mid-$27,000 &#124; Source: BTCUSD on TradingView.com Further downside from here could see BTC return to $26,000 where the next significant support level lies. Thus, it is important that the CPI data comes out with a lower inflation rate and the Fed moves from hawkish to dovish. Otherwise, risk assets such as BTC and the total cryptocurrency market could see a rapid decline. Follow Best Owie on Twitter for market insights, updates, and the occasional funny tweet… Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="p2">As Bitcoin became a more mainstream asset, its correlation with the stock market rose which meant it has been impacted by world events to a higher degree than it did before. This is evident with the asset’s reaction to the rising inflation and the Fed’s continuous hiking of interest rates.</p>
<p class="p2">However, there seems to be a reversal in this trend as inflation is starting to ease. This means the Fed could change its stance on interest rates soon. If this happens, what does it mean for Bitcoin?</p>
<h2 class="p2">Looking Toward The CPI Data Release</h2>
<p class="p2">In the Matrixport Daily Insights report released on Tuesday, Head of Research Markus Thielen outlines a bullish case for Bitcoin as inflation slows down. He starts out by explaining the expectation that inflation is going to fall further which would be a good thing for risk assets such as BTC.</p>

<p class="p2">The inflation Matrixport forecast for the year 2023 puts it below 2% before year’s end, which would be an over 50% reduction. Such low CPIs would no doubt see the Fed reverse interest rates, dropping them significantly. In fact, the report projects interest rate cuts of up to 100 bps.</p>
<p class="p2">“Hedge Funds remain massively hedged equities. The CFTC data for S&amp;P500 positions is equivalent to levels only seen during the 2008 financial crisis and the European Debt crisis in 2011,” the report said. “While this does not necessarily mean that Hedge Funds are short, it indicates that hedge funds have sold those contracts and will have to cover them at some point. This buying will squeeze prices higher.”</p>
<p class="p2"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-530653 aligncenter" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Screenshot-2023-05-09-at-12.06.21-460x197.png" alt="Matrixport bitcoin report" width="460" height="197" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Screenshot-2023-05-09-at-12.06.21-460x197.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Screenshot-2023-05-09-at-12.06.21-860x369.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Screenshot-2023-05-09-at-12.06.21-768x330.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Screenshot-2023-05-09-at-12.06.21-750x322.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Screenshot-2023-05-09-at-12.06.21.png 1118w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px" /></p>

<p class="p2">If inflation were to fall as low as predicted, then the price of BTC would rally toward the $40,000 level before the end of 2023.</p>
<p class="p2">As for the current Bitcoin price and how to play the market, the report further adds that “A stop loss of $27,000(-3%) could offer great risk/reward with the macro data being released soon,” pointing to the CPI data being released on Wednesday, May 10.</p>
<h2 class="p2">Bitcoin Sellers Hold Market Hostage Ahead Of CPI Release</h2>
<p class="p2">With less than one day left to the CPI data release for May, Bitcoin sellers are currently dominating the market. As a result, the digital asset fell to the mid-$27,000 level where it currently trending. This is also understandable as investors tend to move their holdings into stables leading up to important events like this as it can trigger high volatility in the market.</p>

<p class="p2">This decline in price has driven BTC below its 20-day simple moving average (SMA) and puts it dangerously close to its 50-day moving average. If the digital asset were to fall below the latter, it could be disastrous as it would solidify the bears’ hold on the market, further driving down the price.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/0z9mNACX/" alt="Bitcoin price chart from TradingView.com" width="2854" height="1724" /></p>

<p class="p2">Further downside from here could see BTC return to $26,000 where the next significant support level lies. Thus, it is important that the CPI data comes out with a lower inflation rate and the Fed moves from hawkish to dovish. Otherwise, risk assets such as BTC and the total cryptocurrency market could see a rapid decline.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/iStock-186295282-460x260.jpg" width="460" height="260" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cardano DeFi Steals The Show, Outperforms The Market With Explosive Transaction Growth</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/cardano/cardano-defi-steals-the-show-outperforms-the-market-with-explosive-transaction-growth/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 22:30:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cardano]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADAUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano (ADA) Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DeFi]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=530817</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Despite the recent market dip, Cardano&#8217;s decentralized finance (DeFi) ecosystem has seen a significant surge in activity, with transactions on Cardano DeFi apps soaring to 250,000 per epoch from 160,000 transactions during the previous epoch. This remarkable 56% increase in transaction volume has been attributed to the launch of new DeFi protocols on the network and the active community of developers and users driving innovation for the protocol.  Related Reading: Only 6% Left Until Cardano Hits Max Capacity, What This Means For ADA Cardano DeFi Challenges Market Slump According to Cardano Ambassador Yevhen, the latest hype around meme coins like Snek and Pepeblue has also contributed to the transaction surge. Snek is a crypto asset based on memes of snakes with interior monologue captioning, while Pepeblue is a recently introduced crypto asset on the Cardano network and in its metaverse. Yevhen believes this increased interest in meme coins has brought new users to the network and boosted transaction volume. Aside from the hype around meme coins, several crypto exchanges and liquidity protocols on the Cardano blockchain have reported significant increases in activity in recent weeks. Per Yevhen’s analysis, these include Sundaeswap ($SUNDAE), Minswap ($MIN), MuesliSwap ($MILK), Wingriders ($WRT), and Liqwid Finance ($LQ). These protocols have been lauded for their user-friendly interfaces, low transaction fees, and high liquidity. Sundaeswap, for example, is a decentralized exchange that allows users to trade Cardano-based tokens with low slippage and high liquidity. The platform has seen a surge in activity thanks to its user-friendly interface and low transaction fees. Minswap, on the other hand, is a decentralized exchange that allows users to trade Cardano-based tokens with zero fees. Furthermore, Liqwid Finance, a decentralized lending protocol on the Cardano network, has already surpassed $50 million in total value locked in just a few months since its launch. This platform allows users to lend and borrow Cardano-based tokens with low fees and high liquidity. The recent surge in Cardano DeFi activity has been attributed to various factors, including the launch of new DeFi protocols, the active community of developers and users on the network, and the hype around meme coins.  ADA Follows The Market Trend The recent dip in ADA&#8217;s price can be attributed to the broader market downturn affecting the cryptocurrency industry. Over the past few days, several major cryptocurrencies, including Bitcoin and Ethereum, have experienced significant price declines, dragging down the entire market. The price of Cardano&#8217;s native cryptocurrency, ADA, has experienced a significant dip in the past 24 hours, reaching the $0.3586 level. This marks a 40-day low for the cryptocurrency, with the last time it was at this level being April 28th. However, ADA has managed to stall a further decline and has reported a slight gain of 0.9% in the last 24 hours, trading at $0.3630 The decline in Cardano&#8217;s native token, ADA, is further compounded by the fact that it has lost its 50 and 200-day moving averages (MA) since the onset of its decline on April 28th. In the event of further drops, ADA must maintain two critical support levels to prevent a potential decline to the $0.2 territories, which it has not visited since January 2023. These levels are the $0.3441 level and the $0.3034 floor. Related Reading: Litecoin (LTC) Falls Under $80, Is It Time To Buy Now? Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Despite the recent market dip, Cardano&#8217;s decentralized finance (DeFi) ecosystem has seen a significant surge in activity, with transactions on Cardano DeFi apps soaring to 250,000 per epoch from 160,000 transactions during the previous epoch. This remarkable 56% increase in transaction volume has been attributed to the launch of new DeFi protocols on the network and the active community of developers and users driving innovation for the protocol. </p>

<h2><b>Cardano DeFi Challenges Market Slump</b></h2>
<p><a href="https://twitter.com/yevhen_dedotfi/status/1655679171853537284?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">According </a>to Cardano Ambassador Yevhen, the latest hype around meme coins like Snek and Pepeblue has also contributed to the transaction surge. Snek is a crypto asset based on memes of snakes with interior monologue captioning, while Pepeblue is a recently introduced crypto asset on the Cardano network and in its metaverse. Yevhen believes this increased interest in meme coins has brought new users to the network and boosted transaction volume.</p>
<p>Aside from the hype around meme coins, several crypto exchanges and liquidity protocols on the Cardano blockchain have reported significant increases in activity in recent weeks. Per Yevhen’s analysis, these include Sundaeswap ($SUNDAE), Minswap ($MIN), MuesliSwap ($MILK), Wingriders ($WRT), and Liqwid Finance ($LQ). These protocols have been lauded for their user-friendly interfaces, low transaction fees, and high liquidity.</p>
<p>Sundaeswap, for example, is a decentralized exchange that allows users to trade Cardano-based tokens with low slippage and high liquidity. The platform has seen a surge in activity thanks to its user-friendly interface and low transaction fees. Minswap, on the other hand, is a decentralized exchange that allows users to trade Cardano-based tokens with zero fees.</p>
<p>Furthermore, Liqwid Finance, a decentralized lending protocol on the Cardano network, has already surpassed $50 million in total value locked in just a few months since its launch. This platform allows users to lend and borrow Cardano-based tokens with low fees and high liquidity.</p>
<p>The recent surge in Cardano DeFi activity has been attributed to various factors, including the launch of new DeFi protocols, the active community of developers and users on the network, and the hype around meme coins. </p>
<b>ADA Follows The Market Trend</b>
<p>The recent dip in ADA&#8217;s price can be attributed to the broader market downturn affecting the cryptocurrency industry. Over the past few days, several major cryptocurrencies, including Bitcoin and Ethereum, have experienced significant price declines, dragging down the entire market.</p>
<p>The price of Cardano&#8217;s native cryptocurrency, ADA, has experienced a significant dip in the past 24 hours, reaching the $0.3586 level. This marks a 40-day low for the cryptocurrency, with the last time it was at this level being April 28th. However, ADA has managed to stall a further decline and has reported a slight gain of 0.9% in the last 24 hours, trading at $0.3630</p>
<p>The decline in Cardano&#8217;s native token, ADA, is further compounded by the fact that it has lost its 50 and 200-day moving averages (MA) since the onset of its decline on April 28th. In the event of further drops, ADA must maintain two critical support levels to prevent a potential decline to the $0.2 territories, which it has not visited since January 2023. These levels are the $0.3441 level and the $0.3034 floor.</p>





<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/W0s4N0cm/" alt="Cardano " width="1814" height="858" />
<p>Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com </p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/michael-fortsch-6CiqXsgGaM-unsplash-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Whale Suffers $500,000 Loss As PEPE Price Plummets</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/crypto-whale-suffers-500000-loss-as-pepe-price-plummets/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Edyme]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 22:00:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[memecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PEPE]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[whales]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=530772</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Unsurprisingly, the recently hyped frog-themed meme coin PEPE is now beginning to suffer a price decline, impacting late investors negatively. According to LookOnChain’s recent report, a large investor or whale who purchased a large amount of the token amid its rally has now suffered a huge loss.  This loss follows the memecoin ongoing downtrend after the recent rally, which seemed to be never-ending. PEPE experienced a significant spike during its rally, up by more than 3,000% from its all-time low. This spike resulted from the growing interest and hype for the frog-themed token.  Taking A Huge Hit On May 7, popular on-chain analyst LookOnChain reported that a notable investor of PEPE, who bought approximately 962.3 billion of $PEPE worth $2.46M at the time, had lost $541,000. According to LookOnChain, the whale bought the token “with 70 $WBTC ($2.07M) and 470 $ETH ($937,000) at an average buying price of $0.000003122.” This purchase was during PEPE’s hype when the token traded in the green. At the time of writing, the token currently trades at $0.00000188, bringing the whale’s total loss to roughly $607,000. Related Reading: PEPE Token Futures Cast Gloom For Investors As Prices Plummet By 45% Notably, while some whales recorded losses in their PEPE investment, other investors made huge profits from their purchases. As recently reported by NewsBTC, a PEPE wallet holding 2.5 trillion tokens reportedly turned $27 into over $4 million. It&#8217;s crucial to recognize that some investors made a profit while others experienced losses with PEPE. Latecomers suffered losses, while early adopters who bought the token before its widespread popularity profited. Aftermath Of The PEPE Rally It is no more news PEPE recorded huge gains in the past week due to significant hype from the crypto community. Despite the token not having any potential utility, the frog-themed memecoin enjoyed a remarkable spike pushing it to appear among the top 100 cryptocurrencies in the crypto market.  Related Reading: Discovering The Next PEPE And SHIB: Whales To Keep Track Of Aside from the hype, several other factors, including listing on major crypto exchanges such as Binance, contributed to the token’s massive surge. However, following the spike and the dying down of the hype of the token, PEPE has begun to see a major retracement. The asset is currently down 54% from its peak and has declined by over 10% in the past 24 hours. PEPE’s market cap has recorded a huge loss of $5.2 billion in the past 4 days. Meanwhile, its trading volume has seen a significant surge indicating a violent sell-off from investors. Featured image from Unsplash, Chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Unsurprisingly, the recently hyped frog-themed meme coin PEPE is now beginning to suffer a price decline, impacting late investors negatively. According to LookOnChain’s recent <a href="https://twitter.com/lookonchain/status/1655083589967683584?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">report</a>, a large investor or whale who purchased a large amount of the token amid its rally has now suffered a huge loss. </p>
<p>This loss follows the memecoin ongoing downtrend after the recent rally, which seemed to be never-ending. PEPE <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/altcoin/discovering-the-next-pepe-and-shib-whales-to-keep-track-of/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">experienced a significant</a> spike during its rally, up by more than 3,000% from its all-time low. This spike resulted from the growing interest and hype for the frog-themed token. </p>
<h2>Taking A Huge Hit</h2>
<p>On May 7, popular on-chain analyst LookOnChain reported that a notable investor of PEPE, who bought approximately 962.3 billion of $PEPE worth $2.46M at the time, had lost $541,000. According to LookOnChain, the whale bought the token “with 70 $WBTC ($2.07M) and 470 $ETH ($937,000) at an average buying price of $0.000003122.”</p>
<p>This purchase was during PEPE’s hype when the token traded in the green. At the time of writing, the token currently trades at $0.00000188, bringing the whale’s total loss to roughly $607,000.</p>

<p>Notably, while some whales recorded losses in their PEPE investment, other investors made huge profits from their purchases. As recently reported by NewsBTC, a PEPE wallet holding 2.5 trillion tokens reportedly turned <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/pepe/from-27-to-4m-pepe-wallet-unable-to-sell-unstoppable-rally/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">$27 into over $4 million.</a></p>
<p>It&#8217;s crucial to recognize that some investors made a profit while others experienced losses with PEPE. Latecomers suffered losses, while early adopters who bought the token before its widespread popularity profited.</p>
<h2>Aftermath Of The PEPE Rally</h2>
<p>It is no more news PEPE recorded huge gains in the past week due to significant hype from the crypto community. Despite the token not having any potential utility, the frog-themed memecoin enjoyed a remarkable spike pushing it to appear among the top 100 cryptocurrencies in the crypto market. </p>

<p>Aside from the hype, several other factors, including listing<a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/altcoin/breaking-binance-lists-pepe-and-floki-in-innovation-zone/"> on major crypto exchanges</a> such as Binance, contributed to the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/pepe-shoots-up-708/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">token’s massive surge</a>. However, following the spike and the dying down of the hype of the token, PEPE has begun to see a major retracement.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/rB6ao7WP/" alt="PEPE price chart on TradingView" width="2768" height="1556" />
<p>The asset is currently down <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/crypto/meme-coin-pepe-hits-new-all-time-high/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">54% from its peak</a> and has declined by over 10% in the past 24 hours. PEPE’s market cap has recorded a huge loss of $5.2 billion in the past 4 days. Meanwhile, its trading volume has seen a significant surge indicating a violent sell-off from investors.</p>
<p>Featured image from Unsplash, Chart from TradingView</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Optimism-460x259.jpeg" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>South Korean Authorities Investigate Lawmaker Over Alleged Crypto Transfers</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/crypto/south-korean-authorities-investigate-lawmaker-over-alleged-crypto-transfers/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mike D.]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 21:00:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Democratic Party of Korea]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[South Korea]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=530755</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[There&#8217;s a rumor of a conflict of interest around the South Korean opposition lawmaker Kim Nam-Kuk over crypto transactions.  The growing domestic outrage alleged that Kim liquidated over $4 million worth of crypto assets before the lawmakers would enforce the Financial Action Task Force Travel Rule. Lawmaker Moves Crypto Funds Before Implementation Of Law A report from the news outlet, The Korea Times disclosed the joint investigation by the Korean authorities and the country&#8217;s Financial Intelligence Unit (FIU) on Kim.  The investigation is based on the allegation that Kim withdrew 800,000 WEMIX tokens between February and March 2022.  Between January and February 2022, Kim of the Democratic Party of Korea reportedly held 6 billion Won in his digital wallet.  However, the lawmaker was accused of transferring all his crypto holdings before the authorities could implement the Travel Rule on March 25, 2022.  Related Reading: Bitcoin Bull Run In Jeopardy As Parabolic SAR Flips Bearish On Daily Chart It is important to note that regulations mandate all crypto service providers to disclose the personal information of investors involved in trades exceeding a value of 1 million Won in digital assets. The FIU of the Financial Services Commission received the report concerning Kim&#8217;s withdrawals. The South Korean regulator classified them as suspicious transactions and reported them to the prosecutor&#8217;s office accordingly. On his part, Kim Nam-Kuk denied cashing out his digital holdings, stating that he only moved the funds to another crypto exchange. Also, he maintained that he was not obligated to report such transactions by law. The cybercitizens have condemned the act of the lawmaker who had positioned himself as a &#8220;poor&#8221; politician in the past. The Mayor of Daegu, Hong Joon-Pyo, commented that Kim should resign from his political position. The person expressed disappointment in the legislator&#8217;s actions, describing it as a serious moral problem. The Mayor recalled that Kim was among those that delayed crypto taxation through legislative voting. This suggests that the lawmaker used his legislative position to cover personal gains in digital assets. Government To Fix Loopholes In Disclosure For South Korean Public Officials The Korean authorities are still investigating Kim&#8217;s alleged crypto holdings. According to The Korea Herald, the outcome of the investigation will play a vital role in deciding if public officials must disclose their crypto assets. Related Reading: Bitcoin To Drop Further? Whales Show Signs Of Dumping Such a move will mandate all public officials to include digital asset holdings in their asset reports or disclosures. Crypto investment has been a heated subject in South Korea and other parts of the world. In the United States plans, some members of Congress want to pass a bill that will bar members from investing in digital assets and stocks. The Senators and representatives must disclose such investments in their assets reports, but nothing prevents them from trading them.  These investments have created controversy as many believe U.S. Congress members can benefit from insider trading without facing legal consequences. Just last week, a Democratic Congresswoman sold shares from the First Republic Bank just before financial behemoth JP Morgan acquired it. Similarly, the Taiwanese government is considering extending disclosure reports of public officials to digital assets. Taiwon’s Ministry of Justice cited that the rule will ensure public servants disclose their crypto holdings.  Featured image from Pexels and chart from Tradingview]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>There&#8217;s a rumor of a conflict of interest around the South Korean opposition lawmaker Kim Nam-Kuk over crypto transactions. </p>
<p>The growing domestic outrage alleged that Kim liquidated over $4 million worth of crypto assets before the lawmakers would enforce the Financial Action Task Force Travel Rule.</p>
<h2>Lawmaker Moves Crypto Funds Before Implementation Of Law</h2>
<p>A report from the news outlet, <a href="https://www.koreatimes.co.kr/www/biz/2023/05/816_350573.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">The Korea Times</a> disclosed the joint investigation by the Korean authorities and the country&#8217;s Financial Intelligence Unit (FIU) on Kim. </p>
<p>The investigation is based on the allegation that Kim withdrew 800,000 WEMIX tokens between February and March 2022. </p>
<p>Between January and February 2022, Kim of the Democratic Party of Korea reportedly held 6 billion Won in his digital wallet. </p>
<p>However, the lawmaker was accused of transferring all his crypto holdings before the authorities could implement the Travel Rule on March 25, 2022. </p>

<p>It is important to note that regulations mandate all crypto service providers to disclose the personal information of investors involved in trades exceeding a value of 1 million Won in digital assets.</p>
<p>The FIU of the Financial Services Commission received the report concerning Kim&#8217;s withdrawals. The South Korean regulator classified them as suspicious transactions and reported them to the prosecutor&#8217;s office accordingly.</p>
<p>On his part, Kim Nam-Kuk denied cashing out his digital holdings, stating that he only moved the funds to another crypto exchange. Also, he maintained that he was not obligated to report such transactions by law.</p>
<p>The cybercitizens have condemned the act of the lawmaker who had positioned himself as a &#8220;poor&#8221; politician in the past. The Mayor of Daegu, Hong Joon-Pyo, commented that Kim should resign from his political position. The person expressed disappointment in the legislator&#8217;s actions, describing it as a serious moral problem.</p>
<p>The Mayor recalled that Kim was among those that delayed crypto taxation through legislative voting. This suggests that the lawmaker used his legislative position to cover personal gains in digital assets.</p>
<h2>Government To Fix Loopholes In Disclosure For South Korean Public Officials</h2>
<p>The Korean authorities are still investigating Kim&#8217;s alleged crypto holdings. According to <a href="https://www.koreaherald.com/view.php?ud=20230507000195" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">The Korea Herald</a>, the outcome of the investigation will play a vital role in deciding if public officials must disclose their crypto assets.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-drop-further-whales-signs-of-dumping/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin To Drop Further? Whales Show Signs Of Dumping</a></p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-530762 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/WEMIXUSDT_2023-05-09_20-04-10-860x371.png" alt="South Korean Authorities Investigate Lawmaker Over Alleged Crypto Transfers" width="860" height="371" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/WEMIXUSDT_2023-05-09_20-04-10-860x371.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/WEMIXUSDT_2023-05-09_20-04-10-460x198.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/WEMIXUSDT_2023-05-09_20-04-10-768x331.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/WEMIXUSDT_2023-05-09_20-04-10-1536x662.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/WEMIXUSDT_2023-05-09_20-04-10-750x323.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/WEMIXUSDT_2023-05-09_20-04-10-1140x491.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/WEMIXUSDT_2023-05-09_20-04-10.png 1713w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" />
<p>Such a move will mandate all public officials to include digital asset holdings in their asset reports or disclosures. Crypto investment has been a heated subject in South Korea and other parts of the world. </p>
<p>In the <a href="https://fitzpatrick.house.gov/2023/5/fitzpatrick-ocasio-cortez-gaetz-krishnamoorthi-introduce-the-bipartisan-restoring-faith-in-government-act" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">United States plans</a>, some members of Congress want to pass a bill that will bar members from investing in digital assets and stocks. The Senators and representatives must disclose such investments in their assets reports, but nothing prevents them from trading them. </p>
<p>These investments have created controversy as many believe U.S. Congress members can benefit from insider trading without facing legal consequences. Just last week, a Democratic Congresswoman <a href="https://dailycaller.com/2023/05/01/lois-frankel-stock-trades-disclosures-show-jpmorgan-first-republic/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">sold shares</a> from the First Republic Bank just before financial behemoth JP Morgan acquired it.</p>
<p>Similarly, the <a href="https://www.aac.moj.gov.tw/media/311187/%E6%B8%85%E5%BB%89%E5%9F%B7%E6%94%BF%E5%9C%8B%E9%9A%9B%E8%82%AF%E5%AE%9A-%E8%99%9B%E6%93%AC%E9%80%9A%E8%B2%A8%E8%AA%A0%E5%AF%A6%E7%94%B3%E5%A0%B1.pdf?mediaDL=true" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Taiwanese government is considering</a> extending disclosure reports of public officials to digital assets. Taiwon’s Ministry of Justice cited that the rule will ensure public servants disclose their crypto holdings. </p>
<p>Featured image from Pexels and chart from Tradingview</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/handcuffs-g39590b7a2_1280-460x291.jpg" width="460" height="291" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Bull Run: Higher Time Frames Still Bullish Despite Correction</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-bull-run-higher-time-frames-still-bullish-despite-correction/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 20:00:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=530775</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC), the largest cryptocurrency in the market, has been trading sideways since experiencing a drop of over 5% on Monday. Despite this decline, Bitcoin has found support at $27,200, preventing further drops that could potentially jeopardize the next bull run of the leading cryptocurrency. However, many investors wonder whether Bitcoin will show any signs of recovery shortly. Will the cryptocurrency market see a resurgence of bullish sentiment, or will the current bearish trend continue? Related Reading: AVAX Enters The Green Zone After Losing Gains As Bulls Gain Momentum Bitcoin&#8217;s 70-Day Correction, Is May 19th The End Date? Jesse Olson, an experienced cryptocurrency analyst, has recently shared his insights on Bitcoin&#8217;s performance since the bottom. According to Olson, Bitcoin has experienced two major breakouts since its lower lows, with the first resulting in a 54% gain and a subsequent correction of 22% that took 70 days from a pivot low to a pivot low. The second breakout has resulted in a 58% gain, followed by a current correction of 13%. However, Olson points out that Bitcoin&#8217;s price could reach the third target if the second breakout experiences a -22% correction. He also notes that if it takes 70 days from pivot low to pivot low, this correction will last until May 19th. It&#8217;s important to note that these scenarios won&#8217;t be the same, but higher time frames are still bullish. Furthermore, if Bitcoin fails to hold its current trading level at $27,400, it risks losing its 50-day moving average. Despite this, the cryptocurrency&#8217;s biggest support floor is still thousands of dollars below its current mark, at $24,600, noted by the yellow line below (200dMA). According to Jesse Olson&#8217;s analysis, this level would represent one of the three targets if the decline continues. Related Reading: Is the Next Bitcoin Bull Run Tied To The US Presidential Elections? Here’s What History Tells Us Signs Point To Prolonged Volatility Suppression In Bitcoin Market The cryptocurrency market has been characterized by prolonged volatility suppression in recent days. According to the analysis firm King Fisher, this is causing a sense of “pent-up energy” that is expected to be unleashed. Signs show that the market is setting up to hunt x20 leverages, which has caught the attention of the analysis firm.  King Fisher&#8217;s analysis suggests that the current calm in the Bitcoin market may be the calm before the storm, with a potential surge in volatility looming. Furthermore, per King Fisher’s analysis, the cryptocurrency market is currently experiencing a short ratio hovering around 60-70%, indicating a potential short squeeze.  In addition, motivated sellers who are in a rush to convert their assets into cash are appearing on the scene, potentially missing out on potential upside gains. One key player in the recent marginal seller in the Bitcoin market could be linked to Digital Currency Group’s (DCG) potential sell-off of some assets to restructure its financial plan to pay to its subsidiary Genesis.  Meanwhile, the open interest (OI) in the Bitcoin market remains fairly stable, with many investors waiting for a settlement or locking in synthetic USD. This suggests that many investors are cautious, waiting for more certainty before making any major moves. Despite the uncertainty, many experts remain bullish on the long-term prospects for Bitcoin and other cryptocurrencies. With increased adoption and institutional investment, the cryptocurrency market will likely continue to play a major role in the global financial landscape for years. Featured image from Unsplash, a chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin (BTC), the largest cryptocurrency in the market, has been trading sideways since experiencing a drop of over 5% on Monday. Despite this decline, Bitcoin has found support at $27,200, preventing further drops that could potentially jeopardize the next bull run of the leading cryptocurrency.</p>
<p>However, many investors wonder whether Bitcoin will show any signs of recovery shortly. Will the cryptocurrency market see a resurgence of bullish sentiment, or will the current bearish trend continue?</p>

<h2><b>Bitcoin&#8217;s 70-Day Correction, Is May 19th The End Date?</b></h2>
<p>Jesse Olson, an experienced cryptocurrency analyst, has recently shared his <a href="https://twitter.com/JesseOlson/status/1655667288245432328?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">insights </a>on Bitcoin&#8217;s performance since the bottom. According to Olson, Bitcoin has experienced two major breakouts since its lower lows, with the first resulting in a 54% gain and a subsequent correction of 22% that took 70 days from a pivot low to a pivot low. The second breakout has resulted in a 58% gain, followed by a current correction of 13%.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large wp-image-530776" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/FvocGQHaYAIHgSd-860x527.png" alt="Bitcoin " width="860" height="527" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/FvocGQHaYAIHgSd-860x527.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/FvocGQHaYAIHgSd-460x282.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/FvocGQHaYAIHgSd-768x470.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/FvocGQHaYAIHgSd-750x459.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/FvocGQHaYAIHgSd-1140x698.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/FvocGQHaYAIHgSd.png 1422w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" />
<p>However, Olson points out that Bitcoin&#8217;s price could reach the third target if the second breakout experiences a -22% correction. He also notes that if it takes 70 days from pivot low to pivot low, this correction will last until May 19th. It&#8217;s important to note that these scenarios won&#8217;t be the same, but higher time frames are still bullish.</p>
<p>Furthermore, if Bitcoin fails to hold its current trading level at $27,400, it risks losing its 50-day moving average. Despite this, the cryptocurrency&#8217;s biggest support floor is still thousands of dollars below its current mark, at $24,600, noted by the yellow line below (200dMA). According to Jesse Olson&#8217;s analysis, this level would represent one of the three targets if the decline continues.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/HYYpeMB6/" alt="Bitcoin " width="1813" height="858" />

<b>Signs Point To Prolonged Volatility Suppression In Bitcoin Market</b>
<p>The cryptocurrency market has been characterized by prolonged volatility suppression in recent days. According<a href="https://twitter.com/kingfisher_btc/status/1655735633854210049?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow"> </a>to the analysis firm King Fisher,<a href="https://twitter.com/kingfisher_btc/status/1655735633854210049?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow"> this is causing a sense</a> of “pent-up energy” that is expected to be unleashed. Signs show that the market is setting up to hunt x20 leverages, which has caught the attention of the analysis firm. </p>
<p>King Fisher&#8217;s analysis suggests that the current calm in the Bitcoin market may be the calm before the storm, with a potential surge in volatility looming. Furthermore, per King Fisher’s analysis, the cryptocurrency market is currently experiencing a short ratio hovering around 60-70%, indicating a potential short squeeze. </p>
<p>In addition, motivated sellers who are in a rush to convert their assets into cash are appearing on the scene, potentially missing out on potential upside gains. One key player in the recent marginal seller in the Bitcoin market could be linked to Digital Currency Group’s (DCG) potential sell-off of some assets to restructure its financial plan to pay to its subsidiary Genesis. </p>
<p>Meanwhile, the open interest (OI) in the Bitcoin market remains fairly stable, with many investors waiting for a settlement or locking in synthetic USD. This suggests that many investors are cautious, waiting for more certainty before making any major moves.</p>
<p>Despite the uncertainty, many experts remain bullish on the long-term prospects for Bitcoin and other cryptocurrencies. With increased adoption and institutional investment, the cryptocurrency market will likely continue to play a major role in the global financial landscape for years.</p>
<p>Featured image from Unsplash, a chart from TradingView.com</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/traxer-qIcEPVGJsMY-unsplash-460x306.jpg" width="460" height="306" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Stop Protecting American Public, Pro-XRP Attorney Tells SEC Chair</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/crypto/stop-protecting-american-public-pro-xrp-attorney-tells-sec-chair/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mike D.]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 19:00:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gary Gensler]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[John Deaton]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrpusdt]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=530749</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The pro-XRP Attorney and crypto lawyer John Deaton has told SEC Chair Gary Gensler to retreat his regulatory actions. The attorney demands that the commission stop protecting Americans by lashing on crypto companies. The United States has increased the tension in its crypto industry through unclear regulatory measures. Crypto regulators like the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) also affect crypto firms with multiple enforcement actions.  Related Reading: Bitcoin To Drop Further? Whales Show Signs Of Dumping Stop Protecting American Public While Harming Crypto Firms, John Deaton  In a statement via Twitter in response to Gensler’s post appreciating SEC’s staff for upholding the commission’s mission, Attorney Deaton asked SEC boss Gensler to stop protecting the American public. On behalf of the American public we ask you to please stop protecting us. &#8212; John E Deaton (@JohnEDeaton1) May 8, 2023 The SEC has enacted enforcement actions against several crypto entities through its forceful regulatory measures. Some include the Ripple (XRP) blockchain, Paxos (Issuer of BUSD stablecoin), Bittrex, Coinbase, and others. In December 2020, the SEC sued Ripple Labs and some of its executives over the sale of XRP tokens under the Howey Test, stating that the asset passed the definition of an investment contract. Related Reading: Bitcoin Plunge Under $28,000 Only Temporary? This Metric Suggests So Attorney Deaton maintained that XRP is not a security but a digital currency, and the lawsuit has been taking several turns and is still ongoing. The activity of the US SEC on crypto firms in the US has evoked a lot of reactions, especially from top firms such as Coinbase. However,  the commission has maintained that its actions are measures to protect Americans. Moreover, in a video, last month, the SEC chair maintained that intermediaries for investment contracts should comply with securities laws and register fully with the SEC.  He also said that the law only cares about “what something is and not what you call it” As such, digital asset investment firms that list securities must comply with the investor protection obligations like other firms. SEC Pushing Legal Boundaries With Ripple Lawsuit Crypto lawyer John Deaton mentioned earlier that the SEC is pushing legal boundaries by claiming that Ripple violated securities laws. According to a Bloomberg Law publication, Deaton stated that the SEC&#8217;s allegation against XRP is beyond legal contemplation and court rulings on securities. The lawyer mentioned that the US Supreme Court in 1946 defined security in its ruling on SEC v. Howey case. So, the ruling could not account for the complex digital assets with encrypted computer code after almost a century. Featured image from Thinking Crypto and chart from Tradingview]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The pro-XRP Attorney and crypto lawyer John Deaton has told SEC Chair Gary Gensler to retreat his regulatory actions. The attorney demands that the commission stop protecting Americans by lashing on crypto companies.</p>
<p>The United States has increased the tension in its crypto industry through unclear regulatory measures. Crypto regulators like the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) also affect crypto firms with multiple enforcement actions. </p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-drop-further-whales-signs-of-dumping/">Bitcoin To Drop Further? Whales Show Signs Of Dumping</a></p>
<h2>Stop Protecting American Public While Harming Crypto Firms, John Deaton </h2>
<p>In a statement via Twitter in response to Gensler’s <a href="https://twitter.com/GaryGensler/status/1655614745456660483" rel="nofollow">post</a> appreciating SEC’s staff for upholding the commission’s mission, Attorney Deaton asked SEC boss Gensler to stop protecting the American public.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">On behalf of the American public we ask you to please stop protecting us.</p>
<p>&mdash; John E Deaton (@JohnEDeaton1) <a href="https://twitter.com/JohnEDeaton1/status/1655624910046400512?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">May 8, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p></p>
<p>The SEC has enacted enforcement actions against several crypto entities through its forceful regulatory measures. Some include the Ripple (XRP) blockchain, Paxos (Issuer of BUSD stablecoin), Bittrex, Coinbase, and others.</p>
<p>In December 2020, the SEC sued Ripple Labs and some of its executives over the sale of XRP tokens under the Howey Test, stating that the asset passed the definition of an investment contract.</p>

<p>Attorney Deaton maintained that XRP is not a security but a digital currency, and the lawsuit has been taking several turns and is still ongoing.</p>
<p>The activity of the US SEC on crypto firms in the US has evoked a lot of reactions, especially from top firms such as <a href="https://www.reuters.com/technology/coinbase-ceo-crypto-firms-will-develop-offshore-without-clear-regulations-2023-04-18/" rel="nofollow">Coinbase</a>. However,  the commission has maintained that its actions are measures to protect Americans.</p>
<p>Moreover, <a href="https://twitter.com/GaryGensler/status/1651624244445421591?" rel="nofollow">in a video</a>, last month, the SEC chair maintained that intermediaries for investment contracts should comply with securities laws and register fully with the SEC. </p>
<p>He also said that the law only cares about “what something is and not what you call it” As such, digital asset investment firms that list securities must comply with the investor protection obligations like other firms.</p>
<h2>SEC Pushing Legal Boundaries With Ripple Lawsuit</h2>
<p>Crypto lawyer John Deaton mentioned earlier that the SEC is pushing legal boundaries by claiming that Ripple violated securities laws.</p>
<p>According to a <a href="https://news.bloomberglaw.com/us-law-week/sec-crypto-litigation-ventures-into-dangerous-legal-territory" rel="nofollow">Bloomberg Law publication</a>, Deaton stated that the SEC&#8217;s allegation against XRP is beyond legal contemplation and court rulings on securities.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-530753 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSDT_2023-05-09_19-36-08-860x370.png" alt="Stop Protecting American Public, Pro-XRP Attorney Told SEC Chair" width="860" height="370" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSDT_2023-05-09_19-36-08-860x370.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSDT_2023-05-09_19-36-08-460x198.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSDT_2023-05-09_19-36-08-768x331.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSDT_2023-05-09_19-36-08-1536x661.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSDT_2023-05-09_19-36-08-750x323.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSDT_2023-05-09_19-36-08-1140x491.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSDT_2023-05-09_19-36-08.png 1714w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" />
<p>The lawyer mentioned that the US Supreme Court in 1946 defined security in its ruling on SEC v. Howey case. So, the ruling could not account for the complex digital assets with encrypted computer code after almost a century.</p>
<p>Featured image from Thinking Crypto and chart from Tradingview</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/john-deaton-460x259.jpg" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Only 6% Left Until Cardano Hits Max Capacity, What This Means For ADA</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/cardano/only-6-left-until-cardano-hits-max-capacity-what-this-means-for-ada/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mudiaga Iritare]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 18:20:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cardano]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrencies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Layer 1]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=530669</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Recently, the Cardano blockchain ecosystem and decentralized platform have experienced an unprecedentedly high percentage of load pressure, which has led to raised questions and concerns from the blockchain community. At the same time, its native token ADA&#8217;s price has struggled for months and has yet to record any significant gains and upside movements in the cryptocurrency markets. Yesterday, a report analysis made by the cofounder of dcSpark and contributor to the Cardano blockchain clearly reflected where the blockchain platform is in terms of transaction load and what it means for users. Cardano Is Currently At 94% Load, Only 6% Left-What To Expect Sebastien Guillemot, the co-founder of dcSpark and Cardano contributor, recently highlighted a concern about the ADA blockchain network ecosystem. Related Reading: Bitcoin Block 788695: The Day Transaction Fees Took The Crown In a tweet yesterday, Guillemot stated that the Cardano blockchain network is currently at a 94% load, with only 6% left until it reaches max capacity. &#160; Cardano is currently at 94% load! Only 6% left until Cardano is at max capacity What does that mean, and how can you be prepared 🧵 pic.twitter.com/1TZsIUg10N &#8212; Sebastien Guillemot (@SebastienGllmt) May 8, 2023 According to Guillemot, if the load reaches max capacity at 100%, transactions initiated by each user on the blockchain will be queued up alongside other users&#8217; transactions. No &#8220;Cardano node implements transaction prioritization,&#8221; he said, and as such, each user&#8217;s transactions will be processed on a first-come, first-served model. Guillemot further stated that this could mean longer wait times for transactions to show up on-chain, and in extreme cases, user transactions may never make it to the blockchain. The result of this, he said, is caused by light wallet Mempools hitting maximum capacity than it can hold. Related Reading: Ethereum Gas Fees Skyrocket: What Does It Mean For Investors? Another thing users can expect when Cardano hits 100% max capacity is the likelihood of staking pools selling priority access to decentralized applications (dApps) and even to some users. Guillemot urged that when staking pools start selling priority access to select DEXs and dApps, it would be a good time for users to pay attention to how this move impacts one DEX to another and in choosing which DEX is suitable to leverage at any given time.  Way Forward To Scalability While Cardano nears max capacity, the dcSpark co-founder has suggested how to scale and reduce load pressure on the blockchain, having touched on what users can expect if it happens. Guillemot had listed several ways to scale the blockchain, including increasing block sizes and migrating more decentralized applications (dApps) to Plutus V2. He also suggested using sidechains and layer 2 blockchains to shoulder traffic off layer 1 and developing a data availability layer to transfer more data off layer 1 so that there is ample room for more blocks. At press time, ADA trades at $0.363, a 0.91% increase from its daily low. ADA experiences a steep decline in price on the daily timeframe &#124; Source: ADAUSD on TradingView.com &#160; Featured Image from Istock, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Recently, the Cardano blockchain ecosystem and decentralized platform have experienced an unprecedentedly high percentage of<a href="https://pool.pm" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow"> load</a> pressure, which has led to raised questions and concerns from the blockchain community.</p>
<p>At the same time, its native token ADA&#8217;s price has struggled for months and has yet to record any significant gains and upside movements in the cryptocurrency markets.</p>
<p>Yesterday, a report analysis made by the cofounder of dcSpark and contributor to the Cardano blockchain clearly reflected where the blockchain platform is in terms of transaction load and what it means for users.</p>
<h2>Cardano Is Currently At 94% Load, Only 6% Left-What To Expect</h2>
<p>Sebastien Guillemot, the co-founder of dcSpark and Cardano contributor, recently highlighted a concern about the ADA blockchain network ecosystem.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-block-788695-the-day-transaction-fees-took-the-crown/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin Block 788695: The Day Transaction Fees Took The Crown</a></p>
<p>In a <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://twitter.com/SebastienGllmt/status/1655624561789112321?t=5LL-QNgfI4fyhJP-ZDmTHg&amp;s=19" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">tweet</a> yesterday, Guillemot stated that the Cardano blockchain network is currently at a 94% load, with only 6% left until it reaches max capacity.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Cardano is currently at 94% load!</p>
<p>Only 6% left until Cardano is at max capacity</p>
<p>What does that mean, and how can you be prepared <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f9f5.png" alt="🧵" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> <a href="https://t.co/1TZsIUg10N" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/1TZsIUg10N</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Sebastien Guillemot (@SebastienGllmt) <a href="https://twitter.com/SebastienGllmt/status/1655624561789112321?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">May 8, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p></p>
<p>According to Guillemot, if the load reaches max capacity at 100%, transactions initiated by each user on the blockchain will be queued up alongside other users&#8217; transactions.</p>
<p>No &#8220;Cardano node implements transaction prioritization,&#8221; he said, and as such, each user&#8217;s transactions will be processed on a first-come, first-served model.</p>
<p>Guillemot further stated that this could mean longer wait times for transactions to show up on-chain, and in extreme cases, user transactions may never make it to the blockchain. The result of this, he said, is caused by light wallet Mempools hitting maximum capacity than it can hold.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/ethereum-gas-fees-skyrocket/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ethereum Gas Fees Skyrocket: What Does It Mean For Investors?</a></p>
<p>Another thing users can expect when Cardano hits 100% max capacity is the likelihood of staking pools selling priority access to decentralized applications (dApps) and even to some users.</p>
<p>Guillemot urged that when staking pools start selling priority access to select DEXs and dApps, it would be a good time for users to pay attention to how this move impacts one DEX to another and in choosing which DEX is suitable to leverage at any given time.</p>
<h2> Way Forward To Scalability</h2>
<p>While Cardano nears max capacity, the dcSpark co-founder has suggested how to scale and reduce load pressure on the blockchain, having touched on what users can expect if it happens.</p>
<p>Guillemot had listed several ways to scale the blockchain, including increasing block sizes and migrating more decentralized applications (dApps) to Plutus V2.</p>
<p>He also suggested using sidechains and layer 2 blockchains to shoulder traffic off layer 1 and developing a data availability layer to transfer more data off layer 1 so that there is ample room for more blocks.</p>
<p>At press time, ADA trades at $0.363, a 0.91% increase from its daily low.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/Svq2itx9/" alt="Cardano" width="1280" height="538" /></p>

<p>&nbsp;</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/traxer-f0C1ptuSKhg-unsplash-460x326.jpg" width="460" height="326" />	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
