<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
>

<channel>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.newsbtc.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<description>Bitcoin &#38; Cryptocurrency News Today</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 02:40:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Price Surges 8% And Defies Gravity – Bulls Eye $30K</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-eye-30k/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 02:40:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xbtusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=538869</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin price is surging above $28,000. BTC is up nearly 8% and there are chances of a move toward the $30,000 resistance zone. Bitcoin is gaining pace above the $27,000 resistance. The price is trading above $27,500 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average. There is a major bullish trend line forming with support near $27,300 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Kraken). The pair could rise further if it clears the $29,000 and $29,200 resistance levels. Bitcoin Price Rallies Above $28K Bitcoin price formed a strong support base above the $26,000 pivot level. BTC started a fresh rally and was able to clear the $27,500 resistance zone. It opened the doors for a sustained upward move above the $28,000 level. The price even tested the $29,000 resistance zone. A high is formed near $29,000 and the price is now consolidating gains. It is trading above the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the recent surge from the $26,650 swing low to the $29,000 high. Bitcoin price is now trading above $27,500 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average. There is also a major bullish trend line forming with support near $27,300 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair. Source: BTCUSD on TradingView.com On the upside, the price is facing resistance near the $29,000 level. The next major resistance is near the $29,200 level. A close above the $29,200 resistance might spark another strong move in the near term. The next major resistance is near the $30,000 level, above which the bulls might send BTC toward the $30,800 resistance zone. Are Dips Limited in BTC? If Bitcoin’s price fails to clear the $29,000 resistance, it could start a downside correction. Immediate support on the downside is near the $28,450 level. The next major support is near the $27,850 level or the 50% Fib retracement level of the recent surge from the $26,650 swing low to the $29,000 high. The main support is now near $27,500 and the trend line zone, below which the price might start a steady decline toward $27,000. Any more losses might send the price toward $26,500 in the near term. Technical indicators: Hourly MACD – The MACD is now gaining pace in the bullish zone. Hourly RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BTC/USD is in the overbought zone. Major Support Levels – $28,450, followed by $27,850. Major Resistance Levels – $29,000, $29,200, and $30,000.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>Bitcoin price is surging above $28,000. BTC is up nearly 8% and there are chances of a move toward the $30,000 resistance zone.</em></p>
<ul>
<li>Bitcoin is gaining pace above the $27,000 resistance.</li>
<li>The price is trading above $27,500 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average.</li>
<li>There is a major bullish trend line forming with support near $27,300 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could rise further if it clears the $29,000 and $29,200 resistance levels.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Bitcoin Price Rallies Above $28K</h2>
<p>Bitcoin price formed a <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-extends-recovery-27k/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">strong support base</a> above the $26,000 pivot level. BTC started a fresh rally and was able to clear the $27,500 resistance zone.</p>
<p>It opened the doors for a sustained upward move above the $28,000 level. The price even tested the $29,000 resistance zone. A high is formed near $29,000 and the price is now consolidating gains. It is trading above the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the recent surge from the $26,650 swing low to the $29,000 high.</p>
<p>Bitcoin price is now trading above $27,500 and the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-steadies-above-26k/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">100 hourly Simple moving average</a>. There is also a major bullish trend line forming with support near $27,300 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-538870" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-14.png" alt="Bitcoin Price" width="1835" height="845" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-14.png 1835w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-14-460x212.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-14-860x396.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-14-768x354.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-14-1536x707.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-14-750x345.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-14-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1835px) 100vw, 1835px"/></p>
<p>Source: <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BTCUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">BTCUSD on TradingView.com</a></p>
<p>On the upside, the price is facing resistance near the $29,000 level. The next major resistance is near the $29,200 level. A close above the $29,200 resistance might spark another strong move in the near term. The next major resistance is near the $30,000 level, above which the bulls might send BTC toward the $30,800 resistance zone.</p>
<h2>Are Dips Limited in BTC?</h2>
<p>If Bitcoin’s price fails to clear the $29,000 resistance, it could start a downside correction. Immediate support on the downside is near the $28,450 level.</p>
<p>The next major support is near the $27,850 level or the 50% Fib retracement level of the recent surge from the $26,650 swing low to the $29,000 high. The main support is now near $27,500 and the trend line zone, below which the price might start a steady decline toward $27,000. Any more losses might send the price toward $26,500 in the near term.</p>
<p>Technical indicators:</p>
<p>Hourly MACD – The MACD is now gaining pace in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>Hourly RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BTC/USD is in the overbought zone.</p>
<p>Major Support Levels – $28,450, followed by $27,850.</p>
<p>Major Resistance Levels – $29,000, $29,200, and $30,000.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/04/shutterstock_794402125-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>SEC Sues Binance, Coinbase Then BlackRock Files For Bitcoin Spot ETF; Is This An Inside Job?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/sec-sues-binance-coinbase-blackrock-bitcoin-etf-inside-job/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dalmas Ngetich]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 02:30:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin bulls]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[grayscale]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=538859</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[While the cryptocurrency community is excited about the BlackRock Bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF) filing and the planned involvement of other prominent players in traditional finance, such as Fidelity and Deutsche Bank, one observer is skeptical. On Twitter, he notes that these Wall Street giants only became involved after the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) took legal action against Binance, the world’s largest cryptocurrency exchange, and Coinbase, a popular exchange in the United States and Western Europe. Is This An Inside Job? He claimed that the SEC could have colluded with specific players to provide them additional time to catch up. This statement has sparked considerable speculation within the industry. However, there is no evidence to suggest that government regulators, such as the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC), who have filed a lawsuit against Binance, have purposely targeted top cryptocurrency platforms in the United States to enable Wall Street firms to dominate the market. Related Reading: Litecoin Sees 55% Increase In New Daily Addresses As Bullish Sentiment Grows On June 5, the SEC sued Binance, alleging that the exchange was engaged in several illegal activities, including operating an unregistered securities exchange, failing to register as a broker-dealer, and misleading investors about its operations. They also claimed that some of the assets listed by the crypto trading platforms were unregistered securities. The SEC leveled 13 charges against Binance, Changpeng Zhao, the exchange’s CEO, and Binance.US. However, Binance has said it will defend itself against the lawsuit. While the lawsuit is pending in a federal court, the SEC dropped its request for a temporary restraining order (TRO) against Binance.US on June 17, 2023. It means Binance.US clients are free to access their funds while also showing that the SEC could, after all, be willing to work with cryptocurrency exchanges.  BlackRock Bitcoin Spot ETF Filing Good For Grayscale? Notably, the TRO was less than two days when BlackRock, the world&#8217;s largest asset manager, with over $9 trillion in assets under management, applied for a Bitcoin Spot ETF on June 19. Their decision to file effectively legitimizes Bitcoin as an investment asset. If approved by the SEC, it will provide an avenue for institutional investors to get exposure to Bitcoin.  Following BlackRock’s Bitcoin spot ETF application, Grayscale’s Bitcoin Trust (GBTC) soared over 12%. At the same time, the discount, which is the difference between GBTC share price and net asset value (NAV) of Grayscale’s Bitcoin holdings, has been decreasing. After the discount fell to 44% on June 14, this value now stands at 36.6%, trackers on June 20 show. Related Reading: Stacks (STX) Registers 11% Gains As Broader Market Suffers Volatility It remains to be seen whether the SEC will approve the first Bitcoin spot ETF in the country, following Canada, which approved the Purpose Bitcoin ETF in February 2021. In the meantime, Bitcoin prices are reaping higher, soaring 13% in 5 days. In that sense, the Grayscale Bitcoin Trust discount could continue to decrease. This outcome might be the first positive development for the cryptocurrency and the nascent industry. Feature Image From Canva, Chart From TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>While the cryptocurrency community is excited about the BlackRock Bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF) filing and the planned involvement of other prominent players in traditional finance, such as Fidelity and Deutsche Bank, one observer is skeptical. </p>
<p>On Twitter, he <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://twitter.com/PrestonPysh/status/1671153596547874820" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">notes</a> that these Wall Street giants only became involved after the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) took legal action against Binance, the world’s largest cryptocurrency exchange, and Coinbase, a popular exchange in the United States and Western Europe.</p>
<h2>Is This An Inside Job?</h2>
<p>He claimed that the SEC could have colluded with specific players to provide them additional time to catch up. This statement has sparked considerable speculation within the industry. However, there is no evidence to suggest that government regulators, such as the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC), who have filed a lawsuit against Binance, have purposely targeted top cryptocurrency platforms in the United States to enable Wall Street firms to dominate the market.</p>

<p>On June 5, the SEC sued Binance, alleging that the exchange was engaged in several illegal activities, including operating an unregistered securities exchange, failing to register as a broker-dealer, and misleading investors about its operations. They also claimed that some of the assets listed by the crypto trading platforms were unregistered securities. </p>
<p>The SEC leveled 13 charges against Binance, Changpeng Zhao, the exchange’s CEO, and Binance.US. However, Binance has said it will defend itself against the lawsuit.</p>
<p>While the lawsuit is pending in a federal court, the SEC dropped its request for a temporary restraining order (TRO) against Binance.US on June 17, 2023. It means Binance.US clients are free to access their funds while also showing that the SEC could, after all, be willing to work with cryptocurrency exchanges. </p>
<h2>BlackRock Bitcoin Spot ETF Filing Good For Grayscale?</h2>
<p>Notably, the TRO was less than two days when BlackRock, the world&#8217;s largest asset manager, with over $9 trillion in assets under management, applied for a Bitcoin Spot ETF on June 19. Their decision to file effectively legitimizes Bitcoin as an investment asset. If approved by the SEC, it will provide an avenue for institutional investors to get exposure to Bitcoin. </p>
<a href="https://www.tradingview.com/x/A5KJlQWs/" rel="nofollow"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/A5KJlQWs/" alt="Bitcoin price on June 20| Source: BTCUSDT On Binance, TradingView" width="1226" height="595"/></a>
<p>Following BlackRock’s Bitcoin spot ETF application, Grayscale’s Bitcoin Trust (GBTC) soared over 12%. At the same time, the discount, which is the difference between GBTC share price and net asset value (NAV) of Grayscale’s Bitcoin holdings, has been decreasing. After the discount fell to 44% on June 14, this value now stands at 36.6%, trackers on June 20 <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://ycharts.com/companies/GBTC/discount_or_premium_to_nav" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">show</a>.</p>

<p>It remains to be seen whether the SEC will approve the first Bitcoin spot ETF in the country, following Canada, which approved the Purpose Bitcoin ETF in February 2021. In the meantime, Bitcoin prices are reaping higher, soaring 13% in 5 days.</p>
<p>In that sense, the Grayscale Bitcoin Trust discount could continue to decrease. This outcome might be the first positive development for the cryptocurrency and the nascent industry.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/SEC-Coinbase-Binance-Bitcoin-ETF-BlackRock-460x260.jpg" width="460" height="260" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Dominance Surges To 50% As BlackRock ETF Filing Fuels Investor Confidence</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-dominance-surges-to-50-as-blackrock-etf-filing-fuels-investor-confidence/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Semilore Faleti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 01:30:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BlackRock]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[market dominance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=538836</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin is again at 50% market dominance, indicating that the cryptocurrency now accounts for half of the total crypto market cap, valued at $1.052 Trillion. According to data from Tradingview, Bitcoin&#8217;s total market dominance crossed above 50% yesterday, June 19, for the first time in months.  The news of Bitcoin’s renewed dominance has driven much excitement across the crypto community, with many speculating on the reason for such market growth.  However, one possible reason is the news of prominent global asset manager BlackRock filing for a Bitcoin Exchange Traded Fund (ETF) with the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). This move appeared to have boosted investors&#8217; confidence upon announcement, causing BTC&#8217;s price to surge above $28,000 since last month. According to data from CoinMarketCap, BTC is currently trading around $27,432.93, with a 3.13% gain in the last day. The token’s daily trading volume is also up by 83.39%, valued at $17 billion. Meanwhile, Bitcoin currently boasts a staggering market cap of $531.54 billion, covering over 50% of the entire crypto market.  Bitcoin Market Dominance At 50.63% &#124; Source: Tradingview.com Related Reading: Cardano Poised For Consolidation In This Price Zone Prior To Attempting Reversal BlackRock’s ETF Filling: An Influential Mainstream Move The news of BlackRock&#8217;s Bitcoin ETF filing was seen as a major development in the crypto space drawing several reactions from crypto enthusiasts across the globe.  Essentially, a Bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF) mirrors the fluctuations in Bitcoin&#8217;s price, granting investors exposure to the cryptocurrency without requiring direct acquisition.  The foray of a traditional finance company such as BlackRock, with a valuation of $105.25 billion, into the realm of cryptocurrency carries immense significance. There is even a belief among some industry figures that this ETF application will be accepted in a &#8220;short time&#8221; despite the high number of ETF rejections usually dished out by the SEC. This will be the first-ever spot market Bitcoin ETF certified by the SEC if approved.  Related Reading: Why The Ripple General Counsel Demands Impartiality From SEC Staff The Promising Prospects of A Bitcoin ETF Bitcoin has experienced a significant amount of volatility since May 2021. The price of the number one cryptocurrency has fluctuated wildly, reaching an all-time high of over $68,000 before crashing to a low of $26,500.   A Bitcoin ETF would be good news for investors as it provides an easy, secure, and regulated way to invest in Bitcoin and diversify their portfolios. Furthermore, a Bitcoin ETF will likely attract more institutional investors who were previously hesitant about getting into crypto because of custody and regulatory concerns. The buzz surrounding the Bitcoin ETF continues to intensify, with additional news emerging that Fidelity Investments, an asset management powerhouse with assets totaling $4.5 trillion, is seeking a regulatory license to provide crypto custody services. Featured Image: Binance Academy, chart from Tradingview]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin is again at 50% market dominance, indicating that the cryptocurrency now accounts for half of the total crypto market cap, valued at $1.052 Trillion.</p>
<p>According to <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/chart/xg17RJqK/?symbol=CRYPTOCAP%3ABTC.D" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">data from Tradingview</a>, Bitcoin&#8217;s total market dominance crossed above 50% yesterday, June 19, for the first time in months. </p>
<p>The news of Bitcoin’s renewed dominance has driven much excitement across the crypto community, with many speculating on the reason for such market growth. </p>
<p>However, one possible reason is the news of prominent global asset manager BlackRock filing for a Bitcoin Exchange Traded Fund (ETF) with the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). This move appeared to have<a href="https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bitcoin-boost-blackrock-etf-filing-091541460.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow"> boosted investors&#8217;</a> confidence upon announcement, causing BTC&#8217;s price to surge above $28,000 since last month.</p>
<p>According to <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">data from CoinMarketCap</a>, BTC is currently trading around $27,432.93, with a 3.13% gain in the last day. The token’s daily trading volume is also up by 83.39%, valued at $17 billion. Meanwhile, Bitcoin currently boasts a staggering market cap of $531.54 billion, covering over 50% of the entire crypto market. </p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/aHuyFAUr/" alt="Bitcoin" width="1480" height="913"/></p>


<h2>BlackRock’s ETF Filling: An Influential Mainstream Move</h2>
<p>The news of BlackRock&#8217;s Bitcoin ETF filing was seen as a major development in the crypto space drawing several reactions from crypto enthusiasts across the globe. </p>
<p>Essentially, a Bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF) mirrors the fluctuations in Bitcoin&#8217;s price, granting investors exposure to the cryptocurrency without requiring direct acquisition. </p>
<p>The foray of a traditional finance company such as BlackRock, with a valuation of $105.25 billion, into the realm of cryptocurrency carries immense significance. </p>
<p>There is even a <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/imminent-approval-swirl-blackrocks-bitcoin-etf/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">belief</a> among some industry figures that this ETF application will be accepted in a &#8220;short time&#8221; despite the high number of ETF rejections usually dished out by the SEC. This will be the <a href="https://economictimes.indiatimes.com/markets/cryptocurrency/no-spot-bitcoin-etfs-approved-so-far-u-s-sec-official/articleshow/95880705.cms" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">first-ever spot market Bitcoin ETF certified by the SEC if approved</a>. </p>

<h2>The Promising Prospects of A Bitcoin ETF</h2>
<p>Bitcoin has experienced a significant amount of volatility since May 2021. The price of the number one cryptocurrency has fluctuated wildly, reaching an all-time high of over $68,000 before crashing to a low of $26,500.  </p>
<p>A Bitcoin ETF would be<a href="https://www.investopedia.com/investing/bitcoin-etfs-explained/#:~:text=3-,Goals%20of%20Bitcoin%20ETFs,about%20blockchain%2C%20mining%2C%20decentralized%20exchanges%2C%20distributed%20ledgers%2C%20key%20storage%2C%20and%20cryptocurrency.,-How%20to%20Invest" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow"> good</a> news for investors as it provides an easy, secure, and regulated way to invest in Bitcoin and diversify their portfolios. Furthermore, a Bitcoin ETF will likely attract more institutional investors who were previously hesitant about getting into crypto because of custody and regulatory concerns.</p>
<p>The buzz surrounding the Bitcoin ETF continues to intensify, with <a href="https://twitter.com/BitcoinMagazine/status/1670762619677085697?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">additional news</a> emerging that Fidelity Investments, an asset management powerhouse with assets totaling $4.5 trillion, is seeking a regulatory license to provide crypto custody services.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/4ebcb49ae42847d09dfd929a2b86395d-460x259.png" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Polygon Labs Unveils Major Upgrade To Sidechain With &#8216;zkEVM Validium&#8217; Layer 2</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/matic/polygon-labs-unveils-major-upgrade-to-sidechain-with-zkevm-validium-layer-2/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 00:30:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[MATIC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blockchain technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[maticusdt]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Polygon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Polygon (MATIC)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=538850</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Polygon Labs, the engineering team behind the popular Polygon PoS (Proof of Stake) chain, has proposed a major upgrade to the network.  The upgrade would introduce a “first-of-its-kind” decentralized L2 (Layer 2) secured by zero-knowledge (ZK) proofs, making the Polygon ecosystem more secure, performant, and a core part of the upcoming Polygon 2.0 ecosystem. This upgrade marks a significant milestone in the blockchain industry, as it would be the first time an existing chain, especially of this size and importance, adds ZK proofs to become an L2.  Related Reading: Stacks (STX) Registers 11% Gains As Broader Market Suffers Volatility Polygon Labs Sets The Bar High Per the announcement, the upgrade proposes using a zkEVM validium, a lower-cost, higher-throughput sibling of a rollup. Rollups, such as Polygon zkEVM, leverage Ethereum to publish transaction data and verify proofs, inheriting its security and decentralization.  Moreover, the upgrade will involve the migration of Polygon&#8217;s existing PoS to a new PoS network that utilizes the zkEVM technology. The upgraded PoS network, or validium, will operate alongside Polygon&#8217;s existing zkEVM rollup network, offering users the benefits of both technologies depending on their specific needs. Existing Polygon PoS validators will play two critical roles in the upgraded ecosystem, guaranteeing data availability and sequencing transactions. By attesting to data availability, Polygon PoS will become the first validium with decentralized and secure data availability guarantees.  Validators will also operate the chain by deciding which transactions to include in a block and in which order, preserving decentralization and ensuring that transaction fees flow to MATIC-staked validators. This would make Polygon PoS the first L2 with a decentralized sequencer set. Furthermore, the upgraded PoS network will offer high scalability and low fees, making it an ideal fit for applications with high transaction volume and requiring low transaction fees, such as Web3 gaming and social and micro Decentralized Finance (DeFi). Meanwhile, the existing zkEVM rollup network will continue to offer a high level of security, making it a good solution for applications that process high-value transactions and prioritize security, such as high-value DeFi applications. Polygon’s 2.0 vision for scalability and unified liquidity, powered by ZK technology, aims to make every Polygon chain a ZK L2. However, Polygon PoS, in its current state, is secured by its validators, not by ZK proofs.  Related Reading: Cardano Poised For Consolidation In This Price Zone Prior To Attempting Reversal According to the announcement, the upgrade is currently in the Pre-Polygon Improvement Proposal (PIP) stage, with the proposal already live on the governance forum. Assuming it gathers significant support from the community, a formal PIP will be put forward, initiating the prescribed processes.  The proposal will then be discussed on PPG (Polygon Protocol Governance) Calls, governance forums, and other public venues to gather consensus from all relevant ecosystem participants. The implementation could go live on Mainnet by the end of Q1 2024 if a consensus is reached. Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com ]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Polygon Labs, the engineering team behind the popular Polygon PoS (Proof of Stake) chain, has <a href="https://polygon.technology/blog/polygon-2-0-polygon-pos-zk-layer-2" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">proposed </a>a major upgrade to the network. </p>
<p>The upgrade would introduce a “first-of-its-kind” decentralized L2 (Layer 2) secured by zero-knowledge (ZK) proofs, making the Polygon ecosystem more secure, performant, and a core part of the upcoming Polygon 2.0 ecosystem.</p>
<p>This upgrade marks a significant milestone in the blockchain industry, as it would be the first time an existing chain, especially of this size and importance, adds ZK proofs to become an L2. </p>

<h2>Polygon Labs Sets The Bar High</h2>
<p>Per the announcement, the upgrade proposes using a zkEVM validium, a lower-cost, higher-throughput sibling of a rollup. Rollups, such as Polygon zkEVM, leverage Ethereum to publish transaction data and verify proofs, inheriting its security and decentralization. </p>
<p>Moreover, the upgrade will involve the migration of Polygon&#8217;s existing PoS to a new PoS network that utilizes the zkEVM technology. The upgraded PoS network, or validium, will operate alongside Polygon&#8217;s existing zkEVM rollup network, offering users the benefits of both technologies depending on their specific needs.</p>
<p>Existing Polygon PoS validators will play two critical roles in the upgraded ecosystem, guaranteeing data availability and sequencing transactions. By attesting to data availability, Polygon PoS will become the first validium with decentralized and secure data availability guarantees. </p>
<p>Validators will also operate the chain by deciding which transactions to include in a block and in which order, preserving decentralization and ensuring that transaction fees flow to MATIC-staked validators. This would make Polygon PoS the first L2 with a decentralized sequencer set.</p>
<p>Furthermore, the upgraded PoS network will offer high scalability and low fees, making it an ideal fit for applications with high transaction volume and requiring low transaction fees, such as Web3 gaming and social and micro Decentralized Finance (DeFi).</p>
<p>Meanwhile, the existing zkEVM rollup network will continue to offer a high level of security, making it a good solution for applications that process high-value transactions and prioritize security, such as high-value DeFi applications.</p>
<p>Polygon’s 2.0 vision for scalability and unified liquidity, powered by ZK technology, aims to make every Polygon chain a ZK L2. However, Polygon PoS, in its current state, is secured by its validators, not by ZK proofs. </p>

<p>According to the announcement, the upgrade is currently in the Pre-Polygon Improvement Proposal (PIP) stage, with the proposal already live on the governance forum. Assuming it gathers significant support from the community, a formal PIP will be put forward, initiating the prescribed processes. </p>
<p>The proposal will then be discussed on PPG (Polygon Protocol Governance) Calls, governance forums, and other public venues to gather consensus from all relevant ecosystem participants. The implementation could go live on Mainnet by the end of Q1 2024 if a consensus is reached.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/n1La2uG2/" alt="Polygon " width="1815" height="858"/>
<p>Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/guerrillabuzz-ehaoA14lYMc-unsplash-460x259.jpg" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin On The brink Of Historic Golden Cross As Experts Predict Bull Run</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-on-the-brink-of-historic-golden-cross-as-experts-predict-bull-run/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 23:30:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=538837</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin, the largest cryptocurrency in the market appeared to have regained its bullish momentum after taking a liquidity hit of $25,000 in long positions last week. As of June 20th, Bitcoin is trading at $27,800, reflecting a 4% surge in just 24 hours. This recent development has led many experts to believe that the newly formed bull run is in its early stages, with institutional investors eagerly seeking to capitalize on the trend. Related Reading: Why The Ripple General Counsel Demands Impartiality From SEC Staff BTC&#8217;s MA20/200 Set To Make Never-Before-Seen Golden Cross Crypto trader under the pseudonym Moustache recently made a bold prediction about BTC’s future price action, stating that the cryptocurrency will make the first golden cross of the Moving Average (MA) 20/200, which has never happened before.  This unprecedented event has led many to speculate that a major bullish trend is on the horizon, with the potential for a big green candle shortly. For those unfamiliar with the terminology, a golden cross occurs when the 50-day moving average (MA50) crosses above the 200-day moving average (MA200), indicating a bullish trend in the market. Conversely, a death cross occurs when the MA50 crosses below the MA200, indicating a bearish trend. Moustache&#8217;s prediction is significant because it suggests that Bitcoin is about to enter a major bullish trend that has never been seen before. This starkly contrasts with the death cross in September 2022, which preceded the FTX crash.  However, This time, the market appears to be poised for a major rally, with institutional investors and retail traders eagerly seeking to capitalize on the trend. Bitcoin Breaks Multi-Month Downtrend, But Can It Sustain The Momentum? Crypto analyst Rekt Capital has recently observed the current state of Bitcoin&#8217;s price action. While Bitcoin has broken out beyond the multi-month downtrend, there is still uncertainty about the sustainability of this momentum. Rekt Capital has noted that it is difficult to look for daily breakout confirmation for Bitcoin in the context of the blue lower high diagonal resistance, seen in the chart below, as Bitcoin has failed many post-breakout retests on the daily timeframe. Bitcoin&#8217;s recent breakout is undoubtedly a positive sign for the cryptocurrency market, suggesting that the previous bearish trend may end. However, as Rekt Capital notes, there is still a significant amount of resistance to overcome before the breakout can be fully confirmed.  Rekt Capital suggests it may be better to look for confirmation on the weekly timeframe, as this would provide a more reliable indication of the sustainability of Bitcoin&#8217;s breakout. A weekly close beyond the downtrend would strongly confirm the breakout, indicating that the bullish momentum is likely to continue. Related Reading: Cardano Poised For Consolidation In This Price Zone Before Attempting Reversal Bitcoin&#8217;s short-term bullish trend is contingent on the cryptocurrency consolidating above the resistance level of $27,500. Failure to do so may result in consolidation for the largest cryptocurrency in the market. To achieve higher levels, bulls must maintain consolidation above this resistance mark. Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com ]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin, the largest cryptocurrency in the market appeared to have regained its bullish momentum after taking a liquidity hit of $25,000 in long positions last week. As of June 20th, Bitcoin is trading at $27,800, reflecting a 4% surge in just 24 hours.</p>
<p>This recent development has led many experts to believe that the newly formed bull run is in its early stages, with institutional investors eagerly seeking to capitalize on the trend.</p>

<h2>BTC&#8217;s MA20/200 Set To Make Never-Before-Seen Golden Cross</h2>
<p>Crypto trader under the pseudonym Moustache recently made a bold <a href="https://twitter.com/el_crypto_prof/status/1671179681024835585?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">prediction </a>about BTC’s future price action, stating that the cryptocurrency will make the first golden cross of the Moving Average (MA) 20/200, which has never happened before. </p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large wp-image-538840" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/FzE4Pf6XgAQsI21-860x440.png" alt="Bitcoin " width="860" height="440" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/FzE4Pf6XgAQsI21-860x440.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/FzE4Pf6XgAQsI21-460x235.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/FzE4Pf6XgAQsI21-768x393.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/FzE4Pf6XgAQsI21-1536x786.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/FzE4Pf6XgAQsI21-2048x1048.png 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/FzE4Pf6XgAQsI21-750x384.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/FzE4Pf6XgAQsI21-1140x583.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/>
<p>This unprecedented event has led many to speculate that a major bullish trend is on the horizon, with the potential for a big green candle shortly.</p>
<p>For those unfamiliar with the terminology, a golden cross occurs when the 50-day moving average (MA50) crosses above the 200-day moving average (MA200), indicating a bullish trend in the market. Conversely, a death cross occurs when the MA50 crosses below the MA200, indicating a bearish trend.</p>
<p>Moustache&#8217;s prediction is significant because it suggests that Bitcoin is about to enter a major bullish trend that has never been seen before. This starkly contrasts with the death cross in September 2022, which preceded the FTX crash. </p>
<p>However, This time, the market appears to be poised for a major rally, with institutional investors and retail traders eagerly seeking to capitalize on the trend.</p>
Bitcoin Breaks Multi-Month Downtrend, But Can It Sustain The Momentum?
<p>Crypto analyst Rekt Capital has recently <a href="https://twitter.com/rektcapital/status/1671215487294767117?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">observed</a><a href="https://twitter.com/rektcapital/status/1671215487294767117?s=20" rel="nofollow"> </a>the current state of Bitcoin&#8217;s price action. While Bitcoin has broken out beyond the multi-month downtrend, there is still uncertainty about the sustainability of this momentum.</p>
<p>Rekt Capital has noted that it is difficult to look for daily breakout confirmation for Bitcoin in the context of the blue lower high diagonal resistance, seen in the chart below, as Bitcoin has failed many post-breakout retests on the daily timeframe.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large wp-image-538839" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/FzFH2cxXgAAoGM5-860x609.jpg" alt="Bitcoin " width="860" height="609" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/FzFH2cxXgAAoGM5-860x609.jpg 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/FzFH2cxXgAAoGM5-460x326.jpg 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/FzFH2cxXgAAoGM5-768x544.jpg 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/FzFH2cxXgAAoGM5-1536x1088.jpg 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/FzFH2cxXgAAoGM5-120x86.jpg 120w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/FzFH2cxXgAAoGM5-750x531.jpg 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/FzFH2cxXgAAoGM5-1140x807.jpg 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/FzFH2cxXgAAoGM5.jpg 1788w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/>
<p>Bitcoin&#8217;s recent breakout is undoubtedly a positive sign for the cryptocurrency market, suggesting that the previous bearish trend may end. However, as Rekt Capital notes, there is still a significant amount of resistance to overcome before the breakout can be fully confirmed. </p>
<p>Rekt Capital suggests it may be better to look for confirmation on the weekly timeframe, as this would provide a more reliable indication of the sustainability of Bitcoin&#8217;s breakout. A weekly close beyond the downtrend would strongly confirm the breakout, indicating that the bullish momentum is likely to continue.</p>

<p>Bitcoin&#8217;s short-term bullish trend is contingent on the cryptocurrency consolidating above the resistance level of $27,500. Failure to do so may result in consolidation for the largest cryptocurrency in the market. To achieve higher levels, bulls must maintain consolidation above this resistance mark.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/6SMqASI1/" alt="Bitcoin " width="1814" height="858"/>
<p>Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/iStock-1392175988-1-460x248.jpg" width="460" height="248" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Miners Deposit To Exchanges, What Does This Mean?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-miners-deposit-exchanges-more-decline-ahead/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hououin Kyouma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 22:30:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin bearish]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Miner Selling]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin miners]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=538751</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[On-chain data shows that Bitcoin miners have been depositing large amounts to exchanges. Here&#8217;s what this could mean for the asset&#8217;s price. Bitcoin Miners Have Been Depositing Big To Exchanges Recently An analyst in a CryptoQuant post pointed out that BTC miners have been transferring coins out of their wallets recently. The relevant indicator here is the &#8220;miner outflow,&#8221; which measures the total amount of Bitcoin miners withdraw from their combined supply. The counterpart metric, the &#8220;miner inflow,&#8221; naturally keeps track of the reverse flow of coins. Here is a chart that shows the trend in both the Bitcoin miner outflow and the inflow over the past few days: Looks like the value of one of the metrics has been elevated in recent days &#124; Source: CryptoQuant The above graph shows that the Bitcoin miner outflow has observed a spike during the past day, while the inflow has remained relatively low. This would imply that the miners have transferred a net amount of coins from their wallets in this period. Related Reading: Bitcoin Whales Continue To Accumulate As BTC Makes Recovery Push Generally, whenever miners withdraw coins from their wallets, there is always a risk that they are doing so to sell said coins. Such selling can naturally have a bearish effect on the cryptocurrency&#8217;s value. One way to better guess the intent behind these withdrawals is by checking whether the destination of the coins is a centralized exchange platform. The chart also shows the data for the Bitcoin miner to exchange flow. This indicator specifically keeps track of the coins flowing from these chain validators&#8217; holdings to exchange wallets. This indicator has also seen a sharp spike at the same time as the miner outflow surge. The magnitude of both spikes is also pretty much the same; both are slightly above 1,000 BTC. Thus, almost all the outflows from the past day appear to have headed toward exchanges. Related Reading: Bullish Signal: Bitcoin Realized Profit And Loss Fall To October 2020 Levels Knowing that there have been deposits to exchanges only tells us a part of the story, however, as the indicator used here doesn&#8217;t specify which type of platforms the inflows have been towards. A modified version of the indicator, which only tracks deposits to derivative exchanges, reveals that the transfers have been almost entirely toward the derivative platforms. The value of the metric seems to have spiked recently &#124; Source: CryptoQuant When miners plan to sell their coins, they make deposits to spot exchanges. Since they have sent their Bitcoin to derivative platforms instead this time, it would seem likely that the intent behind their transfers may not have been selling after all. As for what effect this might have on the market; usually more derivative positions being opened usually results in higher price volatility. However, this volatility can go either bullish or bearish, depending on the wider sentiment. BTC Price At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading around $27,400, up 6% in the last week. BTC has observed an uplift today &#124; Source: BTCUSD on TradingView Featured image from Michael Förtsch on Unsplash.com, charts from TradingView.com, CryptoQuant.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On-chain data shows that Bitcoin miners have been depositing large amounts to exchanges. Here&#8217;s what this could mean for the asset&#8217;s price.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Miners Have Been Depositing Big To Exchanges Recently</h2>
<p>An analyst in a CryptoQuant <a href="https://cryptoquant.com/insights/quicktake/64915a1f2ec8802caad61604-The-miners-activity-indicates-selling-pressure-on-the-crypto-market" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">post</a> pointed out that BTC miners have been transferring coins out of their wallets recently. The relevant indicator here is the &#8220;miner outflow,&#8221; which measures the total amount of Bitcoin miners withdraw from their combined supply.</p>
<p>The counterpart metric, the &#8220;<a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-miner-inflows-to-exchanges-reach-2021-levels-as-bear-trend-persists/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">miner inflow</a>,&#8221; naturally keeps track of the reverse flow of coins. Here is a chart that shows the trend in both the Bitcoin miner outflow and the inflow over the past few days:</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone aligncenter" src="https://img.cryptoquant.com/35320/quicktake/pesme7Ov_974684484b4dc58e64c0ea727e091a21bf4d1373938b0cd71ab1de327b03c05e.png" alt="Bitcoin Miners" width="1280" height="610"/></p>

<p>The above graph shows that the Bitcoin miner outflow has observed a spike during the past day, while the inflow has remained relatively low. This would imply that the miners have transferred a net amount of coins from their wallets in this period.</p>

<p>Generally, whenever miners withdraw coins from their wallets, there is always a risk that they are doing so to sell said coins. Such selling can naturally have a bearish effect on the cryptocurrency&#8217;s value.</p>
<p>One way to better guess the intent behind these withdrawals is by checking whether the destination of the coins is a centralized exchange platform.</p>
<p>The chart also shows the data for the Bitcoin miner to exchange flow. This indicator specifically keeps track of the coins flowing from these chain validators&#8217; holdings to exchange wallets.</p>
<p>This indicator has also seen a sharp spike at the same time as the miner outflow surge. The magnitude of both spikes is also pretty much the same; both are slightly above 1,000 BTC. Thus, almost all the outflows from the past day appear to have headed toward exchanges.</p>

<p>Knowing that there have been deposits to exchanges only tells us a part of the story, however, as the indicator used here doesn&#8217;t specify which type of platforms the inflows have been towards.</p>
<p>A modified version of the indicator, which only tracks deposits to <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-miners-deposit-big-derivatives-exchanges/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">derivative exchanges</a>, reveals that the transfers have been almost entirely toward the derivative platforms.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone aligncenter" src="https://img.cryptoquant.com/35320/quicktake/e0LVv_0f47bccb831c5eea58b9fed2c41c5eef6b6fb8e9fe6f40d8f1e25d74ad001ef7.png" alt="Bitcoin Miner Derivative Inflows" width="1280" height="806"/></p>

<p>When miners plan to sell their coins, they make deposits to spot exchanges. Since they have sent their Bitcoin to derivative platforms instead this time, it would seem likely that the intent behind their transfers may not have been selling after all.</p>
<p>As for what effect this might have on the market; usually more derivative positions being opened usually results in higher price volatility. However, this volatility can go either bullish or bearish, depending on the wider sentiment.</p>
<h2>BTC Price</h2>
<p>At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading around $27,400, up 6% in the last week.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium aligncenter" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/ZY6fSosj/" alt="Bitcoin Price Chart" width="1534" height="911"/></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/michael-fortsch-kS5ygaqoPKM-unsplash-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dash Price Surges 10% In A Single Week; Is A Bullish Momentum Forming?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/altcoin/dash-price-surges-10-in-a-single-week-is-a-bullish-momentum-forming/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Opeyemi Sule]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 21:30:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dash]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DASHUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Digital Cash]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=538799</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Digital Cash, popularly known as DASH, has been on a remarkable spring, reaching today’s top gainers. The cryptocurrency is on a good streak, with its value jumping by 5% in the past 24 hours.  Related Reading: Optimism (OP) Soars Over 6% Following Launch On BNB Chain Dash Surges Over 10% In A Single Week &#8211; Price Overview The price of DASH soared by more than 10% in the past week. As of this writing, the token is valued at $32.08, gaining over 5% in the past 24 hours, per CoinGecko data. Meanwhile, it boasts a daily trading volume of nearly $45 million.  However, a broader look at the market shows that the price of DASH has barely made it out of consolidation in the past 10 days. This is following the almost-vertical price dip earlier this month, which saw the token lose nearly 26% of its value. DASH, a scalable payment network, has had a mixed first half of the year. On the 28th of February, the cryptocurrency&#8217;s price reached a crest of $74.26. The token has been on a downtrend since March, recording a 56.8% price decline. Although the current price rally of DASH is a bit encouraging, it would take an extraordinary run for the token to return to its peak from earlier this year.  Is Bullish Momentum Building for Dash?  As DASH continues gaining momentum and captivates the crypto community&#8217;s attention, many investors wonder if the token could attain the heights reached earlier this year.  Based on DASH’s 24-hour chart, RSI (Relative Strength Index) has just crossed above 36, indicating that a bullish run may be on the horizon. Meanwhile, the token’s Moving average convergence/divergence (MACD) has just crossed above the signal line below the baseline, indicating a strong bullish signal.  DASHUSD trading at $31.73 &#124; Source: DASHUSD chart from TradingView According to the price prediction site, Coincodex, the current investor sentiment surrounding the DASH token remains bearish, with a neutral Fear &#38; Greed Index of 49. Coincodex predicts DASH to plummet by 6.53% in the next five days, falling to $29.69. However, they project the token to make a recovery trading as high as $35.12 later in one month. Notwithstanding, investors are advised to approach the market cautiously, having done their due diligence. Related Reading: Bitcoin Whales Continue To Accumulate As BTC Makes Recovery Push Featured image from MEXC Global, chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Digital Cash, popularly known as DASH, has been on a remarkable spring, reaching today’s top gainers. The cryptocurrency is on a good streak, with its value jumping by 5% in the past 24 hours. </p>

<h2>Dash Surges Over 10% In A Single Week &#8211; Price Overview</h2>
<p>The price of DASH soared by more than 10% in the past week. As of this writing, the token is valued at $32.08, gaining over 5% in the past 24 hours, per <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/dash" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">CoinGecko data</a>. Meanwhile, it boasts a daily trading volume of nearly $45 million. </p>
<p>However, a broader look at the market shows that the price of DASH has barely made it out of consolidation in the past 10 days. This is following the almost-vertical price dip earlier this month, which saw the token lose nearly 26% of its value.</p>
<p>DASH, a scalable payment network, has had a mixed first half of the year. On the 28th of February, the cryptocurrency&#8217;s price reached a crest of $74.26. The token has been on a downtrend since March, recording a 56.8% price decline.</p>
<p>Although the current price rally of DASH is a bit encouraging, it would take an extraordinary run for the token to return to its peak from earlier this year. </p>
<h2>Is Bullish Momentum Building for Dash? </h2>
<p>As DASH continues gaining momentum and captivates the crypto community&#8217;s attention, many investors wonder if the token could attain the heights reached earlier this year. </p>
<p>Based on DASH’s 24-hour chart, RSI (Relative Strength Index) has just crossed above 36, indicating that a bullish run may be on the horizon. Meanwhile, the token’s Moving average convergence/divergence (MACD) has just crossed above the signal line below the baseline, indicating a strong bullish signal. </p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/dp3R3oYF/" alt="DASH" width="1009" height="534"/></p>

<p>According to the price prediction site, Coincodex, the current investor sentiment surrounding the DASH token remains bearish, with a neutral Fear &amp; Greed Index of 49.</p>
<p>Coincodex predicts DASH to plummet by 6.53% in the next five days, falling to $29.69. However, they project the token to make a recovery trading as high as $35.12 later in one month.</p>
<p>Notwithstanding, investors are advised to approach the market cautiously, having done their due diligence.</p>



]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/DASH-Token-MEXC-1-460x259.jpeg" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Breaks Out Of Ichimoku Cloud, Storms Toward $28,000</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-prepares-ichimoku-cloud-breakout-will-crypto-storm-to-new-aths/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tony "The Bull"]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 20:56:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc cme]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CME futures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ichimoku]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ichimoku Cloud]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xbt]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xbtusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=538811</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin price has made an intraday move higher, pushing above the Ichimoku cloud on BTC CME Futures daily charts. This signal in the past sent the entire cryptocurrency market soaring higher. Will crypto once again continue to storm ahead, or is it about to rain more pain on investors? Bitcoin Storms Above $28,000 After Technical Breakout BTCUSD made a 4% move higher today. While the number is rather insignificant, the minor rally was enough for a major breakout of the Ichimoku cloud on daily timeframes. Related Reading: Bitcoin Recovers Above Critical Level, Why Bulls Could Be Ready To Charge Importantly, the signal has only appeared on BTC CME Futures daily charts thus far. On spot BTCUSD charts, Bitcoin has a little more to climb. However, the breakout on the BTC1 continuous contract chart could be a prelude of what’s to come. Shortly after price action peeked above the top of the cloud, the top cryptocurrency by market cap immediately stormed toward $28,000 per coin. And if history is anything to go by, sky could be the limit on higher prices. Bitcoin has breached above the cloud &#124; BTCUSD on TradingView.com Why Blasting Above The Cloud Could Mean Liftoff For Crypto The Ichimoku cloud consists of Senkou span A and B. When these two spans twist it turns the cloud from green to red, or from red to green. The cloud itself also expands and contracts based on price volatility, and can act as support and resistance. Related Reading: Bitcoin “Throwback” Could Trigger Flawless Technical Bottom Formation Bitcoin escaping the Ichimoku cloud was a crucial breach of dynamic resistance. In the comparison above, BTC leaving the cloud in 2020 led to the most recent bullish rally in crypto. In 2021 after the second top at $68,000 per coin, Bitcoin then retested the cloud and fell right through it. This time, not only did the retest hold, but today’s rally just pushed BTC CME Futures daily chart above the cloud, the Tenkan-sen, and the Kijun-sen. This means that according to the Ichimoku, there is very little daily resistance left. If Bitcoin does behave like the last time it left the cloud, it could be time for liftoff. A close above the cloud could clear #Bitcoin for liftoff 2020&#215;2023 pic.twitter.com/CtC9RyEXen — Tony &#8220;The Bull&#8221; (@tonythebullBTC) June 20, 2023 Tony is the author of the CoinChartist (VIP) newsletter. Follow @TonyTheBullBTC &#38; @coinchartist_io on Twitter. Or join the TonyTradesBTC Telegram for daily market insights and technical analysis education. Please note: Content is educational and should not be considered investment advice. Featured image from iStockPhoto, Charts from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin price has made an intraday move higher, pushing above the Ichimoku cloud on BTC CME Futures daily charts.</p>
<p>This signal in the past sent the entire cryptocurrency market soaring higher. Will crypto once again continue to storm ahead, or is it about to rain more pain on investors?</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Storms Above $28,000 After Technical Breakout</h2>
<p>BTCUSD made a 4% move higher today. While the number is rather insignificant, the minor rally was enough for a major breakout of the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/topic/ichimoku-cloud/">Ichimoku cloud</a> on daily timeframes.</p>

<p>Importantly, the signal has only appeared on BTC CME Futures daily charts thus far. On spot BTCUSD charts, Bitcoin has a little more to climb. However, the breakout on the BTC1 continuous contract chart could be a prelude of what’s to come.</p>
<p>Shortly after price action peeked above the top of the cloud, the top cryptocurrency by market cap immediately stormed toward $28,000 per coin. And if history is anything to go by, sky could be the limit on higher prices.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-large wp-image-538858 aligncenter" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTC1_2023-06-20_16-50-57-860x409.png" alt="bitcoin ichimoku" width="860" height="409" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTC1_2023-06-20_16-50-57-860x409.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTC1_2023-06-20_16-50-57-460x219.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTC1_2023-06-20_16-50-57-768x366.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTC1_2023-06-20_16-50-57-1536x731.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTC1_2023-06-20_16-50-57-2048x975.png 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTC1_2023-06-20_16-50-57-750x357.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTC1_2023-06-20_16-50-57-1140x543.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/></p>
<p style="text-align: center">Bitcoin has breached above the cloud | <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BTCUSD?aff_id=118619" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">BTCUSD on TradingView.com</a></p>
<h2>Why Blasting Above The Cloud Could Mean Liftoff For Crypto</h2>
<p>The <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/topic/ichimoku-cloud/">Ichimoku cloud</a> consists of Senkou span A and B. When these two spans twist it turns the cloud from green to red, or from red to green. The cloud itself also expands and contracts based on price volatility, and can act as support and resistance.</p>

<p>Bitcoin escaping the Ichimoku cloud was a crucial breach of dynamic resistance. In the comparison above, BTC leaving the cloud in 2020 led to the most recent bullish rally in crypto. In 2021 after the second top at $68,000 per coin, Bitcoin then retested the cloud and fell right through it.</p>
<p>This time, not only did the retest hold, but today’s rally just pushed BTC CME Futures daily chart above the cloud, the Tenkan-sen, and the Kijun-sen. This means that according to the Ichimoku, there is very little daily resistance left. If Bitcoin does behave like the last time it left the cloud, it could be time for liftoff.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">A close above the cloud could clear <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Bitcoin?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#Bitcoin</a> for liftoff</p>
<p>2020&#215;2023 <a href="https://t.co/CtC9RyEXen" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/CtC9RyEXen</a></p>
<p>— Tony &#8220;The Bull&#8221; (@tonythebullBTC) <a href="https://twitter.com/tonythebullBTC/status/1671190085675393026?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">June 20, 2023</a></p></blockquote>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/3d-realistic-render-of-a-cloud-with-thunderstorm.jpg_s1024x1024wisk20cyCWsZwXMVN0np-DML5iArF6GLgwdwjuOudjf_UkA9c0-460x259.jpg" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Litecoin Sees 55% Increase In New Daily Addresses As Bullish Sentiment Grows</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/litecoin/litecoin-sees-55-increase-in-new-daily-addresses-as-bullish-sentiment-grows/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 20:30:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Litecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Litecoin Halving]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ltc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ltc price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ltc/usd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LTCUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=538786</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bullish sentiment around Litecoin has been on the rise as the network is drawing closer to its much-anticipated halving event. This positive sentiment is reflected in the number of new daily addresses on the blockchain, which has seen a significant rise over the last week. Litecoin New Addresses Jump 55% In 7 Days In a Twitter post, on-chain data aggregator IntoTheBlock revealed that the number of new addresses on the Litecoin network has been on the rise. Notably, the majority of the growth has been recorded in the last week alone when the total new addresses jumped a whopping 55%. Active addresses &#38; new addresses are back on the rise for #Litecoin. Daily active addresses saw a 28% 7-day increase &#38; new addresses saw a 54.6% 7-day increase! Source: https://t.co/POjEVdh92n pic.twitter.com/PCbcGV7mFH — IntoTheBlock (@intotheblock) June 19, 2023 This meteoric rise in new addresses saw Litecoin’s total addresses cross the 200 million level. This new milestone meant that the total number of LTC addresses has now surpassed that of Ethereum’s 180 million. However, it is still a long way from its biggest rival Bitcoin, which currently boasts over 1 billion total addresses. Related Reading: Best Crypto Narrative For This Summer? Everything About LSDfi Nonetheless, the rapid rise in new Litecoin addresses shows that the bullish sentiment is spreading as new investors flock to the blockchain. This is all happening ahead of the Litecoin halving happening less than two months from now. LTC price trending at 76.12 ahead of halving &#124; Source: LTCUSD on TradingView.com LTC Halving Could See Price Soar The Litecoin halving is an event that sees the block reward for miners on the network cut down in half. It works just like Bitcoin in this way as it happens every four years, and creates an environment of scarcity for the cryptocurrency. This is why the halving can be a bullish event for the digital asset. LTC’s next halving is taking place approximately 44 days from now at a block height of 2,520,000. This halving reward will cut block rewards down from 12.5 LTC to 6.25 LTC, and a block is produced on Litecoin approximately every two-and-a-half minutes. LTC halving happening at block height 2,520,000 &#124; Source: NiceHash As the block rewards are set to be cut in half, investors are flocking to the digital asset in hopes that the halving will trigger a rally. This is not out of the ordinary given that has been the case in the past. Presently, LTC is trading at $76 apiece but as bullish sentiment rises leading up to the event, the cryptocurrency could easily cross the $100 mark. Related Reading: Bitcoin Whales Continue To Accumulate As BTC Makes Recovery Push For now, the bears remain in control as LTC continues to trade well below its 50-day and 100-day moving averages. As momentum picks up leading up to the halving, this is expected to change, putting the buyers in charge of determining its fair price. LTC price is down 0.70% in the last 24 hours and 1.45% on the 7-day chart. Featured image from Currency.com, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="p1">Bullish sentiment around Litecoin has been on the rise as the network is drawing closer to its much-anticipated halving event. This positive sentiment is reflected in the number of new daily addresses on the blockchain, which has seen a significant rise over the last week.</p>
<h2 class="p1">Litecoin New Addresses Jump 55% In 7 Days</h2>
<p class="p1">In a Twitter post, on-chain data aggregator IntoTheBlock revealed that the number of new addresses on the Litecoin network has been on the rise. Notably, the majority of the growth has been recorded in the last week alone when the total new addresses jumped a whopping 55%.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Active addresses &amp; new addresses are back on the rise for <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Litecoin?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#Litecoin</a>. Daily active addresses saw a 28% 7-day increase &amp; new addresses saw a 54.6% 7-day increase!
Source: <a href="https://t.co/POjEVdh92n" rel="nofollow">https://t.co/POjEVdh92n</a> <a href="https://t.co/PCbcGV7mFH" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/PCbcGV7mFH</a></p>
<p>— IntoTheBlock (@intotheblock) <a href="https://twitter.com/intotheblock/status/1670769366885859330?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">June 19, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p class="p1">This meteoric rise in new addresses saw Litecoin’s total addresses cross the 200 million level. This new milestone meant that the total number of LTC addresses has now surpassed that of Ethereum’s 180 million. However, it is still a long way from its biggest rival Bitcoin, which currently boasts over 1 billion total addresses.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/best-crypto-narrative-summer-lsdfi/?swcfpc=1">Best Crypto Narrative For This Summer? Everything About LSDfi</a></p>
<p class="p1">Nonetheless, the rapid rise in new Litecoin addresses shows that the bullish sentiment is spreading as new investors flock to the blockchain. This is all happening ahead of the Litecoin halving happening less than two months from now.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/bQijFT40/" alt="Litecoin (LTC) price chart from TradingView.com" width="2884" height="1724"/></p>

<h2 class="p1">LTC Halving Could See Price Soar</h2>
<p class="p1">The Litecoin halving is an event that sees the block reward for miners on the network cut down in half. It works just like Bitcoin in this way as it happens every four years, and creates an environment of scarcity for the cryptocurrency. This is why the halving can be a bullish event for the digital asset.</p>
<p class="p1">LTC’s next halving is taking place approximately 44 days from now at a block height of 2,520,000. This halving reward will cut block rewards down from 12.5 LTC to 6.25 LTC, and a block is produced on Litecoin approximately every two-and-a-half minutes.</p>


<p class="p1">As the block rewards are set to be cut in half, investors are flocking to the digital asset in hopes that the halving will trigger a rally. This is not out of the ordinary given that has been the case in the past. Presently, LTC is trading at $76 apiece but as bullish sentiment rises leading up to the event, the cryptocurrency could easily cross the $100 mark.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-whales-continue-accumulate-btc-recovery/?swcfpc=1">Bitcoin Whales Continue To Accumulate As BTC Makes Recovery Push</a></p>
<p class="p1">For now, the bears remain in control as LTC continues to trade well below its 50-day and 100-day moving averages. As momentum picks up leading up to the halving, this is expected to change, putting the buyers in charge of determining its fair price.</p>
<p class="p1">LTC price is down 0.70% in the last 24 hours and 1.45% on the 7-day chart.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Litecoin-1-460x307.jpeg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Stacks (STX) Registers 11% Gains As Broader Market Suffers Volatility</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/stacks/stacks-stx-registers-11-gains-as-broader-market-suffers-volatility/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Kent Glory]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 19:30:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Stacks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stacks (STX)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stacks analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[STX price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[STXUSD]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=538772</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[While the broader crypto market experiences turbulent times and volatility, Stacks (STX) stands out with an impressive performance. Stacks is a network created in 2017 as an extension of the Bitcoin blockchain, allowing developers to create and deploy smart contracts. In recent times its native token, called STX, has been exhibiting positive performance in its price movement following the popularity of Bitcoin Ordinals.  Amidst Market Turbulence, Stacks (STX) Defies the Odds, Showcasing a Resilient 11% Surge The price of STX recorded a significant increase of 21.57% in the last 7-day trading session. At the time of writing, STX is still maintaining its bullish momentum. It shows a notable increase of 11.33%, representing its current value of $0.6300. Related Reading: Best Crypto Narrative For This Summer? Everything About LSDfi According to data from CoinMarketCap, STX&#8217;s 24-hour trading volume is experiencing a massive pump of 387.11%, standing at $147 million. This increase suggests strong investor demand and positive sentiment surrounding the asset, potentially indicating a bullish trend. A fundamental factor driving the price of Stacks (STX) is the Bitcoin-based NFTs called Ordinals that have experienced increased adoption. Based on data from Dune analytics, the launch of Ordinals has led to nearly 12,906,466 Bitcoin inscriptions on the network.  This has increased network activity, causing the price of STX to rise significantly. However, with increasing scrutiny and regulatory measures impacting various cryptocurrencies, STX became the first token approved by the SEC.  This approval may have contributed to boosting its price by attracting investors. This regulatory approval sets STX apart from other tokens and reassures investors regarding its legitimacy and regulatory compliance. Stacks Daily Chart Stacks (STX) price is currently above the middle band at the time of analysis. It is heading straight toward the upper band of the Bollinger Bands indicator, suggesting a strong upward momentum. This indicates potential bullishness, with the possibility of the price continuing to rise and reaching higher levels. Also, the Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD) is above the signal line; the histogram bars also display strong green bars. This suggests the asset&#8217;s positive momentum is strengthening, potentially signaling further upward price movement. Related Reading: Bitcoin Whales Continue To Accumulate As BTC Makes Recovery Push The Stacks token, STX, currently trades between its significant support and resistance levels of $0.4679 and $0.6762, respectively. Based on the chart, the asset is moving straight to its primary resistance level of $0.6762. The move suggests that the buyer&#8217;s pressure has outweighed that of the sellers. If the bulls break this level successfully, the next significant resistance point is $0.8294. General Crypto Market Performance Might Boost STX Notably, the global crypto market cap has reached $1.07 trillion, marking a 0.44% increase in the last day. In the past 24 hours, the total crypto market volume has also surged to $29.04 billion, a significant 44.09% rise. According to CoinMarketCap data, Bitcoin&#8217;s dominance has risen to 48.45%, showing a 0.30% increase throughout the day. These metrics suggest that the crypto market is regaining its positive move today and might also rub off on STX. Featured image from Pixabay and chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>While the broader crypto market experiences turbulent times and volatility, Stacks (STX) stands out with an impressive performance.</p>
<p>Stacks is a network created in 2017 as an extension of the Bitcoin blockchain, allowing developers to create and deploy smart contracts. In recent times its native token, called STX, has been exhibiting positive performance in its price movement following the popularity of Bitcoin Ordinals. </p>
<h2>Amidst Market Turbulence, Stacks (STX) Defies the Odds, Showcasing a Resilient 11% Surge</h2>
<p>The price of STX recorded a significant increase of 21.57% in the last 7-day trading session. At the time of writing, STX is still maintaining its bullish momentum. It shows a notable increase of 11.33%, representing its current value of $0.6300.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/best-crypto-narrative-summer-lsdfi/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Best Crypto Narrative For This Summer? Everything About LSDfi</a></p>
<p>According to <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/stacks/#Statistics" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">data</a> from CoinMarketCap, STX&#8217;s 24-hour trading volume is experiencing a massive pump of 387.11%, standing at $147 million. This increase suggests strong investor demand and positive sentiment surrounding the asset, potentially indicating a bullish trend.</p>
<p>A fundamental factor driving the price of Stacks (STX) is the Bitcoin-based NFTs called Ordinals that have experienced increased adoption. Based on data from <a href="https://dune.com/dataalways/ordinals" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Dune analytics</a>, the launch of Ordinals has led to nearly 12,906,466 Bitcoin inscriptions on the network. </p>
<p>This has increased network activity, causing the price of STX to rise significantly. However, with increasing scrutiny and regulatory measures impacting various cryptocurrencies, STX became <a href="https://blog.blockstack.org/blockstack-token-sale-sec-qualified" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">the first token approved by the SEC</a>.  This approval may have contributed to boosting its price by attracting investors.</p>
<p>This regulatory approval sets STX apart from other tokens and reassures investors regarding its legitimacy and regulatory compliance.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/kFLhWE5R/" alt="STXUSD price chart" width="980" height="538"/>
<h2>Stacks Daily Chart</h2>
<p>Stacks (STX) price is currently above the middle band at the time of analysis. It is heading straight toward the upper band of the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/chart/93cDzL9M/?symbol=BINANCE%3ASTXUSDT" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Bollinger Bands indicator,</a> suggesting a strong upward momentum. This indicates potential bullishness, with the possibility of the price continuing to rise and reaching higher levels.</p>
<p>Also, the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/chart/93cDzL9M/?symbol=BINANCE%3ASTXUSDT" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Moving Average Convergence Divergence</a> (MACD) is above the signal line; the histogram bars also display strong green bars. This suggests the asset&#8217;s positive momentum is strengthening, potentially signaling further upward price movement.</p>

<p>The Stacks token, STX, currently trades between its significant support and resistance levels of $0.4679 and $0.6762, respectively. Based on the chart, the asset is moving straight to its primary resistance level of $0.6762. The move suggests that the buyer&#8217;s pressure has outweighed that of the sellers. If the bulls break this level successfully, the next significant resistance point is $0.8294.</p>
General Crypto Market Performance Might Boost STX
<p>Notably, the global crypto market cap has reached $1.07 trillion, marking a 0.44% increase in the last day. In the past 24 hours, the total crypto market volume has also surged to $29.04 billion, a significant 44.09% rise. According to <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">CoinMarketCap data</a>, Bitcoin&#8217;s dominance has risen to 48.45%, showing a 0.30% increase throughout the day.</p>
<p>These metrics suggest that the crypto market is regaining its positive move today and might also rub off on STX.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Stacks-1-460x298.jpg" width="460" height="298" />	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
