<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
>

<channel>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.newsbtc.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<description>Bitcoin &#38; Cryptocurrency News Today</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 02:59:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Price Signals Downside Correction Before Fresh Increase</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-correction-29200/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 02:59:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xbtusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=539591</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin price is correcting gains from the $31,400 zone. BTC could revisit the $29,200 support or even $28,500 before it starts a fresh increase. Bitcoin is currently correcting gains from the $31,400 zone. The price is trading below $30,500 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average. There is a connecting bearish trend line forming with resistance near $30,550 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Kraken). The pair could continue to correct lower toward the $29,200 support or $28,500. Bitcoin Price Starts Downside Correction Bitcoin price remained well-bid above the $29,500 resistance zone. BTC cleared the $30,000 resistance to move further into a positive zone. Finally, there was a push above the $31,000 zone. The price tested the $31,500 zone. A high is formed near $31,435 and the price is now correcting lower. There was a move below the $30,500 level. The price traded below the 50% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $29,550 swing low to the $31,435 high. Bitcoin price is now trading below $30,500 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average. There is also a connecting bearish trend line forming with resistance near $30,550 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair. The pair is trading close to the 76.4% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $29,550 swing low to the $31,435 high. If the price remains stable above the $30,000 level, it could soon start a fresh increase. On the upside, the price is facing resistance near the $30,400 level and the 100 hourly Simple moving average. Source: BTCUSD on TradingView.com The first major resistance is near the $30,550 level and the trend line, above which the price might revisit the $31,400 resistance zone. The next major resistance is near the $32,000 level. Any more gains could send the price toward the $32,500 resistance zone. More Downsides in BTC? If Bitcoin’s price fails to clear the $30,550 resistance, it could continue to move down. Immediate support on the downside is near the $30,000 level. The next major support is near the $29,550 level, below which there is a risk of a move toward the $29,200 support. Any more losses might send the price toward $28,500 in the near term. Technical indicators: Hourly MACD – The MACD is now gaining pace in the bearish zone. Hourly RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BTC/USD is below the 50 level. Major Support Levels – $30,000, followed by $29,550. Major Resistance Levels – $30,400, $30,550, and $31,400.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>Bitcoin price is correcting gains from the $31,400 zone. BTC could revisit the $29,200 support or even $28,500 before it starts a fresh increase.</em></p>
<ul>
<li>Bitcoin is currently correcting gains from the $31,400 zone.</li>
<li>The price is trading below $30,500 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average.</li>
<li>There is a connecting bearish trend line forming with resistance near $30,550 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could continue to correct lower toward the $29,200 support or $28,500.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Bitcoin Price Starts Downside Correction</h2>
<p>Bitcoin price remained well-bid above the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-rally-pauses-30800/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">$29,500 resistance zone</a>. BTC cleared the $30,000 resistance to move further into a positive zone. Finally, there was a push above the $31,000 zone.</p>
<p>The price tested the $31,500 zone. A high is formed near $31,435 and the price is now correcting lower. There was a move below the $30,500 level. The price traded below the 50% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $29,550 swing low to the $31,435 high.</p>
<p>Bitcoin price is now trading below $30,500 and the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-bulls-pushing-30k/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">100 hourly Simple moving average</a>. There is also a connecting bearish trend line forming with resistance near $30,550 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair.</p>
<p>The pair is trading close to the 76.4% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $29,550 swing low to the $31,435 high. If the price remains stable above the $30,000 level, it could soon start a fresh increase. On the upside, the price is facing resistance near the $30,400 level and the 100 hourly Simple moving average.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-539592" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-17.png" alt="Bitcoin Price" width="1835" height="845" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-17.png 1835w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-17-460x212.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-17-860x396.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-17-768x354.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-17-1536x707.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-17-750x345.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-17-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1835px) 100vw, 1835px"/></p>
<p>Source: <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BTCUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">BTCUSD on TradingView.com</a></p>
<p>The first major resistance is near the $30,550 level and the trend line, above which the price might revisit the $31,400 resistance zone. The next major resistance is near the $32,000 level. Any more gains could send the price toward the $32,500 resistance zone.</p>
<h2>More Downsides in BTC?</h2>
<p>If Bitcoin’s price fails to clear the $30,550 resistance, it could continue to move down. Immediate support on the downside is near the $30,000 level.</p>
<p>The next major support is near the $29,550 level, below which there is a risk of a move toward the $29,200 support. Any more losses might send the price toward $28,500 in the near term.</p>
<p>Technical indicators:</p>
<p>Hourly MACD – The MACD is now gaining pace in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>Hourly RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BTC/USD is below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Levels – $30,000, followed by $29,550.</p>
<p>Major Resistance Levels – $30,400, $30,550, and $31,400.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/04/shutterstock_638895124-460x264.jpg" width="460" height="264" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>PEPE Rising: 63% Weekly Gain Showcases Unstoppable Momentum</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/pepe-rising-63-weekly-gain-showcases-unstoppable-momentum/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Olowoporoku Adeniyi]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2023 07:30:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PEPE]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PEPE price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PEPE Pump]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=539578</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The cryptocurrency market has shown no signs of slowing down, with several coins experiencing an extended bull run in recent days. However, amidst this overall market trend, there are still standout performers, and Pepe (PEPE) is one such cryptocurrency that continues to impress. Related Reading: Momentum: Why The Bitcoin Train Is Ready To Leave The Station While many altcoins are charting modest gains or losses, Pepe stands out with a remarkable performance. Over the past 48 hours, PEPE has surged by 10%, adding to its impressive weekly gains of 63%. This makes Pepe the second-best performer of the week after Bitcoin Cash.  PEPE Sustains Positive Momentum In contrast to the choppy price action seen across the market, Pepe upward momentum remains strong, reflecting positive investor sentiment and demand for the token. This surge in value is particularly noteworthy considering the recent major rally in the market, suggesting that Pepe has managed to sustain and build upon its positive momentum. Looking at the broader market, Bitcoin (BTC) is currently trading at a critical level of $30,000, with bulls fiercely battling to defend this important psychological and technical support. While Bitcoin has experienced a slight gain of 0.3% in the past 24 hours, it has still recorded a notable weekly gain of 14.4%. Bitcoin&#8217;s dominance in the market has also increased, reaching 48% compared to 47.7% the previous day. This indicates that Bitcoin outperforms altcoins, further emphasizing its significance and influence within the market. Related Reading: Stacks (STX) Rallies By 29% In The Past 7 Days – Here’s Why As the week approaches, market participants will closely observe the incoming volume and its potential impact on price movements. While the overall market may be experiencing a slowdown, Pepe&#8217;s impressive gains and resilience showcase its potential to continue defying the current market trend. It will be interesting to monitor how Pepe and other cryptocurrencies perform during this period of reduced trading activity. Despite the market&#8217;s current challenges, Pepe&#8217;s ongoing positive trajectory demonstrates its strength and the growing confidence investors have in its potential for further growth. What’s Next For The Memecoin? Pepe has shown resilience in the market and is expected to reach a maximum price of $0.000003 as the market recovers from the crypto winter. The minimum expected price is projected to be around $0.000002, while the average price will likely hover around $0.000002. These price predictions indicate potential growth and stability for Pepe as market conditions improve and investor confidence returns. Currently, Pepe is valued at $0.00000147 per PEPE/USD, with a market capitalization of $577.58 million USD and a 24-hour trading volume of $622.48 million USD. Although Pepe has experienced a decline of 0.81% in the past 24 hours, it is important to note that the cryptocurrency market can be highly volatile, and price fluctuations are common. Nevertheless, Pepe demonstrates a substantial market presence and continues attracting investors&#8217; attention. Featured image from Unsplash.com, charts from CoinMarketCap and TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The cryptocurrency market has shown no signs of slowing down, with several coins experiencing an extended bull run in recent days. However, amidst this overall market trend, there are still standout performers, and Pepe (PEPE) is one such cryptocurrency that continues to impress.</p>
<p><strong>Related Reading:</strong> <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/momentum-why-the-bitcoin-train-station/?swcfpc=1">Momentum: Why The Bitcoin Train Is Ready To Leave The Station</a></p>
<p>While many altcoins are charting modest gains or losses, Pepe stands out with a remarkable performance. Over the past 48 hours, PEPE has surged by 10%, adding to its impressive weekly gains of 63%. This makes Pepe the second-best performer of the week after Bitcoin Cash. </p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium wp-image-539579" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Screenshot_174-460x132.png" alt="Pepe price resurgence has been second only to Bitcoin Cash; source @Coinmarketcap" width="460" height="132" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Screenshot_174-460x132.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Screenshot_174-768x220.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Screenshot_174-750x214.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Screenshot_174.png 815w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px"/>
<h2><strong>PEPE Sustains Positive Momentum</strong></h2>
<p>In contrast to the choppy price action seen across the market, Pepe upward momentum remains strong, reflecting positive investor sentiment and demand for the token. This surge in value is particularly noteworthy considering the recent major rally in the market, suggesting that Pepe has managed to sustain and build upon its positive momentum.</p>
<p>Looking at the broader market, Bitcoin (BTC) is currently trading at a critical level of $30,000, with bulls fiercely battling to defend this important psychological and technical support. While Bitcoin has experienced a slight gain of 0.3% in the past 24 hours, it has still recorded a notable weekly gain of 14.4%. Bitcoin&#8217;s dominance in the market has also increased, reaching 48% compared to 47.7% the previous day. This indicates that Bitcoin outperforms altcoins, further emphasizing its significance and influence within the market.</p>
<p><strong>Related Reading:</strong> <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/stacks-stx-rallies-by-29-in-the-past-7-days-heres-why/?swcfpc=1">Stacks (STX) Rallies By 29% In The Past 7 Days – Here’s Why</a></p>
<p>As the week approaches, market participants will closely observe the incoming volume and its potential impact on price movements. While the overall market may be experiencing a slowdown, Pepe&#8217;s impressive gains and resilience showcase its potential to continue defying the current market trend.</p>
<p>It will be interesting to monitor how Pepe and other cryptocurrencies perform during this period of reduced trading activity. Despite the market&#8217;s current challenges, Pepe&#8217;s ongoing positive trajectory demonstrates its strength and the growing confidence investors have in its potential for further growth.</p>
<h2><strong>What’s Next For The Memecoin?</strong></h2>
<p>Pepe has shown resilience in the market and is expected to reach a maximum price of $0.000003 as the market recovers from the crypto winter. The minimum expected price is projected to be around $0.000002, while the average price will likely hover around $0.000002. These price predictions indicate potential growth and stability for Pepe as market conditions improve and investor confidence returns.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-539580 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/PEPEUSDT_2023-06-25_07-57-22-860x432.png" alt="Pepe price is still riding the momentum ahead of the new week: source @Tradingview.com" width="860" height="432" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/PEPEUSDT_2023-06-25_07-57-22-860x432.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/PEPEUSDT_2023-06-25_07-57-22-460x231.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/PEPEUSDT_2023-06-25_07-57-22-768x386.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/PEPEUSDT_2023-06-25_07-57-22-360x180.png 360w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/PEPEUSDT_2023-06-25_07-57-22-750x377.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/PEPEUSDT_2023-06-25_07-57-22-1140x573.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/PEPEUSDT_2023-06-25_07-57-22.png 1479w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/>
<p>Currently, Pepe is valued at $0.00000147 per PEPE/USD, with a market capitalization of $577.58 million USD and a 24-hour trading volume of $622.48 million USD. Although Pepe has experienced a decline of 0.81% in the past 24 hours, it is important to note that the cryptocurrency market can be highly volatile, and price fluctuations are common. Nevertheless, Pepe demonstrates a substantial market presence and continues attracting investors&#8217; attention.</p>
<p><em>Featured image from Unsplash.com, charts from CoinMarketCap and TradingView.com</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/jack-hamilton-EP_OHkgn1JI-unsplash-1-460x359.jpg" width="460" height="359" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Optimism (OP) Price Crafts A Bullish Cup, But Can It Sustain The Momentum?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/optimism-2/optimism-op-price-crafts-a-bullish-cup-but-can-it-sustain-the-momentum/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ebo Victor]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2023 06:39:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Optimism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bullish]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[OP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[optimism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=539537</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Optimism, a layer-2 solution on the Ethereum blockchain, has gained traction with a TVL exceeding $1.22 billion. The OP price is currently forming a bullish cup pattern, indicating a potential recovery. Trading activity in the optimism crypto market has surged, suggesting an attempt by the OP price to rebound. Optimism: A Quick Look As a layer-2 blockchain solution, transactions are recorded on the Optimism blockchain and then stored on the Ethereum blockchain. During the development of Optimism&#8217;s Layer-2 solution, the focus has been on minimizing complexity. This approach aims to achieve efficient scalability on Ethereum. Its compatibility with the Ethereum network, allows developers to deploy their decentralized applications (dApps) and smart contracts on the Optimism layer 2 infrastructure. By moving transactions off the Ethereum mainnet, OP aims to reduce transaction costs and alleviate network congestion, making transactions more affordable and efficient for users. The project employs various security mechanisms, including fraud proofs and challenge periods, to ensure the integrity of transactions and prevent malicious activities within the layer 2 network. Related Reading: Optimism Crashes 33% Following Token Unlocks, Why There Could Be More Pain To Come Moving Averages And RSI Signals Indicated by price predictions, there are signs that OP token&#8217;s price is attempting to recover. Optimism is currently forming a bullish cup pattern on the daily timeframe. However, it&#8217;s worth noting that the OP token is currently trading below important moving averages, which could pose a challenge for buyers to overcome significant resistance levels. To witness a bullish breakout in the Optimism price, a significant level of buyer support is needed. Also, there has been a noticeable rise in social engagement related to the project. In the last week, the OP token price has increased by 25.65% with a favorable increase in trading activity as buyers and sellers participate actively in the optimism crypto market. The 24-hour trading volume has seen a growth of 34.66%. Technical Analysis Of Optimism Price Currently, the OP price is trading below the 200 Exponential Moving Average (EMA), with the 50 EMA acting as immediate resistance. To observe a potential increase in the OP price, it is important for the Relative Strength Index (RSI) line to successfully surpass the resistance given by the median line. The RSI value of OP token stands at 57.43 points and its line is finding support from the 14 Simple Moving Average (SMA) levels at approximately 36.51 points. Meanwhile, the %K and %D lines in the stochastic RSI are indicating a potential negative crossover. The current value of the stochastic RSI stands at 90.73 points. Related Reading: Optimism (OP) Soars Over 6% Following Launch On BNB Chain As per the analysis, there has been a notable surge in trading activity between buyers and sellers in the optimism crypto market, suggesting an attempt by the OP price to make a rebound. Featured image from iStock, charts from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Optimism, a layer-2 solution on the Ethereum blockchain, has gained traction with a TVL exceeding $1.22 billion.</p>
<ul>
<li>The OP price is currently forming a bullish cup pattern, indicating a potential recovery.</li>
<li>Trading activity in the optimism crypto market has surged, suggesting an attempt by the OP price to rebound.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Optimism: A Quick Look</h2>
<p>As a layer-2 blockchain solution, transactions are recorded on the Optimism blockchain and then stored on the Ethereum blockchain.</p>
<p>During the development of Optimism&#8217;s Layer-2 solution, the focus has been on minimizing complexity. This approach aims to achieve efficient scalability on Ethereum.</p>
<p>Its compatibility with the Ethereum network, allows developers to deploy their decentralized applications (dApps) and smart contracts on the Optimism layer 2 infrastructure. By moving transactions off the Ethereum mainnet, OP aims to reduce transaction costs and alleviate network congestion, making transactions more affordable and efficient for users.</p>
<p>The project employs various security mechanisms, including fraud proofs and challenge periods, to ensure the integrity of transactions and prevent malicious activities within the layer 2 network.</p>

<h2>Moving Averages And RSI Signals</h2>
<p>Indicated by price predictions, there are signs that OP token&#8217;s price is attempting to recover. Optimism is currently forming a <a href="https://coincodex.com/crypto/optimism/price-prediction/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">bullish cup pattern</a> on the daily timeframe.</p>
<p>However, it&#8217;s worth noting that the OP token is currently trading below important moving averages, which could pose a challenge for buyers to overcome significant resistance levels.</p>
<p>To witness a bullish breakout in the Optimism price, a significant level of buyer support is needed.</p>
<p>Also, there has been a noticeable rise in social engagement related to the project.</p>
<p>In the last week, the OP token price has increased by 25.65% with a favorable increase in trading activity as buyers and sellers participate actively in the optimism crypto market. The 24-hour trading volume has seen a growth of 34.66%.</p>
Technical Analysis Of Optimism Price
<p>Currently, the OP price is trading below the 200 Exponential Moving Average (EMA), with the 50 EMA acting as immediate resistance.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/m0PRk5Wx/" alt="Optimism chart" width="1888" height="656"/>
<p>To observe a potential increase in the OP price, it is important for the Relative Strength Index (RSI) line to successfully surpass the resistance given by the median line.</p>
<p>The RSI value of OP token stands at 57.43 points and its line is finding support from the 14 Simple Moving Average (SMA) levels at approximately 36.51 points.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, the %K and %D lines in the stochastic RSI are indicating a potential negative crossover. The current value of the stochastic RSI stands at 90.73 points.</p>

<p>As per the analysis, there has been a notable surge in trading activity between buyers and sellers in the optimism crypto market, suggesting an attempt by the OP price to make a rebound.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Optimism-460x266.jpeg" width="460" height="266" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Momentum: Why The Bitcoin Train Is Ready To Leave The Station</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/momentum-why-the-bitcoin-train-station/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tony "The Bull"]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 19:34:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xbt]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xbtusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=539569</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The latest Bitcoin price action has pushed momentum into the positive on just about every timeframe that matters: From today the daily through the monthly. If these signals confirm with a June monthly close, the train might have officially left the station when it comes to the next crypto bull run. BTCUSD Momentum Builds Across Multiple Timeframes Imagine a train that’s come to a complete stop. It’s a lot easier to board a train as it’s idle, and before it has gained momentum. Momentum starts off slow, then once the train really begins rolling it picks up seemingly unstoppable steam. Slowing back down takes force, time, and distance before it once again comes to a stop. Getting in the train’s path can prove dangerous. Related Reading: Bitcoin Price Breaks Above $30,000: Is The Bull Run Back On? If Bitcoin price can continue to climb through the end of June, strengthening bullish momentum will confirm across nearly every significant timeframe from the daily to the weekly to the monthly. That is according to the LMACD, which in the chart below shows the following timeframes forming a bullish crossover and buy signal: 1D, 3D, 1W, 2W, 3W, and 1M (clockwise). Such a signal could mean the train has left the station. Bitcoin has reclaimed $30,000 &#124; BTCUSD on TradingView.com Are The Stars Aligning For A Bitcoin Bull Run? Much like when stars align, people expect something special, the majority of important timeframes signaling strengthening momentum could mean like a locomotive, Bitcoin is starting to gain steam. And once that begins, and the train leaves the station, it isn’t quite as easy to get on for a ride. However, it isn’t fully clear if yet if that phase has begun, or if the train has a few more stops before it moves onto its final destination. Related Reading: Bitcoin Recovers Above Critical Level, Why Bulls Could Be Ready To Charge In contrast, the weekly LMACD crossover could fail and cause the monthly crossover to follow and diverge downward. At that point, things could get dicey for crypto and put lower timeframe bullish crossovers in serious jeopardy. Anyone aboard the train currently would more than likely end up disappointed. What do you think? Has the train left the station in Bitcoin? This chart originally appeared in Issue #9 of CoinChartist (VIP). Get 10% off a year subscription with this link: https://coinchartist.substack.com/NEWSBTC Tony is the author of the CoinChartist (VIP) newsletter. Follow @TonyTheBullBTC &#38; @coinchartist_io on Twitter. Or join the TonyTradesBTC Telegram for daily market insights and technical analysis education. Please note: Content is educational and should not be considered investment advice. Featured image from iStockPhoto, Charts from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The latest Bitcoin price action has pushed momentum into the positive on just about every timeframe that matters: From today the daily through the monthly.</p>
<p>If these signals confirm with a June monthly close, the train might have officially left the station when it comes to the next crypto bull run.</p>
<h2>BTCUSD Momentum Builds Across Multiple Timeframes</h2>
<p>Imagine a train that’s come to a complete stop. It’s a lot easier to board a train as it’s idle, and before it has gained momentum. Momentum starts off slow, then once the train really begins rolling it picks up seemingly unstoppable steam. Slowing back down takes force, time, and distance before it once again comes to a stop. Getting in the train’s path can prove dangerous.</p>

<p>If Bitcoin price can continue to climb through the end of June, strengthening bullish momentum will confirm across nearly every significant timeframe from the daily to the weekly to the monthly.</p>
<p>That is according to the LMACD, which in the chart below shows the following timeframes forming a bullish crossover and buy signal: 1D, 3D, 1W, 2W, 3W, and 1M (clockwise). Such a signal could mean the train has left the station.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large wp-image-539570 aligncenter" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/A3B67BE4-E78C-4390-A8CF-BDBA0CE6D674-860x534.png" alt="Bitcoin news momentum " width="860" height="534" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/A3B67BE4-E78C-4390-A8CF-BDBA0CE6D674-860x534.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/A3B67BE4-E78C-4390-A8CF-BDBA0CE6D674-460x286.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/A3B67BE4-E78C-4390-A8CF-BDBA0CE6D674-768x477.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/A3B67BE4-E78C-4390-A8CF-BDBA0CE6D674-1536x954.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/A3B67BE4-E78C-4390-A8CF-BDBA0CE6D674-2048x1272.png 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/A3B67BE4-E78C-4390-A8CF-BDBA0CE6D674-750x466.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/A3B67BE4-E78C-4390-A8CF-BDBA0CE6D674-1140x708.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/></p>

<h2>Are The Stars Aligning For A Bitcoin Bull Run?</h2>
<p>Much like when stars align, people expect something special, the majority of important timeframes signaling strengthening momentum could mean like a locomotive, Bitcoin is starting to gain steam.</p>
<p>And once that begins, and the train leaves the station, it isn’t quite as easy to get on for a ride. However, it isn’t fully clear if yet if that phase has begun, or if the train has a few more stops before it moves onto its final destination.</p>

<p>In contrast, the weekly LMACD crossover could fail and cause the monthly crossover to follow and diverge downward. At that point, things could get dicey for crypto and put lower timeframe bullish crossovers in serious jeopardy. Anyone aboard the train currently would more than likely end up disappointed.</p>
<p>What do you think? Has the train left the station in Bitcoin?</p>
<p>This chart originally appeared in <a href="https://coinchartist.substack.com/p/issue-9-a-wake-up-call-for-crypto" rel="nofollow">Issue #9 of CoinChartist (VIP)</a>. Get <b>10% off</b> a year subscription with this link: https://coinchartist.substack.com/NEWSBTC</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/36B857E5-15B9-4078-8396-D2E5FAC3654A-460x310.jpeg" width="460" height="310" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Stacks (STX) Rallies By 29% In The Past 7 Days &#8211; Here’s Why</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/stacks-stx-rallies-by-29-in-the-past-7-days-heres-why/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Olowoporoku Adeniyi]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 14:07:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stacks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[STX]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=539503</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The cryptocurrency Stacks (STX) has recently experienced a remarkable turnaround, with its price bouncing back after reaching a multi-month low of $0.4412. Investors have seized the opportunity to &#8220;buy the dip,&#8221; resulting in a continuous upward trend for STX over the past few days. As a result, STX is now trading at $0.7916, marking a significant 29% increase from its lowest level this month. Potential Catalysts For STX Two primary reasons drive the surge in Stacks&#8217; price. Firstly, the decision by Blackrock to file for a Bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF) with the US Securities and Exchange Commission has sparked positive sentiment. However, uncertainties remain regarding the acceptance of the iShares Bitcoin Trust, as Coinbase is slated to serve as the custodian of the coins. Furthermore, the ongoing conflict between Coinbase and the SEC adds to the regulatory uncertainty surrounding the situation. Related Readings: Bitcoin Just Gained Over 18% In Seven Days: What’s Happened When This Has Occurred In The Past? Furthermore, the SEC&#8217;s lawsuit against major exchanges Binance and Coinbase is expected to benefit Bitcoin, as both regulatory agencies recognize Bitcoin as a commodity rather than a security. Consequently, many investors in alternative cryptocurrencies may shift their focus to the perceived safety of Bitcoin. Stacks, which is closely tied to Bitcoin&#8217;s ecosystem and enables the development of decentralized applications (dApps), stands to benefit from this changing investor sentiment. The expanding Stacks ecosystem is another significant factor contributing to the rise in STX price. Bitflow Finance, a decentralized finance (DeFi) protocol, recently introduced an sBTC/sBTC stableswap pool, enabling seamless token swaps. This development enhances the utility and adoption of Stacks, ultimately bolstering its positive price performance. What’s Next For Stacks? From a technical analysis standpoint, Stacks exhibits promising signals. The daily chart reveals the formation of a bullish falling wedge pattern, indicating a potential trend reversal. STX has also surpassed the 25-day exponential moving average and is currently testing the 50-day MA. Moreover, the breakthrough of the key resistance level at $0.5281, the lowest point in March, further reinforces the bullish sentiment. As buyers set their sights on the next resistance point at $0.90, a potential 9% increase from the current level, Stacks continues to attract attention. Related Readings: Mask Foundation Moves 2.5 Million Tokens To Exchanges, Huge Dip Incoming? The Stacks price is $0.79 at press time, reflecting a change of -2.10% over the past 24 hours. The recent price action has left Stacks&#8217; market capitalization at $1,101,401,654.52. Notably, Stacks has demonstrated an impressive 277.22% change since the beginning of the year, indicating its strong growth potential. STX serves as the native token of the Stacks blockchain, which operates as a layer 2 blockchain network leveraging the security of the Bitcoin blockchain for transaction settlement. With its unique positioning and robust ecosystem, Stacks continues to capture the attention of investors and developers alike. Featured image from iStock.com and charts from Tradingview and Coingecko.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The cryptocurrency Stacks (STX) has recently experienced a remarkable turnaround, with its price bouncing back after reaching a multi-month low of $0.4412. Investors have seized the opportunity to &#8220;buy the dip,&#8221; resulting in a continuous upward trend for STX over the past few days. As a result, STX is now trading at $0.7916, marking a significant 29% increase from its lowest level this month.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-539507 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Screenshot_173-860x109.png" alt="Stacks is up 29% In 7-days: source @coingecko" width="860" height="109" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Screenshot_173-860x109.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Screenshot_173-460x58.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Screenshot_173-768x97.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Screenshot_173-750x95.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Screenshot_173.png 1048w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/>
<h2><strong>Potential Catalysts For STX</strong></h2>
<p>Two primary reasons drive the surge in Stacks&#8217; price. Firstly, the decision by Blackrock to file for a Bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF) with the US Securities and Exchange Commission has sparked positive sentiment. However, uncertainties remain regarding the acceptance of the<a href="https://www.ishares.com/us/products/326614/ishares-blockchain-and-tech-etf/" rel="nofollow"> iShares Bitcoin Trust</a>, as Coinbase is slated to serve as the custodian of the coins. Furthermore, the ongoing conflict between Coinbase and the SEC adds to the regulatory uncertainty surrounding the situation.</p>
<p><strong>Related Readings:</strong> <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-just-gained-over-18-in-seven-days-whats-happened-when-this-has-occurred-in-the-past/">Bitcoin Just Gained Over 18% In Seven Days: What’s Happened When This Has Occurred In The Past?</a></p>
<p>Furthermore, the SEC&#8217;s lawsuit against major exchanges Binance and Coinbase is expected to benefit Bitcoin, as both regulatory agencies recognize Bitcoin as a commodity rather than a security. Consequently, many investors in alternative cryptocurrencies may shift their focus to the perceived safety of Bitcoin. Stacks, which is closely tied to Bitcoin&#8217;s ecosystem and enables the development of decentralized applications (dApps), stands to benefit from this changing investor sentiment.</p>
<p>The expanding Stacks ecosystem is another significant factor contributing to the rise in STX price. Bitflow Finance, a decentralized finance (DeFi) protocol, recently introduced an sBTC/sBTC stableswap pool, enabling seamless token swaps. This development enhances the utility and adoption of Stacks, ultimately bolstering its positive price performance.</p>
<h2><strong>What’s Next For Stacks?</strong></h2>
<p>From a technical analysis standpoint, Stacks exhibits promising signals. The daily chart reveals the formation of a bullish falling wedge pattern, indicating a potential trend reversal. STX has also surpassed the 25-day exponential moving average and is currently testing the 50-day MA.</p>
<p>Moreover, the breakthrough of the key resistance level at $0.5281, the lowest point in March, further reinforces the bullish sentiment. As buyers set their sights on the next resistance point at $0.90, a potential 9% increase from the current level, Stacks continues to attract attention.</p>
<p><strong>Related Readings: </strong><a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/altcoin/mask-foundation-moves-2-5-million-tokens-to-exchanges/">Mask Foundation Moves 2.5 Million Tokens To Exchanges, Huge Dip Incoming?</a></p>
<p>The Stacks price is $0.79 at press time, reflecting a change of -2.10% over the past 24 hours. The recent price action has left Stacks&#8217; market capitalization at $1,101,401,654.52. Notably, Stacks has demonstrated an impressive 277.22% change since the beginning of the year, indicating its strong growth potential.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-539504 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image1-5-860x474.png" alt="Stacks weekly chart shows bullish uptrend: source @tradingview" width="860" height="474" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image1-5-860x474.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image1-5-460x253.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image1-5-768x423.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image1-5-750x413.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image1-5.png 1080w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/>
<p>STX serves as the native token of the Stacks blockchain, which operates as a layer 2 blockchain network leveraging the security of the Bitcoin blockchain for transaction settlement. With its unique positioning and robust ecosystem, Stacks continues to capture the attention of investors and developers alike.</p>
<p><em>Featured image from iStock.com and charts from Tradingview and Coingecko.com</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/iStock-157559643-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>BUSD Market Cap Plunge Of 80% Raises Concerns Of Impending Collapse</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/busd-market-cap-plunge-of-80-in-2023-raises-concerns-of-impending-collapse/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Olowoporoku Adeniyi]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 13:26:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Paxos]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[stablecoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=539496</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The fate of Binance USD (BUSD), the stablecoin introduced by Binance, hangs in the balance as its market capitalization has experienced a significant decline of over 80% in 2023. From November 2022 to June of the current year, BUSD&#8217;s market capitalization has plummeted from USD23 billion to USD4 billion. Notably, the capitalization suffered an 18% loss in May alone, as reported by CCData, an analysis company. TrueUSD (TUSD) Gains Traction As BUSD Market Cap Declines As the market capitalization of BUSD continues to decline and reach a critical level, representing less than 5% of the overall stablecoin market capitalization, Binance has begun actively promoting the adoption of TrueUSD (TUSD). While TUSD&#8217;s market capitalization still falls slightly below that of BUSD, currently standing at over USD3.1 billion, it has surpassed BUSD in terms of trading volumes. According to data provided by CCData, the trading volumes of TUSD have tripled, indicating a growing interest and usage of the stablecoin. Related Reading: Mask Foundation Moves 2.5 Million Tokens To Exchanges, Huge Dip Incoming? TrueUSD (TUSD), introduced in 2017 by TrustToken, has emerged as the fifth-largest stablecoin in the market, trailing closely behind BUSD. Functioning as an Ethereum-based ERC-20 token, TUSD secures its value with dollar reserves deposited in multiple US-based banking entities. The company behind TUSD ensures a 1:1 convertibility with the US currency, instilling confidence in its stability and reliability among users. As BUSD&#8217;s market capitalization experiences a significant decline, the growing popularity and trading volumes of TUSD serve as a testament to the increasing demand for an alternative stablecoin option. Also, Binance&#8217;s shift towards promoting TUSD suggests a strategic response to the changing landscape of stablecoin usage and market dynamics. The steep decline in BUSD&#8217;s market capitalization can be attributed to its impending discontinuation. In February 2023, NewsBTC reported that Paxos would cease issuing the BUSD stablecoin due to an ongoing lawsuit filed by the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). As per Paxos&#8217; official statement, BUSD will be redeemable until February 24, 2024, marking the potential date for its exit from the market. Investors Move To USDT As It Nears Its All-Time High Capitalization As the market capitalization of Tether (USDT) continues to rise steadily, approaching its all-time high, investors are taking notice and making strategic moves. According to data from CoinMarketCap, USDT&#8217;s current market capitalization stands at $82.9 billion (USD), close to its previous peak of $83.2 billion, reached in May 2022. This upward trajectory has prompted investors to diversify their portfolios and explore alternative stablecoin options. Related Reading: Bitcoin Just Gained Over 18% In Seven Days: What’s Happened When This Has Occurred In The Past? Also, Investors are drawn to USDT due to its stability and pegging to the US dollar, offering a reliable store of value amidst market fluctuations. With its widespread acceptance and liquidity, USDT has become a preferred choice for traders, providing a convenient and secure means of preserving their capital during volatile market conditions. At press time, USDT was trading at $0.9780 per coin with a 24-hour price increase of 1.38%. Featured image from iStock, charts from Tradingview and CCData]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The fate of Binance USD (BUSD), the stablecoin introduced by Binance, hangs in the balance as its market capitalization has experienced a significant decline of over 80% in 2023.</p>
<p>From November 2022 to June of the current year, BUSD&#8217;s market capitalization has plummeted from USD23 billion to USD4 billion. Notably, the capitalization suffered an 18% loss in May alone, as reported by CCData, an analysis company.</p>
<h2><strong>TrueUSD (TUSD) Gains Traction As BUSD Market Cap Declines</strong></h2>
<p>As the market capitalization of BUSD continues to decline and reach a critical level, representing less than 5% of the overall stablecoin market capitalization, <a href="https://www.binance.com/en" rel="nofollow">Binance</a> has begun actively promoting the adoption of TrueUSD (TUSD).</p>
<p>While TUSD&#8217;s market capitalization still falls slightly below that of BUSD, currently standing at over USD3.1 billion, it has surpassed BUSD in terms of trading volumes. According to data provided by CCData, the trading volumes of TUSD have tripled, indicating a growing interest and usage of the stablecoin.</p>
<p><strong>Related Reading</strong>: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/altcoin/mask-foundation-moves-2-5-million-tokens-to-exchanges/">Mask Foundation Moves 2.5 Million Tokens To Exchanges, Huge Dip Incoming?</a></p>
<p>TrueUSD (TUSD), introduced in 2017 by TrustToken, has emerged as the fifth-largest stablecoin in the market, trailing closely behind BUSD. Functioning as an Ethereum-based ERC-20 token, TUSD secures its value with dollar reserves deposited in multiple US-based banking entities. The company behind TUSD ensures a 1:1 convertibility with the US currency, instilling confidence in its stability and reliability among users.</p>
<p>As BUSD&#8217;s market capitalization experiences a significant decline, the growing popularity and trading volumes of TUSD serve as a testament to the increasing demand for an alternative stablecoin option. Also, Binance&#8217;s shift towards promoting TUSD suggests a strategic response to the changing landscape of stablecoin usage and market dynamics.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-539498 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image1-4.png" alt="TUSD has been gaining rapidly on BUSD in recent months" width="810" height="315" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image1-4.png 810w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image1-4-460x179.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image1-4-768x299.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image1-4-750x292.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 810px) 100vw, 810px"/>
<p>The steep decline in BUSD&#8217;s market capitalization can be attributed to its impending discontinuation. In February 2023, NewsBTC reported that Paxos would cease issuing the BUSD stablecoin due to an ongoing lawsuit filed by the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC).</p>
<p>As per Paxos&#8217; official statement, BUSD will be redeemable until February 24, 2024, marking the potential date for its exit from the market.</p>
<h2><strong>Investors Move To USDT As It Nears Its All-Time High Capitalization</strong></h2>
<p>As the market capitalization of Tether (USDT) continues to rise steadily, approaching its all-time high, investors are taking notice and making strategic moves. According to data from CoinMarketCap, USDT&#8217;s current market capitalization stands at $82.9 billion (USD), close to its previous peak of $83.2 billion, reached in May 2022. This upward trajectory has prompted investors to diversify their portfolios and explore alternative stablecoin options.</p>
<p><strong>Related Reading: </strong><a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-just-gained-over-18-in-seven-days-whats-happened-when-this-has-occurred-in-the-past/">Bitcoin Just Gained Over 18% In Seven Days: What’s Happened When This Has Occurred In The Past?</a></p>
<p>Also, Investors are drawn to USDT due to its stability and pegging to the US dollar, offering a reliable store of value amidst market fluctuations. With its widespread acceptance and liquidity, USDT has become a preferred choice for traders, providing a convenient and secure means of preserving their capital during volatile market conditions.</p>
<p>At press time, USDT was trading at $0.9780 per coin with a 24-hour price increase of 1.38%.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-539499 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/USDT_2023-06-24_08-03-34-860x432.png" alt="USDT imarketcap is currently around $83 billion: source @Tradingview" width="860" height="432" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/USDT_2023-06-24_08-03-34-860x432.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/USDT_2023-06-24_08-03-34-460x231.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/USDT_2023-06-24_08-03-34-768x386.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/USDT_2023-06-24_08-03-34-360x180.png 360w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/USDT_2023-06-24_08-03-34-750x377.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/USDT_2023-06-24_08-03-34-1140x572.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/USDT_2023-06-24_08-03-34.png 1480w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/>
<p><em>Featured image from iStock, charts from Tradingview and CCData</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/iStock-182393047-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Litecoin (LTC) Bulls Charge Past $91 Following 20% Rally</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/litecoin-ltc-bulls-charge-past-91-following-20-rally/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 07:37:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Litecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ltc price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price action]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=539489</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Litecoin (LTC) has recently witnessed an impressive three-day bullish streak, sparking excitement among investors as its price surged past the $91 level. The cryptocurrency&#8217;s remarkable performance during this period has been celebrated by bullish traders who see it as a significant victory.  With this surge, Litecoin has caught the attention of market participants, generating renewed interest in its potential and signaling a potential shift in the broader cryptocurrency landscape. The remarkable growth of Litecoin in such a short span of time has rekindled optimism among cryptocurrency enthusiasts, who are closely monitoring its progress. Litcoin (LTC) Breaks Past Recent Lows  LTC has defied expectations with a notable 6.1% rally in the past 24 hours, and shooting up to the $91.35 level, as reported by CoinGecko. This upward movement comes as a pleasant surprise for investors and traders who had concerns about LTC&#8217;s descent to the March low of $72 on June 14.  Source: Coingecko The drop to this critical level sparked fears of a potential downward spiral for Litecoin. However, to the relief of bullish market participants, the strong buying pressure at the $72 support level proved resilient and initiated a mild price rally. LTC price movement in the last seven days. Source: Coingecko Related Reading: Conflux Claims Its Place Among Top Altcoins As CFX Price Skyrockets 46% The recent surge in LTC&#8217;s price not only demonstrates the cryptocurrency&#8217;s ability to rebound from critical levels but also solidifies the positive momentum it has gained over the last seven days. During this period, Litecoin experienced a nearly 20% climb. Meanwhile, an important milestone in the acceptance of payments was recently noted in a post on Litecoin&#8217;s official Twitter account. The cryptocurrency specifically reached an all-time high of 167 million transactions. LITECOIN 🛒 Use for payments is at an ATH 🔄167 million transactions 🌎 Liquidity 4th in all of crypto 🏗️ More people building on $LTC than ever before = priceless ⚡ pic.twitter.com/kwr50SDbMR — Litecoin (@litecoin) June 22, 2023 LTC Rides The Wave of Bitcoin&#8217;s Momentum Bitcoin&#8217;s recent surge toward the $30,000 mark has had a significant impact on the broader cryptocurrency market, lifting the prices of various altcoins, including Litecoin. As the leading cryptocurrency experienced a renewed upward movement, investors and traders eagerly embraced the positive market sentiment, driving a surge in altcoin prices. Related Reading: PEPE Leapfrogs With 72% Rally – What’s Behind The Surprise Vigor? The correlation between Bitcoin and altcoins has long been recognized in the cryptocurrency market. When Bitcoin exhibits strong bullish momentum, it often paves the way for other cryptocurrencies to follow suit, benefitting from the overall market optimism. Litecoin, being one of the prominent altcoins, has also reaped the rewards of Bitcoin&#8217;s recent surge, adding to its own positive momentum. Bitcoin halfway into reaching the $31K level on the weekend chart: TradingView.com Bitcoin&#8217;s price movements have historically set the tone for the broader cryptocurrency market, and Litecoin&#8217;s recent rally is a testament to this relationship. As Bitcoin continues to make strides and capture attention with its upward movement, altcoins like Litecoin stand to benefit from the increased market interest and positive sentiment. Featured image from The Market Periodical]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Litecoin (LTC) has recently witnessed an impressive three-day bullish streak, sparking excitement among investors as its price surged past the $91 level. The cryptocurrency&#8217;s remarkable performance during this period has been celebrated by bullish traders who see it as a significant victory. </p>
<p>With this surge, Litecoin has caught the attention of market participants, generating renewed interest in its potential and signaling a potential shift in the broader cryptocurrency landscape.</p>
<p>The remarkable growth of Litecoin in such a short span of time has rekindled optimism among cryptocurrency enthusiasts, who are closely monitoring its progress.</p>
<h2><strong>Litcoin (LTC) Breaks Past Recent Lows </strong></h2>
<p>LTC has defied expectations with a notable 6.1% rally in the past 24 hours, and shooting up to the $91.35 level, as reported by <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/litecoin" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">CoinGecko</a>. This upward movement comes as a pleasant surprise for investors and traders who had concerns about LTC&#8217;s descent to the March low of $72 on June 14. </p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-539497" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Litecoin.png" alt="" width="1149" height="63" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Litecoin.png 1149w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Litecoin-460x25.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Litecoin-860x47.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Litecoin-768x42.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Litecoin-1140x63.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Litecoin-750x41.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 1149px) 100vw, 1149px"/></p>

<p>The drop to this critical level sparked fears of a potential downward spiral for Litecoin. However, to the relief of bullish market participants, the strong buying pressure at the $72 support level proved resilient and initiated a mild price rally.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-539506" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-134.png" alt="" width="765" height="499" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-134.png 765w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-134-460x300.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-134-750x489.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 765px) 100vw, 765px"/></p>


<p>The recent <a href="https://ambcrypto.com/litecoin-bulls-sail-past-80-more-gains-ahead/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">surge in LTC&#8217;s price</a> not only demonstrates the cryptocurrency&#8217;s ability to rebound from critical levels but also solidifies the positive momentum it has gained over the last seven days. During this period, Litecoin experienced a nearly 20% climb.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, an <a href="https://twitter.com/litecoin/status/1671937284487397376?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw%7Ctwcamp%5Etweetembed%7Ctwterm%5E1671937284487397376%7Ctwgr%5Edf9d36dd5ea8222ee9e21915e0d07b88ce6711e8%7Ctwcon%5Es1_&amp;ref_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.crypto-news-flash.com%2Fltc-achieves-payment-transaction-ath-litecoin-making-waves-as-a-crypto-payment-solution%2F" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">important milestone</a> in the acceptance of payments was recently noted in a post on Litecoin&#8217;s official Twitter account. The cryptocurrency specifically reached an all-time high of 167 million transactions.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">LITECOIN</p>
<p><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f6d2.png" alt="🛒" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> Use for payments is at an ATH
<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f504.png" alt="🔄" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />167 million transactions
<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f30e.png" alt="🌎" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> Liquidity 4th in all of crypto
<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f3d7.png" alt="🏗" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> More people building on <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24LTC&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$LTC</a> than ever before = priceless <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/26a1.png" alt="⚡" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> <a href="https://t.co/kwr50SDbMR" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/kwr50SDbMR</a></p>
<p>— Litecoin (@litecoin) <a href="https://twitter.com/litecoin/status/1671937284487397376?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">June 22, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<h2><strong>LTC Rides The Wave of Bitcoin&#8217;s Momentum</strong></h2>
<p><a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-06-23/bitcoin-hits-highest-in-a-year-in-reawakening-of-animal-spirits" rel="nofollow">Bitcoin&#8217;s recent surge</a> toward the $30,000 mark has had a significant impact on the broader cryptocurrency market, lifting the prices of various altcoins, including Litecoin. As the leading cryptocurrency experienced a renewed upward movement, investors and traders eagerly embraced the positive market sentiment, driving a surge in altcoin prices.</p>

<p>The correlation between Bitcoin and altcoins has long been recognized in the cryptocurrency market. When Bitcoin exhibits strong bullish momentum, it often paves the way for other cryptocurrencies to follow suit, benefitting from the overall market optimism. Litecoin, being one of the prominent altcoins, has also reaped the rewards of Bitcoin&#8217;s recent surge, adding to its own positive momentum.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/iiGkCEv8/" width="2315" height="1109"/></p>

<p>Bitcoin&#8217;s price movements have historically set the tone for the broader cryptocurrency market, and Litecoin&#8217;s recent rally is a testament to this relationship. As Bitcoin continues to make strides and capture attention with its upward movement, altcoins like Litecoin stand to benefit from the increased market interest and positive sentiment.</p>
<p><em>Featured image from The Market Periodical</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-135-460x231.png" width="460" height="231" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Gods Unchained launches on Epic Games Store, GODS Spikes 50%</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/gods-unchained-launches-on-epic-games-store-gods-spikes-50/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dalmas Ngetich]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 01:00:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blockchain game]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain games]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Epic Games Store]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[GODS]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gods Unchained]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Immutable Studio]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=539478</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Gods Unchained, a blockchain card trading game developed by Immutable Studio, has launched on Epic Games Store (EGS). Following this launch, GODS, the native token of the Gods Unchained ecosystem, has rallied 50% from June 2023 lows, expanding in line with the broader cryptocurrency markets spearheaded by Bitcoin, which is currently trading above $31,000. Gods Unchained launches on Epic Games Store The game recently announced its debut on Epic Games Store, a digital gaming distribution platform with over 230 million PC gamers, including a community of digital trading card enthusiasts.  As one of the original web3 games, Gods Unchained has been at the forefront of decentralized gaming. Now, intending to attract more mainstream trading card game and strategy gamers, Gods Unchained is undergoing an update, with an updated logo and updated visuals across different points, which would launch with the Epic Games Store release. Related Reading: MATIC Price Recovery Hits Roadblock, When Will Bulls Break Through? The PC game also teased a mobile-friendly design focused on onboarding new users. In a comment about the launch Daniel Paez, the executive producer of Gods Unchained, said EGS will introduce the web3 game to a “massive audience of traditional PC gamers and TCG enthusiasts.&#8221; Blockchain gaming, NFT activity recovering The deployment on EGS is timely. Specifically, it is when the cryptocurrency market is recovering after months of lower lows in 2022. During the last bear cycle, cryptocurrency prices crashed from 2021 peaks, impacting activity. Out of this, there was a significant contraction in non-fungible tokens (NFT) activity, which translated to low activity. In the Gods Unchained blockchain games, all trading cards are represented as unique NFTs. These represent ownership and can be transferred between users, even exchanged for cash or other cryptocurrencies. Since trading cards vary in rarity, the value assigned to each can change. According to DappRadar, unique active wallets (UAWs) remain stable at around 1,150 but lower than 2021 peaks when it spiked to over 4,000. At the same time, Gods Unchained generated over $745,000 in active transaction values. At the moment, GODS, the native token of the Gods Unchained game, is rising in sync with the broader cryptocurrency market. GODS is trading at $0.16, up 50% from June lows. GODSUSDT Candlestick arrangement shows that the token is bottoming up after dropping 75% from February 2023 highs. Last year, Immutable Studio, the developer of Gods Unchained, had to let go of multiple employees, including a senior game designer James Wakeham. These restructuring efforts resulted in a 6% reduction in the company&#8217;s workforce, yet, Immutable Games remained optimistic about its future. Related Reading: FLOKI Soars 26% In A Single Week, Shares 2023 Roadmap Update At the time, a spokesperson for the studio said the decision was to help them “achieve its goal of creating the next generation of web3 games.”  Feature Image From Canva, Chart From TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Gods Unchained, a blockchain card trading game developed by Immutable Studio, has launched on Epic Games Store (EGS). Following this launch, GODS, the native token of the Gods Unchained ecosystem, has rallied 50% from June 2023 lows, expanding in line with the broader cryptocurrency markets spearheaded by Bitcoin, which is currently trading above $31,000.</p>
<h2>Gods Unchained launches on Epic Games Store</h2>
<p>The game recently <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://blog.godsunchained.com/2023/06/22/gods-unchained-launches-on-epic-games-store/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">announced</a> its debut on Epic Games Store, a digital gaming distribution platform with over 230 million PC gamers, including a community of digital trading card enthusiasts. </p>
<p>As one of the original web3 games, Gods Unchained has been at the forefront of decentralized gaming. Now, intending to attract more mainstream trading card game and strategy gamers, Gods Unchained is undergoing an update, with an updated logo and updated visuals across different points, which would launch with the Epic Games Store release.</p>

<p>The PC game also teased a mobile-friendly design focused on onboarding new users. In a comment about the launch Daniel Paez, the executive producer of Gods Unchained, said EGS will introduce the web3 game to a “massive audience of traditional PC gamers and TCG enthusiasts.&#8221;</p>
<h2>Blockchain gaming, NFT activity recovering</h2>
<p>The deployment on EGS is timely. Specifically, it is when the cryptocurrency market is recovering after months of lower lows in 2022. During the last bear cycle, cryptocurrency prices crashed from 2021 peaks, impacting activity. Out of this, there was a significant contraction in non-fungible tokens (NFT) activity, which translated to low activity.</p>
<p>In the Gods Unchained blockchain games, all trading cards are represented as unique NFTs. These represent ownership and can be transferred between users, even exchanged for cash or other cryptocurrencies. Since trading cards vary in rarity, the value assigned to each can change.</p>
<p>According to DappRadar, unique active wallets (UAWs)<a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://dappradar.com/dapp/gods-unchained/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow"> remain</a> stable at around 1,150 but lower than 2021 peaks when it spiked to over 4,000. At the same time, Gods Unchained generated over $745,000 in active transaction values.</p>
<p>At the moment, GODS, the native token of the Gods Unchained game, is rising in sync with the broader cryptocurrency market. GODS is trading at $0.16, up 50% from June lows. GODSUSDT Candlestick arrangement shows that the token is bottoming up after dropping 75% from February 2023 highs.</p>
<a href="https://www.tradingview.com/x/jSvWCUiV/" rel="nofollow"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/jSvWCUiV/" alt="GODS price on June 23| Source: GODSUSDT from Binance, TradingView" width="1226" height="595"/></a>
<p>Last year, Immutable Studio, the developer of Gods Unchained, had to let go of multiple employees, including a senior game designer James Wakeham. These restructuring efforts resulted in a 6% reduction in the company&#8217;s workforce, yet, Immutable Games remained optimistic about its future.</p>

<p>At the time, a spokesperson for the studio <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.kotaku.com.au/2022/07/australian-studio-immutable-redundancies/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">said</a> the decision was to help them “achieve its goal of creating the next generation of web3 games.” </p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Crypto-news-Template23-460x260.jpg" width="460" height="260" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Just Gained Over 18% In Seven Days: What’s Happened When This Has Occurred In The Past?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-just-gained-over-18-in-seven-days-whats-happened-when-this-has-occurred-in-the-past/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[dbthequant]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 23:18:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=539433</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[By the completion of its daily candle on Wednesday, Bitcoin had gained over 18% in just seven consecutive sessions, abruptly ending the steady drift lower which had dominated its price action since Bitcoin put in its mid-April high above 30,000. How unusual is this magnitude gain in only a week’s time, and what’s happened in the past after similarly robust rallies? Let’s take a closer look at Bitcoin’s price history to find out. Bitcoin’s Price History Suggests Higher Prices Ahead As we examine Bitcoin’s price history for which there is reliable data (2011 to the present), the number one cryptocurrency by market cap has experienced numerous instances of gains greater than or equal to +18% over the span of seven days. Bitcoin gains &#62;= 18% in Seven Days &#124; BTCUSD on TradingView.com Related Reading: Bitcoin Recovers Above Critical Level, Why Bulls Could Be Ready To Charge Because the number of occurrences will vary depending on holding time, we’ll start by listing the number of times this has happened next to our hypothetical hold times of 7 days through 90 days. Holding time is defined as the amount of time one held Bitcoin before exiting. For example, if one hypothetically purchased Bitcoin following the trigger event (i.e., +18% over the span of seven days) and sold it 30 days later, this would be a holding time of 30 days. Bitcoin Occurrences of +18% Gains in Seven Consecutive Days by Holding Time (2011 &#8211; Present) 98 occurrences using a 7-day hold time 73 occurrences using a 15-day hold time 57 occurrences using a 30-day hold time 30 occurrences using a 90-day hold time Clearly, gains of this magnitude in just a week’s time are not uncommon for Bitcoin, an asset with numerous instances of large price advances especially when considering its relatively short price history compared to traditional risk assets. Bitcoin Results Slightly Less Bullish In Recent Years While a gain of over 18% in such a brief time period may lead some traders to lean bearish, the data suggests otherwise, with historical average results clearly positive across the board for all holding times from 2011 to the present. &#160; Bitcoin gains &#62;= 18% in Seven Consecutive Days with Various Hold Times. 2011 &#8211; Present. Because Bitcoin’s early price history experienced arguably outsized gains relative to its more recent history, let’s take a look at average results for the same degree of gains in a week’s time but only examining data for the last five years (6/23/18 to the present). Bitcoin gains &#62;= 18% in Seven Consecutive Days with Various Hold Times. Last Five Years. While once again results are positive across the board, the hypothetical results over more recent data are significantly lower, with the average 90-day return of +25.6% over the past five years a far cry from the +109.4% returns for the same 90-day window over the full price history from 2011 to the present. Related Reading: Bitcoin Price Surges 8% And Defies Gravity – Bulls Eye $30K While some traders may argue that the past five years is less representative data due to the occurrence of two major bear markets for Bitcoin and crypto more broadly, Bitcoin has shown positive follow through on average for both time periods across all the hold times we examined. While the past does not predict the future, the recent powerful price advance appears to suggest that Bitcoin is poised for greater gains in relatively near future. DB the Quant is the author of the REKTelligence Report newsletter on Substack. Follow @REKTelligence on Twitter for evidence-based crypto market research and analysis. Important Note: This content is strictly educational in nature and should not be considered investment advice. Featured images created with Tableau. Charts from TradingView.com.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>By the completion of its daily candle on Wednesday, Bitcoin had gained over 18% in just seven consecutive sessions, abruptly ending the steady drift lower which had dominated its price action since Bitcoin put in its mid-April high above 30,000. How unusual is this magnitude gain in only a week’s time, and what’s happened in the past after similarly robust rallies? Let’s take a closer look at Bitcoin’s price history to find out.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin’s Price History Suggests Higher Prices Ahead</h2>
<p>As we examine Bitcoin’s price history for which there is reliable data (2011 to the present), the number one cryptocurrency by market cap has experienced numerous instances of gains greater than or equal to +18% over the span of seven days.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium wp-image-539434 aligncenter" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/CHART_BTC_7D-Gain_062323-460x318.png" alt="" width="460" height="318" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/CHART_BTC_7D-Gain_062323-460x318.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/CHART_BTC_7D-Gain_062323-860x595.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/CHART_BTC_7D-Gain_062323-768x531.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/CHART_BTC_7D-Gain_062323-750x518.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/CHART_BTC_7D-Gain_062323-1140x788.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/CHART_BTC_7D-Gain_062323.png 1150w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px"/></p>
Bitcoin gains &gt;= 18% in Seven Days | <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BTCUSD/?exchange=INDEX" rel="nofollow">BTCUSD on TradingView.com</a>

Because the number of occurrences will vary depending on holding time, we’ll start by listing the number of times this has happened next to our hypothetical hold times of 7 days through 90 days. Holding time is defined as the amount of time one held Bitcoin before exiting. For example, if one hypothetically purchased Bitcoin following the trigger event (i.e., +18% over the span of seven days) and sold it 30 days later, this would be a holding time of 30 days.

<p><strong>Bitcoin Occurrences of +18% Gains in Seven Consecutive Days by Holding Time (2011 &#8211; Present)</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>98 occurrences using a 7-day hold time</li>
<li>73 occurrences using a 15-day hold time</li>
<li>57 occurrences using a 30-day hold time</li>
<li>30 occurrences using a 90-day hold time</li>
</ul>
<p>Clearly, gains of this magnitude in just a week’s time are not uncommon for Bitcoin, an asset with numerous instances of large price advances especially when considering its relatively short price history compared to traditional risk assets.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Results Slightly Less Bullish In Recent Years</h2>
<p>While a gain of over 18% in such a brief time period may lead some traders to lean bearish, the data suggests otherwise, with historical average results clearly positive across the board for all holding times from 2011 to the present.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium wp-image-539436 aligncenter" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Hold-Times_ALL-DATA2-460x285.png" alt="" width="460" height="285" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Hold-Times_ALL-DATA2-460x285.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Hold-Times_ALL-DATA2-860x534.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Hold-Times_ALL-DATA2-768x477.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Hold-Times_ALL-DATA2-750x465.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Hold-Times_ALL-DATA2.png 975w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px"/></p>
Bitcoin gains &gt;= 18% in Seven Consecutive Days with Various Hold Times. 2011 &#8211; Present.
<p>Because Bitcoin’s early price history experienced arguably outsized gains relative to its more recent history, let’s take a look at average results for the same degree of gains in a week’s time but only examining data for the last five years (6/23/18 to the present).</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium wp-image-539437 aligncenter" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Hold-Times_Last-5-Years2-460x285.png" alt="" width="460" height="285" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Hold-Times_Last-5-Years2-460x285.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Hold-Times_Last-5-Years2-860x534.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Hold-Times_Last-5-Years2-768x477.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Hold-Times_Last-5-Years2-750x465.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Hold-Times_Last-5-Years2.png 975w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px"/></p>
Bitcoin gains &gt;= 18% in Seven Consecutive Days with Various Hold Times. Last Five Years.
<p>While once again results are positive across the board, the hypothetical results over more recent data are significantly lower, with the average 90-day return of +25.6% over the past five years a far cry from the +109.4% returns for the same 90-day window over the full price history from 2011 to the present.</p>

<p>While some traders may argue that the past five years is less representative data due to the occurrence of two major bear markets for Bitcoin and crypto more broadly, Bitcoin has shown positive follow through on average for both time periods across all the hold times we examined. While the past does not predict the future, the recent powerful price advance appears to suggest that Bitcoin is poised for greater gains in relatively near future.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/iStock-1314042576-460x288.jpg" width="460" height="288" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Mask Foundation Moves 2.5 Million Tokens To Exchanges, Huge Dip Incoming?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/altcoin/mask-foundation-moves-2-5-million-tokens-to-exchanges/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samuel Edyme]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 23:00:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Loononchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mask]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MASKUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=539425</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[In the volatile and unpredictable world of cryptocurrencies, major transactions often signal impending market movements. Recently, Lookonchain, an on-chain analytics firm, reported a substantial transfer of MASK tokens, initiated by the Mask Network Foundation. According to their findings, the foundation moved nearly 3 million MASK tokens out of its wallets, an event that could potentially lead to significant market fluctuations. At the time of writing, the token was trading at $3.69, following a decline of over 2.5% over the past 24 hours. The noteworthy shift of 2.5 million MASK tokens, equating to over $9 million, could potentially trigger further price variations. Related Reading: DeFi Liquidity Pool: A Guide to Liquidity Pool Token The intent behind the substantial token transfer remains speculative, prompting varied interpretations within the crypto community. Mask Network Foundation transferred 3M $MASK ($11.25M) out today. Among them, 2.5M $MASK ($9.4M) was transferred to #Binance and #OKX. And 500K $MASK was transferred out 1 hour ago, which may be transferred to #OKX later.https://t.co/mBI4PbZaLa pic.twitter.com/BXQNceMuxs — Lookonchain (@lookonchain) June 23, 2023 Mask Network Foundation&#8217;s Large-scale Transfer According to Lookonchain, the Mask Network Foundation distributed 2.5 million tokens, which are worth more than $9 million, between Binance and OKX. An additional 500,000 tokens were also transferred out of the foundation&#8217;s wallets, but they have not yet surfaced on any exchange platform so far. Related Reading: Bitcoin Cash (BCH) Continues To Rise While Market Sees Correction This particular move has led to speculations of an impending sell-off within the next 24-48 hours. Meanwhile, the transfer could signify the Mask Network Foundation&#8217;s strategy to bolster market-making activities. By moving a significant number of the tokens to exchange platforms, the foundation could be aiming to stimulate trading volume and attract a wider range of traders to the project. Despite the 2.5% drop in MASK&#8217;s value, the move could potentially stabilize the token&#8217;s price by fostering liquidity and demand in the market. While it&#8217;s too early to definitively predict the impact of these transactions on MASK&#8217;s market position, the movements undeniably indicate an upcoming shift in the MASK network token market. MASK&#8217;s Latest Price Action The MASK token price has increased in the past 7 days, with the token breaking multiple resistance levels. MASK is currently trading at $3.70, up by nearly 10% over the past week. However, over the past 24 hours, MASK has seen a slight decline down by 2.5%. Though it is not certain if there has been any huge sell-off yet of the tokens transferred to exchanges, the token has plunged from its 24-hour high of $3.84. The token currently has a market capitalization of $302.6 Million, making it rank 107th among the largest cryptocurrency by market cap. MASK&#8217;s daily trading volume has also significantly moved in the past 7 days. The token&#8217;s volume has surged from as low as $31 million last Friday to as high as $93 million in the past 24 hours. Related Reading: Apple’s Vision Pro Launch Impacts Metaverse, Why This Token Recorded 160% In Profits The slight decline in the token&#8217;s price can be attributed to either the trader&#8217;s fear of such a massive influx into exchanges or the overall bearish sentiment in the cryptocurrency market. Featured image from iStock, Chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In the volatile and unpredictable world of cryptocurrencies, major transactions often signal impending market movements. Recently, Lookonchain, an on-chain analytics firm, <a href="https://twitter.com/lookonchain/status/1672147459626401794?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">reported</a> a substantial transfer of MASK tokens, initiated by the Mask Network Foundation. </p>
<p>According to their findings, the foundation moved nearly 3 million MASK tokens out of its wallets, an event that could potentially lead to significant market fluctuations.</p>
<p>At the time of writing, the token was trading at $3.69, following a decline of over 2.5% over the past 24 hours. The noteworthy shift of 2.5 million MASK tokens, equating to over $9 million, could potentially trigger further price variations.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/company/defi-liquidity-pool-a-guide-to-liquidity-pool-token/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">DeFi Liquidity Pool: A Guide to Liquidity Pool Token</a></p>
<p>The intent behind the substantial token transfer remains speculative, prompting varied interpretations within the crypto community.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Mask Network Foundation transferred 3M <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24MASK&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$MASK</a> ($11.25M) out today.</p>
<p>Among them, 2.5M <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24MASK&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$MASK</a> ($9.4M) was transferred to <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Binance?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#Binance</a> and <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/OKX?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#OKX</a>.</p>
<p>And 500K <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24MASK&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$MASK</a> was transferred out 1 hour ago, which may be transferred to <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/OKX?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#OKX</a> later.<a href="https://t.co/mBI4PbZaLa" rel="nofollow">https://t.co/mBI4PbZaLa</a> <a href="https://t.co/BXQNceMuxs" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/BXQNceMuxs</a></p>
<p>— Lookonchain (@lookonchain) <a href="https://twitter.com/lookonchain/status/1672147459626401794?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">June 23, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<h2>Mask Network Foundation&#8217;s Large-scale Transfer</h2>
<p>According to Lookonchain, the Mask Network Foundation distributed 2.5 million <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/ripple/root-network-set-to-reward-its-validators-stakers-with-xrp-tokens/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">tokens</a>, which are worth more than $9 million, between Binance and OKX. An additional 500,000 tokens were also transferred out of the foundation&#8217;s wallets, but they have not yet surfaced on any exchange platform so far.</p>

<p>This particular move has led to speculations of an impending sell-off within the next 24-48 hours. Meanwhile, the transfer could signify the Mask Network Foundation&#8217;s strategy to bolster market-making activities. </p>
<p>By moving a significant number of the tokens to exchange platforms, the foundation could be aiming to stimulate trading volume and attract a wider range of traders to the project. Despite the 2.5% drop in MASK&#8217;s value, the move could potentially stabilize the token&#8217;s price by fostering liquidity and demand in the market.</p>
<p>While it&#8217;s too early to definitively predict the impact of these transactions on MASK&#8217;s market position, the movements undeniably indicate an upcoming shift in the MASK network token market. </p>
<h2>MASK&#8217;s Latest Price Action</h2>
<p>The MASK token price has increased in the past 7 days, with the token breaking multiple resistance levels. MASK is currently trading at $3.70, up by nearly 10% over the past week. However, over the past 24 hours, MASK has seen a slight decline down by 2.5%.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/FNg2pQeD/" alt="MASK token price chart on TradingView" width="2770" height="1556"/>
<p>Though it is not certain if there has been any huge sell-off yet of the tokens transferred to exchanges, the token has plunged from its 24-hour high of $3.84. <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/shiba-inu-ai-meme-token-partners-with-shibarium/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">The token</a> currently has a market capitalization of $302.6 Million, making it rank 107th among the largest cryptocurrency by market cap.</p>
<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w" dir="ltr">MASK&#8217;s daily trading volume has also significantly moved in the past 7 days. The token&#8217;s volume has surged from as low as $31 million last Friday to as high as $93 million in the past 24 hours.</p>

<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w" dir="ltr">The slight decline in the token&#8217;s price can be attributed to either the trader&#8217;s fear of such a massive influx into exchanges or the overall bearish sentiment in the cryptocurrency market. </p>
<p dir="ltr">Featured image from iStock, Chart from TradingView</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/Bitcoin-shorts-460x306.jpeg" width="460" height="306" />	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
