<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
>

<channel>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.newsbtc.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<description>Bitcoin &#38; Cryptocurrency News Today</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 03:36:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Price Steadies Above $26K, Can Bulls Pump It Further?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-steadies-above-26k/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 03:36:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xbtusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=538442</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin price is moving higher above the $26,000 resistance. BTC could continue to rise if there is a clear move above the $26,800 zone. Bitcoin started a recovery wave above the $26,000 resistance. The price is trading above $26,000 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average. There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $26,200 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Kraken). The pair could rise further if it clears the $26,650 and $26,800 resistance levels. Bitcoin Price Regains $26,000 Bitcoin price remained well-bid above the $25,500 resistance zone. As a result, BTC started a fresh recovery wave above the $26,000 resistance zone and even broke $26,200. The bulls pushed the price above the $26,500 level. A high is formed near $26,793 and the price is now consolidating gains. It is now trading near the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $24,751 swing low to the $26,793 high. Bitcoin price is now trading above $26,000 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average. Besides, there is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $26,200 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair. Source: BTCUSD on TradingView.com If there is another increase, the price might face resistance near the $26,650 level. The next major resistance is near the $26,800 level. A clear move above the $26,800 resistance might push the price further higher. The next major resistance is near the $27,200 level, above which the bulls might send BTC toward the $27,500 resistance zone. Dips Limited in BTC? If Bitcoin’s price fails to clear the $26,800 resistance, it could start a downside correction. Immediate support on the downside is near the $26,300 level. The next major support is near the $26,200 level and the trend line, below which the price might start test the 100 hourly Simple moving average. The key support is now near $25,750 or the 50% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $24,751 swing low to the $26,793 high. Any more losses might send the price toward $25,200 in the near term. Technical indicators: Hourly MACD – The MACD is now losing pace in the bullish zone. Hourly RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BTC/USD is below the 50 level. Major Support Levels – $26,200, followed by $26,000. Major Resistance Levels – $26,650, $26,800, and $27,200.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>Bitcoin price is moving higher above the $26,000 resistance. BTC could continue to rise if there is a clear move above the $26,800 zone.</em></p>
<ul>
<li>Bitcoin started a recovery wave above the $26,000 resistance.</li>
<li>The price is trading above $26,000 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average.</li>
<li>There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $26,200 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could rise further if it clears the $26,650 and $26,800 resistance levels.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Bitcoin Price Regains $26,000</h2>
<p>Bitcoin price remained well-bid above the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-aims-26200/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">$25,500 resistance zone</a>. As a result, BTC started a fresh recovery wave above the $26,000 resistance zone and even broke $26,200.</p>
<p>The bulls pushed the price above the $26,500 level. A high is formed near $26,793 and the price is now consolidating gains. It is now trading near the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $24,751 swing low to the $26,793 high.</p>
<p>Bitcoin price is now trading above $26,000 and the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-plunges-24k-next/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">100 hourly Simple moving average</a>. Besides, there is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $26,200 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-538443" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-12.png" alt="Bitcoin Price" width="1835" height="845" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-12.png 1835w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-12-460x212.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-12-860x396.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-12-768x354.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-12-1536x707.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-12-750x345.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-12-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1835px) 100vw, 1835px"/></p>
<p>Source: <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BTCUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">BTCUSD on TradingView.com</a></p>
<p>If there is another increase, the price might face resistance near the $26,650 level. The next major resistance is near the $26,800 level. A clear move above the $26,800 resistance might push the price further higher. The next major resistance is near the $27,200 level, above which the bulls might send BTC toward the $27,500 resistance zone.</p>
<h2>Dips Limited in BTC?</h2>
<p>If Bitcoin’s price fails to clear the $26,800 resistance, it could start a downside correction. Immediate support on the downside is near the $26,300 level.</p>
<p>The next major support is near the $26,200 level and the trend line, below which the price might start test the 100 hourly Simple moving average. The key support is now near $25,750 or the 50% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $24,751 swing low to the $26,793 high. Any more losses might send the price toward $25,200 in the near term.</p>
<p>Technical indicators:</p>
<p>Hourly MACD – The MACD is now losing pace in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>Hourly RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BTC/USD is below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Levels – $26,200, followed by $26,000.</p>
<p>Major Resistance Levels – $26,650, $26,800, and $27,200.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/04/Depositphotos_179514440_s-2019-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Quant Soars 20% After Partnership With Bank Of England, BIS For CBDC Project</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/all/quant-soars-20-after-partnership-with-bank-of-england-bis-for-cbdc-project/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dalmas Ngetich]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 14:50:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[All]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bank of England]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bank of International Settlement]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CBDCs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Digital Pound]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Quant]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=538390</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The native currency of Quant, a  blockchain platform that helps financial institutions incorporate digital currencies into their businesses, on June 15 soared 20% following its partnership announcement with the Bank of England for Project Rosalind. Quant Collaborates With BIS And The Bank Of England Project Rosalind is a central bank digital currency (CBDC) initiative, led by the Bank for International Settlements (BIS) and the Bank of England. It aims to explore the implementation of APIs in CBDC systems to facilitate retail payments. Project Rosalind focuses on leveraging APIs in CBDCs and investigating innovative use cases for the technology. The project uses a collaborative model between the public and private sectors. The public sector provides the needed infrastructure, and the private sector is responsible for developing consumer applications. Related Reading: ZachXBT Slapped With Defamation Lawsuit For MachiBigBrother Exposé Quant contributed to the development of Project Rosalind, by designing and developing API functionalities that would enable programmability within the private sector. Following the announcement of their contribution, QUANT soared 20%, reversing losses posted early this week. Besides designing, Quant also provided the underlying infrastructure and blockchain platform, needed for the interoperability of central bank ledgers. Gilbert Verdian, Founder and CEO of Quant, expressed enthusiasm about the potential of CBDCs, saying:  “For the first time, money is ready for the digital age. A CBDC will enable citizens and businesses to automate cumbersome payments and processes and implement logic into money. For commercial banks and other institutions, the opportunity to apply this programmability to create innovative new products that differentiate themselves from challengers and competitors is almost endless. We encourage every bank and financial institution to read the Project Rosalind report and start planning their smart money infrastructure strategy.” Project Rosalind And CBDCs Project Rosalind, led by the London Centre, was designed to tackle crucial issues within the retail CBDCs&#8217; development. These issues include improving public-private sector collaboration, maximizing interoperability, and meeting the constantly changing needs of citizens. Project Rosalind seeks to improve public-private sector collaboration by creating prototype APIs that enable a central bank to interact safely with private sector service providers. The project adopts a two-tier distribution model, with the central bank in the background, forming the foundation of the retail CBDC and private sector applications handling customer requests. Related Reading: Binance Coin (BNB) Faces Sideways Movement, Bears Threaten Further Sell-Off Through extensive collaborations, Project Rosalind has demonstrated that APIs can play a crucial role in enhancing CBDCs&#8217; payment functionalities and security. By leveraging distributed ledger technologies like blockchain, Quant can also fulfill its vision of being a decentralized network of networks, bringing greater reliability and security to various industries. Feature image from Canva, chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The native currency of Quant, a  blockchain platform that helps financial institutions incorporate digital currencies into their businesses, on June 15 soared 20% following its partnership announcement with the Bank of England for Project Rosalind.</p>
<h2>Quant Collaborates With BIS And The Bank Of England</h2>
<p>Project Rosalind is a central bank digital currency (CBDC) initiative, led by the Bank for International Settlements (BIS) and the Bank of England. It aims to explore the implementation of APIs in CBDC systems to facilitate retail payments.</p>
<p>Project Rosalind focuses on leveraging APIs in CBDCs and investigating innovative use cases for the technology. The project uses a collaborative model between the public and private sectors. The public sector provides the needed infrastructure, and the private sector is responsible for developing consumer applications.</p>

<p>Quant contributed to the development of Project Rosalind, by designing and developing API functionalities that would enable programmability within the private sector.</p>
<p>Following the announcement of their contribution, QUANT soared 20%, reversing losses posted early this week.</p>
<a href="https://www.tradingview.com/x/y8J6WR7r/" rel="nofollow"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/y8J6WR7r/" alt="QUANT Price on June 18| Source: QUANTUSDT On Binance, TradingView" width="1226" height="595"/></a>
<p>Besides designing, Quant also provided the underlying infrastructure and blockchain platform, needed for the interoperability of central bank ledgers.</p>
<p>Gilbert Verdian, Founder and CEO of Quant, expressed enthusiasm about the potential of CBDCs, <a href="https://quant.network/news/quant-collaborates-with-bis-and-the-bank-of-england-on-project-rosalind/" rel="nofollow">saying</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p> “For the first time, money is ready for the digital age. A CBDC will enable citizens and businesses to automate cumbersome payments and processes and implement logic into money. For commercial banks and other institutions, the opportunity to apply this programmability to create innovative new products that differentiate themselves from challengers and competitors is almost endless. We encourage every bank and financial institution to read the Project Rosalind report and start planning their smart money infrastructure strategy.”</p></blockquote>
<h2>Project Rosalind And CBDCs</h2>
<p>Project Rosalind, led by the London Centre, was <a href="https://www.bis.org/about/bisih/topics/cbdc/rosalind.htm" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">designed</a> to tackle crucial issues within the retail CBDCs&#8217; development. These issues include improving public-private sector collaboration, maximizing interoperability, and meeting the constantly changing needs of citizens.</p>
<p>Project Rosalind seeks to improve public-private sector collaboration by creating prototype APIs that enable a central bank to interact safely with private sector service providers. The project adopts a two-tier distribution model, with the central bank in the background, forming the foundation of the retail CBDC and private sector applications handling customer requests.</p>

<p>Through extensive collaborations, Project Rosalind has demonstrated that APIs can play a crucial role in enhancing CBDCs&#8217; payment functionalities and security.</p>
<p>By leveraging distributed ledger technologies like blockchain, Quant can also fulfill its vision of being a decentralized network of networks, bringing greater reliability and security to various industries.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/QUANT-Project-Rosalind-BIS-Bank-of-England-460x260.jpg" width="460" height="260" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Retailers Buying The Dip As BTC Soars Above $26,000</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-retailers-buying-the-dip-as-btc-soars-above-26000/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dalmas Ngetich]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 13:50:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[federal reserve]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=538386</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[On-chain data shows that Bitcoin retail buyers have been loading up the recent dip, a move that also coincided with price gains above $26,000, relieving traders and holders. Early this week, BTC prices crashed to as low as $24,820 before recovering to spot rates, adding 8% in four days. Retail Investors Are Buying The Dip Following a turbulent week in the crypto space, which involved the United States Securities and Exchange Commission, Binance and “crypto” securities-related drama, the price of Bitcoin dipped below $25,000 after the Federal Reserve paused their rate hikes and keeping the US fund rate within the 5% and 5.25% zone, increasing the uncertainty within the market. Related Reading: Polygon (MATIC) Witnesses High Volatility Amid Positive Developments However, the crypto market has since rebounded, with retail bitcoin investors, characterized by those holding 0.01 to 1 BTC, stepping in to buy up the dip. Interestingly, the dip-buying behavior exhibited by retail investors is similar in level to that observed during the Silicon Valley Bank (SVB) collapse earlier in the year, but less than that of the post FTX collapse crash which saw Bitcoin’s price tank below $16,000. With retailers loading up, it could indicate that traders and holders are confident of what lies ahead despite recent unfavorable fundamentals. Bitcoin Whales On The Move Meanwhile, with active Bitcoin retail buyers ramping up, &#8220;whales&#8221; have also been on the move. Crypto whales are addresses holding large amount of coins. A Twitter user also noted that a user with 50 BTC worth around $1.2 million recently moved his coins after being dormant since 2010. The batch of coins was originally mined in June 2010 and had remained untouched since then before being moved. Following the trend, another previously dormant Bitcoin wallet, that has been dormant for a decade, transferred $7.8 million worth of BTC to a new wallet. Another long-term holder moved $11 million worth of BTC after more than 11 years of inactivity. Related Reading: Bitcoin Recovers Above Critical Level, Why Bulls Could Be Ready To Charge At the pivotal moment of BTC’s price and the crypto space, speculators are raising questions about the motives behind such massive movements of BTC. It is known that the trading activities resulting from the transfers can impact the coin’s supply and demand dynamics of Bitcoin, potentially exerting short-term influence on prices. As of writing on June 18, Bitcoin is firm above $26,500, and has reversed losses of June 14. With retailers appearing to be buying the dip, prices may recover in the days ahead, even rallying to $30,000. Even so, Bitcoin remains under pressure and traders should watch how fundamental events, including the SEC lawsuits against Binance and Coinbase, would shape price action. Featured Image from Canva, Chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On-chain data shows that Bitcoin retail buyers have been loading up the recent dip, a move that also coincided with price gains above $26,000, relieving traders and holders. Early this week, BTC prices crashed to as low as $24,820 before recovering to spot rates, adding 8% in four days.</p>
<h2>Retail Investors Are Buying The Dip</h2>
<p>Following a turbulent week in the crypto space, which involved the United States Securities and Exchange Commission, Binance and “crypto” securities-related drama, the price of Bitcoin dipped below $25,000 after the Federal Reserve paused their rate hikes and keeping the US fund rate within the 5% and 5.25% zone, increasing the uncertainty within the market.</p>

<p>However, the crypto market has since <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/14b80es/retail_has_once_again_been_starting_to_buy_the/" rel="nofollow">rebounded</a>, with retail bitcoin investors, characterized by those holding 0.01 to 1 BTC, stepping in to buy up the dip.</p>
<p>Interestingly, the dip-buying behavior exhibited by retail investors is similar in level to that observed during the Silicon Valley Bank (SVB) collapse earlier in the year, but less than that of the post FTX collapse crash which saw Bitcoin’s price tank below $16,000.</p>
<p>With retailers loading up, it could indicate that traders and holders are confident of what lies ahead despite recent unfavorable fundamentals.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Whales On The Move</h2>
<p>Meanwhile, with active Bitcoin retail buyers ramping up, &#8220;whales&#8221; have also been on the move. Crypto whales are addresses holding large amount of coins.</p>
<p>A Twitter user also noted that a user with 50 BTC worth around $1.2 million recently <a href="https://twitter.com/TheWignus/status/1669650442278543360" rel="nofollow">moved</a> his coins after being dormant since 2010.</p>
<p>The batch of coins was originally mined in June 2010 and had remained untouched since then before being moved.</p>
<p>Following the trend, another previously dormant Bitcoin wallet, that has been dormant for a decade, transferred $7.8 million worth of BTC to a new wallet. Another long-term holder moved $11 million worth of BTC after more than 11 years of inactivity.</p>

<p>At the pivotal moment of BTC’s price and the crypto space, speculators are raising questions about the motives behind such massive movements of BTC. It is known that the trading activities resulting from the transfers can impact the coin’s supply and demand dynamics of Bitcoin, potentially exerting short-term influence on prices.</p>
<p>As of writing on June 18, Bitcoin is firm above $26,500, and has reversed losses of June 14. With retailers appearing to be buying the dip, prices may recover in the days ahead, even rallying to $30,000.</p>
<a href="https://www.tradingview.com/x/xGHoInjG/" rel="nofollow"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/xGHoInjG/" alt="Bitcoin Price On June 18| Source: BTCUSDT On Binance, TradingView" width="1226" height="595"/></a>
<p>Even so, Bitcoin remains under pressure and traders should watch how fundamental events, including the SEC lawsuits against Binance and Coinbase, would shape price action.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-Wholecoiners-460x260.jpg" width="460" height="260" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Aptos (APT) Gains 18% In The Last Week &#8211; Could A Market Reversal Finally Be On?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/aptos-apt/aptos-apt-gains-18-in-the-last-week-could-a-market-reversal-finally-be-on/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Semilore Faleti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 13:25:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Aptos (APT)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[APT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Aptos]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Reversal]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=538396</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Aptos (APT) has shown an impressive market performance in the last week gaining by 18.25% to emerge as one of the biggest weekly gainers on CoinMarketCap. This positive price movement is quite significant for many APT investors, as the APT market has been under bearish control for most of 2023. Related Reading: Polygon (MATIC) Witnesses High Volatility Amid Positive Developments Aptos’ Unimpressive 2023 Aptos began the year with a bang, surging by over 500% to hit its all-time high price of $18.58 on January 26. However, the prominent altcoin had since experienced a steady decline since then, with little insignificant price rises.  Due to such disappointing price movement, much concern has been over what was touted as “one of the most promising tokens of 2023”.  The Aptos project, which was launched back in October 2022, received a lot of hype coming into the crypto space.  Much of this interest was driven by the blockchain being an indirect product of the now-defunct Diem blockchain initiative. Aptos boasts various impressive features, including a unique programming language &#8211; Move &#8211; a parallel execution engine, low transaction costs, and high-level security features.  On June 10, APT was trading as low as $5.74, indicating a 69.11% decline from its ATH value in January. However, following its recent impressive performance, many investors wonder if the altcoin could actually be readying for market reversal. Based on data from CoinMarketCap, APT is trading at $7.05, with a 5.38% gain on the last day. The token’s daily trading volume has also moved by 125.76%, attaining a value of $274 million. Meanwhile, APT’s market cap is currently at $1 billion.  APT trading at $7.02 &#124; Source: APTUSD Chart On Tradingview.com Related Reading: Bitcoin Recovers Above Critical Level, Why Bulls Could Be Ready To Charge Is The Market Reversal On? As earlier stated, APT’s current bullish run led to much speculation among investors, with many hoping the token could soon return to the glorious heights seen at the beginning of the year.  This discourse is further fueled by various on-chain activities, an example of which is the gradual increase in daily user transactions on the Aptos network over the last few months.  According to data from aptscan.ai, an analytics tool native to the Aptos chain, the number of daily active daily transactions on the network moved from 75,806 on March 1 to 162,071 on June 16, yesterday.  Source: Aptscan.ai This continuous increase in adoption shows that many users have maintained their faith in the novel blockchain project despite the poor performance of its native asset.  According to popular price prediction site, Coincodex, the current investor sentiment around APT is neutral, with a Fear &#38; Greed index of 49, indicating the token may be a favorable investment at this point in time.  The team predicts APT to decline only by 0.86% in the next 5 days. They remain largely optimistic, backing an APT reversal as they project the token to hit a price of $15.32 in the next month.  However, note these predictions are not to be relied on as financial advice. All investors are admonished to do their due diligence before engaging the market.  Featured Image: Aptos Labs, Chart from Tradingview]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Aptos (APT) has shown an impressive market performance in the last week gaining by 18.25% to emerge as one of the <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/gainers-losers/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">biggest weekly gainers on CoinMarketCap</a>. This positive price movement is quite significant for many APT investors, as the APT market has been under bearish control for most of 2023.</p>

<h2><strong>Aptos’ Unimpressive 2023</strong></h2>
<p>Aptos began the year with a bang, surging by over 500% to hit its all-time high price of $18.58 on January 26. However, the prominent altcoin had since experienced a steady decline since then, with little insignificant price rises. </p>
<p>Due to such disappointing price movement, much concern has been over what was touted as “one of the most promising tokens of 2023”.  The Aptos project, which was launched back in October 2022, received a lot of hype coming into the crypto space. </p>
<p>Much of this interest was driven by the blockchain being an indirect product of the now-defunct Diem blockchain initiative. Aptos boasts various impressive features, including a unique programming language &#8211; Move &#8211; a parallel execution engine, low transaction costs, and high-level security features. </p>
<p>On June 10, APT was trading as low as $5.74, indicating a 69.11% decline from its ATH value in January. However, following its recent impressive performance, many investors wonder if the altcoin could actually be readying for market reversal.</p>
<p>Based on <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/aptos/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">data from CoinMarketCap</a>, APT is trading at $7.05, with a 5.38% gain on the last day. The token’s daily trading volume has also moved by 125.76%, attaining a value of $274 million. Meanwhile, APT’s market cap is currently at $1 billion. </p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/Xm09z79k/" alt="Aptos" width="1480" height="913"/></p>


<h2><strong>Is The Market Reversal On?</strong></h2>
<p>As earlier stated, APT’s current bullish run led to much speculation among investors, with many hoping the token could soon return to the glorious heights seen at the beginning of the year. </p>
<p>This discourse is further fueled by various on-chain activities, an example of which is the gradual increase in daily user transactions on the Aptos network over the last few months. </p>
<p>According to data from<a href="https://analytics.aptscan.ai/public/dashboards/ie5Gu6NerkaezgQiImQ01AL6cc9DGiDbRKaQUbxp?org_slug=default" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow"> aptscan.ai,</a> an analytics tool native to the Aptos chain, the number of daily active daily transactions on the network moved from 75,806 on March 1 to 162,071 on June 16, yesterday. </p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large wp-image-538399 aligncenter" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Screenshot-6-1-860x215.png" alt="" width="860" height="215" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Screenshot-6-1-860x215.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Screenshot-6-1-460x115.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Screenshot-6-1-768x192.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Screenshot-6-1-1536x384.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Screenshot-6-1-750x188.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Screenshot-6-1-1140x285.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Screenshot-6-1.png 1920w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/></p>
<p style="text-align: center">Source: <a href="https://analytics.aptscan.ai/public/dashboards/ie5Gu6NerkaezgQiImQ01AL6cc9DGiDbRKaQUbxp?org_slug=default" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Aptscan.ai</a></p>
<p>This continuous increase in adoption shows that many users have maintained their faith in the novel blockchain project despite the poor performance of its native asset. </p>
<p>According to popular price prediction site, <a href="https://coincodex.com/crypto/aptos/price-prediction/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Coincodex,</a> the current investor sentiment around APT is neutral, with a Fear &amp; Greed index of 49, indicating the token may be a favorable investment at this point in time. </p>
<p>The team predicts APT to decline only by 0.86% in the next 5 days. They remain largely optimistic, backing an APT reversal as they project the token to hit a price of $15.32 in the next month. </p>
<p>However, note these predictions are not to be relied on as financial advice. All investors are admonished to do their due diligence before engaging the market. </p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/aptos_meta_og_aptos-labs-5e53cba6bf9a1a30e03301fd6ff233a4b7c123de-460x242.png" width="460" height="242" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Shiba Inu (SHIB) Burn Rate Suffers 87% Decline In Single Week</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/shiba-inu-shib-burn-rate-suffers-87-decline-in-single-week/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Opeyemi Sule]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 12:59:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[SHIB]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shiba Inu]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=538397</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[In recent weeks, the burn numbers of Shiba Inu tokens have not been particularly great, especially in the past seven days. This is despite the growing optimism amongst investors about the ecosystem’s prospects. In fact, there are speculations about a potential bullish run &#8211; as things stand. The price of the SHIB coin has been on a steady rise recently, gaining over 7% in the last seven days. According to data from CoinGecko, SHIB is currently valued at $0.00000716, with a daily trading volume of more than $118.9 million. SHIBUSD trading at $0.00000717 &#124; SHIBUSD chart from TradingView Related Reading: Shiba Inu (SHIB) Positive Social Sentiment Sparks Bullish Speculation SHIB Burn Rate Drops By 87% The amount of SHIB tokens sent to the dead wallet has decreased dramatically in the past seven days. Interestingly, these dwindling burn numbers coincide with the launch of an in-real-life (IRL) component by the popular meme-inspired ecosystem. This positive development capped off what was an overall great week.  That said, the dramatic dip in the amount of Shiba Inu tokens being burnt might be something to worry about. According to data from the Shibburn wallet tracker on Twitter, only 38,673,239 SHIB tokens were transferred to the dead wallet in the last seven days, indicating an 87% overall decrease in the token’s burn rate. It is worth noting that SHIB’s burn rate is on some recovery at the moment, as over a million tokens have been set ablaze in the past day. This represents a whopping 281% burn rate increase in the last 24 hours. Shibacals Launches In Anticipation Of Shibarium Shytoshi Kusama, a prominent Shiba Inu developer, has noted in the past the challenge of moving the SHIB price based on burns only. He, however, said introducing new technologies and utilities and expanding the ecosystem can help boost SHIB’s value. With the falling burn numbers and the launch of Shibarium drawing closer, it is clear that there should be a focus on improving the project’s value through new products and technologies. Hence, it can be said that the launch of Shibacals &#8211; the in-real-life component of Shiba Inu &#8211; is a move in the right direction. This newly-launched product is expected to push the ecosystem beyond the digital space. According to a tweet showing a screenshot of Shytoshi’s message, Shibacals also brings us one step closer to the takeoff of Shibarium &#8211; Shiba Inu’s Layer-2 protocol. Although there is no set date for the launch of the layer-2 protocol, there are strong speculations it will launch in the Q3 of 2023. That said, the Shibarium protocol is expected to undergo a series of tests and audits before it goes live on the mainnet. Related Reading: Shiba Inu Collapses: How Long Can The Meme Coin Climb Back Up? Featured image from Dreamstime.com, chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p> In recent weeks, the burn numbers of Shiba Inu tokens have not been particularly great, especially in the past seven days. This is despite the growing optimism amongst investors about the ecosystem’s prospects. In fact, there are speculations about a potential bullish run &#8211; as things stand.</p>
<p>The price of the SHIB coin has been on a steady rise recently, gaining over 7% in the last seven days. According to data from <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/shiba-inu" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">CoinGecko</a>, SHIB is currently valued at $0.00000716, with a daily trading volume of more than $118.9 million.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/gG66M3rE/" alt="Shiba Inu" width="1009" height="591"/></p>

<p>Related Reading: <a style="color: #212121" href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/shiba-inu-shib-positive-social-sentiment-sparks-bullish-speculation/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Shiba Inu (SHIB) Positive Social Sentiment Sparks Bullish Speculation</a></p>
<h2><strong>SHIB Burn Rate Drops By 87%</strong></h2>
<p>The amount of SHIB tokens sent to the dead wallet has decreased dramatically in the past seven days. Interestingly, these dwindling burn numbers coincide with the launch of an in-real-life (IRL) component by the popular meme-inspired ecosystem. This positive development capped off what was an overall great week. </p>
<p>That said, the dramatic dip in the amount of Shiba Inu tokens being burnt might be something to worry about. According to <a href="https://twitter.com/shibburn/status/1670370819585835010?s=46&amp;t=Vga4cmDMTcDim0dXxouNGw" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">data from the Shibburn wallet tracker</a> on Twitter, only 38,673,239 SHIB tokens were transferred to the dead wallet in the last seven days, indicating an 87% overall decrease in the token’s burn rate.</p>
<p>It is worth noting that SHIB’s burn rate is on some recovery at the moment, as over a million tokens have been set ablaze in the past day. This represents a whopping 281% burn rate increase in the last 24 hours.</p>
<h2><strong>Shibacals Launches In Anticipation Of Shibarium</strong></h2>
<p>Shytoshi Kusama, a prominent Shiba Inu developer, has noted in the past the challenge of moving the SHIB price based on burns only. He, however, said introducing new technologies and utilities and expanding the ecosystem can help boost SHIB’s value.</p>
<p>With the falling burn numbers and the launch of Shibarium drawing closer, it is clear that there should be a focus on improving the project’s value through new products and technologies. Hence, it can be said that the <a href="https://twitter.com/lucieshib/status/1669628347662360576?s=46&amp;t=Vga4cmDMTcDim0dXxouNGw" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">launch of Shibacals</a> &#8211; the in-real-life component of Shiba Inu &#8211; is a move in the right direction. This newly-launched product is expected to push the ecosystem beyond the digital space.</p>
<p>According to a <a href="https://twitter.com/lucieshib/status/1669430140152020992?s=46&amp;t=2ssMCjOHfnc-NvhTW-sU2A" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">tweet</a> showing a screenshot of Shytoshi’s message, Shibacals also brings us one step closer to the takeoff of Shibarium &#8211; Shiba Inu’s Layer-2 protocol. Although there is no set date for the launch of the layer-2 protocol, there are strong speculations it will launch in the Q3 of 2023.</p>
<p>That said, the Shibarium protocol is expected to undergo a series of tests and audits before it goes live on the mainnet.</p>





]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/shiba-inu-coin-one-stack-bitcoins-over-white-background-222358955-460x306.jpg" width="460" height="306" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Floki Inu Dull, Motionless Following Binance Metaverse Integration &#8211; Here&#8217;s Why</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/floki-inu-dull-and-motionless-following-binance-metaverse-integration-heres-why/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 06:57:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FLOKI]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Floki Inu]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[meme coin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Metaverse]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=538373</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Binance, the global crypto exchange renowned for its vast scale and influence, has taken a step towards promoting the widespread acceptance and usage of Floki Inu, the popular memecoin that has captured the attention of crypto enthusiasts worldwide. Embarking on a strategic initiative, Binance has ingeniously incorporated Floki Inu into two exceptional categories within its expansive ecosystem, namely the Metaverse and Gaming sections. With this development, Binance has effectively opened up new avenues for the crypto named after billionaire Elon Musk&#8217;s dog, propelling its growth trajectory and solidifying its position as a prominent player in the ever-evolving crypto landscape. #Binance has added $FLOKI to the #Metaverse and #Gaming categories on its exchange! 🔥 This is a big deal and allows millions of users to trade #Floki alongside top metaverse and gaming cryptocurrencies like $SAND, $MANA, $AXS, $IMX, $GALA, and $ENJ.#Floki adoption continues! pic.twitter.com/UKIssfoOih — FLOKI (@RealFlokiInu) June 16, 2023 The Floki Inu team may have hoped that news of Binance&#8217;s decision to add the meme to the Metaverse area would increase the value of their coin, but this was not the case today. Floki Inu Price Wasn&#8217;t Feeling It At the time of writing, FLOKI price was nearly unchanged, managing to notch a meager 1.4% increase in the last 24 hours, data from crypto market tracker Coingecko shows. In the last seven days, the meme coin was only able to maintain a less than 5% gain. Source: Coingecko The dog-themed token was likewise struggling in the 14-day and 30-day timeframes, shedding an average of 30% declines as questions about its capability to reclaim its recent strong performance mount. Source: Coingecko Floki&#8217;s popularity has been on the rise in recent months, making it the fourth largest meme coin by market cap. Bitci, a leading cryptocurrency exchange in Turkey with more than 5 million customers, has added support for the token. The meme coin&#8217;s recent tweet, stating its plans to develop a crypto education platform, also caused a stir in the crypto community. The University Of Floki is an online resource designed to meet the needs of the estimated 1 billion cryptocurrency users worldwide by 2025. As of today, the market cap of cryptocurrencies stood at $1.03 trillion. Chart: TradingView.com By placing Floki Inu in the Metaverse section of the exchange, Binance has essentially set up the way for the meme coin to flourish in the field of virtual reality and digital environment. By also realizing Floki Inu&#8217;s potential in the gaming industry, Binance has created a link between the cryptocurrency industry and the ever-evolving world of digital entertainment. Related Reading: Polygon (MATIC) Sees Surge In Whale Buying Despite US Regulatory Pressure Dismal Social Volume Figure Meanwhile, Santiment&#8217;s research reveals that FLOKI&#8217;s social volume suggests there was minimal excitement or speculation about the token after the Binance metaverse integration was announced. The social volume measures the amount of buzz surrounding a coin in a certain time frame. FLOKI weighted sentiment and social volume. Source: Santiment Like the total social volume, the weighted sentiment of FLOKI remained in the negative zone. Despite some uncertainty, the general attitude toward FLOKI has remained unfavorable as measured by its weighted sentiment rating of (minus) 0.536. This number is an aggregate expression of opinion across all available data on FLOKI, such as threads, comments, and interactions. Related Reading: Shiba Inu (SHIB) Positive Social Sentiment Sparks Bullish Speculation Persistently unfavorable sentiment indicates widespread doubt, anxiety, or discontent about FLOKI and its associated variables among the community and market participants. If people are generally optimistic while talking about a token, it can be inferred that their opinion toward the asset is good. In contrast, FLOKI&#8217;s predominance of negative numbers indicates that pessimistic commentary predominates. This shows that people are mostly apprehensive rather than optimistic about the meme coin. Featured image from Sam Cooling x Floki Inu]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Binance, the global crypto exchange renowned for its vast scale and influence, has taken a step towards promoting the widespread acceptance and usage of Floki Inu, the popular memecoin that has captured the attention of crypto enthusiasts worldwide.</p>
<p>Embarking on a strategic initiative, Binance has ingeniously incorporated Floki Inu into two exceptional categories within its expansive ecosystem, namely the Metaverse and Gaming sections.</p>
<p>With this development, Binance has effectively opened up new avenues for the crypto named after billionaire Elon Musk&#8217;s dog, propelling its growth trajectory and solidifying its position as a prominent player in the ever-evolving crypto landscape.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en"><a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Binance?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#Binance</a> has added <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24FLOKI&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$FLOKI</a> to the <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Metaverse?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#Metaverse</a> and <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Gaming?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#Gaming</a> categories on its exchange! <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f525.png" alt="🔥" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /></p>
<p>This is a big deal and allows millions of users to trade <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Floki?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#Floki</a> alongside top metaverse and gaming cryptocurrencies like <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24SAND&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$SAND</a>, <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24MANA&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$MANA</a>, <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24AXS&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$AXS</a>, <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24IMX&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$IMX</a>, <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24GALA&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$GALA</a>, and <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24ENJ&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$ENJ</a>.<a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Floki?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#Floki</a> adoption continues! <a href="https://t.co/UKIssfoOih" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/UKIssfoOih</a></p>
<p>— FLOKI (@RealFlokiInu) <a href="https://twitter.com/RealFlokiInu/status/1669762218517209094?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">June 16, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p>The Floki Inu team may have hoped that news of Binance&#8217;s decision to add the meme to the Metaverse area would increase the value of their coin, but this was not the case today.</p>
<h2><strong>Floki Inu Price Wasn&#8217;t Feeling It</strong></h2>
<p>At the time of writing, FLOKI price was nearly <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/?page=2" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">unchanged</a>, managing to notch a meager 1.4% increase in the last 24 hours, data from crypto market tracker Coingecko shows. In the last seven days, the meme coin was only able to maintain a less than 5% gain.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-538378" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Floki.png" alt="" width="1138" height="64" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Floki.png 1138w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Floki-460x26.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Floki-860x48.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Floki-768x43.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Floki-750x42.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 1138px) 100vw, 1138px"/></p>

<p>The dog-themed token was likewise struggling in the 14-day and 30-day timeframes, shedding an average of <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/floki" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">30% declines</a> as questions about its capability to reclaim its recent strong performance mount.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-538377" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-105.png" alt="" width="767" height="105" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-105.png 767w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-105-460x63.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-105-750x103.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 767px) 100vw, 767px"/></p>

<p>Floki&#8217;s popularity has been on the rise in recent months, making it the fourth largest meme coin by market cap. Bitci, a leading cryptocurrency exchange in Turkey with more than 5 million customers, has added support for the token.</p>
<p>The meme coin&#8217;s recent tweet, stating its plans to develop a crypto education platform, also caused a stir in the crypto community. The University Of Floki is an online resource designed to meet the needs of the estimated 1 billion cryptocurrency users worldwide by 2025.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/13i7M7uS/" width="2315" height="1109"/></p>

<p>By placing Floki Inu in the Metaverse section of the exchange, Binance has essentially set up the way for the meme coin to flourish in the field of virtual reality and digital environment.</p>
<p>By also realizing Floki Inu&#8217;s potential in the gaming industry, Binance has created a link between the cryptocurrency industry and the ever-evolving world of digital entertainment.</p>

<h2><strong>Dismal Social Volume Figure</strong></h2>
<p>Meanwhile, Santiment&#8217;s research reveals that FLOKI&#8217;s social volume suggests there was minimal excitement or speculation about the token after the Binance metaverse integration was announced. The social volume measures the amount of buzz surrounding a coin in a certain time frame.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-538375 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-104-860x297.png" alt="" width="860" height="297" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-104-860x297.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-104-460x159.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-104-768x265.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-104-1536x530.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-104-750x259.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-104-1140x394.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-104.png 1552w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/></p>

<p>Like the total social volume, the weighted sentiment of FLOKI remained in the negative zone. Despite some uncertainty, the general attitude toward FLOKI has remained unfavorable as measured by its weighted sentiment rating of (minus) 0.536.</p>
<p>This number is an aggregate expression of opinion across all available data on FLOKI, such as threads, comments, and interactions.</p>

<p>Persistently unfavorable sentiment indicates widespread doubt, anxiety, or discontent about FLOKI and its associated variables among the community and market participants.</p>
<p>If people are generally optimistic while talking about a token, it can be inferred that their opinion toward the asset is good.</p>
<p>In contrast, FLOKI&#8217;s predominance of negative numbers indicates that pessimistic commentary predominates. This shows that people are mostly apprehensive rather than optimistic about the meme coin.</p>
<p><em>Featured image from Sam Cooling x Floki Inu</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-106-460x255.png" width="460" height="255" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Recovers Above Critical Level, Why Bulls Could Be Ready To Charge</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-recovers-above-critical-level-2023/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tony "The Bull"]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 19:22:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusdc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=538352</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin CME Futures BTC1 front month continuous contract price action closes over the weekend, making Friday evening the closing bell for the week. This Friday&#8217;s close saw price recover above a crucial level that in the past led to a bullish impulse in crypto. Here is a closer look at why bulls could be ready to charge in the coming weeks. Using BTC CME Futures As A Crypto Crystal Ball Large institutional traders don&#8217;t just trade spot BTCUSD, nor do they trade on Binance, ByBit, or another crypto platform. When they want to speculate and trade using derivatives contracts, they look to the Chicago Mercantile Exchange, better known as CME Group. Unlike the 24/7, always-on crypto market, CME Group charts close down for the weekend and holidays much like stocks. Due to this behavior, the chart often features gaps that don&#8217;t appear on standard BTCUSD price charts. Discrepancies between BTC CME Futures charts and BTCUSD charts can lead to fakeouts and shakeouts. Related Reading: One Coin, Two Trades: Why Bitcoin Futures And Spot Signals Don’t Match Up Because Bitcoin CME Futures does stop on Friday for the weekend, it also can provide early clues as to how spot price charts might close on Sunday night. In this case, BTC Futures has reclaimed the Bollinger Band basis line, often referred to as the &#8220;mid-BB&#8221;. Is the third time the charm? &#124; BTCUSD on TradingView.com Bitcoin Price Recovers Above The Bollinger Band Basis Line The basis line on the Bollinger Bands is a 20-period simple moving average. The tool&#8217;s creator, John Bollinger, then adds an upper and lower band set at two standard deviations of the SMA. This causes the bands to expand and contract with market volatility. Like any moving average, it can act as dynamic support and resistance, holding up price action or preventing it from pushing along further. Following this Friday&#8217;s BTC Futures weekly close, Bitcoin has made it back above the mid-BB, possibly confirming it as support. Related Reading: Bitcoin “Throwback” Could Trigger Flawless Technical Bottom Formation In the upper portion of the chart above, Bitcoin goes on an impulsive uptrend after holding above the basis line in 2019 and 2020. The lower portion depicts a closer look at this latest weekly close. Unless there is a massive collapse before Sunday night, BTCUSD technicals should follow suit. And if history repeats, a bull run could follow. Is Bitcoin ready for a strong rally higher after reclaiming the key level as support? This chart was featured in issue #8 of CoinChartist (VIP) alongside a dozen other exclusive crypto charts. Click here to learn more. Tony is the author of the CoinChartist (VIP) newsletter. Follow @TonyTheBullBTC &#38; @coinchartist_io on Twitter. Or join the TonyTradesBTC Telegram for daily market insights and technical analysis education. Please note: Content is educational and should not be considered investment advice. Featured image from iStockPhoto, Charts from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin CME Futures BTC1 front month continuous contract price action closes over the weekend, making Friday evening the closing bell for the week. This Friday&#8217;s close saw price recover above a crucial level that in the past led to a bullish impulse in crypto. Here is a closer look at why bulls could be ready to charge in the coming weeks.</p>
<h2>Using BTC CME Futures As A Crypto Crystal Ball</h2>
<p>Large institutional traders don&#8217;t just trade spot BTCUSD, nor do they trade on Binance, ByBit, or another crypto platform. When they want to speculate and trade using derivatives contracts, they look to the Chicago Mercantile Exchange, better known as <a href="https://www.cmegroup.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">CME Group</a>.</p>
<p>Unlike the 24/7, always-on crypto market, CME Group charts close down for the weekend and holidays much like stocks. Due to this behavior, the chart often features gaps that don&#8217;t appear on standard BTCUSD price charts. Discrepancies between BTC CME Futures charts and BTCUSD charts can lead to <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-futures-and-spot-signals-dont-match-up/">fakeouts and shakeouts</a>.</p>

<p>Because Bitcoin CME Futures does stop on Friday for the weekend, it also can provide <em>early</em> <em>clues</em> as to how spot price charts might close on Sunday night. In this case, BTC Futures has reclaimed the Bollinger Band basis line, often referred to as the &#8220;mid-BB&#8221;.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-large wp-image-538353 aligncenter" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTC1_2023-06-17_09-27-32-860x470.png" alt="BTC1!_2023-06-17_09-27-32" width="860" height="470" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTC1_2023-06-17_09-27-32-860x470.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTC1_2023-06-17_09-27-32-460x252.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTC1_2023-06-17_09-27-32-768x420.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTC1_2023-06-17_09-27-32-1536x840.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTC1_2023-06-17_09-27-32-2048x1120.png 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTC1_2023-06-17_09-27-32-750x410.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTC1_2023-06-17_09-27-32-1140x623.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/></p>

<h2>Bitcoin Price Recovers Above The Bollinger Band Basis Line</h2>
<p>The basis line on the <a href="https://coinchartist.io/bollinger-bands/education/technical-indicators-oscillators/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Bollinger Bands</a> is a 20-period simple moving average. The tool&#8217;s creator, John Bollinger, then adds an upper and lower band set at two standard deviations of the SMA. This causes the bands to expand and contract with market volatility.</p>
<p>Like any moving average, it can act as dynamic support and resistance, holding up price action or preventing it from pushing along further. Following this Friday&#8217;s BTC Futures weekly close, Bitcoin has made it back above the mid-BB, possibly confirming it as support.</p>

<p>In the upper portion of the chart above, Bitcoin goes on an impulsive uptrend after holding above the basis line in 2019 and 2020. The lower portion depicts a closer look at this latest weekly close. Unless there is a massive collapse before Sunday night, BTCUSD technicals should follow suit. And if history repeats, a bull run could follow.</p>
<p>Is Bitcoin ready for a strong rally higher after reclaiming the key level as support? This chart was featured in <a href="https://coinchartist.substack.com/p/issue-8-btc-2023-2020-2019" rel="nofollow">issue #8 of CoinChartist (VIP)</a> alongside a dozen other exclusive crypto charts. Click <a href="https://coinchartist.substack.com/p/issue-8-btc-2023-2020-2019" rel="nofollow">here</a> to learn more.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/iStock-933665824-460x339.jpg" width="460" height="339" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Polygon (MATIC) Witnesses High Volatility Amid Positive Developments</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/matic-analysis/polygon-matic-witnesses-high-volatility-amid-positive-developments/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Olowoporoku Adeniyi]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 13:50:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[MATIC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Matic Network]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Polygon]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=538338</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Polygon (MATIC), one of the prominent Web3 networks, has recently experienced a period of volatility in its price. Currently trading at $0.625112 USD, with a 24-hour trading volume of $547,815,952 USD, MATIC has shown a 9.63% increase in the last 24 hours. Polygon has rebounded from the bearish sentiments earlier in the week. This comes on the back of recent developments within the Polygon ecosystem towards increasing utility and partnerships with key financial institutions.  Polygon Launches &#8216;The Value Prop&#8217; Polygon has made an important announcement, launching &#8220;The Value Prop,&#8221; an open database of blockchain use cases. This comprehensive catalog contains over 300 applications and diverse use cases across multiple business sectors, blockchain networks, and geographical locations. The initiative aims to showcase positive applications for blockchain technology, presenting it as a versatile tool beyond asset trading. Related Reading: Percentage Of ETH Addresses In Profit Reaches 5-Month Low Amid the negative sentiment surrounding blockchain technology due to regulatory pressures on major market participants like Binance and Coinbase, Polygon&#8217;s move to highlight real-world applications is significant. It aligns with the belief among Web3 experts and industry players that blockchain should be viewed as a general-purpose technology addressing real-world challenges. Web3 Development And Positive Trends Polygon&#8217;s efforts to boost Web3 development and unlock new use cases align with the industry&#8217;s overall trajectory. Ripple (XRP) recently partnered with Banco de la República, Colombia&#8217;s central bank, to explore blockchain use cases. This indicates a growing recognition of the potential of blockchain technology beyond cryptocurrencies. Polygon&#8217;s co-founder, Sandeep Nailwal, also launched the Nailwal Fellowship, a grant program providing financial support and resources to early-stage Web3 developers. This initiative offers funding, mentorship, and access to top founders and investors, nurturing the growth of the Web3 ecosystem. Related Reading: Shiba Inu (SHIB) Positive Social Sentiment Sparks Bullish Speculation Despite the U.S. banking crisis contagion, Web3 development has shown resilience. According to Alchemy, a blockchain developer platform, Q1 2023 witnessed rapid growth in Web3 development. The number of developer teams working on the Alchemy platform reached a record high, with increased activity compared to the previous year. Future Prospect For Polygon MATIC, the native token of Polygon, is trading in the positive zone and is up 9% in the last 24 hours. At the time of writing, the price is $0.6228, according to TradingView chart. However, amid the price volatility, the launch of &#8220;The Value Prop&#8221; and the focus on Web3 development suggest potential positive catalysts for Polygon&#8217;s future performance. As the blockchain industry continues to evolve, market participants will closely monitor the progress of Web3 development, the expansion of real-world use cases, and the regulatory landscape. These factors will significantly impact the prospects of Polygon and its native token, MATIC. Featured image from iStock, charts from Tradingview and Coingecko]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Polygon (MATIC), one of the prominent Web3 networks, has recently experienced a period of volatility in its price. Currently trading at $0.625112 USD, with a 24-hour trading volume of $547,815,952 USD, MATIC has shown a 9.63% increase in the last 24 hours. Polygon has rebounded from the bearish sentiments earlier in the week. This comes on the back of recent developments within the Polygon ecosystem towards increasing utility and partnerships with key financial institutions. </p>
<h2><strong>Polygon Launches &#8216;The Value Prop&#8217;</strong></h2>
<p>Polygon has made an important announcement, launching &#8220;The Value Prop,&#8221; an open database of blockchain use cases. This comprehensive catalog contains over 300 applications and diverse use cases across multiple business sectors, blockchain networks, and geographical locations. The initiative aims to showcase positive applications for blockchain technology, presenting it as a versatile tool beyond asset trading.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-538345 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Screenshot_169.png" alt="Matic Is up 5.9% in the past 7-days: source @coingecko" width="814" height="77" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Screenshot_169.png 814w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Screenshot_169-460x44.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Screenshot_169-768x73.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Screenshot_169-750x71.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 814px) 100vw, 814px"/>
<p><strong>Related Reading</strong>: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/ethereum/percentage-of-eth-addresses-in-profit-reaches-5-month-low/">Percentage Of ETH Addresses In Profit Reaches 5-Month Low</a></p>
<p>Amid the negative sentiment surrounding blockchain technology due to regulatory pressures on major market participants like Binance and Coinbase, Polygon&#8217;s move to highlight real-world applications is significant. It aligns with the belief among Web3 experts and industry players that blockchain should be viewed as a general-purpose technology addressing real-world challenges.</p>
<h2><strong>Web3 Development And Positive Trends</strong></h2>
<p>Polygon&#8217;s efforts to boost Web3 development and unlock new use cases align with the industry&#8217;s overall trajectory. Ripple (XRP) recently partnered with <a href="https://www.banrep.gov.co/es" rel="nofollow">Banco de la República</a>, Colombia&#8217;s central bank, to explore blockchain use cases. This indicates a growing recognition of the potential of blockchain technology beyond cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p>Polygon&#8217;s co-founder, Sandeep Nailwal, also launched the Nailwal Fellowship, a grant program providing financial support and resources to early-stage Web3 developers. This initiative offers funding, mentorship, and access to top founders and investors, nurturing the growth of the Web3 ecosystem.</p>
<p><strong>Related Reading</strong>: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/shiba-inu-shib-positive-social-sentiment-sparks-bullish-speculation/?swcfpc=1">Shiba Inu (SHIB) Positive Social Sentiment Sparks Bullish Speculation</a></p>
<p>Despite the U.S. banking crisis contagion, Web3 development has shown resilience. According to Alchemy, a blockchain developer platform, Q1 2023 witnessed rapid growth in Web3 development. The number of developer teams working on the Alchemy platform reached a record high, with increased activity compared to the previous year.</p>
<strong>Future Prospect For Polygon</strong>
<p>MATIC, the native token of Polygon, is trading in the positive zone and is up 9% in the last 24 hours. At the time of writing, the price is $0.6228, according to TradingView chart. However, amid the price volatility, the launch of &#8220;The Value Prop&#8221; and the focus on Web3 development suggest potential positive catalysts for Polygon&#8217;s future performance.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-538344 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/MATICUSD_2023-06-17_13-18-43-860x445.png" alt="Matic has experienced a bullish rally in the past 24 hours: source @tradingview" width="860" height="445" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/MATICUSD_2023-06-17_13-18-43-860x445.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/MATICUSD_2023-06-17_13-18-43-460x238.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/MATICUSD_2023-06-17_13-18-43-768x397.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/MATICUSD_2023-06-17_13-18-43-1536x794.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/MATICUSD_2023-06-17_13-18-43-750x388.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/MATICUSD_2023-06-17_13-18-43-1140x589.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/MATICUSD_2023-06-17_13-18-43.png 1567w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/>
<p>As the blockchain industry continues to evolve, market participants will closely monitor the progress of Web3 development, the expansion of real-world use cases, and the regulatory landscape. These factors will significantly impact the prospects of Polygon and its native token, MATIC.</p>
<p><em>Featured image from iStock, charts from Tradingview and Coingecko</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/iStock-1291935777-460x263.jpg" width="460" height="263" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>ZachXBT Slapped With Defamation Lawsuit For MachiBigBrother Exposé</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/crypto/zachxbt-slapped-with-defamation-lawsuit-for-machibigbrother-expose/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 13:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto investigation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto lawsuit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MachiBigBrother]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ZachXBT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=538337</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A throwback article just came back to haunt one of the crypto industry&#8217;s favorite crypto investigators. ZachXBT, a popular crypto on-chain sleuth recently got slapped with a defamatory lawsuit over an article he published last year.  The Controversial Article That Started It All Around a year ago, ZachXBT published an article accusing Jeffrey Huang aka MachiBigBrother, of embezzling crypto assets using various methods ranging from failed pump and dump tokens to NFT projects. The article quickly gained widespread attention at the time, but it has been largely forgotten up until this point.  Related Reading: Shiba Inu (SHIB) Positive Social Sentiment Sparks Bullish Speculation Jeffrey Huang, known online as Machi Big Brother, is a former Taiwanese-American musician and tech entrepreneur.  Huang has now filed a defamation lawsuit against ZachXBT, claiming the year-old article has damaged his reputation. Huang has insisted, at least according to a post that he published on Twitter, that ZachXBT&#8217;s charges are false and defamatory. As a result, he has decided to sue for defamation of character. A cursory reading of the article, on the other hand, reveals that it is an investigational piece that goes into considerable detail. In the article, ZachXBT provided on-chain data to back up his claims. The crypto sleuth initially accused Machi Big Brother of embezzling 22,000 ETH from Formosa Financial, a treasury management platform built for blockchain companies in 2018. Furthermore, ZachXBT then provided a list of other projects like Machi X and Wifey Finance. Total market cap still sitting above $1 trillion &#124; Source: Crypto Total Market Cap on TradingView.com How ZachXBT Is Fighting Back Against The Lawsuit ZachXBT is not taking this lawsuit lying down as he’s come out swinging against what he calls a baseless lawsuit with &#8220;an attempt to chill free speech.&#8221; ZachXBT has asked his followers and subscribers to support him against censorship and cancel culture, ensuring the truth survives.  He termed the whole situation as a &#8220;classic David &#38; Goliath story,” and many have spoken out on social media defending his right to express his opinions. Brown Rudnick, a law firm with its headquarters in Boston famous for defending Johnny Depp in his case against his ex-wife Amber Heard, has agreed to represent ZachXBT in the lawsuit. Related Reading: PEPE Jumps Nearly 10% In 24 Hours, Sparking Speculation Of A New Rally While lawsuits can be expensive to defend, ZachXBT says he will rely on donations from his followers to mount a proper defense. In this case, he says legal costs associated with the defense of this matter could easily exceed $1 million while providing a donation address. Donations have started to troop in. At the time of this writing, the address now contains more than $290,000.  The outcome of this case could have significant implications for crypto media and regulations around defamation and libel for public figures in the crypto industry.  Featured image from Legacy Design Strategies, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A throwback article just came back to haunt one of the crypto industry&#8217;s favorite crypto investigators. ZachXBT, a popular crypto on-chain sleuth recently got slapped with a defamatory lawsuit over an article he published last year. </p>
<h2>The Controversial Article That Started It All</h2>
<p>Around a year ago, ZachXBT published an <a href="https://medium.com/@investigationsbyzachxbt/22-000-eth-embezzled-and-over-ten-projects-failed-the-story-of-machi-big-brother-jeff-huang-a1ad073fcfa8" rel="nofollow">article </a>accusing Jeffrey Huang aka MachiBigBrother, of embezzling crypto assets using various methods ranging from failed pump and dump tokens to NFT projects. The article quickly gained widespread attention at the time, but it has been largely forgotten up until this point. </p>

<p>Jeffrey Huang, known online as Machi Big Brother, is a former Taiwanese-American musician and tech entrepreneur. </p>
<p>Huang has now filed a defamation lawsuit against ZachXBT, claiming the year-old article has damaged his reputation. Huang has insisted, at least according to a <a href="https://twitter.com/machibigbrother/status/1669780922449956864?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw%7Ctwcamp%5Etweetembed%7Ctwterm%5E1669780922449956864%7Ctwgr%5E66e989d4ba25dc44d5ef67f4c0184b3d3311aaa4%7Ctwcon%5Es1_&amp;ref_url=https%3A%2F%2Fcointelegraph.com%2Fnews%2Fzach-xbt-sued-libel-claimed-plaintiff-drained-funds-from-project" rel="nofollow">post </a>that he published on Twitter, that ZachXBT&#8217;s charges are false and defamatory. As a result, he has decided to sue for defamation of character.</p>
<p>A cursory reading of the article, on the other hand, reveals that it is an investigational piece that goes into considerable detail. In the article, ZachXBT provided on-chain data to back up his claims. The crypto sleuth initially accused Machi Big Brother of embezzling 22,000 ETH from Formosa Financial, a treasury management platform built for blockchain companies in 2018. Furthermore, ZachXBT then provided a list of other projects like Machi X and Wifey Finance.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/Jjbwg7rR/" alt="Crypto total market cap chart from TradingView.com" width="2884" height="1724"/></p>

<h2>How ZachXBT Is Fighting Back Against The Lawsuit</h2>
<p>ZachXBT is not taking this lawsuit lying down as he’s come out swinging against what he calls a baseless lawsuit with &#8220;an attempt to chill free speech.&#8221; ZachXBT has asked his followers and subscribers to support him against censorship and cancel culture, ensuring the truth survives. </p>
<p>He termed the whole situation as a &#8220;classic David &amp; Goliath story,” and many have spoken out on social media defending his right to express his opinions. Brown Rudnick, a law firm with its headquarters in Boston famous for defending Johnny Depp in his case against his ex-wife Amber Heard, has agreed to represent ZachXBT in the lawsuit.</p>

<p>While lawsuits can be expensive to defend, ZachXBT says he will rely on donations from his followers to mount a proper defense. In this case, he says legal costs associated with the defense of this matter could easily exceed $1 million while providing a donation address. Donations have started to troop in. At the time of this writing, the address now contains more than $290,000. </p>
<p>The outcome of this case could have significant implications for crypto media and regulations around defamation and libel for public figures in the crypto industry. </p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ZachXBT-crypto-lawsuit-460x299.jpeg" width="460" height="299" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance Coin (BNB) Faces Sideways Movement, Bears Threaten Further Sell-Off</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/binance-coin/binance-coin-bnb-faces-sideways-movement-bears-threaten-further-sell-off/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Olowoporoku Adeniyi]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 12:06:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Binance Coin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BNB]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BNB analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=538333</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Binance Coin (BNB), the native token of the Binance exchange, has recently experienced a period of sideways movement. Despite reaching a weekly high of $307 on June 4th, BNB&#8217;s price has encountered resistance and is currently trading at $246.2. This article provides an analysis of the recent price action, discusses the potential reasons behind BNB&#8217;s performance, and explores the future prospects for the coin. The recent decline in BNB&#8217;s price can be attributed to several factors. Firstly, the overall market sentiment has been influenced by a broader correction in the cryptocurrency market. Many altcoins, including BNB, have witnessed a decrease in value as investors take profits and adjust their portfolios. Additionally, concerns over regulatory developments and market uncertainties have added to the selling pressure on BNB. Bearish Threat And Technical Indicators Despite attempts by bulls to regain control, bears pose a significant threat to BNB&#8217;s price stability. The crucial resistance level of $308 has become a battleground for market participants. If the bears manage to break down this level, it could trigger a further sell-off, potentially pushing the price lower.  Technical indicators paint a cautious picture for BNB. The Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD) indicator has exhibited a bearish crossover, signaling a continuation of selling pressure in the near term. Furthermore, the Relative Strength Index (RSI) currently stands at 35.63 levels, suggesting that there could be a further downside if buying pressure does not increase. Related Reading: PEPE Jumps Nearly 10% In 24 Hours, Sparking Speculation Of A New Rally Moreover, the 50-Weekly Moving Average positioned below the 200-Weekly MA indicates a bearish trend for BNB. This configuration suggests that the price could continue downward in the coming days unless significant positive developments or market catalysts emerge. What’s Next For BNB? Market participants will closely monitor the price action around the critical resistance level of $308. A successful breach above this level could ignite renewed bullish momentum, potentially leading to a recovery in BNB&#8217;s price. Traders and investors will also pay attention to any regulatory developments and market trends that could influence BNB&#8217;s performance. Despite the current challenges, Binance Coin holds promise as a key player in the cryptocurrency ecosystem. As Binance continues to expand its services and offerings, including its decentralized exchange (DEX) and various partnerships, there is potential for increased adoption of BNB, which could positively impact its price in the long run. Related Reading: Percentage Of ETH Addresses In Profit Reaches 5-Month Low It is important to note that the cryptocurrency market is highly volatile, and prices can change rapidly. Investors are advised to conduct thorough research, stay informed about market developments, and exercise caution when making investment decisions. At press time, Binance Coin (BNB) was trading at $246.2 with a daily price increase of 2.93%. Featured image from iStock.com, charts from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Binance Coin (BNB), the native token of the Binance exchange, has recently experienced a period of sideways movement. Despite reaching a weekly high of $307 on June 4th, BNB&#8217;s price has encountered resistance and is currently trading at $246.2. This article provides an analysis of the recent price action, discusses the potential reasons behind BNB&#8217;s performance, and explores the future prospects for the coin.</p>
<p>The recent decline in BNB&#8217;s price can be attributed to several factors. Firstly, the overall market sentiment has been influenced by a broader correction in the cryptocurrency market. Many altcoins, including BNB, have witnessed a decrease in value as investors take profits and adjust their portfolios. Additionally, concerns over regulatory developments and market uncertainties have added to the selling pressure on BNB.</p>
<h2><strong>Bearish Threat And Technical Indicators</strong></h2>
<p>Despite attempts by bulls to regain control, bears pose a significant threat to BNB&#8217;s price stability. The crucial resistance level of $308 has become a battleground for market participants. If the bears manage to break down this level, it could trigger a further sell-off, potentially pushing the price lower. </p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium wp-image-538334" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image1-3-460x215.png" alt="BNB weekly chart shows sideways movement: source @Tradingview" width="460" height="215" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image1-3-460x215.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image1-3-750x351.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image1-3.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px"/>
<p>Technical indicators paint a cautious picture for BNB. The Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD) indicator has exhibited a bearish crossover, signaling a continuation of selling pressure in the near term. Furthermore, the Relative Strength Index (RSI) currently stands at 35.63 levels, suggesting that there could be a further downside if buying pressure does not increase.</p>
<p><strong>Related Reading</strong>: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/pepe-jumps-nearly-10-in-24-hours-sparking-speculation-of-a-new-rally/">PEPE Jumps Nearly 10% In 24 Hours, Sparking Speculation Of A New Rally</a></p>
<p>Moreover, the 50-Weekly Moving Average positioned below the 200-Weekly MA indicates a bearish trend for BNB. This configuration suggests that the price could continue downward in the coming days unless significant positive developments or market catalysts emerge.</p>
<h2><strong>What’s Next For BNB?</strong></h2>
<p>Market participants will closely monitor the price action around the critical resistance level of $308. A successful breach above this level could ignite renewed bullish momentum, potentially leading to a recovery in BNB&#8217;s price. Traders and investors will also pay attention to any regulatory developments and market trends that could influence BNB&#8217;s performance.</p>
<p>Despite the current challenges, Binance Coin holds promise as a key player in the cryptocurrency ecosystem. As Binance continues to expand its services and offerings, including its decentralized exchange (DEX) and various partnerships, there is potential for increased adoption of BNB, which could positively impact its price in the long run.</p>
<p><strong>Related Reading: </strong><a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/ethereum/percentage-of-eth-addresses-in-profit-reaches-5-month-low/">Percentage Of ETH Addresses In Profit Reaches 5-Month Low</a></p>
<p>It is important to note that the cryptocurrency market is highly volatile, and prices can change rapidly. Investors are advised to conduct thorough research, stay informed about market developments, and exercise caution when making investment decisions. At press time, Binance Coin (BNB) was trading at $246.2 with a daily price increase of 2.93%.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium wp-image-538335" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image2-2-460x253.png" alt="Binance coin still trading below the $250 resistance mark" width="460" height="253" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image2-2-460x253.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image2-2-860x474.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image2-2-768x423.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image2-2-750x413.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image2-2.png 1080w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px"/>
<p><em>Featured image from iStock.com, charts from TradingView</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/iStock-1385861326-1-460x248.jpg" width="460" height="248" />	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
