<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	 xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" >

<channel>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://newsbtc.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://newsbtc.com</link>
	<description>Bitcoin &#38; cryptocurrency news today, price &#38; technical analysis</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 20:55:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<link>https://newsbtc.com</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Investor Sentiment Remains Steady As BTC Stalls At $16,000</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-investor-sentiment/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Best Owie]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 23:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin performance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=514270</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin investor sentiment has reached a standstill amid struggling prices in the market. While the digital asset continues to hold the $16,000 level, investors have backed off from the market, ensuring no significant movements either up or down, and as a result, investor sentiment hasn’t moved. Bitcoin Investors Still In Fear The crypto Fear &#38; Greed Index shows that bitcoin investor sentiment hasn’t really moved much in the last month. It closed out the month of November at a score of 29 which put it right in the fear territory but since then has been unable to break out of this trend.  Related Reading: Solana Suffers Double-Digit Losses, Is There An End In Sight? The score on this index over the month of December has staggered between 26-30 for the most part, maintaining a nearly straight-line trend during this period. Even now, the Fear &#38; Greed Index sits at a score of 28 and is up one point from last week’s close of 27. Fear &#38; Greed Index trends in an almost straight line &#124; Source: alternative.me What this trend in the Fear &#38; Greed Index shows is that bitcoin investors are not willing to take any risk. This is why the index has been unable to move into the greed territory. On the flip side, sell sentiment has not been as strong as expected during a time like this. If investors were selling more of their bitcoin, then it would have been obvious given that the index would slide further down. Instead, it continues to maintain a near-consistent score level, meaning hold sentiment now dominates the market. Will BTC See A Recovery Soon? Bitcoin is still finding a hard time regaining the momentum it has lost over the past month. This hesitancy from investors to do anything with their tokens has seen the price of the digital asset follow the same path as sentiment. BTC has now refused to move out of the $16,000 price level. BTC price maintains $16,000 level &#124; Source: BTCUSD on TradingView.com As a result of this, bitcoin volatility has fallen to historical lows. So it is likely that the last two days of the year 2022 will follow this same trend. Recovery should not be expected in any way because momentum will continue to decline as people take a break from the markets to celebrate with family. Related Reading: Dogecoin Beats Bitcoin, Ethereum For Best Performance In Crypto Top 10 Rather, it is important that BTC holds above $16,000 to close out the year. Anything below this level would be very bearish and could trigger more declines in the market as bears take control. But a finish above $16,000 strengthens investors’ resolve to hold their coins. BTC is changing hands at a price of $16,519 at the time of this writing. Its price is down 0.43% in the last 24 hours and 2.01% in the last 7 days. Featured image from Finbold, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="p2">Bitcoin investor sentiment has reached a standstill amid struggling prices in the market. While the digital asset continues to hold the $16,000 level, investors have backed off from the market, ensuring no significant movements either up or down, and as a result, investor sentiment hasn’t moved.</p>
<h2 class="p2">Bitcoin Investors Still In Fear</h2>
<p class="p2">The <a href="https://alternative.me/crypto/fear-and-greed-index/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">crypto Fear &amp; Greed Index</a> shows that bitcoin investor sentiment hasn’t really moved much in the last month. It closed out the month of November at a score of 29 which put it right in the fear territory but since then has been unable to break out of this trend. </p>

<p class="p2">The score on this index over the month of December has staggered between 26-30 for the most part, maintaining a nearly straight-line trend during this period. Even now, the Fear &amp; Greed Index sits at a score of 28 and is up one point from last week’s close of 27.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-514272 aligncenter" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Fear-Greed-index-460x279.png" alt="Bitcoin Fear &amp; Greed index" width="460" height="279" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Fear-Greed-index-460x279.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Fear-Greed-index-860x522.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Fear-Greed-index-768x466.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Fear-Greed-index-1536x933.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Fear-Greed-index-2048x1243.png 2048w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Fear-Greed-index-750x455.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Fear-Greed-index-1140x692.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px" /></p>

<p class="p2">What this trend in the Fear &amp; Greed Index shows is that bitcoin investors are not willing to take any risk. This is why the index has been unable to move into the greed territory. On the flip side, sell sentiment has not been as strong as expected during a time like this. If investors were selling more of their bitcoin, then it would have been obvious given that the index would slide further down. Instead, it continues to maintain a near-consistent score level, meaning hold sentiment now dominates the market.</p>
<h2 class="p2">Will BTC See A Recovery Soon?</h2>
<p class="p2">Bitcoin is still finding a hard time regaining the momentum it has lost over the past month. This hesitancy from investors to do anything with their tokens has seen the price of the digital asset follow the same path as sentiment. BTC has now refused to move out of the $16,000 price level.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/Zwz3MvAI/" alt="Bitcoin price chart from TradingView.com" width="3284" height="1760" /></p>

<p class="p2">As a result of this, bitcoin volatility has fallen to historical lows. So it is likely that the last two days of the year 2022 will follow this same trend. Recovery should not be expected in any way because momentum will continue to decline as people take a break from the markets to celebrate with family.</p>

<p class="p2">Rather, it is important that BTC holds above $16,000 to close out the year. Anything below this level would be very bearish and could trigger more declines in the market as bears take control. But a finish above $16,000 strengthens investors’ resolve to hold their coins.</p>
<p class="p2">BTC is changing hands at a price of $16,519 at the time of this writing. Its price is down 0.43% in the last 24 hours and 2.01% in the last 7 days.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/bitcoin-3-460x307.jpeg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Price Remains Stagnated, How Soon Can You Expect A Rebound?</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-stagnated-soon-can-you-expect-a-rebound/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[anushsamal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 23:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=514315</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[It has been a rough year for Bitcoin and most major altcoins. Over the last 24 hours, Bitcoin lost 1% of its value, which points towards consolidated price action. BTC has not made much progress over the past week either, as the coin only lost 1.6% of its market value. For multiple weeks, the coin has been oscillating between $16,400 and $18,000. The closest support line for the coin stood at $16,000. The technical outlook for Bitcoin depicted mundane price action due to a decline in the buying strength on the one-day chart. Since the price of Bitcoin has remained undecided for quite some time now, sellers have flooded the market, indicating that the coin is headed toward another round of depreciation. The trading volume of Bitcoin has declined considerably, reinforcing that bears were in charge of the asset&#8217;s price. If the selling pressure keeps mounting, BTC will soon lose its crucial price level of $16,000. Currently, BTC is down 76% from its all-time high, secured in 2021. Related Reading: Ethereum Finishes 2022 With ATH Correlation To Bitcoin, Despite The Merge Bitcoin Price Analysis: One-Day Chart BTC was trading at $16,550 at the time of writing. Bitcoin was trading close to its immediate support level of $16,000. Going by the technical outlook, the coin might undergo further depreciation before it starts to reverse its price action. Overhead resistance for Bitcoin was $16,900; clearing this could help the crypto reach $17,400 and eventually attempt to breach $18,000. On the flip side, if Bitcoin moves below the current price mark, it will fall through $16,000 and exceed $15,800. The amount of Bitcoin traded in the last session declined, indicating a fall in buying strength for the asset. Technical Analysis BTC traders might again witness a fall in asset prices over the upcoming trading sessions. The Relative Strength Index (RSI) was below the half-line, near the 40-mark, which indicates that sellers outnumbered buyers heavily. RSI had also noted a downtick, signifying further loss of value. Similarly, the BTC price was below the 20-Simple Moving Average (SMA) line, which signals that sellers were driving the price momentum in the market. The SMA also formed a death cross; it is formed when a longer moving average line crosses over a shorter moving average line; in this case, the 50-SMA line was above the 20-SMA line. This sign on the chart is accompanied by the bears strengthening in the market. Other technical indicators have also pointed out that sellers are here to stay a little longer. The Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD) indicates price momentum and reversals. MACD depicted a sell signal as the indicator noted red signal bars after undergoing a bearish crossover. The sell signal could mean that the price would depreciate further. The Directional Movement Index, which portrays the price direction, was negative. The -DI (orange) line was above the +DI (blue) line. The Average Directional Index (red) was near the 20-mark with an uptick, emphasizing that bearish action could gain momentum over the immediate trading sessions. Related Reading: A Crypto Holiday Special: Past, Present, And Future With Ex-Binance CFO Wei Zhou Featured Image From Unsplash, Charts From TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>It has been a rough year for Bitcoin and most major altcoins. Over the last 24 hours, Bitcoin lost 1% of its value, which points towards consolidated price action. BTC has not made much progress over the past week either, as the coin only lost 1.6% of its market value.</p>
<p>For multiple weeks, the coin has been oscillating between $16,400 and $18,000. The closest support line for the coin stood at $16,000. The technical outlook for Bitcoin depicted mundane price action due to a decline in the buying strength on the one-day chart.</p>
<p>Since the price of Bitcoin has remained undecided for quite some time now, sellers have flooded the market, indicating that the coin is headed toward another round of depreciation. The trading volume of Bitcoin has declined considerably, reinforcing that bears were in charge of the asset&#8217;s price.</p>
<p>If the selling pressure keeps mounting, BTC will soon lose its crucial price level of $16,000. Currently, BTC is down 76% from its all-time high, secured in 2021.</p>

<h2>Bitcoin Price Analysis: One-Day Chart</h2>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-514318 size-full" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-31_01-08-09.png" alt="Bitcoin" width="1817" height="830" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-31_01-08-09.png 1817w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-31_01-08-09-460x210.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-31_01-08-09-860x393.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-31_01-08-09-768x351.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-31_01-08-09-1536x702.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-31_01-08-09-750x343.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-31_01-08-09-1140x521.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1817px) 100vw, 1817px" />
<p>BTC was trading at $16,550 at the time of writing. Bitcoin was trading close to its immediate support level of $16,000. Going by the technical outlook, the coin might undergo further depreciation before it starts to reverse its price action.</p>
<p>Overhead resistance for Bitcoin was $16,900; clearing this could help the crypto reach $17,400 and eventually attempt to breach $18,000.</p>
<p>On the flip side, if Bitcoin moves below the current price mark, it will fall through $16,000 and exceed $15,800. The amount of Bitcoin traded in the last session declined, indicating a fall in buying strength for the asset.</p>
<h2>Technical Analysis</h2>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-514319 size-full" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-31_01-09-39.png" alt="Bitcoin" width="1877" height="743" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-31_01-09-39.png 1877w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-31_01-09-39-460x182.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-31_01-09-39-860x340.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-31_01-09-39-768x304.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-31_01-09-39-1536x608.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-31_01-09-39-750x297.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-31_01-09-39-1140x451.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1877px) 100vw, 1877px" />
<p>BTC traders might again witness a fall in asset prices over the upcoming trading sessions. The Relative Strength Index (RSI) was below the half-line, near the 40-mark, which indicates that sellers outnumbered buyers heavily. RSI had also noted a downtick, signifying further loss of value.</p>
<p>Similarly, the BTC price was below the 20-Simple Moving Average (SMA) line, which signals that sellers were driving the price momentum in the market.</p>
<p>The SMA also formed a death cross; it is formed when a longer moving average line crosses over a shorter moving average line; in this case, the 50-SMA line was above the 20-SMA line. This sign on the chart is accompanied by the bears strengthening in the market.</p>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-514321 size-full" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-31_01-10-14.png" alt="Bitcoin" width="1877" height="743" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-31_01-10-14.png 1877w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-31_01-10-14-460x182.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-31_01-10-14-860x340.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-31_01-10-14-768x304.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-31_01-10-14-1536x608.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-31_01-10-14-750x297.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-31_01-10-14-1140x451.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1877px) 100vw, 1877px" />
<p>Other technical indicators have also pointed out that sellers are here to stay a little longer. The Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD) indicates price momentum and reversals. MACD depicted a sell signal as the indicator noted red signal bars after undergoing a bearish crossover.</p>
<p>The sell signal could mean that the price would depreciate further. The Directional Movement Index, which portrays the price direction, was negative.</p>
<p>The -DI (orange) line was above the +DI (blue) line. The Average Directional Index (red) was near the 20-mark with an uptick, emphasizing that bearish action could gain momentum over the immediate trading sessions.</p>





]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/woliul-hasan-aAvzCO-B5aA-unsplash-460x460.jpg" width="460" height="460" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Polygon (MATIC) Depicts Further Downtrend, This Could Be The Next Support Level</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/matic/polygon-depicts-downtrend-next-support-level/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[anushsamal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 21:00:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[MATIC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[maticusdt]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Polygon]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=514283</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Polygon (MATIC) price has been on a downward spiral for the last couple of weeks. Over the last 24 hours, MATIC lost 4% of its value. The altcoin has also lost about 6% in the last week. Earlier in November, MATIC touched the $1.20 price mark and plunged significantly. Since the coin plummeted in November, the Polygon price has noted a freefall in its value. Going by the technical outlook on the daily chart, buyers are nowhere to be found. It will be difficult for MATIC to sustain itself above its immediate support level. The buying strength of Polygon has to increase considerably for it to remain above the local support line. Over the past month, the coin has breached several important price floors. After trading sideways for a while, MATIC lost buyers further, which made the coin fall on its chart again. For Polygon, the most important price floor currently stands at $0.74. If MATIC loses that support line, the coin can register a significant decline of 14%. The market capitalization of MATIC also declined over the past few weeks, which depicts bearishness for the coin. Currently, the coin is trading 74% below its all-time high secured one year ago. Related Reading: Most Public Crypto Firms Underperformed Bitcoin In 2022, Miners Hit Worst MATIC Price Analysis: One-Day Chart Polygon was trading at $0.76 at the time of writing. The coin was trading extremely close to the immediate support line of $0.74; one push from the sellers and the price could take another significant bearish turn. Overhead resistance for MATIC was $0.81; crossing this price level will help the altcoin reach $0.84. The $0.84 level has previously acted as a propelling point for the asset&#8217;s price, so this could mean that moving above the $0.84 level would help the coin reverse its price action. On the other hand, a fall from the present price mark will bring the altcoin to $0.67 and then to $0.63. The amount of Polygon traded in the last session was red, indicating selling dominance. Technical Analysis The coin was in the seller&#8217;s dominant zone for most of this month. The coin barely recovered after it lost the $0.84 support line. The Relative Strength Index was below the 40-mark, which depicted that the coin received more sellers than buyers. In correspondence with the same, the coin moved below the 20-Simple Moving Average (SMA) line. This meant that the sellers were driving the price momentum in the market. Usually, when the coin hovers too close to the oversold zone, the price reverses. If demand returns, the coin will move above the 200-SMA line (green), which points towards a potential rally. Regarding selling strength, the indicators pointed out that the selling spree is not over yet. The Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD) indicator depicts price momentum and reversals. MACD showed red signal bars, which are tied to a sell signal. This was an indication that the coin could dip further on the chart. The Chaikin Money Flow reads capital inflows and outflows; the indicator was below the half-line, signifying lower capital inflows than outflows. Related Reading: Santiment: Bitcoin Will Trend Lower Because Whales Are Still Selling Featured Image From Unsplash, Charts From TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Polygon (MATIC) price has been on a downward spiral for the last couple of weeks. Over the last 24 hours, MATIC lost 4% of its value. The altcoin has also lost about 6% in the last week. Earlier in November, MATIC touched the $1.20 price mark and plunged significantly.</p>
<p>Since the coin plummeted in November, the Polygon price has noted a freefall in its value. Going by the technical outlook on the daily chart, buyers are nowhere to be found. It will be difficult for MATIC to sustain itself above its immediate support level.</p>
<p>The buying strength of Polygon has to increase considerably for it to remain above the local support line. Over the past month, the coin has breached several important price floors. After trading sideways for a while, MATIC lost buyers further, which made the coin fall on its chart again.</p>
<p>For Polygon, the most important price floor currently stands at $0.74. If MATIC loses that support line, the coin can register a significant decline of 14%. The market capitalization of MATIC also declined over the past few weeks, which depicts bearishness for the coin. Currently, the coin is trading 74% below its all-time high secured one year ago.</p>

<h2>MATIC Price Analysis: One-Day Chart</h2>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-514296 size-full" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MATICUSD_2022-12-30_22-49-40.png" alt="Polygon" width="1816" height="830" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MATICUSD_2022-12-30_22-49-40.png 1816w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MATICUSD_2022-12-30_22-49-40-460x210.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MATICUSD_2022-12-30_22-49-40-860x393.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MATICUSD_2022-12-30_22-49-40-768x351.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MATICUSD_2022-12-30_22-49-40-1536x702.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MATICUSD_2022-12-30_22-49-40-750x343.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MATICUSD_2022-12-30_22-49-40-1140x521.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1816px) 100vw, 1816px" />
<p>Polygon was trading at $0.76 at the time of writing. The coin was trading extremely close to the immediate support line of $0.74; one push from the sellers and the price could take another significant bearish turn.</p>
<p>Overhead resistance for MATIC was $0.81; crossing this price level will help the altcoin reach $0.84. The $0.84 level has previously acted as a propelling point for the asset&#8217;s price, so this could mean that moving above the $0.84 level would help the coin reverse its price action.</p>
<p>On the other hand, a fall from the present price mark will bring the altcoin to $0.67 and then to $0.63. The amount of Polygon traded in the last session was red, indicating selling dominance.</p>
<h2>Technical Analysis</h2>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-514299 size-full" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MATICUSD_2022-12-30_23-01-09.png" alt="Polygon" width="1816" height="743" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MATICUSD_2022-12-30_23-01-09.png 1816w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MATICUSD_2022-12-30_23-01-09-460x188.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MATICUSD_2022-12-30_23-01-09-860x352.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MATICUSD_2022-12-30_23-01-09-768x314.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MATICUSD_2022-12-30_23-01-09-1536x628.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MATICUSD_2022-12-30_23-01-09-750x307.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MATICUSD_2022-12-30_23-01-09-1140x466.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1816px) 100vw, 1816px" />
<p>The coin was in the seller&#8217;s dominant zone for most of this month. The coin barely recovered after it lost the $0.84 support line. The Relative Strength Index was below the 40-mark, which depicted that the coin received more sellers than buyers.</p>
<p>In correspondence with the same, the coin moved below the 20-Simple Moving Average (SMA) line. This meant that the sellers were driving the price momentum in the market.</p>
<p>Usually, when the coin hovers too close to the oversold zone, the price reverses. If demand returns, the coin will move above the 200-SMA line (green), which points towards a potential rally.</p>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-514303 size-full" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MATICUSD_2022-12-30_23-01-31.png" alt="Polygon" width="1816" height="743" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MATICUSD_2022-12-30_23-01-31.png 1816w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MATICUSD_2022-12-30_23-01-31-460x188.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MATICUSD_2022-12-30_23-01-31-860x352.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MATICUSD_2022-12-30_23-01-31-768x314.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MATICUSD_2022-12-30_23-01-31-1536x628.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MATICUSD_2022-12-30_23-01-31-750x307.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MATICUSD_2022-12-30_23-01-31-1140x466.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1816px) 100vw, 1816px" />
<p>Regarding selling strength, the indicators pointed out that the selling spree is not over yet. The Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD) indicator depicts price momentum and reversals. MACD showed red signal bars, which are tied to a sell signal.</p>
<p>This was an indication that the coin could dip further on the chart. The Chaikin Money Flow reads capital inflows and outflows; the indicator was below the half-line, signifying lower capital inflows than outflows.</p>





]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/barefoot-communications-z2M7JefmTEw-unsplash-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum Finishes 2022 With ATH Correlation To Bitcoin, Despite The Merge</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/ethereum/ethereum-ath-correlation-bitcoin-merge/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hououin Kyouma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 19:00:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Stock market correlation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum Bitcoin Correlation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum Merge]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Merge]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=514285</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Data shows Ethereum&#8217;s year of high correlation with Bitcoin is coming to an end with the metric hitting ATH values. Ethereum Ends 2022 With All-Time High Correlation To Bitcoin According to the year-end report from Arcane Research, the global markets have all fallen strongly correlated this year. The &#8220;30-day correlations&#8221; is an indicator that measures how in-tune Bitcoin has been with another asset in terms of price movement over a 30-day period. When the value of this metric is greater than zero, it means there has been a positive correlation between BTC and the other asset in the past month. On the other hand, negative values imply that the price of the crypto has been reacting to changes in the value of the other asset by moving in the opposite direction. Also, the higher the metric value (in either direction), the more the degree of the correlation. Naturally, the metric has a value equal to zero suggesting the two prices aren&#8217;t tied to each other at the moment. Related Reading: Analyst Explains Why Ethereum Is Bullish Against Bitcoin Now, here is a chart that shows the trend in Bitcoin&#8217;s 30-day correlations with Ethereum, S&#38;P 500, and Nasdaq over the past year: Looks like the metric's value corresponding to ETH has been very high in recent weeks &#124; Source: Arcane Research's 2022 - Year in Review As the above graph displays, Bitcoin positively correlated with these three assets during 2022. BTC&#8217;s correlation has been around or above 0.5 for most of the year for the US equities, suggesting it has been decently tied with them. The correlation with Ethereum, however, has been at values of around 0.9 or more, implying Bitcoin has been extremely correlated with it. Even now, as the year&#8217;s end, the correlation between these cryptos stands at 0.97, around ATH levels. Back in September of this year, ETH successfully finished its much-anticipated transition to a Proof-of-Stake consensus system, an event known as the Merge. Since the Merge brought some developments unique to Ethereum, the correlation with BTC dropped, as is apparent in the chart. However, it wasn&#8217;t long before the two started moving on the same wavelength again, so even the Merge wasn&#8217;t enough to cause sufficient impact to separate the coins. Related Reading: Most Public Crypto Firms Underperformed Bitcoin In 2022, Miners Hit Worst Also, since Bitcoin is highly correlated with stocks, so is Ethereum. Though, Arcane Research expects that this correlation between the cryptos and the US equities will soften in the next year due to trading volumes in the crypto market declining substantially. ETH Price At the time of writing, Ethereum&#8217;s price floats around $1,200, down 2% in the last week. ETH seems to have gone down recently &#124; Source: ETHUSD on TradingView Featured image from Pierre Borthiry &#8211; Peiobty on Unsplash.com, charts from TradingView.com, Arcane Research]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Data shows Ethereum&#8217;s year of high correlation with Bitcoin is coming to an end with the metric hitting ATH values.</p>
<h2>Ethereum Ends 2022 With All-Time High Correlation To Bitcoin</h2>
<p>According to the year-end report from <a href="https://arcane.no/research/2022-year-in-review" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Arcane Research</a>, the global markets have all fallen strongly correlated this year. The &#8220;<a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-moves-us-stock-market-correlation-weakening/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">30-day correlations</a>&#8221; is an indicator that measures how in-tune Bitcoin has been with another asset in terms of price movement over a 30-day period.</p>
<p>When the value of this metric is greater than zero, it means there has been a positive correlation between BTC and the other asset in the past month. On the other hand, negative values imply that the price of the crypto has been reacting to changes in the value of the other asset by moving in the opposite direction.</p>
<p>Also, the higher the metric value (in either direction), the more the degree of the correlation. Naturally, the metric has a value equal to zero suggesting the two prices aren&#8217;t tied to each other at the moment.</p>

<p>Now, here is a chart that shows the trend in Bitcoin&#8217;s 30-day correlations with Ethereum, S&amp;P 500, and Nasdaq over the past year:</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone wp-image-514298 size-full aligncenter" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/chart-41.png" alt="Bitcoin And Ethereum Correlation" width="771" height="518" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/chart-41.png 771w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/chart-41-460x309.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/chart-41-768x516.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/chart-41-750x504.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 771px) 100vw, 771px" /></p>

<p>As the above graph displays, Bitcoin positively correlated with these three assets during 2022. BTC&#8217;s correlation has been around or above 0.5 for most of the year for the US equities, suggesting it has been decently tied with them.</p>
<p>The correlation with Ethereum, however, has been at values of around 0.9 or more, implying Bitcoin has been extremely correlated with it. Even now, as the year&#8217;s end, the correlation between these cryptos stands at 0.97, around ATH levels.</p>
<p>Back in September of this year, ETH successfully finished its much-anticipated transition to a Proof-of-Stake consensus system, an event known as the <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/company/the-ethereum-merge-what-is-trading-headed-towards/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Merge</a>. Since the Merge brought some developments unique to Ethereum, the correlation with BTC dropped, as is apparent in the chart.</p>
<p>However, it wasn&#8217;t long before the two started moving on the same wavelength again, so even the Merge wasn&#8217;t enough to cause sufficient impact to separate the coins.</p>

<p>Also, since Bitcoin is highly correlated with stocks, so is Ethereum. Though, Arcane Research expects that this correlation between the cryptos and the US equities will soften in the next year due to trading volumes in the crypto market declining substantially.</p>
<h2>ETH Price</h2>
<p>At the time of writing, <a href="https://newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-signals-bearish-1100/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ethereum&#8217;s price</a> floats around $1,200, down 2% in the last week.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone wp-image-514304 size-large aligncenter" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/chart-42-860x482.png" alt="Ethereum Price Chart" width="860" height="482" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/chart-42-860x482.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/chart-42-460x258.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/chart-42-768x430.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/chart-42-750x420.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/chart-42.png 973w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" /></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/pierre-borthiry-peiobty-vBCVcWUyvyM-unsplash-1-460x333.jpg" width="460" height="333" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Crypto Holiday Special: Past, Present, And Future With Ex-Binance CFO Wei Zhou</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/interview/crypto-holiday-past-future-binance-cfo-zhou/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reynaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 18:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Interview]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=514186</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[2022 is coming to an end, and our staff at NewsBTC decided to launch this Crypto Holiday Special to provide some perspective on the crypto industry. We will talk with multiple guests to understand this year’s highs and lows for crypto. Related Reading: A Crypto Holiday Special: Past, Present, And Future With Ex BNY Mellon David Schwed In the spirit of Charles Dicken’s classic, “A Christmas Carol,” we’ll look into crypto from different angles, look at its possible trajectory for 2023 and find common ground amongst these different views of an industry that might support the future of finances. Zhou: “It won’t be business as usual for centralized exchanges. For one, the days of commingling users and the exchanges’ assets are long gone.” We are ending our institutional round with Wei Zhou; he worked as Chief Financial Officer for three years at the largest crypto exchange worldwide, Binance. Above the rest, this company and its current CEO, Changpeng “CZ” Zhao, heavily impacted the nascent industry and will continue to exercise influence in the coming years. Zhou: “Bitcoin, just like the Internet, will survive any storm that comes its way; this I have no inkling of doubt about.” Zhou reviews the biggest moment in 2022 from his unique perspective. In addition, he talks about the fundamentals that will keep crypto alive and on track to fulfill its destiny. This is what he told us: Q: What’s the most significant difference for the crypto market today compared to Christmas 2021? Beyond the price of Bitcoin, Ethereum, and others, what changed from that moment of euphoria to today’s perpetual fear? Has there been a decline in adoption and liquidity? Are fundamentals still valid? A: The crypto market has certainly changed a lot in the past year. Collapse of key industry players I think the biggest change this year has been due to the collapse of some key industry players, from Celsius, 3AC to BlockFi and most recently FTX. With billions of dollars affected, investors have become cautious. The collapse of these giants has served to remind us to be prudent and diligent with our crypto investment decisions. Users should conduct thorough research and abstain from entities whose licensing and regulatory status is unclear. I believe that the situation will change in 2023 and that investor confidence will resume, but we can’t afford to forget the lessons learned this year. Liquidity affected but adoption will continue to grow With the collapse of a big market maker like FTX, liquidity in the market was affected as several exchanges relied on it. Investors have also pulled quite a bit of their money from exchanges which further escalated the liquidity crunch.  Speculative trading may have pulled back, but for those to whom crypto was more focused on use cases like value transfer, web3 gaming and financial inclusion, crypto adoption will continue to surge especially in the Philippines. Q: What are the dominant narratives driving this change in market conditions? And what should be the narrative today? What are most people overlooking? We saw a major crypto exchange blowing up, a hedge fund thought to be untouchable, and an ecosystem that promised a financial utopia. Is Crypto still the future of finance, or should the community pursue a new vision? A: This year’s market downturn has fueled crypto skeptics and several mainstream media houses who have become re-energized in their fight against crypto. This narrative has put doubts in the minds of investors. However, most people are overlooking that Bitcoin is designed to be a decentralized electronic currency. Crypto is still the future of finance. If you recall, when the dot-com bubble burst, there were all manner of questions about the viability of the Internet as a technology and the companies building on it. But look at Amazon, Facebook, Google and others today &#8211; they are defining the world we live in. This is because, despite the shake-ups with the market players, the underlying technology was fundamentally transformative. Bitcoin, just like the Internet, will survive this winter. Q: If you must choose one, what do you think was a significant moment for crypto in 2022? And will the industry feel its consequences across 2023? Where do you see the industry next Christmas? Will it survive this winter? Mainstream is once again declaring the death of the industry. Will they finally get it right? A: I would point to the FTX collapse as a landmark moment. Its impact has been and will continue to be felt in the industry. Investors are keener about who they trust with their assets and how custodians and exchanges store the assets. Investors are now exploring self-custody solutions, which contrary to opinion I think is a great direction to take. When they require to trade their assets, they are now keen to work with exchanges that are fully regulated like Coins.ph which is licensed by the Philippines central bank and is regularly audited. Regulators are more concerned about the industry. We will also see a trend where regulators around the world will begin to create a more comprehensive regulatory framework around cryptocurrency. The crypto industry has gone through worse. In 2017, the crypto markets peaked and crashed to $3,000, and the industry endured a three-year-long crypto winter. In 2022, we now have institutional investors who are advancing the sector, unlike during prior winters. I believe the industry will survive because there are now much more use cases than there were in the past. Q: What&#8217;s next for exchanges such as Binance in 2023 and beyond? Do you think the recent events with FTX will jeopardize the future of these platforms? Many are already speculating about the shift in liquidity from Centralize to Decentralize Exchanges (DEX) due to the users&#8217; lack of confidence in the former A: The days of commingling users and the exchanges’ assets are long gone. FTX has woken up the entire industry to the dangers this practice can have. Proof of reserves is already becoming a big trend as more investors ask questions about how and where their assets are stored. Related Reading: A Crypto Holiday Special: Past, Present, And Future With Blofin Regulators are also cracking down much harder on exchanges. In the Philippines, for instance, the BSP was quick to audit exchanges in order to probe if they had been exposed to the FTX contagion. Thankfully, neither Coins.ph nor our peers were exposed to FTX. The crypto industry will be shifting to focus on Web3, decentralized exchanges and self-custody. More users are now exploring wallets that give them full ownership of their crypto. I am a big supporter of self-custody for those with the technical ability to do it successfully. When they require trade, I would advise them to always use an exchange that’s licensed and supervised by a recognized national or regional watchdog.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>2022 is coming to an end, and our staff at NewsBTC decided to launch this Crypto Holiday Special to provide some perspective on the crypto industry. We will talk with multiple guests to understand this year’s highs and lows for crypto.</strong></p>

<p><strong>In the spirit of Charles Dicken’s classic, “A Christmas Carol,” we’ll look into crypto from different angles, look at its possible trajectory for 2023 and find common ground amongst these different views of an industry that might support the future of finances. </strong></p>
<p style="text-align: center"><strong>Zhou: “It won’t be business as usual for centralized exchanges. For one, the days of commingling users and the exchanges’ assets are long gone.”</strong></p>
<p>We are ending our institutional round with Wei Zhou; he worked as Chief Financial Officer for three years at the largest crypto exchange worldwide, Binance. Above the rest, this company and its current CEO, Changpeng “CZ” Zhao, heavily impacted the nascent industry and will continue to exercise influence in the coming years.</p>
<p style="text-align: center"><strong>Zhou: “Bitcoin, just like the Internet, will survive any storm that comes its way; this I have no inkling of doubt about.”</strong></p>
<p>Zhou reviews the biggest moment in 2022 from his unique perspective. In addition, he talks about the fundamentals that will keep crypto alive and on track to fulfill its destiny. This is what he told us:</p>
<p><strong>Q: What’s the most significant difference for the crypto market today compared to Christmas 2021? Beyond the price of Bitcoin, Ethereum, and others, what changed from that moment of euphoria to today’s perpetual fear? Has there been a decline in adoption and liquidity? Are fundamentals still valid?</strong></p>
<p>A: The crypto market has certainly changed a lot in the past year.</p>
<p><strong>Collapse of key industry players </strong></p>
<p>I think the biggest change this year has been due to the collapse of some key industry players, from Celsius, 3AC to BlockFi and most recently FTX. With billions of dollars affected, investors have become cautious. The collapse of these giants has served to remind us to be prudent and diligent with our crypto investment decisions. Users should conduct thorough research and abstain from entities whose licensing and regulatory status is unclear. I believe that the situation will change in 2023 and that investor confidence will resume, but we can’t afford to forget the lessons learned this year.</p>
<p><strong>Liquidity affected but adoption will continue to grow</strong></p>
<p>With the collapse of a big market maker like FTX, liquidity in the market was affected as several exchanges relied on it. Investors have also pulled quite a bit of their money from exchanges which further escalated the liquidity crunch.  Speculative trading may have pulled back, but for those to whom crypto was more focused on use cases like value transfer, web3 gaming and financial inclusion, crypto adoption will continue to surge especially in the Philippines.</p>
<p><strong>Q: What are the dominant narratives driving this change in market conditions? And what should be the narrative today? What are most people overlooking? We saw a major crypto exchange blowing up, a hedge fund thought to be untouchable, and an ecosystem that promised a financial utopia. Is Crypto still the future of finance, or should the community pursue a new vision?</strong></p>
<p>A: This year’s market downturn has fueled crypto skeptics and several mainstream media houses who have become re-energized in their fight against crypto. This narrative has put doubts in the minds of investors. However, most people are overlooking that Bitcoin is designed to be a decentralized electronic currency.</p>
<p>Crypto is still the future of finance. If you recall, when the dot-com bubble burst, there were all manner of questions about the viability of the Internet as a technology and the companies building on it. But look at Amazon, Facebook, Google and others today &#8211; they are defining the world we live in. This is because, despite the shake-ups with the market players, the underlying technology was fundamentally transformative. Bitcoin, just like the Internet, will survive this winter.</p>
<p><strong>Q: If you must choose one, what do you think was a significant moment for crypto in 2022? And will the industry feel its consequences across 2023? Where do you see the industry next Christmas? Will it survive this winter? Mainstream is once again declaring the death of the industry. Will they finally get it right?</strong></p>
<p>A: I would point to the FTX collapse as a landmark moment. Its impact has been and will continue to be felt in the industry.</p>
<ul>
<li>Investors are keener about who they trust with their assets and how custodians and exchanges store the assets. Investors are now exploring self-custody solutions, which contrary to opinion I think is a great direction to take. When they require to trade their assets, they are now keen to work with exchanges that are fully regulated like Coins.ph which is licensed by the Philippines central bank and is regularly audited.</li>
<li>Regulators are more concerned about the industry. We will also see a trend where regulators around the world will begin to create a more comprehensive regulatory framework around cryptocurrency.</li>
</ul>
<p>The crypto industry has gone through worse. In 2017, the crypto markets peaked and crashed to $3,000, and the industry endured a three-year-long crypto winter. In 2022, we now have institutional investors who are advancing the sector, unlike during prior winters.</p>
<p>I believe the industry will survive because there are now much more use cases than there were in the past.</p>
<p><strong>Q: What&#8217;s next for exchanges such as Binance in 2023 and beyond? Do you think the recent events with FTX will jeopardize the future of these platforms? Many are already speculating about the shift in liquidity from Centralize to Decentralize Exchanges (DEX) due to the users&#8217; lack of confidence in the former </strong></p>
<p>A: The days of commingling users and the exchanges’ assets are long gone. FTX has woken up the entire industry to the dangers this practice can have. Proof of reserves is already becoming a big trend as more investors ask questions about how and where their assets are stored.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://newsbtc.com/interview/crypto-holiday-past-present-future-blofin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">A Crypto Holiday Special: Past, Present, And Future With Blofin</a></p>
<p>Regulators are also cracking down much harder on exchanges. In the Philippines, for instance, the BSP was quick to audit exchanges in order to probe if they had been exposed to the FTX contagion. Thankfully, neither Coins.ph nor our peers were exposed to FTX.</p>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-514198 size-large" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Crypto-holiday-BTC-BTCUSDT-Binance-CFO-Wei-Zhou-860x376.png" alt="Crypto holiday BTC BTCUSDT Binance CFO Wei Zhou" width="860" height="376" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Crypto-holiday-BTC-BTCUSDT-Binance-CFO-Wei-Zhou-860x376.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Crypto-holiday-BTC-BTCUSDT-Binance-CFO-Wei-Zhou-460x201.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Crypto-holiday-BTC-BTCUSDT-Binance-CFO-Wei-Zhou-768x336.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Crypto-holiday-BTC-BTCUSDT-Binance-CFO-Wei-Zhou-1536x672.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Crypto-holiday-BTC-BTCUSDT-Binance-CFO-Wei-Zhou-750x328.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Crypto-holiday-BTC-BTCUSDT-Binance-CFO-Wei-Zhou-1140x499.png 1140w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Crypto-holiday-BTC-BTCUSDT-Binance-CFO-Wei-Zhou.png 1813w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" />
<p>The crypto industry will be shifting to focus on Web3, decentralized exchanges and self-custody. More users are now exploring wallets that give them full ownership of their crypto. I am a big supporter of self-custody for those with the technical ability to do it successfully. When they require trade, I would advise them to always use an exchange that’s licensed and supervised by a recognized national or regional watchdog.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Crypto-Holiday-Special-cover-image-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Santiment: Bitcoin Will Trend Lower Because Whales Are Still Selling</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/santiment-bitcoin-will-trend-lower/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Best Owie]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 17:00:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin performance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin whales]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=514269</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The impact of bitcoin whales and their activities has always been felt in the general market. This goes from buying to selling, and just the way they move their coins. Once again, these whales still hold sway in the market and their activity could spell a bottom signal. Santiment Says Bitcoin Whales Are Selling In a recent community post on the Santiment website, the activity of whales is analyzed in depth. This time around, a look at the balances of large holders shows that they are still selling. These whales who hold between 1,000 and 10,000 BTC have reduced their holdings from almost 8 million BTC back in December 2021 to less than 7 million BTC in December 2022. Related Reading: Dogecoin Beats Bitcoin, Ethereum For Best Performance In Crypto Top 10 Even in the last couple of months, they have reduced their balances by more than 200,000 BTC, showing that they are still selling. Given this sell trend among these large holders, the report predicts that the market will see “sideways or even lower prices for BTC in the next 6-12 months.” BTC whales are still selling &#124; Source: Santiment If this selling from large investors flows into 2023, then it is likely that the digital asset would start out the year seeing prices below $16,000. It is also important to note that the analysis in the report of whale addresses shows that the bottom of the market may not be reached yet. BTC Bottom Is Still Not In Now, the activity of whales is important to watch as accumulation by them could lead to a rally, and vice versa. One of the ways to try to pinpoint the bitcoin bottoms is with whale activity. At the very bottom of a bear market or at least close to it, whale address activities have historically declined. However, the Santiment report notes that the average 7-day transaction count was still hovering around 10,000 presently. Compared to the previous bear markets when the market had marked its bottom, whale transaction counts had declined to 1,200 and 2,500.  “This may mean that we need to wait for the average to drop further before we can conclude that even the big players are giving up,” the report reads. BTC price succumbs to selling pressure &#124; Source: BTCUSD on TradingView.com Another metric that the report points to is volume gaps. These usually show where the whales are accumulating and unfortunately, both volume gaps identified in the report lie well below the current trading price of bitcoin. The two key gaps identified were the $14,600 and $12,200 price levels, which could be a possible accumulation level for whales. Related Reading: Solana Suffers Double-Digit Losses, Is There An End In Sight? Essentially, the advice was to put off buying until whale transactions fall lower, as well as wait for the current selling pressure to subside. “To sum up, the activity of BTC whales and the presence of volume gaps at 14,600 USD and 12,200 USD may be worth watching,” Santiment said. Featured image from Crypto Insiders, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="p2">The impact of bitcoin whales and their activities has always been felt in the general market. This goes from buying to selling, and just the way they move their coins. Once again, these whales still hold sway in the market and their activity could spell a bottom signal.</p>
<h2 class="p2">Santiment Says Bitcoin Whales Are Selling</h2>
<p class="p2">In a <a href="https://insights.santiment.net/read/examining-the-impact-of-btc-whale-behavior-on-price-trends-7156?utm_source=twitter&amp;utm_medium=post&amp;utm_campaign=twitter_examining_btc_whale_behavior_impact_insight_sanrking_122922/&amp;fpr=twitter" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">recent community post on the Santiment website</a>, the activity of whales is analyzed in depth. This time around, a look at the balances of large holders shows that they are still selling. These whales who hold between 1,000 and 10,000 BTC have reduced their holdings from almost 8 million BTC back in December 2021 to less than 7 million BTC in December 2022.</p>

<p class="p2">Even in the last couple of months, they have reduced their balances by more than 200,000 BTC, showing that they are still selling. Given this sell trend among these large holders, the report predicts that the market will see “sideways or even lower prices for BTC in the next 6-12 months.”</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-514271 aligncenter" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Screen-Shot-2022-12-30-at-15.08.13-460x191.png" alt="Bitcoin whales " width="460" height="191" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Screen-Shot-2022-12-30-at-15.08.13-460x191.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Screen-Shot-2022-12-30-at-15.08.13-860x357.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Screen-Shot-2022-12-30-at-15.08.13-768x318.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Screen-Shot-2022-12-30-at-15.08.13-750x311.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Screen-Shot-2022-12-30-at-15.08.13-1140x473.png 1140w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Screen-Shot-2022-12-30-at-15.08.13.png 1442w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px" /></p>

<p class="p2">If this selling from large investors flows into 2023, then it is likely that the digital asset would start out the year seeing prices below $16,000. It is also important to note that the analysis in the report of whale addresses shows that the bottom of the market may not be reached yet.</p>
<h2 class="p2">BTC Bottom Is Still Not In</h2>
<p class="p2">Now, the activity of whales is important to watch as accumulation by them could lead to a rally, and vice versa. One of the ways to try to pinpoint the bitcoin bottoms is with whale activity. At the very bottom of a bear market or at least close to it, whale address activities have historically declined.</p>
<p class="p2">However, the Santiment report notes that the average 7-day transaction count was still hovering around 10,000 presently. Compared to the previous bear markets when the market had marked its bottom, whale transaction counts had declined to 1,200 and 2,500. </p>
<p class="p2">“This may mean that we need to wait for the average to drop further before we can conclude that even the big players are giving up,” the report reads.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/Zwz3MvAI/" alt="Bitcoin price chart from TradingView.com" width="3284" height="1760" /></p>

<p class="p2">Another metric that the report points to is volume gaps. These usually show where the whales are accumulating and unfortunately, both volume gaps identified in the report lie well below the current trading price of bitcoin. The two key gaps identified were the $14,600 and $12,200 price levels, which could be a possible accumulation level for whales.</p>

<p class="p2">Essentially, the advice was to put off buying until whale transactions fall lower, as well as wait for the current selling pressure to subside. “To sum up, the activity of BTC whales and the presence of volume gaps at 14,600 USD and 12,200 USD may be worth watching,” Santiment said.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-whales-460x263.png" width="460" height="263" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Most Public Crypto Firms Underperformed Bitcoin In 2022, Miners Hit Worst</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/crypto/crypto-firms-bitcoin-2022-miners-hit-worst/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hououin Kyouma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 16:00:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin miners]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Companies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Bitcoin Mining Companies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Crypto Companies]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=514237</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Data shows almost all the big public crypto companies have underperformed Bitcoin this year, with the mining firms taking an especially hard hit. Most Public Mining Companies Saw Drawdowns Of 90% Or More In 2022 As per the year-end report from Arcane Research, 2022 was a very challenging year for public firms in the crypto sector. The below chart displays the drawdowns in the valuations of some of the big players in the market, as well as that of Bitcoin, during the last twelve months: The deep red performance of the public companies in the digital asset sector &#124; Source: Arcane Research's 2022 - Year in Review As the graph shows, Bitcoin performed terribly this year, seeing negative returns of around 65%, but the large public crypto firms have done worse still. Even Microstrategy, the company whose stocks&#8217; main attraction is exposure to BTC through its large reserves, couldn&#8217;t perform comparably to the asset and observed a deeper year-to-date drawdown of about 74%. The market cap of the popular crypto exchange Coinbase has gone down by 87% this year, which has led to the firm being valued lower than meme coin Dogecoin. The worst performer in the list seems to have been Core Scientific, recording a drawdown of 99%. Core Scientific is one of the biggest Bitcoin mining companies, but due to these large losses, the firm had to file for Chapter 11 bankruptcy earlier in the month. Similarly to Core, other BTC miners have also sustained major drawdowns this year, with most of them being 90% or more underwater for the period. But why did the mining firms perform especially poorly? The explanation behind that is multifold. Related Reading: Bitcoin Now Under Realized Price For 163 Days, Here’s How This Compares Historically &#8220;Similar to how crypto lenders were incentivized to prioritize short-term growth over long-term sound business decisions to attract private capital, public miners were incentivized to take on debt and rapidly expand its hashrate share to attract more capital,&#8221; the report explains. But three factors meant that this bet from these companies couldn&#8217;t pan out. First, the interest rates kept rising this year. Second, the bear market meant that the price of Bitcoin kept plunging, leading to the value of miners&#8217; rewards also becoming lower. And finally, the third nail in the coffin was the rising energy prices, which resulted in very low or no profits for miners as they have to constantly pay electricity bills to keep their facilities running. All these factors lead to the public miners collapsing under the weight of their short-sighted decisions. Related Reading: Bitcoin Interexchange Flow Pulse About To Reverse, What Does It Mean? For 2023, Arcane Research&#8217;s prediction for these public crypto companies is that there will be new Chapter 11 bankruptcies filed in the year. BTC Price At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading around $16,500, down 2% in the last week. Looks like BTC has gone downhill in recent days &#124; Source: BTCUSD on TradingView Featured image from Becca on Unsplash.com, charts from TradingView.com, Arcane Research]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Data shows almost all the big public crypto companies have underperformed Bitcoin this year, with the mining firms taking an especially hard hit.</p>
<h2>Most Public Mining Companies Saw Drawdowns Of 90% Or More In 2022</h2>
<p>As per the year-end report from <a href="https://arcane.no/research" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Arcane Research</a>, 2022 was a very challenging year for public firms in the crypto sector. The below chart displays the drawdowns in the valuations of some of the big players in the market, as well as that of Bitcoin, during the last twelve months:</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone wp-image-514249 size-large aligncenter" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/chart-39-860x362.png" alt="Crypto Firms And Bitcoin Miners" width="860" height="362" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/chart-39-860x362.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/chart-39-460x194.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/chart-39-768x324.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/chart-39-750x316.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/chart-39.png 1106w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" /></p>

<p>As the graph shows, Bitcoin performed terribly this year, seeing negative returns of around 65%, but the large public crypto firms have done worse still. Even <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/microstrategy-bought-bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Microstrategy</a>, the company whose stocks&#8217; main attraction is exposure to BTC through its large reserves, couldn&#8217;t perform comparably to the asset and observed a deeper year-to-date drawdown of about 74%.</p>
<p>The market cap of the popular crypto exchange Coinbase has gone down by 87% this year, which has led to the firm being valued lower than <a href="https://newsbtc.com/analysis/dogecoin-price-tumbles-070/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">meme coin Dogecoin</a>. The worst performer in the list seems to have been Core Scientific, recording a drawdown of 99%. Core Scientific is one of the biggest <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/why-most-public-bitcoin-miners-have-performed-terribly-in-their-lifetimes/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin mining companies</a>, but due to these large losses, the firm had to file for Chapter 11 bankruptcy earlier in the month.</p>
<p>Similarly to Core, other BTC miners have also sustained major drawdowns this year, with most of them being 90% or more underwater for the period. But why did the mining firms perform especially poorly? The explanation behind that is multifold.</p>

<p>&#8220;Similar to how crypto lenders were incentivized to prioritize short-term growth over long-term sound business decisions to attract private capital, public miners were incentivized to take on debt and rapidly expand its hashrate share to attract more capital,&#8221; the report explains.</p>
<p>But three factors meant that this bet from these companies couldn&#8217;t pan out. First, the interest rates kept rising this year. Second, the bear market meant that the price of Bitcoin kept plunging, leading to the value of miners&#8217; rewards also becoming lower.</p>
<p>And finally, the third nail in the coffin was the rising energy prices, which resulted in very low or no profits for miners as they have to constantly pay electricity bills to keep their facilities running. All these factors lead to the public miners collapsing under the weight of their short-sighted decisions.</p>

<p>For 2023, Arcane Research&#8217;s prediction for these public crypto companies is that there will be new Chapter 11 bankruptcies filed in the year.</p>
<h2>BTC Price</h2>
<p>At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading around $16,500, down 2% in the last week.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone wp-image-514254 size-large aligncenter" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/chart-40-860x481.png" alt="Bitcoin Price Chart" width="860" height="481" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/chart-40-860x481.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/chart-40-460x257.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/chart-40-768x429.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/chart-40-750x419.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/chart-40.png 973w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" /></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/becca-_r6w0R6SueQ-unsplash-460x342.jpg" width="460" height="342" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hedera: Is 2023 The Comeback Year For HBAR NFTs?</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/hedera-2023-comeback-year-for-nfts/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 13:40:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[HBAR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hedera Ecosystem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NFT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tags: Hedera]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=514253</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The year 2022 has not been kind to the NFT market and the crypto industry as a whole. However, Hedera’s partnership with LG Art Lab might somehow bring a new wave of enthusiasm for digital art.  Related Reading: Dogecoin Breaking Past This Key Barrier Could Spell 10% Spike For DOGE NFT Interest On The Rise Again?  A recent interview done by Crypto Digest with The HBAR Foundation’s Chief Legal Officer Jorge Pesok sheds some insight into the current state of NFTs in the Hedera L1 ecosystem. According to the interview, more than 150 projects are granted support by the company.  Pesok also mentioned that LG is rolling out its new television technology that is integrated with its native NFT marketplace where new users can buy digital collectibles. The TVs would also allow users to display the NFTs that they own. Governing Council Member @LGElectronics has launched LG Art Lab &#8211; built on @Hedera &#8211; enabling LG TV owners to buy, sell and showcase #HederaNFTs from their screens. All LG TVs running webOS5.0 will be able to interact with the LG Art Lab app. #HelloFuturehttps://t.co/KQBUgaE2j5 — Hedera (@hedera) September 5, 2022 This can be huge for the NFT industry as LG has a large market share in the home appliance industry. However, recent events in crypto space might slow down the growth of interest in NFTs. Not to mention that the sector is not free from scams and frauds.  Just this month, Logan Paul, a major influencer on YouTube, was investigated by Coffeezilla for defrauding his fans on his abandoned crypto project CryptoZoo. Despite these very negative developments for crypto and NFTs as a whole, we can expect a healthy adoption of digital art as LG continues to leverage this new technology.  Chart: TradingView Dark Horizons? The crypto industry has taken a heavy beating courtesy of the collapse of FTX and the NFT space has been struggling ever since interest on digital items waned. But with LG’s partnership with Hedera, we might see a brighter tomorrow for NFTs and the crypto market as a whole.  However, this &#8220;bright future&#8221; doesn’t come without losses. According to CoinGecko, Hedera’s native token HBAR has seen better days with the token dropping 5.6% in the past 24 hours.  The charts are also very bearish for the token. HBAR is heavily correlated with Ethereum. This means that if ETH continues to buckle under the bearish pressure, HBAR will follow the decline in value.  Related Reading: Chainlink Nears Crucial $6 Level As LINK Ushers In The New Year Crypto total market cap at $963 million on the daily chart &#124; Chart: TradingView.com These short-term developments are in line with Jorge Pesok’s thoughts on crypto and NFTs in its entirety: “My prediction, at least in the short term, is that the industry will continue to face a bear market but will come out of it much more mature and garner more retail and institutional adoption” he said in the interview.  As Hedera partners with more institutional entities like LG, Boeing, and Deutsche Telekom, we will see the company playing a bigger role in the adoption of digital assets with real world utility.  &#8211; Featured image: Adobe/S_E]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The year 2022 has not been kind to the NFT market and the crypto industry as a whole. However, Hedera’s partnership with <a href="https://hedera.com/blog/lg-joins-hedera-governing-council-to-accelerate-innovation-and-adoption-of-public-dlt-globally" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">LG Art Lab</a> might somehow bring a new wave of enthusiasm for digital art. </p>

<h2><strong>NFT Interest On The Rise Again? </strong></h2>
<p>A recent <a href="https://www.crowellcryptodigest.com/2022/11/interview-with-jorge-pesok-of-the-hbar-foundation/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">interview</a> done by Crypto Digest with The HBAR Foundation’s Chief Legal Officer Jorge Pesok sheds some insight into the current state of NFTs in the Hedera L1 ecosystem. </p>
<p>According to the interview, more than 150 projects are granted support by the company. </p>
<p>Pesok also mentioned that LG is rolling out its new television technology that is integrated with its native NFT marketplace where new users can buy digital collectibles. The TVs would also allow users to display the NFTs that they own.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Governing Council Member <a href="https://twitter.com/LGElectronics?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">@LGElectronics</a> has launched LG Art Lab &#8211; built on <a href="https://twitter.com/hedera?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">@Hedera</a> &#8211; enabling LG TV owners to buy, sell and showcase <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/HederaNFTs?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">#HederaNFTs</a> from their screens. All LG TVs running webOS5.0 will be able to interact with the LG Art Lab app. <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/HelloFuture?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">#HelloFuture</a><a href="https://t.co/KQBUgaE2j5" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">https://t.co/KQBUgaE2j5</a></p>
<p>— Hedera (@hedera) <a href="https://twitter.com/hedera/status/1566602758358061058?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">September 5, 2022</a></p></blockquote>
<p>This can be huge for the NFT industry as LG has a large <a href="https://www.statista.com/statistics/1148081/lg-electronics-television-global-market-share/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">market share</a> in the home appliance industry. However, <a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/tech/ftx-collapse-sam-bankman-fried-charged-b2244374.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">recent </a>events in crypto space might slow down the growth of interest in NFTs. Not to mention that the sector is not free from scams and frauds. </p>
<p>Just this month, Logan Paul, a major influencer on YouTube, was investigated by <a href="https://www.youtube.com/@Coffeezilla" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Coffeezilla</a> for defrauding his fans on his abandoned crypto project <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/that-is-insane-levels-of-greed-ludwig-responds-to-logan-paul-cryptozoo-scam/ar-AA15Mveo" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">CryptoZoo</a>. Despite these very negative developments for crypto and NFTs as a whole, we can expect a healthy adoption of digital art as LG continues to leverage this new technology. </p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-514262 size-full" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/aa-2.png" alt="" width="681" height="339" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/aa-2.png 681w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/aa-2-460x229.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/aa-2-360x180.png 360w" sizes="(max-width: 681px) 100vw, 681px" /></p>

<h2><strong>Dark Horizons?</strong></h2>
<p>The crypto industry has taken a heavy beating courtesy of the collapse of <a href="https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bankman-fried-met-white-house-213838446.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">FTX</a> and the NFT space has been struggling ever since interest on digital items waned. But with LG’s partnership with Hedera, we might see a brighter tomorrow for NFTs and the crypto market as a whole. </p>
<p>However, this &#8220;bright future&#8221; doesn’t come without losses. According to <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/hedera" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">CoinGecko</a>, Hedera’s native token HBAR has seen better days with the token dropping 5.6% in the past 24 hours. </p>
<p>The charts are also very bearish for the token. HBAR is heavily correlated with Ethereum. This means that if ETH continues to buckle under the bearish pressure, HBAR will follow the decline in value. </p>

<p><img loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/RTAMiKNL/" width="2047" height="979" /></p>

<p>These short-term developments are in line with Jorge Pesok’s thoughts on crypto and NFTs in its entirety:</p>
<blockquote><p><strong>“My prediction, at least in the short term, is that the industry will continue to face a bear market but will come out of it much more mature and garner more retail and institutional adoption” he said in the interview. </strong></p></blockquote>
<p>As Hedera partners with more institutional entities like LG, Boeing, and Deutsche Telekom, we will see the company playing a bigger role in the adoption of digital assets with real world utility. </p>
<p>&#8211;</p>
<p><em>Featured image: Adobe/S_E</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Hedera-460x279.png" width="460" height="279" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>These Are The Bitcoin Predictions For 2023 By Arcane Research</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-prediction-2023-arcane-research/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jake Simmons]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 12:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[2023]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[arcane research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[prediction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=514228</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Historically, 2022 could end up being the second-worst year for Bitcoin since 2011. At the current price, BTC has a year-to-date (YTD) performance of -65%, topped only by 2018 when the price lost -73% in one year. As Arcane Research notes in its year-end report for 2022, physical gold (-1% YTD) has significantly outperformed digital gold, Bitcoin, in a period of high inflation. As a result, the analytics firm notes that the digital gold narrative was premature. As Arcane Research notes, the crypto winter was essentially fueled by tightening macroeconomic conditions and crypto-specific leverage and miserable risk management by core market participants. BTC had followed the U.S. equity markets due to its high correlation. &#8220;Apart from two distinct events in 2022, BTC followed U.S. equities very closely. The two outliers of June (3AC, Celsius etc.) and November (FTX), are responsible for the entire underperformance of BTC vs. the U.S. equities,&#8221; the report states, displaying the following chart. Bitcoin Predictions For 2023 For the coming year 2023, Arcane Research expects that contagion effects will &#8220;probably&#8221; continue in early 2023. &#8220;[B]ut we view it as likely that the majority of 2023 will be less frantic and borderline uneventful compared to the last three years,&#8221; Arcane Research predicts. Related Reading: Solana Prediction For 2023: SOL Is Not Dead Yet, Analyst Says With that in mind, the firm expects Bitcoin to trade in a &#8220;mostly flat range&#8221; in 2023, but to finish the year with a higher price than it did at the start. Bitcoin&#8217;s current drawdowns closely resemble the bear market patterns of previous cycles, Arcane Research elicits. While the 2018 bear market lasted 364 days from peak to end, the 2014-15 bear market lasted 407 days. The current cycle is on its 376th day. This puts the ongoing bear market exactly between the duration in both previous cycles. &#8220;If a new bottom is reached in 2023, this will be the longest-lasting BTC drawdown ever,&#8221; the firm said and further elaborated that there are quite a few potential catalysts for a renowned bull market: The FTX proceedings may incentivize more rapid progress with regulations, and we view both positive signals related to U.S. spot BTC ETF launches and more coherent classifications of tokens as a plausible outcome by the end of the year, with exchange tokens being particularly exposed for potential security classifications. Regarding Grayscale&#8217;s Bitcoin spot ETF application, February 3 will be an important date for the industry when the three-judge panel will rule on the SEC complaint. Related Reading: Bitcoin Price Could End The Year Further Lower, Key Resistance Intact In addition, Arcane Research expects another catalyst from Europe: namely, the passage of the MiCA Act by the European Parliament in February 2023. The core prediction for 2023 remains that Bitcoin will recover despite the tightening macroeconomic situation and that now is &#8220;an excellent area to build gradual BTC exposure.&#8221; However, the start of 2023 could be bumpy as trading volumes and volatility decline in a much duller market than in the past three years. In summary, Arcane Research therefore estimates: As we advance into the next year, patience and long-term positioning will be key. At press time, the BTC price traded at $16,497, facing further downward pressure, probably due to tax harvesting by year-end. Featured image from Wance Paleri / Unsplash, Charts from Arcane Research and TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Historically, 2022 could end up being the second-worst year for Bitcoin since 2011. At the current price, BTC has a year-to-date (YTD) performance of -65%, topped only by 2018 when the price lost -73% in one year.</p>
<p>As Arcane Research notes in its year-end <a href="https://assets.ctfassets.net/4rilomtvvae4/5DgOdTmxer4KBlLsOTXapd/b19f517260fa1f0d25c87b79fd88944c/2022_Year_in_Review_-_Arcane_Research.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">report</a> for 2022, physical gold (-1% YTD) has significantly outperformed digital gold, Bitcoin, in a period of high inflation. As a result, the analytics firm notes that the digital gold narrative was premature.</p>
<p>As Arcane Research notes, the crypto winter was essentially fueled by tightening macroeconomic conditions and crypto-specific leverage and miserable risk management by core market participants. BTC had followed the U.S. equity markets due to its high correlation.</p>
<p>&#8220;Apart from two distinct events in 2022, BTC followed U.S. equities very closely. The two outliers of June (3AC, Celsius etc.) and November (<a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/company/what-happens-if-crypto-exchange-binance-bust-like-ftx-and-terra/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">FTX</a>), are responsible for the entire underperformance of BTC vs. the U.S. equities,&#8221; the report states, displaying the following chart.</p>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-514233 size-full" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTC-vs-US-equities-1.png" alt="Bitcoin vs. S&amp;P 500 vs. gold" width="1653" height="1265" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTC-vs-US-equities-1.png 1653w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTC-vs-US-equities-1-460x352.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTC-vs-US-equities-1-860x658.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTC-vs-US-equities-1-768x588.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTC-vs-US-equities-1-1536x1175.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTC-vs-US-equities-1-750x574.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTC-vs-US-equities-1-1140x872.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1653px) 100vw, 1653px" />
<h2>Bitcoin Predictions For 2023</h2>
<p>For the coming year 2023, Arcane Research expects that contagion effects will &#8220;probably&#8221; continue in early 2023. &#8220;[B]ut we view it as likely that the majority of 2023 will be less frantic and borderline uneventful compared to the last three years,&#8221; Arcane Research predicts.</p>

<p>With that in mind, the firm expects Bitcoin to trade in a &#8220;mostly flat range&#8221; in 2023, but to finish the year with a higher price than it did at the start.</p>
<p>Bitcoin&#8217;s current drawdowns closely resemble the bear market patterns of previous cycles, Arcane Research elicits. While the 2018 <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-bear-market-momentum-record/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">bear market</a> lasted 364 days from peak to end, the 2014-15 bear market lasted 407 days. The current cycle is on its 376th day. This puts the ongoing bear market exactly between the duration in both previous cycles.</p>
<p>&#8220;If a new bottom is reached in 2023, this will be the longest-lasting BTC drawdown ever,&#8221; the firm said and further elaborated that there are quite a few potential catalysts for a renowned bull market:</p>
<blockquote><p><strong>The FTX proceedings may incentivize more rapid progress with regulations, and we view both positive signals related to U.S. spot BTC ETF launches and more coherent classifications of tokens as a plausible outcome by the end of the year, with exchange tokens being particularly exposed for potential security classifications.</strong></p></blockquote>
<p>Regarding Grayscale&#8217;s Bitcoin <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/grayscale-set-to-file-for-bitcoin-spot-etf/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">spot ETF</a> application, February 3 will be an important date for the industry when the three-judge panel will rule on the SEC complaint.</p>

<p>In addition, Arcane Research expects another catalyst from Europe: namely, the passage of the MiCA Act by the European Parliament in February 2023. The core prediction for 2023 remains that Bitcoin will recover despite the tightening macroeconomic situation and that now is &#8220;an excellent area to build gradual BTC exposure.&#8221;</p>
<p>However, the start of 2023 could be bumpy as trading volumes and volatility decline in a much duller market than in the past three years. In summary, Arcane Research therefore estimates:</p>
<blockquote><p><strong>As we advance into the next year, patience and long-term positioning will be key.</strong></p></blockquote>
<p>At press time, the BTC price traded at $16,497, facing further downward pressure, probably due to tax harvesting by year-end.</p>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-514235 size-full" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-30_12-25-53.png" alt="Bitcoin BTC USD 2022-12-30" width="2956" height="1615" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-30_12-25-53.png 2956w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-30_12-25-53-460x251.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-30_12-25-53-860x470.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-30_12-25-53-768x420.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-30_12-25-53-1536x839.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-30_12-25-53-2048x1119.png 2048w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-30_12-25-53-750x410.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-30_12-25-53-1140x623.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 2956px) 100vw, 2956px" />

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/wance-paleri-NvZQct9lZmU-unsplash-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dogecoin Price Tumbles Below Support, Why This Could Be Strong Bearish</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/analysis/dogecoin-price-tumbles-070/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 11:52:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Technical analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[doge]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DOGE/USDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dogeusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dogeusdt]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=514243</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Dogecoin extended its decline below the $0.070 support against the US Dollar. DOGE could continue to move down towards the $0.0620 support zone. DOGE gained pace and traded below the $0.072 support against the US dollar. The price is trading below the $0.0700 zone and the 100 simple moving average (4-hours). There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.0698 on the 4-hours chart of the DOGE/USD pair (data source from Kraken). The pair could dive further towards the $0.062 support in the near term. Dogecoin Price Signals Bearish In the past few days, dogecoin saw a steady decline from the $0.080 resistance zone. DOGE reacted to the downside below the $0.0750 and $0.0720 support levels. The decline gained pace below the $0.072 level and the 100 simple moving average (4-hours). More importantly, there was a clear move below the $0.070 support zone, opening the doors for a major decline. The price is now trading well below the $0.0700 zone and the 100 simple moving average (4-hours). Doge price traded as low as $0.0667 and is currently showing a lot of bearish signs, similar bitcoin and ethereum. On the upside, the price is facing resistance near the $0.0695 level. The first major resistance is near the $0.0700 level. There is also a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.0698 on the 4-hours chart of the DOGE/USD pair. The trend line is near the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $0.0795 swing high to $0.0667 low. A clear move above the trend line might send the price towards the $0.073 resistance. It is near the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $0.0795 swing high to $0.0667 low. Source: DOGEUSD on TradingView.com Any more gains might send the price towards the $0.0765 level and the 100 SMA. The main hurdle seems to be forming near the $0.080 zone. A clear move above the $0.080 resistance could open the gates for a rally towards the $0.100 level. More Losses in DOGE? If DOGE price fails to gain pace above the $0.070 level, it could continue to move down. An initial support on the downside is near the $0.0665 level. The next major support is near the $0.062 level. If there is a downside break below the $0.0620 support, the price could decline further. In the stated case, the price might decline towards the $0.060 level. Technical Indicators 4-Hours MACD – The MACD for DOGE/USD is now gaining momentum in the bearish zone. 4-Hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for DOGE/USD is now in the oversold zone. Major Support Levels – $0.0665, $0.0662 and $0.0600. Major Resistance Levels – $0.070, $0.0730 and $0.080.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>Dogecoin extended its decline below the $0.070 support against the US Dollar. DOGE could continue to move down towards the $0.0620 support zone.</em></p>
<ul>
<li>DOGE gained pace and traded below the $0.072 support against the US dollar.</li>
<li>The price is trading below the $0.0700 zone and the 100 simple moving average (4-hours).</li>
<li>There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.0698 on the 4-hours chart of the DOGE/USD pair (data source from Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could dive further towards the $0.062 support in the near term.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Dogecoin Price Signals Bearish</h2>
<p>In the past few days, dogecoin saw a steady decline from the $0.080 resistance zone. DOGE reacted to the downside below the $0.0750 and $0.0720 support levels.</p>
<p>The decline gained pace below the $0.072 level and the 100 simple moving average (4-hours). More importantly, there was a clear move below the $0.070 support zone, opening the doors for a major decline. The price is now trading well below the $0.0700 zone and the 100 simple moving average (4-hours).</p>
<p>Doge price traded as low as $0.0667 and is currently showing a lot of bearish signs, similar <a href="https://newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-further-lower-16k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">bitcoin</a> and <a href="https://newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-signals-bearish-1100/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">ethereum</a>. On the upside, the price is facing resistance near the $0.0695 level.</p>
<p>The first major resistance is near the $0.0700 level. There is also a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.0698 on the 4-hours chart of the DOGE/USD pair. The trend line is near the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $0.0795 swing high to $0.0667 low.</p>
<p>A clear move above the trend line might send the price towards the $0.073 resistance. It is near the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $0.0795 swing high to $0.0667 low.</p>
<p><a href="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Doegcoin-DOGE-1.png"><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-514244" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Doegcoin-DOGE-1.png" alt="Dogecoin Price" width="1950" height="1109" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Doegcoin-DOGE-1.png 1950w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Doegcoin-DOGE-1-460x262.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Doegcoin-DOGE-1-860x489.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Doegcoin-DOGE-1-768x437.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Doegcoin-DOGE-1-1536x874.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Doegcoin-DOGE-1-750x427.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Doegcoin-DOGE-1-1140x648.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1950px) 100vw, 1950px" /></a></p>
<p>Source: <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/DOGEUSD/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">DOGEUSD on TradingView.com</a></p>
<p>Any more gains might send the price towards the $0.0765 level and the 100 SMA. The main hurdle seems to be forming near the $0.080 zone. A clear move above the $0.080 resistance could open the gates for a rally towards the $0.100 level.</p>
<h2>More Losses in DOGE?</h2>
<p>If DOGE price fails to gain pace above the $0.070 level, it could continue to move down. An initial support on the downside is near the $0.0665 level.</p>
<p>The next major support is near the $0.062 level. If there is a downside break below the $0.0620 support, the price could decline further. In the stated case, the price might decline towards the $0.060 level.</p>
<p>Technical Indicators</p>
<p>4-Hours MACD – The MACD for DOGE/USD is now gaining momentum in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>4-Hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for DOGE/USD is now in the oversold zone.</p>
<p>Major Support Levels – $0.0665, $0.0662 and $0.0600.</p>
<p>Major Resistance Levels – $0.070, $0.0730 and $0.080.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/shutterstock_1100038610-460x272.jpg" width="460" height="272" />	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
