<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
>

<channel>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.newsbtc.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<description>Bitcoin &#38; Cryptocurrency News Today</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 13:13:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Bitcoin&#8217;s Realized Cap Nears $400 Billion Despite Price Struggle At $30,000</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-realized-cap-nears-400b-price-reclaims/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samuel Edyme]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 14:30:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[glassnode]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=543084</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Despite Bitcoin&#8217;s current struggle to surpass the $30,000 mark, data analytics firm Glassnode earlier today reported that the asset&#8217;s realized capitalization has since been on an upward trajectory, nearing the $400 billion mark. Bitcoin Realized Cap Nears $400 Billion According to Data analytics firm Glassnode, Bitcoin&#8217;s Realized Cap is now inching closer to $400 billion, showing that new capital is continuously entering the market despite the year&#8217;s ups and downs.  Related Reading: Standard Chartered Raises Bitcoin Forecast To $120,000, Citing Miners’ Reduced Selling Bitcoin&#8217;s Realized Cap represents the total value of all BTC at the price they were last moved or transacted, indicating the cost basis of holders. When this metric rises, it reveals that BTC is being traded at progressively higher prices, which suggests an increase in demand. Glassnode reported that the increase in BTC&#8217;s realized cap signals the consistent influx of capital into the asset throughout the year 2023. This steady inflow represents a stable investment climate surrounding Bitcoin, despite its recent price fluctuations. Furthermore, Glassnode&#8217;s assessment of the ascending realized cap is indicative of a broader trend in the cryptocurrency market. The data analytics firms said, &#8220;It signals that coins are changing hands at higher prices on net,&#8221; &#8211; a phenomenon that underlines a rising demand for Bitcoin. It is worth noting that this recorded increasing demand for Bitcoin comes at a time the asset might have flashed a hope of bullish moves following the surge in Spot Bitcoin ETF filings and financial giants such as BlackRock embracing the largest asset by market cap. BTC Struggles To Push Past $30,000 Meanwhile, as Bitcoin realized&#8217;s cap is approaching $400 billion, the asset has struggled to make a significant move above the $30,000 mark. Over the past 24 hours alone, the BTC price has traded both below and above the $30,000 mark, suggesting a level of consolidation at this point. Particularly, the asset currently has a 24-hour high of $30,292 and a 24-hour low of $29,792, at the time of writing. However, regardless of that, BTC is currently down by only a slight dip of 1% in the last 24 hours with a trading price of $29,882.  This latest price action follows Bitcoin&#8217;s quick spike which was seen last week on July 13. This surge brought Bitcoin price to trade even above the $31,000 mark before briefly slipping below $30,000. Over the past few days, however, a total of more than $30 billion has been removed from the BTC market cap. Related Reading: Galaxy Digital Founder Anticipates BTC Price Surge Due To This Reason The asset&#8217;s market cap has plunged from a high of $614 billion seen on July 13 to $583 billion, as of today. Additionally, BTC trading volume has also declined in the past week indicating less trading activity. Featured image from iStock, Chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Despite Bitcoin&#8217;s current struggle to surpass the $30,000 mark, data analytics firm Glassnode earlier today <a href="https://twitter.com/glassnode/status/1681239117777043456?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">reported</a> that the asset&#8217;s realized capitalization has since been on an upward trajectory, nearing the $400 billion mark.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Realized Cap Nears $400 Billion</h2>
<p dir="ltr">According to Data analytics firm Glassnode, <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/standard-chartered-raises-bitcoin-forecast/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Bitcoin&#8217;s</a> Realized Cap is now inching closer to $400 billion, showing that new capital is continuously entering the market despite the year&#8217;s ups and downs. </p>
<p dir="ltr">Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/standard-chartered-raises-bitcoin-forecast/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Standard Chartered Raises Bitcoin Forecast To $120,000, Citing Miners’ Reduced Selling</a></p>
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin&#8217;s Realized Cap represents the total value of all BTC at the price they were last moved or transacted, indicating the cost basis of holders. When this metric rises, it reveals that BTC is being traded at progressively higher prices, which suggests an increase in demand.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Glassnode reported that the increase in BTC&#8217;s realized cap signals the consistent <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/surging-demand-for-bitcoin-ordinals-propels-to-210m/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">influx of capital</a> into the asset throughout the year 2023. This steady inflow represents a stable investment climate surrounding Bitcoin, despite its recent price fluctuations.</p>
<img decoding="async" class="size-medium wp-image-543098" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/F1T193rXoAAp3jg-460x265.jpeg" alt="Bitcoin (BTC) realised market cap." width="460" height="265" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/F1T193rXoAAp3jg-460x265.jpeg 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/F1T193rXoAAp3jg-860x496.jpeg 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/F1T193rXoAAp3jg-768x443.jpeg 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/F1T193rXoAAp3jg-750x432.jpeg 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/F1T193rXoAAp3jg-1140x657.jpeg 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/F1T193rXoAAp3jg.jpeg 1199w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px" loading="lazy"/>
<p>Furthermore, Glassnode&#8217;s assessment of the ascending realized cap is indicative of a broader trend in the cryptocurrency market. The data analytics firms said, &#8220;It signals that coins are changing hands at higher prices on net,&#8221; &#8211; a phenomenon that underlines a rising demand for Bitcoin. </p>
<p>It is worth noting that this recorded increasing demand for Bitcoin comes at a time the asset might have flashed a hope of bullish moves following the surge in <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/dormant-bitcoin-supply-peaks-as-institutional-investors/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Spot Bitcoin ETF filings and financial giants</a> such as BlackRock embracing the largest asset by market cap.</p>
<h2>BTC Struggles To Push Past $30,000</h2>
<p>Meanwhile, as Bitcoin realized&#8217;s cap is approaching $400 billion, the asset has struggled to make a significant move above the $30,000 mark. Over the past 24 hours alone, the BTC price has traded both below and above the $30,000 mark, suggesting a level of consolidation at this point.</p>
<p>Particularly, the asset currently has a 24-hour high of $30,292 and a 24-hour low of $29,792, at the time of writing. However, regardless of that, BTC is currently down by only a slight dip of 1% in the last 24 hours with a trading price of $29,882. </p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/J9rSX7U8/" alt="Bitcoin (BTC)’s price chart on TradingView" width="2770" height="1556"/>
<p>This latest price action follows <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/founder-anticipates-btc-price-surge-forecasts-bitcoin-etfs/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Bitcoin&#8217;s quick spike</a> which was seen last week on July 13. This surge brought Bitcoin price to trade even above the $31,000 mark before briefly slipping below $30,000. Over the past few days, however, a total of more than $30 billion has been removed from the BTC market cap.</p>

<p>The asset&#8217;s market cap has plunged from a high of $614 billion seen on July 13 to $583 billion, as of today. Additionally, BTC trading volume has also declined in the past week indicating less trading activity.</p>
<p>Featured image from iStock, Chart from TradingView</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/andre-francois-mckenzie-iGYiBhdNTpE-unsplash-2-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>SUI Surges 11% In Just 24 Hours, Is It Still Worth Buying?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/sui-surges-11-just-24-hours-still-worth-buying/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jake Simmons]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 13:30:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SUI]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SUIUSD]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=543107</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[After the launch of the mainnet on May 3, the SUI token fell into a deep downtrend, which has caused the price to drop by more than 87%. Low user numbers and poor on-chain data have severely clouded the outlook. However, a few days ago, there was a surprise that gave a big boost to the SUI price. The SUI network made waves in the crypto space by surpassing its competitor Solana in daily transactions. However, with a sudden record of 29 million transactions in 24 hours, SUI has left many crypto enthusiasts questioning the validity and sustainability of this sudden surge. Renowned analyst and crypto whale Andrew Kang, known for his insightful commentary, has raised concerns about the authenticity of these transactions, suggesting that SUI may be artificially inflating its numbers. Kang writes today: Sui pumping their numbers up. Chart looks good, market does not seem to be discerning about validity of transactions. Fake it til you make it. Is SUI Still Worth Buying? As Kang argues, the question is: Are the numbers legitimate and can drive a sustainable upward trend, or will the hype quickly die down because of fake numbers? Related Reading: SUI Continues Rally As Sui 8192 Web3 Game Fuels Blockchain Activity To Hit New Peak The recent surge in transactions can be primarily attributed to the introduction of the on-chain game, &#8220;Sui 8192.&#8221; Developed by the team behind the wallet provider, Ethos Wallet, this casual game has captured the attention of users with its gameplay reminiscent of the classic puzzle game &#8220;2048.&#8221; Each move within the game triggers a transaction, resulting in the state of the game being recorded on the blockchain. With the integration of a pre-approval mechanism in Ethos Wallet, players can optimize their gameplay experience by setting a token amount before each game. It&#8217;s Important to know that the SUI Foundation has allocated $5 million to further stimulate activity within the game, offering players the opportunity to earn rewards in the form of SUI tokens by competing against others or completing tasks. However, this could call into question the sustainability of this increase in transaction activity. Related Reading: Sui Foundation Refutes Claims Of Dumping Locked Staking Rewards On Binance Perhaps the game is only experiencing a short hype at the moment because players want to grab the free tokens. Once the marketing budget is exhausted, the hype could quickly be over. SUI traders and investors should therefore be cautious. Prior to this transaction surge, the project had been marred by negative headlines, including allegations of suspicious token movements, concerns about venture capital influence, and opaque tokenomics. These controversies have left some investors wary of the project&#8217;s long-term prospects. Price Analysis However, as stated by Kang, the SUI chart looks promising at the moment. The price has broken out of the downward trend that existed since the mainnet launch. The bulls also managed to defend the 23.6 Fibonacci retracement level in a retest. Currently, the price is contending with the 38.2% retracement level at $0.76. If it manages to break above this resistance, $0.84 and $0.92 could be the next price target. Featured image from Boxmining, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>After the launch of the mainnet on May 3, the SUI token fell into a deep downtrend, which has caused the price to drop by more than 87%. Low user numbers and poor on-chain data have severely clouded the outlook. However, a few days ago, there was a surprise that gave a big boost to the SUI price.</p>
<p>The SUI network made waves in the crypto space by surpassing its competitor Solana in daily transactions. However, with a sudden record of 29 million transactions in 24 hours, SUI has left many crypto enthusiasts questioning the validity and sustainability of this sudden surge.</p>
<p>Renowned analyst and crypto whale Andrew Kang, known for his insightful commentary, has raised concerns about the authenticity of these transactions, suggesting that SUI may be artificially inflating its numbers. Kang writes today:</p>
<blockquote><p><strong>Sui pumping their numbers up. Chart looks good, market does not seem to be discerning about validity of transactions. Fake it til you make it.</strong></p></blockquote>
<h2>Is SUI Still Worth Buying?</h2>
<p>As Kang argues, the question is: Are the numbers legitimate and can drive a sustainable upward trend, or will the hype quickly die down because of fake numbers?</p>

<p>The recent surge in transactions can be primarily attributed to the introduction of the on-chain game, &#8220;Sui 8192.&#8221; Developed by the team behind the wallet provider, Ethos Wallet, this casual game has captured the attention of users with its gameplay reminiscent of the classic puzzle game &#8220;2048.&#8221;</p>
<p>Each move within the game triggers a transaction, resulting in the state of the game being recorded on the blockchain. With the integration of a pre-approval mechanism in Ethos Wallet, players can optimize their gameplay experience by setting a token amount before each game.</p>
<p>It&#8217;s Important to know that the SUI Foundation has allocated $5 million to further stimulate activity within the game, offering players the opportunity to earn rewards in the form of SUI tokens by competing against others or completing tasks. However, this could call into question the sustainability of this increase in transaction activity.</p>

<p>Perhaps the game is only experiencing a short hype at the moment because players want to grab the free tokens. Once the marketing budget is exhausted, the hype could quickly be over. SUI traders and investors should therefore be cautious.</p>
<p>Prior to this transaction surge, the project had been marred by negative headlines, including allegations of suspicious token <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/altcoin/sui-foundation-refutes-claims-of-dumping-locked-staking-rewards-on-binance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">movements</a>, concerns about venture capital influence, and opaque <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/altcoin/sui-price-plummets-by-38/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">tokenomics</a>. These controversies have left some investors wary of the project&#8217;s long-term prospects.</p>
<h2>Price Analysis</h2>
<p>However, as stated by Kang, the SUI chart looks promising at the moment. The price has broken out of the downward trend that existed since the mainnet launch. The bulls also managed to defend the 23.6 Fibonacci retracement level in a retest. Currently, the price is contending with the 38.2% retracement level at $0.76. If it manages to break above this resistance, $0.84 and $0.92 could be the next price target.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-543126 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/SUIUSD_2023-07-18_13-35-31.png" alt="SUI price" width="3628" height="1672" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/SUIUSD_2023-07-18_13-35-31.png 3628w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/SUIUSD_2023-07-18_13-35-31-460x212.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/SUIUSD_2023-07-18_13-35-31-860x396.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/SUIUSD_2023-07-18_13-35-31-768x354.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/SUIUSD_2023-07-18_13-35-31-1536x708.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/SUIUSD_2023-07-18_13-35-31-2048x944.png 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/SUIUSD_2023-07-18_13-35-31-750x346.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/SUIUSD_2023-07-18_13-35-31-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 3628px) 100vw, 3628px"/>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/sui-460x259.png" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Chainlink CCIP Goes Live On Mainnet, LINK Jumps By Nearly 10%</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/altcoin/chainlink-ccip-goes-live-on-mainnet-link-jumps-by-nearly-10/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Opeyemi Sule]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 12:30:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CCIP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[chainlink]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Link]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LINK token]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LINKUSD]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=543072</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Cross-Chain Interoperability Protocol (CCIP), designed for building cross-chain applications and services, has now launched for early access users on the Avalanche, Ethereum, Optimism, and Polygon blockchains. On July 20, the Chainlink protocol will become available to developers across the four blockchains’ testnets and also Arbitrum’s Goerli. As a result of this, the price of Chainlink’s native token, LINK, rallied nearly 10% to touch $7.30 following this announcement on Monday. Chainlink&#8217;s CCIP &#8211; The Future Of Interoperability? In a blog post dated July 17, Chainlink announced the launch of the Cross-Chain Interoperability Protocol to early access users on Avalanche, Ethereum, Optimism, and Polygon blockchains. While DeFi lending protocol Aave is set to integrate the protocol, it has already been adopted on the derivatives platform Synthetix. Related Reading: Bitcoin Price Needs To Clear $30,500 For Hopes of a Fresh Rally According to the post, CCIP is an interoperability protocol that allows developers to design their own cross-chain solutions. It also offers &#8220;Simplified Token Transfers&#8221;, which allows protocols to swiftly send tokens across chains through audited token pool contracts.   Chainlink claims that CCIP is a blockchain layer designed to foster a connection between enterprises and any public or private blockchain ecosystem. The cross-chain protocol is a collaborative effort with Swift, the renowned global financial messaging network. It leverages Swift&#8217;s messaging infrastructure to facilitate token transfers across various public and private blockchains. According to Chainlink’s co-founder Sergey Nazarov, CCIP is a solution that aims to “connect the fragmented public blockchain landscape and the growing bank ecosystem into a single Internet of Contracts.” He also stated that such technology will be crucial to developing and maintaining a blockchain-powered society. Just like key standards such as TCP/IP remade a fragmented early internet into the single global internet we all know and use today, we are making CCIP to connect the fragmented public blockchain landscape and the growing bank chain ecosystem into a single Internet of Contracts.… https://t.co/BDMFMfknY2 pic.twitter.com/DDscglD2An — Sergey Nazarov (@SergeyNazarov) July 17, 2023 Some of the financial institutions and enterprises also exploring the Cross-Chain Interoperability Protocol include Australia and New Zealand Banking Group (ANZ), BNP Paribas, BNY Mellon, Citi, Euroclear, and Lloyds Banking Group. Chainlink (LINK) Up By 35% In One Month &#8211; Price Overview Following the announcement of the CCIP launch, the price of LINK experienced a significant pump, recording an almost 10% increase in the early hours of Tuesday. However, the token’s price appears to be slowing down, losing over 2% since reaching a 24-hour high of $7.29. As of this writing, LINK is valued at $7.12, with a 7.3% increase in the last day. CoinGecko data shows that the cryptocurrency has a daily trading volume of roughly $549.8 million, representing a 219% boost in the last 24 hours. Related Reading: LINK Price Prediction: Chainlink Rallies Over 7% As The Bulls Aim $8.8 A broader look at the Chainlink market reveals that the LINK price has been on an upward trajectory in recent weeks. Thanks to this bullish momentum, the token has gained about 35% in the past month. LINKUSD trading at $7.091&#124; Source: LINKUSD chart from TradingView Featured image from Binance Academy, chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Cross-Chain Interoperability Protocol (CCIP), designed for building cross-chain applications and services, has now launched for early access users on the Avalanche, Ethereum, Optimism, and Polygon blockchains. </p>
<p>On July 20, the Chainlink protocol will become available to developers across the four blockchains’ testnets and also Arbitrum’s Goerli. As a result of this, the price of Chainlink’s native token, LINK, rallied nearly 10% to touch $7.30 following this announcement on Monday.</p>
<h2>Chainlink&#8217;s CCIP &#8211; The Future Of Interoperability?</h2>
<p>In a <a href="https://blog.chain.link/ccip-mainnet-early-access/" rel="nofollow">blog post</a> dated July 17, Chainlink announced the launch of the Cross-Chain Interoperability Protocol to early access users on Avalanche, Ethereum, Optimism, and Polygon blockchains. While DeFi lending protocol Aave is set to integrate the protocol, it has already been adopted on the derivatives platform Synthetix.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-30500-fresh-rally/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Bitcoin Price Needs To Clear $30,500 For Hopes of a Fresh Rally</a></p>
<p>According to the post, CCIP is an interoperability protocol that allows developers to design their own cross-chain solutions. It also offers &#8220;Simplified Token Transfers&#8221;, which allows protocols to swiftly send tokens across chains through audited token pool contracts.  </p>
<p>Chainlink claims that CCIP is a blockchain layer designed to foster a connection between enterprises and any public or private blockchain ecosystem. </p>
<p>The cross-chain protocol is a <a href="https://www.swift.com/news-events/news/swift-explores-blockchain-interoperability-remove-friction-tokenised-asset-settlement" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">collaborative effort with Swift</a>, the renowned global financial messaging network. It leverages Swift&#8217;s messaging infrastructure to facilitate token transfers across various public and private blockchains.</p>
<p>According to Chainlink’s co-founder Sergey Nazarov, CCIP is a solution that aims to “connect the fragmented public blockchain landscape and the growing bank ecosystem into a single Internet of Contracts.” </p>
<p>He also stated that such technology will be crucial to developing and maintaining a blockchain-powered society.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Just like key standards such as TCP/IP remade a fragmented early internet into the single global internet we all know and use today, we are making CCIP to connect the fragmented public blockchain landscape and the growing bank chain ecosystem into a single Internet of Contracts.… <a href="https://t.co/BDMFMfknY2" rel="nofollow">https://t.co/BDMFMfknY2</a> <a href="https://t.co/DDscglD2An" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/DDscglD2An</a></p>
<p>— Sergey Nazarov (@SergeyNazarov) <a href="https://twitter.com/SergeyNazarov/status/1681064341515259904?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">July 17, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p>Some of the financial institutions and enterprises also exploring the Cross-Chain Interoperability Protocol include Australia and New Zealand Banking Group (ANZ), BNP Paribas, BNY Mellon, Citi, Euroclear, and Lloyds Banking Group.</p>
<h2>Chainlink (LINK) Up By 35% In One Month &#8211; Price Overview</h2>
<p>Following the announcement of the CCIP launch, the price of LINK experienced a significant pump, recording an almost 10% increase in the early hours of Tuesday. However, the token’s price appears to be slowing down, losing over 2% since reaching a 24-hour high of $7.29.</p>
<p>As of this writing, LINK is valued at $7.12, with a 7.3% increase in the last day. <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/chainlink" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">CoinGecko data</a> shows that the cryptocurrency has a daily trading volume of roughly $549.8 million, representing a 219% boost in the last 24 hours.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/link/link-price-prediction-chainlink-to-8-8/?swcfpc=1">LINK Price Prediction: Chainlink Rallies Over 7% As The Bulls Aim $8.8</a></p>
<p>A broader look at the Chainlink market reveals that the LINK price has been on an upward trajectory in recent weeks. Thanks to this bullish momentum, the token has gained about 35% in the past month.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/5kDek0rP/" alt="Chainlink" width="997" height="586"/></p>





]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Chainlink-3-460x259.png" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>XRP Holdings On Bitrue Exchange Surges By 300%</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/xrp-holdings-on-bitrue-exchange-surges-by-300/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Semilore Faleti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 11:30:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitrue]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[futures market]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrp]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=543076</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Over the last week, the XRP token has dominated the headlines following Ripple’s partial court victory over the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC).  On July 13, Judge Analisa Torres of the US District Court of the Southern District of New York ruled that XRP doesn&#8217;t qualify as a security leading to a massive price surge in which the token gained by almost 90%. However, while it may appear that XRP&#8217;s positive effect on the market is waning, with most assets slipping into a bearish state, there is still a high level of interest surrounding this altcoin, proven by a recent report from prominent crypto exchange Bitrue. Bitrue Users Accumulate $800M Worth Of XRP In Futures Market.  In the late hours of yesterday, a crypto analyst with the Twitter handle @cowboycrypto313 revealed that Bitrue had shared a report via email with its users, noting a massive increase in the notional value of the open interest of the XRP token. Related Reading: XRP Price Retreats After Massive 80% Rally, Buy The Dips? The notional value of open interest refers to the total value of outstanding contracts in a futures or optional market. In this context, it represents the total value of XRP on the Bitrue exchange based on what its traders have pledged to buy or sell in the future.  In this report, Bitrue states that XRP holdings in its Futures service spiked from less than $200 million to over $800 million during the weekend. Interestingly, the exchange further revealed that 88% of its users are holding a long position on this asset. According to a chart shared by Bitrue, the notional value of open interest for XRP on its platform had been below $200 million for the majority of the last two weeks. However, following the court ruling on July 13, this index started rising, with the XRP Futures market recording a notable spike on July 16.  Source: Twitter XRP Soars By 57% In Seven Days In other news, XRP remains the center of the crypto market attention, recording a 56.73% gain in the last week, according to data from CoinMarketCap. Currently, XRP, which now ranks as the fourth-biggest cryptocurrency, is tagged biggest weekly gainer. Nevertheless, it is worth noting that this token has shown little to no price movement in the last few days, with its price hovering around the $0.74 region. As of this writing, XRP is trading at $0.742 with a 1.14% gain on the last day.  Related Reading: BTC Price Analysis: Why Is Bitcoin Down Today? However, its daily trading volume has seen a sharp decline falling by 40.29% to its current value of $2.41 billion. Other major weekly gainers include Stellar (XLM) and Synthetix (SNX), with their market prices rising by 25.75% and 30.24%, respectively.  XRP Trading At $0.7445 On The 4-Hour Chart &#124; Source: XRPUSD Chart On Tradingview.com Featured Image From Business Standard, Chart From Tradingview.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Over the last week, the XRP token has dominated the headlines following Ripple’s partial court victory over the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). </p>
<p>On July 13, Judge Analisa Torres of the US District Court of the Southern District of New York <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/ripple-judge-deems-xrp-sale-non-investment-contract/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">ruled that X</a>RP doesn&#8217;t qualify as a security leading to a massive price surge in which the token gained by almost 90%.</p>
<p>However, while it may appear that XRP&#8217;s positive effect on the market is waning, with most assets slipping into a bearish state, there is still a high level of interest surrounding this altcoin, proven by a recent report from prominent crypto exchange Bitrue.</p>
<h2>Bitrue Users Accumulate $800M Worth Of XRP In Futures Market. </h2>
<p>In the late hours of yesterday, a crypto analyst with the Twitter handle @cowboycrypto313 <a href="https://twitter.com/cowboycrypto313/status/1681071716087332866?s=46&amp;t=JAUmthpFclo8jS4VJkm3DQ" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">revealed</a> that Bitrue had shared a report via email with its users, noting a massive increase in the notional value of the open interest of the XRP token.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/xrp-price-retreats-rally-0-95/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">XRP Price Retreats After Massive 80% Rally, Buy The Dips?</a></p>
<p>The notional value of open interest refers to the total value of outstanding contracts in a futures or optional market. In this context, it represents the total value of XRP on the Bitrue exchange based on what its traders have pledged to buy or sell in the future. </p>
<p>In this report, Bitrue states that XRP holdings in its Futures service spiked from less than $200 million to over $800 million during the weekend. Interestingly, the exchange further revealed that 88% of its users are holding a long position on this asset.</p>
<p>According to a chart shared by Bitrue, the notional value of open interest for XRP on its platform had been below $200 million for the majority of the last two weeks. However, following the court ruling on July 13, this index started rising, with the XRP Futures market recording a notable spike on July 16. </p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-large wp-image-543087" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/photo_2023-07-18_11-27-26-860x649.jpg" alt="XRP" width="860" height="649" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/photo_2023-07-18_11-27-26-860x649.jpg 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/photo_2023-07-18_11-27-26-460x347.jpg 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/photo_2023-07-18_11-27-26-768x580.jpg 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/photo_2023-07-18_11-27-26-750x566.jpg 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/photo_2023-07-18_11-27-26-1140x861.jpg 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/photo_2023-07-18_11-27-26.jpg 1229w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/></p>

<h2>XRP Soars By 57% In Seven Days</h2>
<p>In other news, XRP remains the center of the crypto market attention, recording a 56.73% gain in the last week, according to <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/xrp/#Chart" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">data from CoinMarketCap</a>. Currently, XRP, which now ranks as the fourth-biggest cryptocurrency, is tagged biggest weekly gainer.</p>
<p>Nevertheless, it is worth noting that this token has shown little to no price movement in the last few days, with its price hovering around the $0.74 region. As of this writing, XRP is trading at $0.742 with a 1.14% gain on the last day. </p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/btc-price-analysis-why-is-bitcoin-down-today/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">BTC Price Analysis: Why Is Bitcoin Down Today?</a></p>
<p>However, its daily trading volume has seen a sharp decline falling by 40.29% to its current value of $2.41 billion. Other major weekly gainers include Stellar (XLM) and Synthetix (SNX), with their market prices rising by 25.75% and 30.24%, respectively. </p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/WFhgvKUH/" alt="XRP" width="1480" height="913"/></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/1431356871-9178-460x329.jpg" width="460" height="329" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>This Under-The-Radar Coin Just Beat The Top 100 Cryptocurrencies With 120% Explosion</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/all/cryptocurrencies-this-coin-soars-120/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 10:35:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[All]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto casino]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrencies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[RLB]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Rollbit]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=543073</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Cryptocurrencies and the gaming industry have a new contender in Rollbit, and it has been making headlines over the past few days thanks to a slew of improvements to its blockchain technology. In a recent development, Rollbit disclosed its most current changes to the platform&#8217;s blockchain technology, propelling it to the forefront of the market. Notably, the company has started offering strong support for its own native cryptocurrency, Rollbit Coin (RLB), giving customers access to better ecosystem functionality and advantages. Related Reading: Elon Musk Fires Another Tweet – But Did It Lift Dogecoin Price? Based on crypto market tracker Coingecko figures, this lesser-known RLB coin has skyrocketed by more than 120% in the last seven days. At the time of writing, RLB was trading at $0.1224, up 24% over the previous 24 hours. Source: Coingecko RLB is a crucial part of the Rollbit lottery system, which decided to airdrop RLB tokens to their current Rollbit.com gaming and trading platform customers rather than holding an initial coin offering (ICO). RLB seven-day price action. Source: Coingecko Despite being a relatively new platform, Rollbit has quickly become one of the top competitors in crypto casinos. Rollbit has established itself as a dominant and significant power in the business, with an average monthly wagering volume above $1 billion. RLB has a market valuation of $357,728,046 with a 24-hour trading volume of $15,311,290. There are 3.3 billion coins in circulation. The highest transaction for RLB today was $0.1248. Its current price is over 14% less than its previous peak. As of today, cryptocurrencies have a market cap of $1.16 trillion. Chart: TradingView.com The Unstoppable Growth Of Cryptocurrencies And Bitcoin Casinos One of the newest trends in the cryptocurrencies and gaming sector, crypto casinos, could change the face of the industry as we know it. Some of the biggest Bitcoin casinos on the market now have thousands of active players worldwide, thanks to their numerous advantages over conventional casinos, including quicker payments, better security, and greater transparency. According to Casinos Blockchain, the global crypto casino market will be worth nearly $280 billion this year, with a $250 million gambling market. Over the years, cryptocurrency has accounted for 4% of all gambling, which is quickly rising. Related Reading: Shiba Inu Encounters Familiar Resistance, Prompting Concerns About Bull Run By the end of 2030, Straits Research projects that the global industry for online cryptocurrency gambling will be worth $153 billion, expanding at a CAGR of about 12%. Meanwhile, based on Captain Altcoin&#8217;s research, Rollbit (RLB) earns an astounding annualized revenue of $498,582,700 by collecting almost $1.36 million daily. This revenue exceeds that of Ethereum, a cryptocurrency with 2,000 times the value of Rollbit. (This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk). Featured image from BitcoinChaser]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Cryptocurrencies and the gaming industry have a new contender in Rollbit, and it has been making headlines over the past few days thanks to a slew of improvements to its blockchain technology.</p>
<p>In a recent development, Rollbit disclosed its most current changes to the platform&#8217;s blockchain technology, propelling it to the forefront of the market.</p>
<p>Notably, the company has started offering strong support for its own native cryptocurrency, Rollbit Coin (RLB), giving customers access to better ecosystem functionality and advantages.</p>

<p>Based on crypto market tracker Coingecko figures, this lesser-known RLB coin has <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/?page=2" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">skyrocketed by more than 120%</a> in the last seven days. At the time of writing, RLB was trading at $0.1224, up 24% over the previous 24 hours.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-543077" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-114.png" alt="" width="1146" height="71" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-114.png 1146w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-114-460x28.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-114-860x53.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-114-768x48.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-114-1140x71.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-114-750x46.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 1146px) 100vw, 1146px"/></p>

<p>RLB is a crucial part of the Rollbit lottery system, which decided to airdrop RLB tokens to their current Rollbit.com gaming and trading platform customers rather than holding an initial coin offering (ICO).</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-543085" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-115.png" alt="" width="849" height="547" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-115.png 849w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-115-460x296.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-115-768x495.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-115-750x483.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 849px) 100vw, 849px"/></p>

<p>Despite being a relatively new platform, Rollbit has quickly become one of the top competitors in crypto casinos. Rollbit has established itself as a dominant and significant power in the business, with an average monthly wagering volume above $1 billion.</p>
<p>RLB has a market valuation of $357,728,046 with a 24-hour trading volume of $15,311,290. There are 3.3 billion coins in circulation.</p>
<p>The highest transaction for RLB today was $0.1248. Its current price is over 14% less than its previous peak.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/93hfSPLk/" width="2475" height="1187"/></p>

<h2><strong>The Unstoppable Growth Of Cryptocurrencies And Bitcoin Casinos</strong></h2>
<p>One of the newest trends in the cryptocurrencies and gaming sector, crypto casinos, could change the face of the industry as we know it.</p>
<p>Some of the biggest Bitcoin casinos on the market now have thousands of active players worldwide, thanks to their numerous advantages over conventional casinos, including quicker payments, better security, and greater transparency.</p>
<p>According to Casinos Blockchain, the global crypto casino market will be worth nearly <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/elon-musk-fires-another-tweet/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">$280 billion this year</a>, with a $250 million gambling market. Over the years, cryptocurrency has accounted for 4% of all gambling, which is quickly rising.</p>

<p>By the end of 2030, Straits Research projects that the global industry for online cryptocurrency gambling will be worth $153 billion, expanding at a CAGR of about 12%.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, based on Captain Altcoin&#8217;s research, Rollbit (RLB) earns an astounding <a href="https://captainaltcoin.com/could-this-rollbits-next-move-ignite-an-ultimate-rlb-price-explosion/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">annualized revenue</a> of $498,582,700 by collecting almost $1.36 million daily. This revenue exceeds that of Ethereum, a cryptocurrency with 2,000 times the value of Rollbit.</p>
<p><em>(This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk).</em></p>
<p><em>Featured image from BitcoinChaser</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-116-460x275.png" width="460" height="275" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>BTC Price Analysis: Why Is Bitcoin Down Today?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/btc-price-analysis-why-is-bitcoin-down-today/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jake Simmons]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 08:00:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=543045</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Bitcoin price has fallen to the lower end of its almost one-month trading range between $29,800 and $31,300. Already yesterday, BTC briefly fell to as low as $29,704, only to recover to $30,306 within a few hours. At press time, BTC was again moving towards the $30,000 mark, and another fall and liquidity grab seems likely. While this week the macro data releases are pretty quiet, it&#8217;s worth taking a look at what&#8217;s happening in the Bitcoin market itself. Why Is Bitcoin Down Today? Swissblock Insights observed a peculiar calm in the market when Bitcoin reached a new yearly high of $31.840 last week. However, the momentum quickly faded, and selling pressure increased, causing BTC to drop to the low $30ks. They highlight the narrow Bollinger Bands, stating, &#8220;The Bollinger Bands are very narrow, with only a 4.2% value difference separating the upper and lower bands. A move is brewing.&#8221; Moreover, the analysts emphasize the need for a significant catalyst to inject life into the current lackluster scenario: Volatility is expected to appear on the scene, although, in the short term, we are in no man’s land; liquidity remains low, open interest is still flat and shorts are nowhere to be seen. There’s no command in the direction we are going, and only a significant catalyst can spice things up in this dull scenario we are in. According to the analysts, a breakdown of the $29.650 support level would invalidate a long setup. On the other hand, a bullish leg up $31.500 could reignite momentum and surge the price to $33,000. But for this to happen, spot demand needs to reignite strongly and longs need to enter the market, “otherwise momentum will continue to fading.&#8221; Related Reading: This Bitcoin Continuation Pattern Points To 3-6 Months Of Uptrend Ahead Glassnode, an on-chain data provider, further illuminates the current state of the Bitcoin market. Despite the temporary yearly high, they describe the market as &#8220;extremely quiet&#8221;, also pointing to the Bollinger Bands. This compression in volatility signals a market reminiscent of the calm observed in early January, as NewsBTC reported yesterday. Furthermore, Glassnode’s analysis reveals a slow but steady inflow of capital into Bitcoin. The Realized Cap currently sits just shy at $396 billion. After hitting a cycle low at $380 billion, the metric indicates that a slow but steady stream of capital is entering the market throughout 2023. Glasnode also emphasizes that investors remain unwilling to part with their held supply, resulting in choppy market conditions similar to those seen in 2016 and 2019-20 periods. Total realized profit and loss resembles the historic trend: If we take a ratio between total realized profit and loss, [&#8230;] we can also note that a lower high in this ratio was set this week. If sustained, it may allude to similar choppy market conditions seen in both 2019-20, and again in the second half of 2021. The analysis also highlights the profit-locking behavior among Bitcoin holders, with the majority of both short-term (88%) and long-term holders&#8217; balances (73%) held in profit. However, short-term holders are the primary entities that are active in the market. Related Reading: Big Bitcoin Move Ahead: Bollinger Bands See Extreme Squeeze Out of the total 39.600 BTC in daily exchange inflows, 78% of this is associated with the STH cohort. This means that short term holders may have to trim their profits for the time being before selling pressure eases and the bulls can take the upper hand again. GreekLive, an options expert, explains that the Bitcoin market is still losing liquidity, which makes it highly susceptible to spikes and V-shaped recoveries: Cryptocurrencies encountered a V-shaped market today, with BTC falling below $29,700 and ETH below $1,875, before rebounding in a V-shaped during Asian trading hours to regain the round number of points, but the options market barely reacted to this. The analysis advises sellers to focus on static protection and have risk control plans for holding options until expiration. For buyers, timely profit-taking and using futures to hedge options are recommended risk management strategies. At press time, BTC traded at $30,064. Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Bitcoin price has fallen to the lower end of its almost one-month trading range between $29,800 and $31,300. Already yesterday, BTC briefly fell to as low as $29,704, only to recover to $30,306 within a few hours. At press time, BTC was again moving towards the $30,000 mark, and another fall and liquidity grab seems likely.</p>
<p>While this week the macro data releases are pretty quiet, it&#8217;s worth taking a look at what&#8217;s happening in the Bitcoin market itself.</p>
<h2>Why Is Bitcoin Down Today?</h2>
<p>Swissblock Insights <a href="https://swissblock.substack.com/p/no-mans-land" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">observed</a> a peculiar calm in the market when Bitcoin reached a new yearly high of $31.840 last week. However, the momentum quickly faded, and selling pressure increased, causing BTC to drop to the low $30ks. They highlight the narrow Bollinger Bands, stating, &#8220;The Bollinger Bands are very narrow, with only a 4.2% value difference separating the upper and lower bands. A move is brewing.&#8221;</p>
<p>Moreover, the analysts emphasize the need for a significant catalyst to inject life into the current lackluster scenario:</p>
<blockquote><p><strong>Volatility is expected to appear on the scene, although, in the short term, we are in no man’s land; liquidity remains low, open interest is still flat and shorts are nowhere to be seen. There’s no command in the direction we are going, and only a significant catalyst can spice things up in this dull scenario we are in.</strong></p></blockquote>
<p>According to the analysts, a breakdown of the $29.650 support level would invalidate a long setup. On the other hand, a bullish leg up $31.500 could reignite momentum and surge the price to $33,000. But for this to happen, spot demand needs to reignite strongly and longs need to enter the market, “otherwise momentum will continue to fading.&#8221;</p>

<p>Glassnode, an on-chain data provider, further <a href="https://insights.glassnode.com/the-week-onchain-week-29-2023/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">illuminates</a> the current state of the Bitcoin market. Despite the temporary yearly high, they describe the market as &#8220;extremely quiet&#8221;, also pointing to the Bollinger Bands. This compression in volatility signals a market reminiscent of the calm observed in early January, as NewsBTC <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/big-bitcoin-move-ahead-bollinger-bands-see-extreme-squeeze/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">reported</a> yesterday.</p>
<p>Furthermore, Glassnode’s analysis reveals a slow but steady inflow of capital into Bitcoin. The Realized Cap currently sits just shy at $396 billion. After hitting a cycle low at $380 billion, the metric indicates that a slow but steady stream of capital is entering the market throughout 2023.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-543060 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/01_RealizedCap.png" alt="Bitcoin Realized Cap" width="2400" height="1382" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/01_RealizedCap.png 2400w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/01_RealizedCap-460x265.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/01_RealizedCap-860x495.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/01_RealizedCap-768x442.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/01_RealizedCap-1536x884.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/01_RealizedCap-2048x1179.png 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/01_RealizedCap-750x432.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/01_RealizedCap-1140x656.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 2400px) 100vw, 2400px"/>
<p>Glasnode also emphasizes that investors remain unwilling to part with their held supply, resulting in choppy market conditions similar to those seen in 2016 and 2019-20 periods. Total realized profit and loss resembles the historic trend:</p>
<blockquote><p><strong>If we take a ratio between total realized profit and loss, [&#8230;] we can also note that a lower high in this ratio was set this week. If sustained, it may allude to similar choppy market conditions seen in both 2019-20, and again in the second half of 2021.</strong></p></blockquote>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-543059 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/03_RealizedPnLRatio.png" alt="Bitcoin Realized PnL Ratio" width="2400" height="1382" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/03_RealizedPnLRatio.png 2400w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/03_RealizedPnLRatio-460x265.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/03_RealizedPnLRatio-860x495.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/03_RealizedPnLRatio-768x442.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/03_RealizedPnLRatio-1536x884.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/03_RealizedPnLRatio-2048x1179.png 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/03_RealizedPnLRatio-750x432.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/03_RealizedPnLRatio-1140x656.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 2400px) 100vw, 2400px"/>
<p>The analysis also highlights the profit-locking behavior among Bitcoin holders, with the majority of both short-term (88%) and long-term holders&#8217; balances (73%) held in profit. However, short-term holders are the primary entities that are active in the market.</p>

<p>Out of the total 39.600 BTC in daily exchange inflows, 78% of this is associated with the STH cohort. This means that short term holders may have to trim their profits for the time being before selling pressure eases and the bulls can take the upper hand again.</p>
<p>GreekLive, an options expert, <a href="https://twitter.com/GreeksLive/status/1681118606451707904" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">explains</a> that the Bitcoin market is still losing liquidity, which makes it highly susceptible to spikes and V-shaped recoveries:</p>
<blockquote><p><strong>Cryptocurrencies encountered a V-shaped market today, with BTC falling below $29,700 and ETH below $1,875, before rebounding in a V-shaped during Asian trading hours to regain the round number of points, but the options market barely reacted to this.</strong></p></blockquote>
<p>The analysis advises sellers to focus on static protection and have risk control plans for holding options until expiration. For buyers, timely profit-taking and using futures to hedge options are recommended risk management strategies.</p>
<p>At press time, BTC traded at $30,064.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-543061 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD_2023-07-18_09-14-59.png" alt="Bitcoin price" width="3628" height="1672" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD_2023-07-18_09-14-59.png 3628w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD_2023-07-18_09-14-59-460x212.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD_2023-07-18_09-14-59-860x396.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD_2023-07-18_09-14-59-768x354.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD_2023-07-18_09-14-59-1536x708.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD_2023-07-18_09-14-59-2048x944.png 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD_2023-07-18_09-14-59-750x346.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD_2023-07-18_09-14-59-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 3628px) 100vw, 3628px"/>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/iStock-1410473489-460x259.jpg" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Elon Musk Fires Another Tweet &#8211; But Did It Lift Dogecoin Price?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/elon-musk-fires-another-tweet/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 06:43:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Doge price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[meme coins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price action]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=543048</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Elon Musk has consistently proven to be a pivotal figure in cryptocurrencies, particularly Dogecoin (DOGE), his crypto of choice. His influence on DOGE has been nothing short of remarkable, with any mention or action from him causing significant fluctuations in its price. In the digital currency landscape, where DOGE has struggled to keep pace with its counterparts despite the recent positive sentiment surrounding cryptocurrencies, any movement on the meme coin carries a heightened significance. Related Reading: Shiba Inu Encounters Familiar Resistance, Prompting Concerns About Bull Run Enthusiasts eagerly await every word uttered by Musk, recognizing the potential impact his statements can have on the price and overall market sentiment. Given this context, what did Elon Musk, the Tesla and SpaceX top honcho and Twitter owner, say this time, and how did it reverberate within the DOGE community? Elon Musk ‘Doges’ Preference Boosts Dogecoin Price Musk recently responded to a question on a popular social media platform. The question was about his preference between cats and dogs, and the enigmatic billionaire, promptly answered, &#8220;Doges.&#8221; This seemingly innocuous response had an immediate impact on the price of the meme coin. Doges — Elon Musk (@elonmusk) July 17, 2023 Following Musk&#8217;s endorsement, Dogecoin experienced a surge in its price on Monday, with a notable 3% gain. Its trading value climbed from $0.07 to $0.073, reflecting the enthusiastic market response to Musk&#8217;s statement. The sudden price increase further solidified the significance of Musk&#8217;s influence on Dogecoin and the broader cryptocurrency market. DOGE to USD gets a little boost. Source: CoinMarketCap However, as of the time of writing, the initial excitement has subsided, and DOGE’s price on Coingecko has adjusted to $0.070024. Despite the slight dip from the peak, the meme coin still managed to record a modest increase of 0.5% within the last 24 hours. Over seven days, Dogecoin showcased a more promising rally, with a substantial gain of 8.2%. Source: Coingecko Crypto Trading Expert Foresees DOGE Breakout Meanwhile, crypto trading expert Ali Martinez recently took to Twitter to share his prediction that Dogecoin is on the brink of a breakout, presenting an opportunity for investors. Leveraging an analysis of critical resistance levels and historical data on address accumulation, Martinez foresees a potential 10% price surge if DOGE surpasses the significant $0.75 supply wall. #Dogecoin is trying to break out! Slicing through the $0.75 supply wall will trigger a 10% upswing to $0.85, where 176,000 addresses had previously purchased over 12.34 billion $DOGE. pic.twitter.com/RJw7v7q30X — Ali (@ali_charts) July 15, 2023 His insightful analysis suggests that breaking through the $0.75 supply wall can catalyze a notable upswing in Dogecoin&#8217;s price, propelling it toward the $0.85 mark. DOGE market cap nearing the $10 billion level. Chart: TradingView.com Related Reading: Polkadot (DOT) Price Momentum Builds As Open Interest Climbs – Details This specific price level holds particular significance because of the presence of approximately 176,000 addresses that had previously acquired a substantial amount of over 12.34 billion DOGE. (This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk). Featured image from Doha News]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Elon Musk has consistently proven to be a pivotal figure in cryptocurrencies, particularly Dogecoin (DOGE), his crypto of choice. His influence on DOGE has been nothing short of remarkable, with any mention or action from him causing significant fluctuations in its price.</p>
<p>In the digital currency landscape, where DOGE has struggled to keep pace with its counterparts despite the recent positive sentiment surrounding cryptocurrencies, any movement on the meme coin carries a heightened significance.</p>

<p>Enthusiasts eagerly await every word uttered by Musk, recognizing the potential impact his statements can have on the price and overall market sentiment.</p>
<p>Given this context, what did Elon Musk, the Tesla and SpaceX top honcho and Twitter owner, say this time, and how did it reverberate within the DOGE community?</p>
<h2><strong>Elon Musk ‘Doges’ Preference Boosts Dogecoin Price</strong></h2>
<p>Musk recently responded to a question on a popular social media platform. The question was about his preference between cats and dogs, and the enigmatic billionaire, <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1680815158157877248" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">promptly answered, &#8220;Doges.&#8221;</a> This seemingly innocuous response had an immediate impact on the price of the meme coin.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Doges</p>
<p>— Elon Musk (@elonmusk) <a href="https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1680815158157877248?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">July 17, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p>Following Musk&#8217;s endorsement, Dogecoin experienced a surge in its price on Monday, with a notable 3% gain. Its trading value climbed from $0.07 to $0.073, reflecting the enthusiastic market response to Musk&#8217;s statement. </p>
<p>The sudden price increase further solidified the significance of Musk&#8217;s influence on Dogecoin and the broader cryptocurrency market.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-543049" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-110.png" alt="" width="745" height="336" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-110.png 745w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-110-460x207.png 460w" sizes="(max-width: 745px) 100vw, 745px"/></p>

<p>However, as of the time of writing, the initial excitement has subsided, and <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1680815158157877248" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">DOGE’s price on Coingecko</a> has adjusted to $0.070024. Despite the slight dip from the peak, the meme coin still managed to record a modest increase of 0.5% within the last 24 hours. </p>
<p>Over seven days, Dogecoin showcased a more promising rally, with a substantial gain of 8.2%.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-543051" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-111.png" alt="" width="943" height="70" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-111.png 943w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-111-460x34.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-111-860x64.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-111-768x57.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-111-750x56.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 943px) 100vw, 943px"/></p>

<h2><strong>Crypto Trading Expert Foresees DOGE Breakout</strong></h2>
<p>Meanwhile, crypto trading expert Ali Martinez recently took<a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://twitter.com/ali_charts/status/1680141210122371072" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow"> to Twitter</a> to share his prediction that Dogecoin is on the brink of a breakout, presenting an opportunity for investors. </p>
<p>Leveraging an analysis of critical resistance levels and historical data on address accumulation, Martinez foresees a potential 10% price surge if DOGE surpasses the significant $0.75 supply wall.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en"><a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Dogecoin?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#Dogecoin</a> is trying to break out!</p>
<p>Slicing through the $0.75 supply wall will trigger a 10% upswing to $0.85, where 176,000 addresses had previously purchased over 12.34 billion <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24DOGE&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$DOGE</a>. <a href="https://t.co/RJw7v7q30X" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/RJw7v7q30X</a></p>
<p>— Ali (@ali_charts) <a href="https://twitter.com/ali_charts/status/1680141210122371072?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">July 15, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p>His insightful analysis suggests that breaking through the $0.75 supply wall can catalyze a notable upswing in Dogecoin&#8217;s price, propelling it toward the $0.85 mark. </p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/GxipMy2U/" width="2475" height="1187"/></p>


<p>This specific price level holds particular significance because of the presence of approximately 176,000 addresses that had previously acquired a substantial amount of over 12.34 billion DOGE.</p>
<p><em>(This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk).</em></p>
<p><em>Featured image from Doha News</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-112-460x258.png" width="460" height="258" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>LINK Price Prediction: Chainlink Rallies Over 7% As The Bulls Aim $8.8</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/link/link-price-prediction-chainlink-to-8-8/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 04:02:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[LINK]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[chainlink]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Link]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LINKUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[linkusdt]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=543042</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Chainlink’s LINK price is gaining pace above $7.00. The price could rise further if it clears the $7.35 and $7.50 resistance levels. Chainlink token price is showing positive signs and rising from $6.50 against the US dollar. The price is trading above the $7.00 level and the 100 simple moving average (4 hours). There is a major bullish trend line forming with support near $6.65 on the 4-hour chart of the LINK/USD pair (data source from Kraken). The price could gain bullish momentum above the $7.35 resistance zone. Chainlink (LINK) Price Eyes More Gains After a short-term downside correction, LINK price found support near the $6.45 level against the US Dollar. A low was formed near $6.458 and the price started a fresh increase, unlike Bitcoin and Ethereum. There was a clear move above the $6.65 and $6.90 resistance levels. The price climbed above the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $7.36 swing high to the $6.458 low. LINK price is now trading above the $7.00 level and the 100 simple moving average (4 hours). There is also a major bullish trend line forming with support near $6.65 on the 4-hour chart of the LINK/USD pair. The pair is now facing resistance near the 76.4% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $7.36 swing high to the $6.458 low. Source: LINKUSD on TradingView.com The first major resistance is near the $7.35 zone. A clear break above $7.35 may possibly start a fresh increase toward the $7.50 and $7.85 levels. The next major resistance is near the $8.00 level, above which the price could revisit $8.80. Dips Supported? If Chainlink’s price fails to climb above the $7.35 resistance level, there could be a downside correction. Initial support on the downside is near the $6.90 level. The next major support is near the $6.65 level and the trend line zone, below which the price might test the $6.45 level. Any more losses could lead the price toward the $6.00 level in the near term. Technical Indicators 4 hours MACD – The MACD for LINK/USD is gaining momentum in the bullish zone. 4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for LINK/USD is now above the 50 level. Major Support Levels – $6.90 and $6.65. Major Resistance Levels – $7.35 and $8.00.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>Chainlink’s LINK price is gaining pace above $7.00. The price could rise further if it clears the $7.35 and $7.50 resistance levels.</em></p>
<ul>
<li>Chainlink token price is showing positive signs and rising from $6.50 against the US dollar.</li>
<li>The price is trading above the $7.00 level and the 100 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There is a major bullish trend line forming with support near $6.65 on the 4-hour chart of the LINK/USD pair (data source from Kraken).</li>
<li>The price could gain bullish momentum above the $7.35 resistance zone.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Chainlink (LINK) Price Eyes More Gains</h2>
<p>After a short-term downside correction, LINK price found support near the $6.45 level against the US Dollar. A low was formed near $6.458 and the price started a fresh increase, unlike <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-30500-fresh-rally/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Bitcoin</a> and <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-downsides-1900/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Ethereum</a>.</p>
<p>There was a clear move above the $6.65 and $6.90 resistance levels. The price climbed above the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $7.36 swing high to the $6.458 low. LINK price is now trading above the $7.00 level and the 100 simple moving average (4 hours).</p>
<p>There is also a major bullish trend line forming with support near $6.65 on the 4-hour chart of the LINK/USD pair. The pair is now facing resistance near the 76.4% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $7.36 swing high to the $6.458 low.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-543043" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Chainlink-LINK.png" alt="LINK Price Prediction" width="1835" height="845" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Chainlink-LINK.png 1835w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Chainlink-LINK-460x212.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Chainlink-LINK-860x396.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Chainlink-LINK-768x354.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Chainlink-LINK-1536x707.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Chainlink-LINK-750x345.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Chainlink-LINK-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1835px) 100vw, 1835px"/></p>
<p>Source: <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/LINKUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">LINKUSD on TradingView.com</a></p>
<p>The first major resistance is near the $7.35 zone. A clear break above $7.35 may possibly start a fresh increase toward the $7.50 and $7.85 levels. The next major resistance is near the $8.00 level, above which the price could revisit $8.80.</p>
<h2>Dips Supported?</h2>
<p>If Chainlink’s price fails to climb above the $7.35 resistance level, there could be a downside correction. Initial support on the downside is near the $6.90 level.</p>
<p>The next major support is near the $6.65 level and the trend line zone, below which the price might test the $6.45 level. Any more losses could lead the price toward the $6.00 level in the near term.</p>
<p>Technical Indicators</p>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for LINK/USD is gaining momentum in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for LINK/USD is now above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Levels – $6.90 and $6.65.</p>
<p>Major Resistance Levels – $7.35 and $8.00.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/shutterstock_309774656-460x311.jpg" width="460" height="311" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum Price Indicators Suggest A Strong Case For More Downsides</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-downsides-1900/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 03:49:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=543039</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Ethereum price corrected further lower below the $1,900 level against the US Dollar. ETH is showing bearish signs and might decline further toward $1,825. Ethereum extended its decline and tested the $1,875 level. The price is trading below $1,930 and the 100-hourly Simple Moving Average. There is a connecting bearish trend line forming with resistance near $1,910 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD (data feed via Kraken). The pair could decline further if it stays below the $1,910 and $1,940 resistance levels. Ethereum Price Could Extend Losses Ethereum’s price made a fresh attempt to start a decent increase above the $1,950 resistance. However, ETH struggled to gain strength for a move above $1,950. A high was formed near $1,943 and the price reacted to the downside. There was a break below the $1,900 support zone. A new weekly low is formed near $1,875 and the price is now attempting a fresh increase. It broke the $1,890 and $1,900 levels. There was a move above the 50% Fib retracement level recent decline from the $1,943 swing high to the $1,875 low. Ether is now trading below $1,930 and the 100-hourly Simple Moving Average. On the upside, immediate resistance is near the $1,910 level. There is also a connecting bearish trend line forming with resistance near $1,910 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD. The trend line is near the 61.8% Fib retracement level recent decline from the $1,943 swing high to the $1,875 low. Source: ETHUSD on TradingView.com The first major resistance is near the $1,950 zone, above which the price could rise toward the $1,985 resistance zone. The next major resistance is near the $2,030 level. Any more gains could send Ether toward the $2,120 resistance or even $2,200. More Losses in ETH? If Ethereum fails to clear the $1,910 resistance, it could start a fresh decline. Initial support on the downside is near the $1,890 level. The first major support is near the $1,875 level, below which the price could extend its decline. The next major support is near the $1,825 support level. Any more losses could send Ether toward the $1,780 support level in the near term. Technical Indicators Hourly MACD – The MACD for ETH/USD is losing momentum in the bearish zone. Hourly RSI &#8211; The RSI for ETH/USD is now below the 50 level. Major Support Level – $1,875 Major Resistance Level – $1,910]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>Ethereum price corrected further lower below the $1,900 level against the US Dollar. ETH is showing bearish signs and might decline further toward $1,825.</em></p>
<ul>
<li>Ethereum extended its decline and tested the $1,875 level.</li>
<li>The price is trading below $1,930 and the 100-hourly Simple Moving Average.</li>
<li>There is a connecting bearish trend line forming with resistance near $1,910 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD (data feed via Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could decline further if it stays below the $1,910 and $1,940 resistance levels.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Ethereum Price Could Extend Losses</h2>
<p>Ethereum’s price made a fresh attempt to start a decent increase above the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-move-1900/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">$1,950 resistance</a>. However, ETH struggled to gain strength for a move above $1,950.</p>
<p>A high was formed near $1,943 and the price reacted to the downside. There was a break below the $1,900 support zone. A new weekly low is formed near $1,875 and the price is now attempting a fresh increase. It broke the $1,890 and $1,900 levels.</p>
<p>There was a move above the 50% Fib retracement level recent decline from the $1,943 swing high to the $1,875 low. Ether is now trading below $1,930 and the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-breaks-2000/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">100-hourly Simple Moving Average</a>.</p>
<p>On the upside, immediate resistance is near the $1,910 level. There is also a connecting bearish trend line forming with resistance near $1,910 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD. The trend line is near the 61.8% Fib retracement level recent decline from the $1,943 swing high to the $1,875 low.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-543040" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ethereum-11.png" alt="Ethereum Price" width="1835" height="845" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ethereum-11.png 1835w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ethereum-11-460x212.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ethereum-11-860x396.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ethereum-11-768x354.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ethereum-11-1536x707.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ethereum-11-750x345.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ethereum-11-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1835px) 100vw, 1835px"/></p>
<p>Source: <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/ETHUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">ETHUSD on TradingView.com</a></p>
<p>The first major resistance is near the $1,950 zone, above which the price could rise toward the $1,985 resistance zone. The next major resistance is near the $2,030 level. Any more gains could send Ether toward the $2,120 resistance or even $2,200.</p>
<h2>More Losses in ETH?</h2>
<p>If Ethereum fails to clear the $1,910 resistance, it could start a fresh decline. Initial support on the downside is near the $1,890 level.</p>
<p>The first major support is near the $1,875 level, below which the price could extend its decline. The next major support is near the $1,825 support level. Any more losses could send Ether toward the $1,780 support level in the near term.</p>
<p>Technical Indicators</p>
<p>Hourly MACD<strong> – </strong>The MACD for ETH/USD is losing momentum in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>Hourly RSI<strong> &#8211; </strong>The RSI for ETH/USD is now below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Level – $1,875</p>
<p>Major Resistance Level – $1,910</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/04/shutterstock_481530088-460x314.jpg" width="460" height="314" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Price Needs To Clear $30,500 For Hopes of a Fresh Rally</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-30500-fresh-rally/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 03:20:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xbtusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=543036</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin price is again moving lower toward the $29,200 level. BTC must surpass $30,500 to attempt a fresh increase in the near term. Bitcoin is showing bearish signs and trading well below the $30,500 zone. The price is trading below $30,300 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average. There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $30,200 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Kraken). The pair could continue to move down if it stays below the $30,500 resistance. Bitcoin Price Extends Decline Bitcoin price attempted a fresh increase above the $30,250 level but failed to gain bullish momentum. BTC stayed below the key $30,500 resistance zone. A high was formed near $30,447 before the price dropped below $30,000. It traded to a new weekly low at $29,669 and is currently correcting losses. It broke the 50% Fib retracement level of the recent decline from the $30,447 swing high to the $29,669 low. The price was able to climb above the $30,000 level. Bitcoin price is now trading below $30,300 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average. Immediate resistance is near the $30,200 level. There is also a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $30,200 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair. The trend line is near the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the recent decline from the $30,447 swing high to the $29,669 low. The first major resistance is near $30,265. The main resistance is now forming near the $30,450 and $30,500 levels. A close above the $30,500 level might start a fresh increase. Source: BTCUSD on TradingView.com The next major resistance is near the $30,850 level. Any more gains could open the doors for a move toward the $31,500 resistance zone. More Losses in BTC? If Bitcoin fails to clear the $30,500 resistance, it could continue to move down. Immediate support on the downside is near the $29,850 level. The next major support is near the $29,550 level, below which there could be a drop toward the $29,200 support zone. Any more losses might send the price toward the $28,750 level in the near term. Technical indicators: Hourly MACD – The MACD is now gaining pace in the bearish zone. Hourly RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BTC/USD is now near the 50 level. Major Support Levels – $29,850, followed by $29,200. Major Resistance Levels – $30,200, $30,265, and $30,500.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>Bitcoin price is again moving lower toward the $29,200 level. BTC must surpass $30,500 to attempt a fresh increase in the near term.</em></p>
<ul>
<li>Bitcoin is showing bearish signs and trading well below the $30,500 zone.</li>
<li>The price is trading below $30,300 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average.</li>
<li>There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $30,200 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could continue to move down if it stays below the $30,500 resistance.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Bitcoin Price Extends Decline</h2>
<p>Bitcoin price attempted a <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-aims-31k/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">fresh increase above the $30,250 level</a> but failed to gain bullish momentum. BTC stayed below the key $30,500 resistance zone.</p>
<p>A high was formed near $30,447 before the price dropped below $30,000. It traded to a new weekly low at $29,669 and is currently correcting losses. It broke the 50% Fib retracement level of the recent decline from the $30,447 swing high to the $29,669 low.</p>
<p>The price was able to climb above the $30,000 level. Bitcoin price is now trading below $30,300 and the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-attempts-to-follow-xrp/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">100 hourly Simple moving average</a>. Immediate resistance is near the $30,200 level.</p>
<p>There is also a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $30,200 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair. The trend line is near the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the recent decline from the $30,447 swing high to the $29,669 low.</p>
<p>The first major resistance is near $30,265. The main resistance is now forming near the $30,450 and $30,500 levels. A close above the $30,500 level might start a fresh increase.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-543037" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-11.png" alt="Bitcoin Price" width="1835" height="845" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-11.png 1835w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-11-460x212.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-11-860x396.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-11-768x354.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-11-1536x707.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-11-750x345.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-11-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1835px) 100vw, 1835px"/></p>
<p>Source: <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BTCUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">BTCUSD on TradingView.com</a></p>
<p>The next major resistance is near the $30,850 level. Any more gains could open the doors for a move toward the $31,500 resistance zone.</p>
<h2>More Losses in BTC?</h2>
<p>If Bitcoin fails to clear the $30,500 resistance, it could continue to move down. Immediate support on the downside is near the $29,850 level.</p>
<p>The next major support is near the $29,550 level, below which there could be a drop toward the $29,200 support zone. Any more losses might send the price toward the $28,750 level in the near term.</p>
<p>Technical indicators:</p>
<p>Hourly MACD – The MACD is now gaining pace in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>Hourly RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BTC/USD is now near the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Levels – $29,850, followed by $29,200.</p>
<p>Major Resistance Levels – $30,200, $30,265, and $30,500.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/shutterstock_1363186970-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
