<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"

	xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
	xmlns:geo="http://www.w3.org/2003/01/geo/wgs84_pos#"
	>

<channel>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.newsbtc.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<description>Bitcoin &#38; Cryptocurrency News Today</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:38:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-cropped-favicon.png?fit=32%2C32</url>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
<site xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">221170450</site>	<item>
		<title>Is Bitcoin Mispriced? Lessons From Past Volatility Slumps</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/is-bitcoin-mispriced-lessons-past-volatility-slumps/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jake Simmons]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:20:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin on-chain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[glassnode]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=546148</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Since its inception, Bitcoin has (almost) always been the poster child for volatility. Yet, the Bitcoin price is hardly moving in any direction at the moment. But the latest data suggests a surprising twist in the tale. As per a recent report by on-chain data provider Glassnode, &#8220;Bitcoin markets are experiencing an incredibly quiet patch, with several measures of volatility collapsing towards all-time lows.&#8221; This raises the question: Are we entering a new era of Bitcoin price stability, or is the market misreading the signs? Historical Context For The Volatility Of Bitcoin To truly understand the current state of the market, it&#8217;s essential to delve into the historical context. The Glassnode report notes, &#8220;It has been 842-days since the bull market peak was set in April 2021.&#8221; During this period, Bitcoin&#8217;s recovery has been more robust than in previous cycles, trading at -54% below its all-time high (ATH), compared to a historical average of -64%. Related Reading: Bitcoin Fate Hangs In The Balance, 50% Chance Of Falling Below $25,000 In September Drawing parallels with past cycles, the report highlights that both the 2015-16 and 2019-20 cycles underwent a &#8220;6-month period of sideways boredom before the market accelerated above the -54% drawdown level.&#8221; This could be indicative of a similar &#8220;boredom&#8221; phase in the current cycle. One of the most striking revelations from the Glassnode report is the extreme volatility compression Bitcoin is currently undergoing. &#8220;Bitcoin realized volatility ranging from 1-month to 1-year observation windows has fallen dramatically in 2023, reaching multi-year lows.&#8221; This is reminiscent of four distinct periods in Bitcoin&#8217;s history, including the late stage of the 2015 bear market and the post-March 2020 consolidation following the outbreak of COVID-19. Following the furious rally at the beginning to 2023, the price performance on both a quarterly and monthly basis has moderated. This mirrors Bitcoin’s previous cycles where the initial surge from the low is robust, but then transitions into a prolonged phase of uneven consolidation, a phase of re-accumulation. Furthermore, the report states, &#8220;The price range which separates the 7-day high and low is just 3.6%. Just 4.8% of all trading days have ever experienced a tighter weekly trade range.&#8221; The 30-day price range is even more extreme, constricting price to just a 9.8%, and with only 2.8% of all months in BTC&#8217;s history being tighter. Such levels of price compression are rare for Bitcoin, suggesting an anomaly or a potential precursor to a significant market move. Derivatives Market Insights The derivatives market, often seen as a barometer for underlying asset sentiment, is also echoing this quiet spell. &#8220;The combined Futures and Options trade volume for [BTC and ETH] are at, or approaching all-time-lows,&#8221; the report notes. This is further emphasized by the fact that &#8220;BTC is currently seeing $19.0B in aggregate derivatives trade volume, whilst ETH markets have just $9.2B/day.&#8221; Related Reading: Why Low Volatility Bitcoin Could Last A Lot Longer Interestingly, the options market is showing signs of a significant &#8220;volatility crush.&#8221; As per Glassnode, &#8220;Options are pricing in the smallest volatility premium in history, with IV between 24% and 52%, less than half of the long-term baseline.&#8221; This is further corroborated by the historically low Put/Call Ratio and the 25-delta skew metric, suggesting a net bullish sentiment in the market. The crux of the matter lies in interpreting these signs. The report aptly questions, &#8220;Given the context of Bitcoin&#8217;s infamous volatility, is a new era of BTC price stability upon us, or is volatility mispriced?&#8221; Historically, periods of low volatility in Bitcoin have often been followed by significant price movements. Whether this is a calm before a storm or a genuine shift towards a more stable Bitcoin remains to be seen. But as Tony &#8220;The Bull&#8221;, the chief chart technician at NewsBTC, has pointed out yesterday, the technical indicators are also pointing to a prolonged period of re-accumulation, meaning that the phase of low volatility is likely to continue for some time to come. At press time, the BTC price was at $29,277. Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Since its inception, Bitcoin has (almost) always been the poster child for volatility. Yet, the Bitcoin price is hardly moving in any direction at the moment. But the latest data suggests a surprising twist in the tale.</p>
<p>As per a recent <a href="https://insights.glassnode.com/the-week-onchain-week-32-2023/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">report</a> by on-chain data provider Glassnode, &#8220;Bitcoin markets are experiencing an incredibly quiet patch, with several measures of volatility collapsing towards all-time lows.&#8221; This raises the question: Are we entering a new era of Bitcoin price stability, or is the market misreading the signs?</p>
<h2>Historical Context For The Volatility Of Bitcoin</h2>
<p>To truly understand the current state of the market, it&#8217;s essential to delve into the historical context. The Glassnode report notes, &#8220;It has been 842-days since the bull market peak was set in April 2021.&#8221; During this period, Bitcoin&#8217;s recovery has been more robust than in previous cycles, trading at -54% below its all-time high (ATH), compared to a historical average of -64%.</p>

<p>Drawing parallels with past cycles, the report highlights that both the 2015-16 and 2019-20 cycles underwent a &#8220;6-month period of sideways boredom before the market accelerated above the -54% drawdown level.&#8221; This could be indicative of a similar &#8220;boredom&#8221; phase in the current cycle.</p>
<img decoding="async" class="wp-image-546158 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/03_cycleath.png?resize=2400%2C1382" alt="Bitcoin cycles" width="2400" height="1382" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/03_cycleath.png?resize=2400%2C1382?w=2400 2400w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/03_cycleath.png?resize=2400%2C1382?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/03_cycleath.png?resize=2400%2C1382?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/03_cycleath.png?resize=2400%2C1382?w=860 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/03_cycleath.png?resize=2400%2C1382?w=1536 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/03_cycleath.png?resize=2400%2C1382?w=2048 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/03_cycleath.png?resize=2400%2C1382?w=750 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/03_cycleath.png?resize=2400%2C1382?w=1140 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" loading="lazy" data-recalc-dims="1"/>
<p>One of the most striking revelations from the Glassnode report is the extreme volatility compression Bitcoin is currently undergoing. &#8220;Bitcoin realized volatility ranging from 1-month to 1-year observation windows has fallen dramatically in 2023, reaching multi-year lows.&#8221; This is reminiscent of four distinct periods in Bitcoin&#8217;s history, including the late stage of the 2015 bear market and the post-March 2020 consolidation following the outbreak of COVID-19.</p>
<p>Following the furious rally at the beginning to 2023, the price performance on both a quarterly and monthly basis has moderated. This mirrors Bitcoin’s previous cycles where the initial surge from the low is robust, but then transitions into a prolonged phase of uneven consolidation, a phase of re-accumulation.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-546157 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/04_quarterlyperformance.png?resize=2400%2C1382" alt="Bitcoin price performance" width="2400" height="1382" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/04_quarterlyperformance.png?resize=2400%2C1382?w=2400 2400w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/04_quarterlyperformance.png?resize=2400%2C1382?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/04_quarterlyperformance.png?resize=2400%2C1382?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/04_quarterlyperformance.png?resize=2400%2C1382?w=860 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/04_quarterlyperformance.png?resize=2400%2C1382?w=1536 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/04_quarterlyperformance.png?resize=2400%2C1382?w=2048 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/04_quarterlyperformance.png?resize=2400%2C1382?w=750 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/04_quarterlyperformance.png?resize=2400%2C1382?w=1140 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" data-recalc-dims="1"/>
<p>Furthermore, the report states, &#8220;The price range which separates the 7-day high and low is just 3.6%. Just 4.8% of all trading days have ever experienced a tighter weekly trade range.&#8221; The 30-day price range is even more extreme, constricting price to just a 9.8%, and with only 2.8% of all months in BTC&#8217;s history being tighter. Such levels of price compression are rare for Bitcoin, suggesting an anomaly or a potential precursor to a significant market move.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-546156 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/07_30dayrange.png?resize=2400%2C1382" alt="Bitcoin 30-day range" width="2400" height="1382" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/07_30dayrange.png?resize=2400%2C1382?w=2400 2400w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/07_30dayrange.png?resize=2400%2C1382?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/07_30dayrange.png?resize=2400%2C1382?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/07_30dayrange.png?resize=2400%2C1382?w=860 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/07_30dayrange.png?resize=2400%2C1382?w=1536 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/07_30dayrange.png?resize=2400%2C1382?w=2048 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/07_30dayrange.png?resize=2400%2C1382?w=750 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/07_30dayrange.png?resize=2400%2C1382?w=1140 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" data-recalc-dims="1"/>
<h2>Derivatives Market Insights</h2>
<p>The derivatives market, often seen as a barometer for underlying asset sentiment, is also echoing this quiet spell. &#8220;The combined Futures and Options trade volume for [BTC and ETH] are at, or approaching all-time-lows,&#8221; the report notes. This is further emphasized by the fact that &#8220;BTC is currently seeing $19.0B in aggregate derivatives trade volume, whilst ETH markets have just $9.2B/day.&#8221;</p>

<p>Interestingly, the options market is showing signs of a significant &#8220;volatility crush.&#8221; As per Glassnode, &#8220;Options are pricing in the smallest volatility premium in history, with IV between 24% and 52%, less than half of the long-term baseline.&#8221; This is further corroborated by the historically low Put/Call Ratio and the 25-delta skew metric, suggesting a net bullish sentiment in the market.</p>
<p>The crux of the matter lies in interpreting these signs. The report aptly questions, &#8220;Given the context of Bitcoin&#8217;s infamous volatility, is a new era of BTC price stability upon us, or is volatility mispriced?&#8221; Historically, periods of low volatility in Bitcoin have often been followed by significant price movements. Whether this is a calm before a storm or a genuine shift towards a more stable Bitcoin remains to be seen.</p>
<p>But as Tony &#8220;The Bull&#8221;, the chief chart technician at NewsBTC, has <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/why-low-volatility-bitcoin-could-last-a-lot-longer/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">pointed</a> out yesterday, the technical indicators are also pointing to a prolonged period of re-accumulation, meaning that the phase of low volatility is likely to continue for some time to come.</p>
<p>At press time, the BTC price was at $29,277.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-546161 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD_2023-08-08_08-30-15.png?resize=3628%2C1673" alt="Bitcoin price" width="3628" height="1673" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD_2023-08-08_08-30-15.png?resize=3628%2C1673?w=3628 3628w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD_2023-08-08_08-30-15.png?resize=3628%2C1673?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD_2023-08-08_08-30-15.png?resize=3628%2C1673?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD_2023-08-08_08-30-15.png?resize=3628%2C1673?w=860 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD_2023-08-08_08-30-15.png?resize=3628%2C1673?w=1536 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD_2023-08-08_08-30-15.png?resize=3628%2C1673?w=2048 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD_2023-08-08_08-30-15.png?resize=3628%2C1673?w=750 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD_2023-08-08_08-30-15.png?resize=3628%2C1673?w=1140 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD_2023-08-08_08-30-15.png?resize=3628%2C1673?w=3000 3000w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" data-recalc-dims="1"/>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/iStock-501851154.jpg?fit=460%2C270" width="460" height="270" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">546148</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Price Could Stage Steady Increase If It Clears This Hurdle</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-increase-29-5k/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:21:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xbtusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=546151</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin price is still facing strong resistance near $29,500. BTC is slowly moving higher and might start a steady increase above $29,500. Bitcoin is moving higher toward the $29,500 pivot level. The price is trading above $29,000 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average. There was a break above a key bearish trend line with resistance near $29,080 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Kraken). The pair could start a steady increase if there is a close above the $29,500 resistance zone. Bitcoin Price Eyes Fresh Increase Bitcoin price extended its decline below the $28,800 support zone. However, the downsides were limited below the $28,600 level. A low is formed near $28,628 and the price is now attempting a fresh increase. There was a move above the $28,900 and $29,000 levels. Besides, there was a break above a key bearish trend line with resistance near $29,080 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair. The pair is now trading above $29,000 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average. A high is formed near $29,280 and the price is now consolidating gains. Bitcoin is trading above the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $28,628 swing low to the $29,280 high. Source: BTCUSD on TradingView.com Immediate resistance is near the $29,300 zone. The first major resistance is near the $29,400 level. The next major resistance is near the $29,500 level. A close above the $29,500 resistance might start a steady increase. In the stated case, the price could test $30,000. Any more gains might open the doors for a move toward $31,200. Fresh Decline In BTC? If Bitcoin fails to clear the $29,400 resistance, it could start a fresh decline. Immediate support on the downside is near the $29,100 level the 100 hourly Simple moving average. The next major support is near the $28,800 level, below which the price could accelerate lower. The next support is near the $28,400 level. Any more losses might call for a move toward the $28,000 level in the near term. Technical indicators: Hourly MACD – The MACD is now gaining pace in the bullish zone. Hourly RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BTC/USD is now above the 50 level. Major Support Levels – $29,100, followed by $28,800. Major Resistance Levels – $29,300, $29,400, and $29,500.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>Bitcoin price is still facing strong resistance near $29,500. BTC is slowly moving higher and might start a steady increase above $29,500.</em></p>
<ul>
<li>Bitcoin is moving higher toward the $29,500 pivot level.</li>
<li>The price is trading above $29,000 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average.</li>
<li>There was a break above a key bearish trend line with resistance near $29,080 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could start a steady increase if there is a close above the $29,500 resistance zone.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Bitcoin Price Eyes Fresh Increase</h2>
<p>Bitcoin price <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-muted-29k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">extended its decline below the $28,800 support zone</a>. However, the downsides were limited below the $28,600 level. A low is formed near $28,628 and the price is now attempting a fresh increase.</p>
<p>There was a move above the $28,900 and $29,000 levels. Besides, there was a break above a key bearish trend line with resistance near $29,080 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair. The pair is now trading above $29,000 and the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-stuck-in-range-but-heres-why-bulls-are-safe/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">100 hourly Simple moving average</a>.</p>
<p>A high is formed near $29,280 and the price is now consolidating gains. Bitcoin is trading above the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $28,628 swing low to the $29,280 high.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-546152" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-2.png?resize=1024%2C465" alt="Bitcoin Price" width="1024" height="465" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-2.png?resize=1024%2C465?w=1950 1950w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-2.png?resize=1024%2C465?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-2.png?resize=1024%2C465?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-2.png?resize=1024%2C465?w=860 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-2.png?resize=1024%2C465?w=1536 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-2.png?resize=1024%2C465?w=750 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-2.png?resize=1024%2C465?w=1140 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" data-recalc-dims="1"/></p>
<p>Source: <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BTCUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">BTCUSD on TradingView.com</a></p>
<p>Immediate resistance is near the $29,300 zone. The first major resistance is near the $29,400 level. The next major resistance is near the $29,500 level. A close above the $29,500 resistance might start a steady increase. In the stated case, the price could test $30,000. Any more gains might open the doors for a move toward $31,200.</p>
<h2>Fresh Decline In BTC?</h2>
<p>If Bitcoin fails to clear the $29,400 resistance, it could start a fresh decline. Immediate support on the downside is near the $29,100 level the 100 hourly Simple moving average.</p>
<p>The next major support is near the $28,800 level, below which the price could accelerate lower. The next support is near the $28,400 level. Any more losses might call for a move toward the $28,000 level in the near term.</p>
<p>Technical indicators:</p>
<p>Hourly MACD – The MACD is now gaining pace in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>Hourly RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BTC/USD is now above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Levels – $29,100, followed by $28,800.</p>
<p>Major Resistance Levels – $29,300, $29,400, and $29,500.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/shutterstock_555674926.jpg?fit=460%2C313" width="460" height="313" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">546151</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Few Bitcoin Holders Withdrawing BTC From Exchanges, Is Fear Creeping In?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/few-bitcoin-holders-withdrawing-btc-exchanges-fear-creeping-in/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dalmas Ngetich]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 03:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=546113</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Recent data from CryptoQuant on August 7 shows that few Bitcoin holders are moving coins away from centralized cryptocurrency exchanges like Binance and Coinbase. Despite BTC prices increasing in recent weeks and teetering close to the $30,000 psychological level, this observation is accurate.  More Bitcoin Held in Exchanges As of July 28, there were 30,663 addresses withdrawing coins from exchanges though prices were relatively higher, trading around $28,000, up from around $25,000 registered on June 14 when 39,311 addresses moved coins. On April 14, when BTC changed hands at around $30,000, 132,237 addresses withdrew the coin from exchanges. The drop in the number of exchange addresses moving coins to external, often non-custodial wallets can be a concern, significantly if prices are rising.  The shift also raises important questions about why more Bitcoin holders opt to store coins in exchanges despite these ramps being targets by hackers. Usually, when fewer people transfer their Bitcoin to external, often non-custodial wallets, it might mean they&#8217;re unsure about the uptrend. As such, they keep their coins on exchanges to quickly sell for USDT or traditional currencies like USD or Euro if needed.  Optimism Abound Even with this change, the broader Bitcoin community remains positive about the coin&#8217;s potential in the coming months. This optimism comes partly from recent classifications from agencies like the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) and Commodity Futures Trade Commission (CFTC) that expressly endorse Bitcoin as a commodity subject to capital gains tax.  Related Reading: Solana Products See Strong Inflows, Bitcoin And Crypto Lose $107 Million Other digital assets like ETH have not been categorized as such, sowing doubts among some Ethereum holders that US regulators can classify the second most valuable coin as a security. Because of this positive outlook on the world&#8217;s most valuable coin, advanced derivatives, like BlackRock&#8217;s planned launch (if approved) of a spot Bitcoin Exchange-Traded Fund (ETF), are being developed. Complex Bitcoin trading products are already live in Canada and other parts of the world. Bloomberg Intelligence analysts say that the odds of a Bitcoin ETF getting approved by the SEC are 65%. The increase is partly due to bullish progress, including SEC Chair Gary Gensler&#8217;s comments on Bitcoin, the regulator&#8217;s reportedly insisting that BTC is the only commodity before Coinbase was sued, and the agency accepting re-filing from BlackRock&#8217;s ETF. Related Reading: XRP Journey To $10: Unveiling The Forces That Could Trigger An Upward Momentum While the upcoming halving of Bitcoin in 2024 could be good news, Bloomberg analysts argue that the expected upswing appears to be &#8220;priced in&#8221; based on &#8220;previous cycles.&#8221; Subsequently, analysts think BTC may rally to $50,000 by April 2024, looking at how prices have been performing in the recent few months.  Feature image from Canva, chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Recent data from CryptoQuant on August 7 <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptoquant.com/asset/btc/chart/exchange-flows/exchange-withdrawing-addresses?exchange=all_exchange&amp;window=DAY&amp;sma=0&amp;ema=0&amp;priceScale=log&amp;metricScale=linear&amp;chartStyle=line" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">shows</a> that few Bitcoin holders are moving coins away from centralized cryptocurrency exchanges like Binance and Coinbase. Despite BTC prices increasing in recent weeks and teetering close to the $30,000 psychological level, this observation is accurate. </p>
<h2>More Bitcoin Held in Exchanges</h2>
<p>As of July 28, there were 30,663 addresses withdrawing coins from exchanges though prices were relatively higher, trading around $28,000, up from around $25,000 registered on June 14 when 39,311 addresses moved coins. On April 14, when BTC changed hands at around $30,000, 132,237 addresses withdrew the coin from exchanges. </p>
<p>The drop in the number of exchange addresses moving coins to external, often non-custodial wallets can be a concern, significantly if prices are rising. </p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-546114" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-Exchange-Withdrawing-Addresses-All-Exchanges.png?resize=1024%2C645" alt="Bitcoin Exchange Withdrawing Addresses - All Exchanges| CryptoQuant" width="1024" height="645" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-Exchange-Withdrawing-Addresses-All-Exchanges.png?resize=1024%2C645?w=4287 4287w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-Exchange-Withdrawing-Addresses-All-Exchanges.png?resize=1024%2C645?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-Exchange-Withdrawing-Addresses-All-Exchanges.png?resize=1024%2C645?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-Exchange-Withdrawing-Addresses-All-Exchanges.png?resize=1024%2C645?w=860 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-Exchange-Withdrawing-Addresses-All-Exchanges.png?resize=1024%2C645?w=1536 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-Exchange-Withdrawing-Addresses-All-Exchanges.png?resize=1024%2C645?w=2048 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-Exchange-Withdrawing-Addresses-All-Exchanges.png?resize=1024%2C645?w=750 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-Exchange-Withdrawing-Addresses-All-Exchanges.png?resize=1024%2C645?w=1140 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-Exchange-Withdrawing-Addresses-All-Exchanges.png?resize=1024%2C645?w=3000 3000w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" data-recalc-dims="1"/>
<p>The shift also raises important questions about why more Bitcoin holders opt to store coins in exchanges despite these ramps being targets by hackers. Usually, when fewer people transfer their Bitcoin to external, often non-custodial wallets, it might mean they&#8217;re unsure about the uptrend. As such, they keep their coins on exchanges to quickly sell for USDT or traditional currencies like USD or Euro if needed. </p>
<h2>Optimism Abound</h2>
<p>Even with this change, the broader Bitcoin community remains positive about the coin&#8217;s potential in the coming months. This optimism comes partly from recent classifications from agencies like the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) and Commodity Futures Trade Commission (CFTC) that expressly endorse Bitcoin as a commodity subject to capital gains tax. </p>

<p>Other digital assets like ETH have not been categorized as such, sowing doubts among some Ethereum holders that US regulators can classify the second most valuable coin as a security. </p>
<p>Because of this positive outlook on the world&#8217;s most valuable coin, advanced derivatives, like BlackRock&#8217;s planned launch (if approved) of a spot Bitcoin Exchange-Traded Fund (ETF), are being developed. Complex Bitcoin trading products are already live in Canada and other parts of the world.</p>
<p>Bloomberg Intelligence analysts say that the <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-spot-etf-odds-65-bloomberg-analysts/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">odds</a> of a Bitcoin ETF getting approved by the SEC are 65%. The increase is partly due to bullish progress, including SEC Chair Gary Gensler&#8217;s comments on Bitcoin, the regulator&#8217;s reportedly insisting that BTC is the only commodity before Coinbase was sued, and the agency accepting re-filing from BlackRock&#8217;s ETF.</p>

<p>While the upcoming halving of Bitcoin in 2024 could be good news, Bloomberg analysts argue that the expected upswing appears to be &#8220;priced in&#8221; <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-04-23/bitcoin-btc-halving-in-2024-spurs-predictions-of-rally-past-50-000" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">based</a> on &#8220;previous cycles.&#8221; Subsequently, analysts think BTC may rally to $50,000 by April 2024, looking at how prices have been performing in the recent few months. </p>
<a href="https://www.tradingview.com/x/6W4R30Kp/" rel="nofollow"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/6W4R30Kp/" alt="BTC price on August 7 as few Bitcoin holders move coins from exchanges| Source: BTCUSDT on Binance, TradingView" width="1226" height="595"/></a>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-Few-BTC-Holders-Moving-Coins-From-Exchanges.jpg?fit=460%2C260" width="460" height="260" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">546113</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Fate Hangs In The Balance, 50% Chance Of Falling Below $25,000 In September</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-fate-hangs-in-the-balance-50-chance-of-falling-below-25000-in-september/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 02:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=546120</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) has been no stranger to dramatic price swings in the volatile cryptocurrency world. As September approaches, market analysts closely monitor BTC&#8217;s possibility of plunging below the $25,000 mark.  However, history has shown that September&#8217;s struggles often pave the way for a resurgence in October, with massive rallies that rekindle investor optimism.  Potential For BTC To Drop Below $25,000 Before A Promising October When examining Bitcoin&#8217;s historical performance during September, it becomes evident that the month has posed challenges for the world&#8217;s most renowned cryptocurrency.  Related Reading: BREAKING: Did Solana Miss A Golden Opportunity To Collaborate With PayPal’s PYUSD Stablecoin? Previous September has witnessed BTC experiencing declines of up to 13%. This downward trend has undoubtedly concerned traders and investors, raising questions about the sustainability of Bitcoin&#8217;s bullish momentum. According to Timothy Peterson, market analyst and investment Manager, based on current market analysis, there is a 50% probability that Bitcoin&#8217;s price will dip below the $25,000 threshold before September concludes.  While a potential drop below $25,000 might cause temporary unease among Bitcoin enthusiasts, historical patterns suggest that October could be the month to look forward to.  In the past, September&#8217;s price declines have often catalyzed significant rallies in the subsequent month. Observing the heatmap above, Peterson identified instances where Bitcoin rebounded with gains as high as 48% following sharp declines in September. If Bitcoin does indeed experience a dip below $25,000 in September, it may mark the final significant correction before the commencement of a new bull run cycle.  On this note, Peterson believes that such a dip, coupled with the subsequent recovery and October&#8217;s potential rally, could set the stage for substantial gains in the coming months. Bitcoin Bullish Divergence As BTC experienced a drop from $32,000 to $29,000, trader Ali Martinez highlighted a significant trend; the number of new Bitcoin addresses continued to rise steadily.  Related Reading: Ripple Is Now A Member Of Trade Organization That Hosts The Likes Of BlackRock This intriguing divergence between price and network growth provides insights into BTC&#8217;s potentially stable long-term uptrend.  While Bitcoin&#8217;s price exhibited a downward trajectory, the number of newly created Bitcoin addresses has consistently grown.  This divergence is noteworthy, suggesting that despite short-term price fluctuations, the network&#8217;s expansion remains robust. It signifies a growing interest in Bitcoin adoption and usage, which, in turn, supports the notion of a stable and sustainable long-term uptrend. Conversely, Bitcoin remains trapped within a price range of $29,200 and $28,900, a pattern that has persisted since the start of August. As of the time of writing, BTC is trading at $28,960, reflecting a 0.5% decrease in the last 24 hours. Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin (BTC) has been no stranger to dramatic price swings in the volatile cryptocurrency world. As September approaches, market analysts closely monitor BTC&#8217;s possibility of plunging below the $25,000 mark. </p>
<p>However, history has shown that September&#8217;s struggles often pave the way for a resurgence in October, with massive rallies that rekindle investor optimism. </p>
<h2>Potential For BTC To Drop Below $25,000 Before A Promising October</h2>
<p>When examining Bitcoin&#8217;s historical performance during September, it becomes evident that the month has posed challenges for the world&#8217;s most renowned cryptocurrency. </p>

<p>Previous September has witnessed BTC experiencing declines of up to 13%. This downward trend has undoubtedly concerned traders and investors, raising questions about the sustainability of Bitcoin&#8217;s bullish momentum.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-546125 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F24krh4X0AEBMJ4.jpg?w=860&#038;resize=860%2C653" alt="Bitcoin " width="860" height="653" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F24krh4X0AEBMJ4.jpg?w=1195 1195w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F24krh4X0AEBMJ4.jpg?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F24krh4X0AEBMJ4.jpg?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F24krh4X0AEBMJ4.jpg?w=860&#038;resize=860%2C653 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F24krh4X0AEBMJ4.jpg?w=750 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F24krh4X0AEBMJ4.jpg?w=1140 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" data-recalc-dims="1"/>
<p><a href="https://twitter.com/nsquaredcrypto/status/1688328067255840768?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">According </a>to Timothy Peterson, market analyst and investment Manager, based on current market analysis, there is a 50% probability that Bitcoin&#8217;s price will dip below the $25,000 threshold before September concludes. </p>
<p>While a potential drop below $25,000 might cause temporary unease among Bitcoin enthusiasts, historical patterns suggest that October could be the month to look forward to. </p>
<p>In the past, September&#8217;s price declines have often catalyzed significant rallies in the subsequent month. Observing the heatmap above, Peterson identified instances where Bitcoin rebounded with gains as high as 48% following sharp declines in September.</p>
<p>If Bitcoin does indeed experience a dip below $25,000 in September, it may mark the final significant correction before the commencement of a new bull run cycle. </p>
<p>On this note, Peterson believes that such a dip, coupled with the subsequent recovery and October&#8217;s potential rally, could set the stage for substantial gains in the coming months.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Bullish Divergence</h2>
<p>As BTC experienced a drop from $32,000 to $29,000, trader Ali Martinez <a href="https://twitter.com/ali_charts/status/1688441865832386560?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">highlighted </a>a significant trend; the number of new Bitcoin addresses continued to rise steadily. </p>

<p>This intriguing divergence between price and network growth provides insights into BTC&#8217;s potentially stable long-term uptrend. </p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-546124 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F26LxOyWMAA6HX1.jpg?w=860&#038;resize=860%2C484" alt="Bitcoin " width="860" height="484" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F26LxOyWMAA6HX1.jpg?w=1800 1800w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F26LxOyWMAA6HX1.jpg?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F26LxOyWMAA6HX1.jpg?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F26LxOyWMAA6HX1.jpg?w=860&#038;resize=860%2C484 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F26LxOyWMAA6HX1.jpg?w=1536 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F26LxOyWMAA6HX1.jpg?w=750 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F26LxOyWMAA6HX1.jpg?w=1140 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" data-recalc-dims="1"/>
<p>While Bitcoin&#8217;s price exhibited a downward trajectory, the number of newly created Bitcoin addresses has consistently grown. </p>
<p>This divergence is noteworthy, suggesting that despite short-term price fluctuations, the network&#8217;s expansion remains robust. It signifies a growing interest in Bitcoin adoption and usage, which, in turn, supports the notion of a stable and sustainable long-term uptrend.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/07HUytHc/" alt="Bitcoin " width="1814" height="858"/>
<p>Conversely, Bitcoin remains trapped within a price range of $29,200 and $28,900, a pattern that has persisted since the start of August. As of the time of writing, BTC is trading at $28,960, reflecting a 0.5% decrease in the last 24 hours.</p>
<p>Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/iStock-1393470258.jpg?fit=460%2C164" width="460" height="164" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">546120</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>YGG Surged 580% Before Crashing, Why Are Whales Rapidly Selling?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/ygg-surged-580-before-crashing-whales-selling/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dalmas Ngetich]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 01:00:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Axie Infinity]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AXS]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[venture capitals]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[YGG]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Yield Guild Games]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=546103</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Yield Guild Games (YGG) token recently surged, rising by 580% in less than a week before crashing, as visible in the daily chart. YGG is currently changing hands at $0.37 with a market capitalization of over $101 million when writing on August 7.  Prices have since retraced from the $0.99 recorded earlier today as the token fell by over 60%. The recent spike and general volatility have seen trading volumes soar as trading activity is concentrated on Binance and KuCoin. YGG Whales Dumping Amidst the notable growth, there are reports of venture capital (VC) companies that initially backed the project, backing off and reportedly selling the token primarily on Binance. For instance, Lookonchain data on August 7 shows that Bitkraft Ventures and DWF Labs have moved their YGG to Binance and will likely sell.  Last year, DWF Labs received 29.13 million YGG from Yield Guild Games Treasury. However, on-chain data shows that most of these tokens have since been moved to exchanges.  Related Reading: Shiba Inu Sees 10% Pullback, But Here’s Why Rally Can Still Continue Bitkraft used Wintermute and FalconX to move coins to Binance. Trackers show that the official Wintermute Trading wallet has deposited 11.1 million YGG to exchanges over the past four days. The crypto market maker still holds 2.5 million YGG.  Youbi Capital has also deposited 1 million YGG to Binance. Currently, it holds 11.6 million YGG. Sfermion is also joining the selling bandwagon, which initially claimed 1.2 million YGG. It used FalconX, a provider serving crypto whales, to deposit the token to Binance. Partnership With Axie Infinity Developer Yield Guild Games is a gaming guild primarily focusing on play-to-earn (P2E) blockchain games. As a community, the platform uses non-fungible tokens (NFTs) and has created a collaborative network of players and investors to navigate NFT gaming.  In mid-July, YGG partnered with Axie Infinity&#8217;s developer to release SUPERQUESTS. The feature, Yield Guild Games said, aims to enable guild members to engage in web3 games and earn enhanced in-game rewards. They added that this initiative was a significant step towards improving the web3 gaming experience for members.   Related Reading: Ripple Is Now A Member Of Trade Organization That Hosts The Likes Of BlackRock Over the months, NFT, metaverse, and blockchain gaming activity have rapidly contracted as token asset prices fell throughout 2022. Furthermore, fears of regulatory crackdown appear to be discouraging developers. In June, the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) cited AXS by Axie Infinity as an example of unregistered security. Feature image from Canva, chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Yield Guild Games (YGG) token recently surged, rising by 580% in less than a week before crashing, as visible in the daily chart. YGG is currently changing hands at $0.37 with a market capitalization of over $101 million when writing on August 7. </p>
<p>Prices have since retraced from the $0.99 recorded earlier today as the token fell by over 60%. The recent spike and general volatility have seen trading volumes soar as trading activity is <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/yield-guild-games/#Markets" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">concentrated</a> on Binance and KuCoin.</p>
<h2>YGG Whales Dumping</h2>
<p>Amidst the notable growth, there are reports of venture capital (VC) companies that initially backed the project, backing off and reportedly selling the token primarily on Binance. For instance, Lookonchain data on August 7 shows that Bitkraft Ventures and DWF Labs have moved their YGG to Binance and will likely sell. </p>
<p>Last year, DWF Labs <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://twitter.com/lookonchain/status/1688200366402498560" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">received</a> 29.13 million YGG from Yield Guild Games Treasury. However, on-chain data shows that most of these tokens have since been moved to exchanges. </p>

<p>Bitkraft used Wintermute and FalconX to move coins to Binance. Trackers show that the official Wintermute Trading wallet has <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://twitter.com/lookonchain/status/1688169792417763328" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">deposited</a> 11.1 million YGG to exchanges over the past four days. The crypto market maker still holds 2.5 million YGG. </p>
<a href="https://www.tradingview.com/x/Mj1MKR1j/" rel="nofollow"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/Mj1MKR1j/" alt="YGG price on august 7| Source: YGGUSDT on Binance, TradingView" width="1226" height="595"/></a>
<p>Youbi Capital has also <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://twitter.com/lookonchain/status/1688380666755665920" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">deposited</a> 1 million YGG to Binance. Currently, it holds 11.6 million YGG. Sfermion is also joining the selling bandwagon, which initially claimed 1.2 million YGG. It used FalconX, a provider serving crypto whales, to deposit the token to Binance.</p>
<h2>Partnership With Axie Infinity Developer</h2>
<p>Yield Guild Games is a gaming guild primarily focusing on play-to-earn (P2E) blockchain games. As a community, the platform uses non-fungible tokens (NFTs) and has created a collaborative network of players and investors to navigate NFT gaming. </p>
<p>In mid-July, YGG <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://medium.com/yield-guild-games/ygg-launches-first-superquest-with-axie-infinity-8425b3911a02" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">partnered</a> with Axie Infinity&#8217;s developer to release SUPERQUESTS. The feature, Yield Guild Games said, aims to enable guild members to engage in web3 games and earn enhanced in-game rewards. They added that this initiative was a significant step towards improving the web3 gaming experience for members.  </p>

<p>Over the months, NFT, metaverse, and blockchain gaming activity have rapidly contracted as token asset prices fell throughout 2022. Furthermore, fears of regulatory crackdown appear to be discouraging developers. In June, the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) cited AXS by Axie Infinity as an example of unregistered security.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/YGG-Binance-Crypto-Whales.jpg?fit=460%2C260" width="460" height="260" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">546103</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Litecoin Hashrate Taps New All-Time High, Will LTC Price Follow Suit?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/litecoin/litecoin-hashrate-taps-new-all-time-high-will-ltc-price-follow-suit/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Best Owie]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 23:00:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Litecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Litecoin Halving]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Litecoin hashrate]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Litecoin mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ltc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ltc/usd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LTCUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=546087</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Litecoin hashrate has been going up steadily over the last year. This was mainly driven by the anticipation leading up to the Litecoin halving that was slated to take place in August. Now that the halving event has come and gone, the hashrate has risen to a new all-time high, but the question is, whether the price of LTC will follow suit. Litecoin Hashrate Taps New ATH Of 1.03 PH/s The steady rise in the Litecoin hashrate is a testament to the growing interest in the network. The hashrate points to the fact that there are more miners on the blockchain trying to guess the correct answers to each block. And this translates to better security overall for the Litecoin network. Related Reading: Ethereum Price Could Break Above $2,000 If This Happens Interestingly, this increase in hashrate has seen the network hit not only a new all-time high but a significant milestone. According to data from CoinWarz, the Litecoin hashrate rose as high as 1.03 pentahashes per second (PH/s) on August 4. This means that for the first time, LTC’s hashrate has left the terahashes per second (TH/s) territory and crossed into the pentahashes per second (PH/s) territory. Although it is still a long way from Bitcoin’s exahashes per second (EH/s), it is a testament to how much the Litecoin network has grown. The Litecoin hashrate has since retraced back into the TH/s territory, now sitting at 739.88 TH/s as of Monday, August 7. But a look over the last year’s hashrate chart shows that even this is a high level for the blockchain’s hashrate. LTC hashrate remains high compared to 2022 &#124; Source: CoinWarz Will LTC’s Price Follow The Hashrate? Since the Litecoin hashrate hit its new all-time high, the price of LTC has been more volatile than normal. This is not out of the ordinary though as the altcoin has been following the general market trend and LTC’s is a testament to that trend. So far though, it doesn’t seem like LTC has made any effort to break out of this trend. If anything, it has suffered more declines than recoveries, even dipping to as low as $$80.65 on August 4. This decline shows that the new hashrate ATH has not moved investors to invest more in the coin. Related Reading: Bitcoin Investor Sentiment Flips Toward Greed Despite Fall Below $29,000 For now, something that could lead to an uptrend for Litecoin’s price is if Bitcoin begins another rally and the crypto market starts to see improved sentiment. Otherwise, LTC will likely continue to toe the $82 line for the better part of the week. At the time of writing, LTC price is trading at $82.80, down 0.47% in the last day and 11.67% in the last week. LTC price trending at $82.42 &#124; Source: LTCUSD on Tradingview.com Follow Best Owie on Twitter for market insights, updates, and the occasional funny tweet… Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="p2">The Litecoin hashrate has been going up steadily over the last year. This was mainly driven by the anticipation leading up to the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/ltc/litecoin-sharks-buy-more-200000-ltc/">Litecoin halving</a> that was slated to take place in August. Now that the halving event has come and gone, the hashrate has risen to a new all-time high, but the question is, whether the price of LTC will follow suit.</p>
<h2 class="p2">Litecoin Hashrate Taps New ATH Of 1.03 PH/s</h2>
<p class="p2">The steady rise in the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/litecoin/litecoin-bull-case-grows-stronger-as-hashrate-touches-new-all-time-high/">Litecoin hashrate</a> is a testament to the growing interest in the network. The hashrate points to the fact that there are more miners on the blockchain trying to guess the correct answers to each block. And this translates to better security overall for the Litecoin network.</p>

<p class="p2">Interestingly, this increase in hashrate has seen the network hit not only a new all-time high but a significant milestone. According to data from <a href="https://www.coinwarz.com/mining/litecoin/hashrate-chart" rel="nofollow">CoinWarz</a>, the Litecoin hashrate rose as high as 1.03 pentahashes per second (PH/s) on August 4.</p>
<p class="p2">This means that for the first time, LTC’s hashrate has left the terahashes per second (TH/s) territory and crossed into the pentahashes per second (PH/s) territory. Although it is still a long way from Bitcoin’s exahashes per second (EH/s), it is a testament to how much the Litecoin network has grown.</p>
<p class="p2">The Litecoin hashrate has since retraced back into the TH/s territory, now sitting at 739.88 TH/s as of Monday, August 7. But a look over the last year’s hashrate chart shows that even this is a high level for the blockchain’s hashrate.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-546089 aligncenter" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot-2023-08-07-at-15.04.00.png?w=460&#038;resize=460%2C247" alt="Litecoin hashrate" width="460" height="247" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot-2023-08-07-at-15.04.00.png?w=2216 2216w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot-2023-08-07-at-15.04.00.png?w=460&#038;resize=460%2C247 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot-2023-08-07-at-15.04.00.png?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot-2023-08-07-at-15.04.00.png?w=860 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot-2023-08-07-at-15.04.00.png?w=1536 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot-2023-08-07-at-15.04.00.png?w=2048 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot-2023-08-07-at-15.04.00.png?w=750 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot-2023-08-07-at-15.04.00.png?w=1140 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px" data-recalc-dims="1"/></p>

<h2 class="p2">Will LTC’s Price Follow The Hashrate?</h2>
<p class="p2">Since the Litecoin hashrate hit its new all-time high, the price of LTC has been more volatile than normal. This is not out of the ordinary though as the altcoin has been following the general market trend and LTC’s is a testament to that trend.</p>
<p class="p2">So far though, it doesn’t seem like LTC has made any effort to break out of this trend. If anything, it has suffered more declines than recoveries, even dipping to as low as $$80.65 on August 4. This decline shows that the new hashrate ATH has not moved investors to invest more in the coin.</p>

<p class="p2">For now, something that could lead to an uptrend for Litecoin’s price is if Bitcoin begins another rally and the crypto market starts to see improved sentiment. Otherwise, LTC will likely continue to toe the $82 line for the better part of the week.</p>
<p class="p2">At the time of writing, LTC price is trading at $82.80, <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/litecoin/litecoin-completes-halving-but-price-plunges-6/">down 0.47% in the last day and 11.67% in the last week</a>.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/ps8GvDwh/" alt="Litecoin (LTC) price chart from Tradingview.com" width="2884" height="1746"/></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/iStock-1385861333.jpg?fit=460%2C248" width="460" height="248" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">546087</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Why Low Volatility Bitcoin Could Last A Lot Longer</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/why-low-volatility-bitcoin-could-last-a-lot-longer/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tony "The Bull"]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 22:26:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bollinger bands]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=546137</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Much has been said in recent weeks regarding how uncharacteristically calm Bitcoin has been. On weekly timeframes, volatility measures are at their lowest ever. Unfortunately, despite the record-setting lull, directionless sideways price action could continue for a lot longer. Record-Breaking Low Volatility State Could Continue Longer Bitcoin price is at a standstill compared to its usually explosive self. It’s remained locked in a tight trading range, to the point where even a $300 move to either side might feel like a major breakout. Related Reading: Crypto Storm Brewing: Bitcoin Vortex Indicator Flashes Buy Alert Few points throughout history on lower timeframes have ever been this quiet. This is according to the weekly Bollinger Bands and Bollinger Band Width readings. Extreme tightening in the Bollinger Bands suggests what’s a called a Squeeze setup — a situation where following a low volatility phase of narrowing, the bands then expand and release a wave of volatility. It could be a lot longer until that happens, however. The monthly bands might need further tightening &#124; BTCUSD on TradingView.com Examining Monthly Bollinger Band Width While the weekly is at record tightness, using the very same tool on the monthly timeframe, shows that that there could be a lot further to go. The Bollinger Band Width isn’t as low as it has been prior to past bull runs — notably to the lows of early 2016 and late 2020. This could suggest the possibility of months more sideways before a meaningful breakout to new all-time highs or a collapse back to lows. Related Reading: This Long-Term Bitcoin Price Average Is Setting ATHs None of this says much about direction thus far, but %B might hint at a move to the upside. The tool is plotted depending on price’s percentage relation to the upper, middle, and lower Bollinger Bands. As long as %B remains above 0.5 it means price is above the Bollinger Band basis — which is a 20-month simple moving average Although we don’t know which direction Bitcoin ultimately moves, we do know that one thing is for certain: volatility will return in a major way. It’s just a matter of when, and how long we have to wait. The #Bitcoin 1W Bollinger Bands have been the &#34;tightest in its history&#34; for several weeks nowhttps://t.co/1Oux6TB537 But there is a lot more going on if you turn on Bollinger Band Width and %B – two ancillary technical tools related to the BB itself John Bollinger created the… pic.twitter.com/iGVwoBPWrg &#8212; Tony &#34;The Bull&#34; (@tonythebullBTC) August 7, 2023 Tony is the author of the CoinChartist (VIP) newsletter. Sign up for free. Follow @TonyTheBullBTC &#38; @coinchartist_io on Twitter. Or join the TonyTradesBTC Telegram for daily market insights and technical analysis education. Please note: Content is educational and should not be considered investment advice. Featured image from iStockPhoto, Charts from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Much has been said in recent weeks regarding how uncharacteristically calm Bitcoin has been. On weekly timeframes, volatility measures are at their lowest ever.</p>
<p>Unfortunately, despite the record-setting lull, directionless sideways price action could continue for a lot longer.</p>
<h2>Record-Breaking Low Volatility State Could Continue Longer</h2>
<p>Bitcoin price is at a standstill compared to its usually explosive self. It’s remained locked in a tight trading range, to the point where even a $300 move to either side might feel like a major breakout.</p>

<p>Few points throughout history on lower timeframes have ever been this quiet. This is according to the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-bollinger-bands-are-the-tightest-ever-what-happens-next/">weekly Bollinger Bands and Bollinger Band Width readings</a>.</p>
<p>Extreme tightening in the Bollinger Bands suggests what’s a called a Squeeze setup — a situation where following a low volatility phase of narrowing, the bands then expand and release a wave of volatility. It could be a lot longer until that happens, however.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large wp-image-546138 aligncenter" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/IMG_5139.png?w=860&#038;resize=860%2C535" alt="Bitcoin low volatility " width="860" height="535" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/IMG_5139.png?w=2428 2428w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/IMG_5139.png?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/IMG_5139.png?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/IMG_5139.png?w=860&#038;resize=860%2C535 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/IMG_5139.png?w=1536 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/IMG_5139.png?w=2048 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/IMG_5139.png?w=750 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/IMG_5139.png?w=1140 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" data-recalc-dims="1"/></p>

<h2>Examining Monthly Bollinger Band Width</h2>
<p>While the weekly is at record tightness, using the very same tool on the monthly timeframe, shows that that there could be a lot further to go.</p>
<p>The Bollinger Band Width isn’t as low as it has been prior to past bull runs — notably to the lows of early 2016 and late 2020. This could suggest the possibility of months more sideways before a meaningful breakout to new all-time highs or a collapse back to lows.</p>

<p>None of this says much about direction thus far, but %B might hint at a move to the upside. The tool is plotted depending on price’s percentage relation to the upper, middle, and lower Bollinger Bands. As long as %B remains above 0.5 it means price is above the Bollinger Band basis — which is a 20-month simple moving average</p>
<p>Although we don’t know which direction Bitcoin ultimately moves, we do know that one thing is for certain: volatility will return in a major way. It’s just a matter of when, and how long we have to wait.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">The <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Bitcoin?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#Bitcoin</a> 1W Bollinger Bands have been the &quot;tightest in its history&quot; for several weeks now<a href="https://t.co/1Oux6TB537" rel="nofollow">https://t.co/1Oux6TB537</a></p>
<p>But there is a lot more going on if you turn on Bollinger Band Width and %B – two ancillary technical tools related to the BB itself</p>
<p>John Bollinger created the… <a href="https://t.co/iGVwoBPWrg" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/iGVwoBPWrg</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Tony &quot;The Bull&quot; (@tonythebullBTC) <a href="https://twitter.com/tonythebullBTC/status/1688529963979313152?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">August 7, 2023</a></p></blockquote>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/IMG_5142.jpeg?fit=460%2C307" width="460" height="307" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">546137</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>TRON’s Justin Sun Reassures Crypto Community That Huobi Exchange Is Solvent</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/huobi-ht/justin-sun-huobi-exchange-is-solvent/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 22:00:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Huobi (HT)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[huobi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Huobi global. Huobi exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Justin Sun]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tron founder]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=546100</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[In a recent development, Justin Sun, founder of popular blockchain Tron, has urged people to disregard speculations that the crypto exchange Huobi is facing severe challenges following news of the alleged detention of some of the platform&#8217;s officials.  The rumors appear to be a major contributing factor to why the firm experienced multi-million withdrawals during the weekend, while Tron’s Total Value Locked (TVL) has fallen below $2.5 billion.  Trouble In Paradise? Over the past weekend, cryptocurrency exchange Huobi experienced massive outflows worth about $64 million amid reports that Chinese authorities were investigating its executives and the likelihood of insolvency. There were speculations that the platform’s leaders were arrested on the 5th of August in China. According to popular Chinese reporter Colin Wu, the arrest was due to Huobi’s involvement with gambling websites. One top official of the exchange also recently left the company, though it remains unclear if that was connected to the ongoing investigations by Chinese authorities. Related Reading: XRP Whales Trigger Price Decline With Large Selling A third of the $64 million is believed to be made up of Bitcoin (BTC), while Tron’s native token (TRX) and Huobi Token (HT) follow respectively at 26.5% and 20.3%. The rumors were so rife that the withdrawals triggered serious volatility in HT’s price and the token fluctuated during the weekend before settling at its present level of about $2.66. Furthermore, there are also rumors that the exchange is undergoing protracted financial challenges. According to Adam Cochran, an angel investor and fintech executive, there are some discrepancies in the platform’s Tether (USDT) holding.  Based on on-chain data, Huobi held less than $90 million of assets on the 5th of August. However, their recent “Merkle Tree Audit” claims they hold $630 million in USDT.  Cochran believes this means that Huobi might be insolvent, implying the platform may not have sufficient funds to meet its obligations. HT price sitting at $2.6 &#124; Source: HTUSD on Tradingview.com Huobi Reacts To Speculations In response to the speculations, Justin Sun, who serves as an Advisor to the exchange, recently took to his Twitter account to offer some clarifications. In a series of tweets, he asked users to “ignore FUD, keep! #TRON  and Huobi will thrive through continuous development. Trust in our vision and community efforts for a stronger future. Perseverance guarantees success!” Related Reading: Curve Finance Announces $1.85 Million Bounty For Stable Pool Exploiter Many users simply responded by posting the figure “4” below his tweet. The figure, which was popularized in the crypto space by Changpeng ‘CZ’ Zhao, Binance CEO, simply means “Ignore FUD, fake news, attacks, etc.”  This is not the first time Sun and his team are facing serious troubles. In the past, there have been rumors of financial troubles at the exchange. However, it remains to be seen what the likely fallout would be in the most recent event. Featured image from Coinpedia, chart from Tradingview.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In a recent development, Justin Sun, founder of popular blockchain Tron, has urged people to disregard speculations that the crypto exchange Huobi is facing severe challenges following news of the alleged detention of some of the platform&#8217;s officials. </p>
<p>The rumors appear to be a major contributing factor to why the firm experienced multi-million withdrawals during the weekend, while Tron’s Total Value Locked (TVL) has <a href="https://defillama.com/cex/huobi?usdInflows=true&amp;tvl=true" rel="nofollow">fallen</a> below $2.5 billion. </p>
<h2>Trouble In Paradise?</h2>
<p>Over the past weekend, cryptocurrency exchange Huobi experienced massive outflows worth about $64 million amid reports that Chinese authorities were investigating its executives and the likelihood of insolvency.</p>
<p>There were speculations that the platform’s leaders were arrested on the 5th of August in China. According to popular Chinese <a href="https://twitter.com/WuBlockchain/status/1687764670340591618" rel="nofollow">reporter</a> Colin Wu, the arrest was due to Huobi’s involvement with gambling websites. One top official of the exchange also recently left the company, though it remains unclear if that was connected to the ongoing investigations by Chinese authorities.</p>

<p>A third of the $64 million is believed to be made up of Bitcoin (BTC), while Tron’s native token (TRX) and Huobi Token (HT) follow respectively at 26.5% and 20.3%. The rumors were so rife that the withdrawals triggered serious volatility in HT’s price and the token fluctuated during the weekend before settling at its present level of about $2.66.</p>
<p>Furthermore, there are also rumors that the exchange is undergoing protracted financial challenges. According to Adam Cochran, an angel investor and fintech executive, there are some <a href="https://twitter.com/adamscochran/status/1687959096316542976" rel="nofollow">discrepancies</a> in the platform’s Tether (USDT) holding. </p>
<p>Based on on-chain data, Huobi held less than $90 million of assets on the 5th of August. However, their recent “Merkle Tree Audit” claims they hold $630 million in USDT. </p>
<p>Cochran believes this means that<a href="https://bitcoinist.com/huobi-insolvency-exec-arrests-crypto-storm/" rel="nofollow"> Huobi might be insolvent</a>, implying the platform may not have sufficient funds to meet its obligations.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/ZwHznG89/" alt="Huobi Token (HT) price chart from Tradingview.com" width="2884" height="1746"/></p>

<h2>Huobi Reacts To Speculations</h2>
<p>In response to the speculations, Justin Sun, who serves as an Advisor to the exchange, recently took to his <a href="https://twitter.com/justinsuntron/status/1688396464417120256" rel="nofollow">Twitter</a> account to offer some clarifications. In a series of tweets, he asked users to “ignore FUD, keep! #TRON  and Huobi will thrive through continuous development. Trust in our vision and community efforts for a stronger future. Perseverance guarantees success!”</p>

<p>Many users simply responded by posting the figure “4” below his tweet. The figure, which was <a href="https://twitter.com/cz_binance/status/1610018096122851328?s=20" rel="nofollow">popularized</a> in the crypto space by Changpeng ‘CZ’ Zhao, Binance CEO, simply means “Ignore FUD, fake news, attacks, etc.” </p>
<p>This is not the first time Sun and his team are facing serious troubles. In the <a href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/doubts-mount-over-huobi-s-future-as-harsh-layoff-rumors-denied" rel="nofollow">past</a>, there have been rumors of financial troubles at the exchange. However, it remains to be seen what the likely fallout would be in the most recent event.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Justin-Sun-Huobi-exchange.png?fit=460%2C242" width="460" height="242" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">546100</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>These Bitcoin Metrics Are At Important Retests, Will Bullish Trend Prevail?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-metrics-important-retests-bullish-trend-prevail/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hououin Kyouma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 21:00:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Bullish Trend]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Retest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=546067</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[On-chain data shows two Bitcoin indicators are currently retesting levels that have historically been relevant for the market&#8217;s course. Bitcoin NUPL For Both Short-Term &#38; Mid-Term Holders Is Neutral Currently As pointed out by an analyst in a CryptoQuant post, the BTC NUPL has been retesting crucial levels recently. The &#8220;Net Unrealized Profit/Loss&#8221; (NUPL) is a metric that keeps track of the net amount of profit or loss that investors are holding currently. This indicator works by looking through the on-chain history of each coin in circulation to see what price it was last moved at. If this previous transfer price for any coin was less than the current spot price of Bitcoin, then that particular coin is holding a profit right now. The NUPL counts this profit that the coin is holding in the unrealized profit. Similarly, the loss that underwater coins are holding gets included in the unrealized loss. The metric then takes the difference between these two numbers to find the net profit/loss status of the entire market. In the context of the current discussion, the entire market isn&#8217;t of interest, however, only specific sections of it are. In particular, two BTC cohorts called the &#8220;short-term holders&#8221; (STHs) and the &#8220;mid-term holders&#8221; (MTHs) are of relevance. The STHs include all investors who bought their coins within the last six months, while the MTHs are those who have been holding their coins since at least six months ago and at most 2 years ago. First, here is a chart that shows the trend in the Bitcoin NUPL specifically for the STHs: Looks like the value of the metric has approached zero recently &#124; Source: CryptoQuant As displayed in the above graph, the Bitcoin STH NUPL has been positive throughout this rally that first started back in January of this year. Generally, this is the case in bullish trends, as the STHs are those who bought relatively recently, so any price rises immediately reflect on their profit/loss status. What&#8217;s more significant, however, is the indicator&#8217;s relationship with the zero mark. At this line, the STHs as a whole are neutral, meaning that their unrealized losses equal their unrealized profits. Usually, whenever the metric retests this line from above during bullish trends, it finds support and the price feels a bullish effect. This could be seen working in action during this rally alone, as the rebounds in March and June both occurred when the STH NUPL approached this line. Related Reading: Bitcoin NVT Shows Bearish Crossover, Price Drop Incoming? From the chart, it&#8217;s visible that the metric has once again fallen to this line recently. This retest may be quite important, as a plunge below could mean a reversal back toward a bearish regime. In the below graph, it&#8217;s also visible that the MTH NUPL is retesting the same line, although this indicator is approaching it from the negative zone. The metric is retesting the break-even line &#124; Source: CryptoQuant The MTHs had been sitting in losses until now, but they are on the verge of transitioning back into profits currently. If the metric can manage to break through the level, then it would be a positive sign for the rally, as the bullish trend has historically continued whenever these investors have come back above water. Related Reading: Will Bitcoin Rebound Anytime Soon? Here’s What On-Chain Data Says The break-even line providing resistance to Bitcoin, however, is also a possibility, in which case the asset would feel a bearish effect. It now remains to be seen how this retest, as well as the one of the STH NUPL, would pan out in the coming days. BTC Price At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading around $29,000, down 1% in the last week. BTC continues to move sideways &#124; Source: BTCUSD on TradingView Featured image from Michael Förtsch on Unsplash.com, charts from TradingView.com, CryptoQuant.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On-chain data shows two Bitcoin indicators are currently retesting levels that have historically been relevant for the market&#8217;s course.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin NUPL For Both Short-Term &amp; Mid-Term Holders Is Neutral Currently</h2>
<p>As pointed out by an analyst in a CryptoQuant <a href="https://cryptoquant.com/insights/quicktake/64d0ac9143e72e1dce17d680-The-decisive-period-is-probably-very-close-based-on-the-following-on-chain-data-" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">post</a>, the BTC NUPL has been retesting crucial levels recently. The &#8220;<a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-bearish-nupl-rejection-long-term-resistance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Net Unrealized Profit/Loss</a>&#8221; (NUPL) is a metric that keeps track of the net amount of profit or loss that investors are holding currently.</p>
<p>This indicator works by looking through the on-chain history of each coin in circulation to see what price it was last moved at. If this previous transfer price for any coin was less than the current spot price of Bitcoin, then that particular coin is holding a profit right now.</p>
<p>The NUPL counts this profit that the coin is holding in the unrealized profit. Similarly, the loss that underwater coins are holding gets included in the unrealized loss. The metric then takes the difference between these two numbers to find the net profit/loss status of the entire market.</p>
<p>In the context of the current discussion, the entire market isn&#8217;t of interest, however, only specific sections of it are. In particular, two BTC cohorts called the &#8220;<a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-short-term-holders-exchange-inflows-price/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">short-term holders</a>&#8221; (STHs) and the &#8220;mid-term holders&#8221; (MTHs) are of relevance.</p>
<p>The STHs include all investors who bought their coins within the last six months, while the MTHs are those who have been holding their coins since at least six months ago and at most 2 years ago.</p>
<p>First, here is a chart that shows the trend in the Bitcoin NUPL specifically for the STHs:</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone aligncenter" src="https://i0.wp.com/img.cryptoquant.com/254665/quicktake/oe2rAEe_466e152d73e5f04f929dfce12398433a353d24f5ec5c88e4cfa4a5a0ae749fe1.png?resize=1280%2C806&#038;ssl=1" alt="Bitcoin NUPL" width="1280" height="806"  data-recalc-dims="1"/></p>

<p>As displayed in the above graph, the Bitcoin STH NUPL has been positive throughout this <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-rally-may-not-resume-until-this-happens/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">rally</a> that first started back in January of this year. Generally, this is the case in bullish trends, as the STHs are those who bought relatively recently, so any price rises immediately reflect on their profit/loss status.</p>
<p>What&#8217;s more significant, however, is the indicator&#8217;s relationship with the zero mark. At this line, the STHs as a whole are neutral, meaning that their unrealized losses equal their unrealized profits.</p>
<p>Usually, whenever the metric retests this line from above during bullish trends, it finds support and the price feels a bullish effect. This could be seen working in action during this rally alone, as the rebounds in March and June both occurred when the STH NUPL approached this line.</p>

<p>From the chart, it&#8217;s visible that the metric has once again fallen to this line recently. This retest may be quite important, as a plunge below could mean a reversal back toward a bearish regime.</p>
<p>In the below graph, it&#8217;s also visible that the MTH NUPL is retesting the same line, although this indicator is approaching it from the negative zone.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone aligncenter" src="https://i0.wp.com/img.cryptoquant.com/254665/quicktake/O6GvH_036d1fbe4ca395603b3d591fd61380f526742ca24ecd1ed65cfb08b317480fac.png?resize=1280%2C806&#038;ssl=1" alt="Bitcoin MTH NUPL" width="1280" height="806"  data-recalc-dims="1"/></p>

<p>The MTHs had been sitting in losses until now, but they are on the verge of transitioning back into profits currently. If the metric can manage to break through the level, then it would be a positive sign for the rally, as the bullish trend has historically continued whenever these investors have come back above water.</p>

<p>The break-even line providing resistance to Bitcoin, however, is also a possibility, in which case the asset would feel a bearish effect. It now remains to be seen how this retest, as well as the one of the STH NUPL, would pan out in the coming days.</p>
<h2>BTC Price</h2>
<p>At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading around $29,000, down 1% in the last week.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium aligncenter" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/c6rlUyXq/" alt="Bitcoin Price Chart" width="1534" height="877"/></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/michael-fortsch-gRAS87wSVCs-unsplash.jpg?fit=460%2C307" width="460" height="307" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">546067</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum Whale $4.5 Million Burn Shocks ETH Community, What&#8217;s Going On?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/ethereum/ethereum-whale-4-5-million-burn/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 20:00:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH burn]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH whale]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum Whale]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Whale]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=546094</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The crypto space is never lacking of events &#8211; from hacks to memecoins frenzy, to traders realizing huge profits from trades. This time, it is the action of a particular Ethereum whale that has caught attention, one that has the ETH community in shock as to the reasons for such action.  The mysterious whale in question with the Ethereum address ‘nd4.eth’ sent $4.5 million worth of Ether (2,500 ETH) to a ‘burn’ address, in a move that removes these tokens from circulation forever. This interesting event, which occurred on July 26, has led to a burning question on the lips of everyone &#8211; who is this mysterious whale? Who Is The Mysterious Ethereum Whale? Although there is currently limited information on the mysterious whale, Crypto Twitter has been able to dig up some information as to who this person might be. Recent Twitter discussions revealed that the user behind ‘nd4.eth’ was on Binance Leaderboard which shows the traders in profits on the platform.  Related Reading: Curve Finance Announces $1.85 Million Bounty For Stable Pool Exploiter Another Twitter user (@serialsexhaver) revealed that the trader had over $20 million in earnings on GMT long and “went all in on a btc short” and then deleted his account. The Tweet read: Last year he was on Binance leaderboard, made north on 20mill on gmt long, was giving away anons gmt sneakers and went all in on a btc short &#8230;then deleted his account This is also not the first time this particular user is doing something like this. According to information gotten from Web3 portfolio tracker DeBank, the “nd4.eth’ address had previously sent Wrapped Ethereum (WETH) to another burn address many times, with these transactions amounting to approximately $8,000 in total. The address still has a huge portfolio though, with close to $3.57 million staked on GMX and GNS. ETH price plunges to $1,823 &#124; Source: ETHUSD on Tradingview.com Contributing To The Growth Of ETH While the crypto community continues to speculate the reasons for the ‘$4.5 million burn,’ there is no doubt that the ‘nd4.eth’ address has, for whatever reason, contributed to the growth of the Ethereum ecosystems.  His actions also further fuel the Ethereum as an ‘ultra-sound money’ narrative. Laurence Day, the creator of the Wildcat Protocol, jokingly commended the individual when he stated: “If you didn’t wake up this morning and say thank you to nd4.eth for contributing to the ultrasound money narrative, I want you to have a long, hard think about what you’re trying to achieve here.” Related Reading: Crypto Funds Vs Bitcoin Holders: Who Was The Better Performer In H1 2023 True to it, the burning of tokens makes it deflationary and is usually done to decrease the token’s circulating supply and help boost demand and increase its market value. Ethereum isn’t the only ecosystem that the said individual is contributing to.  According to a tweet from Lookonchain, the user “spent 5,330 $DAI to buy $GMX and $GNS on July 29 and also transferred 34.9 GMX ($1,989) and 600 GNX ($2,733) to the dead address.” Featured image from iStock, chart from Tradingview.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The crypto space is never lacking of events &#8211; from hacks to memecoins frenzy, to traders realizing huge profits from trades. This time, it is the action of a particular Ethereum whale that has caught attention, one that has the ETH community in shock as to the reasons for such action. </p>
<p>The mysterious whale in question with the Ethereum address ‘nd4.eth’ <a href="https://etherscan.io/tx/0x36f899bb27aa365c30a6f559c3512c063c366dae515d43fe05ec530ed440bb5a" rel="nofollow">sent</a> $4.5 million worth of Ether (2,500 ETH) to a ‘burn’ address, in a move that removes these tokens from circulation forever. This interesting event, which occurred on July 26, has led to a burning question on the lips of everyone &#8211; who is this mysterious whale?</p>
<h2>Who Is The Mysterious Ethereum Whale?</h2>
<p>Although there is currently limited information on the mysterious whale, Crypto Twitter has been able to dig up some information as to who this person might be. Recent Twitter<a href="https://twitter.com/Blackfortuna/status/1688439261970776065?s=20" rel="nofollow"> discussions</a> revealed that the user behind ‘nd4.eth’ was on Binance Leaderboard which shows the traders in profits on the platform. </p>

<p>Another Twitter user (@serialsexhaver) revealed that the trader had over $20 million in earnings on GMT long and “went all in on a btc short” and then deleted his account.</p>
<p>The Tweet <a href="https://twitter.com/serialsexhaver/status/1688439968166002689?s=20" rel="nofollow">read</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>Last year he was on Binance leaderboard, made north on 20mill on gmt long, was giving away anons gmt sneakers and went all in on a btc short &#8230;then deleted his account</p></blockquote>
<p>This is also not the first time this particular user is doing something like this. According to <a href="https://debank.com/profile/0xefbbc3fa829af506bc7afe1a0c31b3c7419456f7" rel="nofollow">information</a> gotten from Web3 portfolio tracker DeBank, the “nd4.eth’ address had previously sent Wrapped Ethereum (WETH) to another burn address many times, with these transactions amounting to approximately $8,000 in total. The address still has a huge portfolio though, with close to $3.57 million staked on GMX and GNS.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/x2pzXg8s/" alt="Ethereum (ETH) price chart from Tradingview.com" width="2884" height="1746"/></p>

<h2>Contributing To The Growth Of ETH</h2>
<p>While the crypto community continues to speculate the reasons for the ‘$4.5 million burn,’ there is no doubt that the ‘nd4.eth’ address has, for whatever reason, contributed to the growth of the Ethereum ecosystems. </p>
<p>His actions also further fuel the Ethereum as an ‘ultra-sound money’ narrative. Laurence Day, the creator of the Wildcat Protocol, jokingly commended the individual when he stated:</p>
<p>“If you didn’t wake up this morning and say thank you to nd4.eth for contributing to the ultrasound money narrative, I want you to have a long, hard think about what you’re trying to achieve here.”</p>

<p>True to it, the burning of tokens makes it deflationary and is usually done to decrease the token’s circulating supply and help boost demand and increase its market value. Ethereum isn’t the only ecosystem that the said individual is contributing to. </p>
<p>According to a <a href="https://twitter.com/lookonchain/status/1688474075054886912?s=20" rel="nofollow">tweet</a> from Lookonchain, the user “spent 5,330 $DAI to buy $GMX and $GNS on July 29 and also transferred 34.9 GMX ($1,989) and 600 GNX ($2,733) to the dead address.”</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/iStock-1360442132.jpg?fit=460%2C310" width="460" height="310" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">546094</post-id>	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
