<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"

	xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
	xmlns:geo="http://www.w3.org/2003/01/geo/wgs84_pos#"
	>

<channel>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.newsbtc.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<description>Bitcoin &#38; Cryptocurrency News Today</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 15:32:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-cropped-favicon.png?fit=32%2C32</url>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
<site xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">221170450</site>	<item>
		<title>SEC Approval Could Propel Bitcoin To New Heights: Analyst Forecasts $150,000 Clearing Price</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/sec-approval-could-propel-bitcoin-to-new-heights-analyst-forecasts-150000-clearing-price/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 21:00:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=547572</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[In a recent interview, Tom Lee, CNBC’s head of research, shared his insights on the potential impact of a Spot Bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF) approval by the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) on the price of the largest cryptocurrency in the market.  Lee expressed optimism that introducing a Bitcoin ETF could propel the digital asset to price levels of $150,000 or even $180,000, representing a significant surge from current levels.  Optimistic View On BTC Lee&#8217;s bullish stance on the potential for a Bitcoin ETF to drive price appreciation reflects the growing anticipation within the cryptocurrency community, as an ETF would provide traditional investors with a regulated and easily accessible vehicle for gaining exposure to Bitcoin, potentially attracting substantial capital inflows into the market.  According to Lee, if the SEC were to approve a Spot Bitcoin ETF, it could unlock a new wave of investor interest and significantly boost the price of Bitcoin.  He estimated that this approval could drive the cryptocurrency to $150,000 or even $180,000, representing a substantial appreciation from its current levels.  The endorsement of a regulated ETF would likely instill confidence among institutional investors who have hesitated to enter the cryptocurrency market due to concerns about custody and regulatory oversight. Related Reading: SEI Token Breaks Into Top 100 One Day Post-Debut On Major Exchanges However, Lee also acknowledged the influence of the upcoming Bitcoin halving event on the price trajectory. Bitcoin&#8217;s protocol is designed to undergo halvings approximately every four years, reducing the block reward miners receive by half.  Considering the impact of the halving, Lee tempered expectations of Bitcoin reaching six-figure prices in the immediate aftermath. While he expressed confidence in the long-term potential of the digital asset, he suggested that the effects of the halving might delay the realization of such high valuations.  Bitcoin Holds Critical Zone Amidst Intensifying Bull-Bear Battle While continuing to experience a consolidation phase and decide which side will crack first,  Bitcoin has found itself in a critical zone, prompting both bullish and bearish sentiments among market participants.  Keith Alan, co-founder of the analysis firm Material Indicators, has highlighted vital indicators and technical levels that are currently shaping the market&#8217;s direction.  While the bears actively seek to test support and potentially trigger a macro bear market, the bulls have maintained the trading range thus far, keeping the macro bull market prospects alive. The significance of maintaining the range cannot be understated. According to Alan’s analysis, key Moving Averages and the green resistance/support (R/S) Flip Zone have demarcated critical levels that Bitcoin must hold.  As BTC’s price approaches the lower end of the range, below $29,000, Alan closely observes the technical support at the 21-Week Moving Average, as a breach of this level could have far-reaching implications for the overall market sentiment. According to Keith, a break below the range and the subsequent formation of a Lower Low (LL) in price action would signal the onset of a macro bear market. This would imply a prolonged period of downward price pressure and a potential shift in the broader market trend.  Related Reading: Is An XRP Spot ETF Coming To The US Soon? Bloomberg Analyst Answers Conversely, a successful defense of the range, coupled with a clearance of the 100-Week Moving Average and the formation of a Higher High (HH), would indicate the potential for a macro bull market characterized by sustained upward momentum. Despite the bearish signs of “price erosion” and diminishing liquidity, the bulls can still find solace in the fact that they are currently holding the range. This suggests that the market is yet to tip in favor of the bears decisively.  However, the bears remain determined to test this support, making it a crucial juncture for determining the near to mid-term trend of Bitcoin. Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com ]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In a recent <a href="https://twitter.com/BitcoinNews2905/status/1691803938889072862?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">interview</a>, Tom Lee, CNBC’s head of research, shared his insights on the potential impact of a Spot Bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF) approval by the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) on the price of the largest cryptocurrency in the market. </p>
<p>Lee expressed optimism that introducing a Bitcoin ETF could propel the digital asset to price levels of $150,000 or even $180,000, representing a significant surge from current levels. </p>
<h2>Optimistic View On BTC</h2>
<p>Lee&#8217;s bullish stance on the potential for a Bitcoin ETF to drive price appreciation reflects the growing anticipation within the cryptocurrency community, as an ETF would provide traditional investors with a regulated and easily accessible vehicle for gaining exposure to Bitcoin, potentially attracting substantial capital inflows into the market. </p>
<p>According to Lee, if the SEC were to approve a Spot Bitcoin ETF, it could unlock a new wave of investor interest and significantly boost the price of Bitcoin. </p>
<p>He estimated that this approval could drive the cryptocurrency to $150,000 or even $180,000, representing a substantial appreciation from its current levels. </p>
<p>The endorsement of a regulated ETF would likely instill confidence among institutional investors who have hesitated to enter the cryptocurrency market due to concerns about custody and regulatory oversight.</p>

<p>However, Lee also acknowledged the influence of the upcoming Bitcoin halving event on the price trajectory. Bitcoin&#8217;s protocol is designed to undergo halvings approximately every four years, reducing the block reward miners receive by half. </p>
<p>Considering the impact of the halving, Lee tempered expectations of Bitcoin reaching six-figure prices in the immediate aftermath. While he expressed confidence in the long-term potential of the digital asset, he suggested that the effects of the halving might delay the realization of such high valuations. </p>
<h2>Bitcoin Holds Critical Zone Amidst Intensifying Bull-Bear Battle</h2>
<p>While continuing to experience a consolidation phase and decide which side will crack first,  Bitcoin has found itself in a critical zone, prompting both bullish and bearish sentiments among market participants. </p>
<p>Keith Alan, co-founder of the analysis firm Material Indicators, has <a href="https://twitter.com/KAProductions/status/1691810030528467185?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">highlighted </a>vital indicators and technical levels that are currently shaping the market&#8217;s direction. </p>
<p>While the bears actively seek to test support and potentially trigger a macro bear market, the bulls have maintained the trading range thus far, keeping the macro bull market prospects alive.</p>
<p>The significance of maintaining the range cannot be understated. According to Alan’s analysis, key Moving Averages and the green resistance/support (R/S) Flip Zone have demarcated critical levels that Bitcoin must hold. </p>
<p>As BTC’s price approaches the lower end of the range, below $29,000, Alan closely observes the technical support at the 21-Week Moving Average, as a breach of this level could have far-reaching implications for the overall market sentiment.</p>
<p>According to Keith, a break below the range and the subsequent formation of a Lower Low (LL) in price action would signal the onset of a macro bear market. This would imply a prolonged period of downward price pressure and a potential shift in the broader market trend. </p>

<p>Conversely, a successful defense of the range, coupled with a clearance of the 100-Week Moving Average and the formation of a Higher High (HH), would indicate the potential for a macro bull market characterized by sustained upward momentum.</p>
<p>Despite the bearish signs of “price erosion” and diminishing liquidity, the bulls can still find solace in the fact that they are currently holding the range. This suggests that the market is yet to tip in favor of the bears decisively. </p>
<p>However, the bears remain determined to test this support, making it a crucial juncture for determining the near to mid-term trend of Bitcoin.</p>
<img decoding="async" fetchpriority="high" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/gww7ZzBG/" alt="Bitcoin" width="1814" height="858" loading="lazy"/>
<p>Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Downloader.la-64dce79c1a5ed.jpg?fit=460%2C345" width="460" height="345" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">547572</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Toncoin (TON) Investors Load Up Their Bags As Majority Of Cryptos Nosedive</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/toncoin-ton/toncoin-ton-investors-load-up-their-bags-as-majority-of-cryptos-nosedive/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Kent Glory]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 20:00:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Toncoin (TON)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[TON analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ton price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[TON price analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Toncoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[TONUSD]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=547546</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Toncoin (TON) has showcased healthy market status since the end of last week. According to historical data from TradingView, it witnessed a consecutive bullish trajectory from August 11, 2023, until today, August 16. The upward movement drew the attention of investors, resulting in a price increment of over 12% gain in the past seven days. Notably, the latest developments within Toncoin’s ecosystem could be the reason for the market uptick in the past few days.  However, TON’s market value today, August 16, is $1.44, representing a price drop of over 2% in the last 24 hours. With this current price, the asset is almost 19.7% up in the past 14 days, 7% in 30 days, and 17% in the past year.  Related Reading: Best-Selling Author Touts Buy XRP Now, But This Price Is Crucial Recent Development Within Toncoin Ecosystem Pushes TON’s Value There have been a lot of events on Toincoin’s ecosystem attracting massive investor attention and investment. Today August 16, Toincoin shared a post on X about its Indonesia event in Bali slated for August 23, inviting the crypto community to join.  Also, on August 14, Toincoin shared another update on expanding its ecosystem globally through the X platform. Toincoin shared that it has taken another step to increase its global reach by launching the network’s website in Ukraine. This move shows the project&#8217;s commitment to increasing the asset&#8217;s adoption. Also, the team behind the TON projects wants to discover how Web3 teams could easily sign documents in Telegram.  In its X post, the team behind TON wrote: For those who will be in Lisbon this Thursday, August 17, TON Society Europe is kicking off its journey with an exciting offline event. Earlier on August 11, the TON community, via its X handle, shared a tweet from a known payment gateway for cryptocurrencies, NOWPayments.  The report noted that the payment service had incorporated TON into its technology to enable a seamless non-fungible token checkout from different marketplaces. This announcement triggered a rise in the market value of TON, verifiably from historical data on TradingView. From the data, the digital asset kick-started its bullish trend on the same day the news was announced.  It recorded a price gain from $1.259 to $1.302, reflecting a positive price change of about 3.4% in 24 hours. As the news spread, investors filled their portfolios with TON, despite the price decline of some other crypto assets. Related Reading: SEI Token Breaks Into Top 100 One-Day Post-Debut On Major Exchanges Toncoin entry into the NFT sector could have been the reason for the continued purchase of more TON tokens. Investors are hopeful that the digital asset&#8217;s value will appreciate in the future because of NFTs. These new updates contributed to the positive market sentiment after the association with NOWPayments triggered the price gains. Featured image from Pixabay and chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Toncoin (TON) has showcased healthy market status since the end of last week. According to historical data from <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/chart/UbXsBwCv/?symbol=OKX%3ATONUSDT" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">TradingView</a>, it witnessed a consecutive bullish trajectory from August 11, 2023, until today, August 16.</p>
<p>The upward movement drew the attention of investors, resulting in a price increment of over 12% gain in the past seven days. Notably, the latest developments within Toncoin’s ecosystem could be the reason for the market uptick in the past few days. </p>
<p>However, TON’s market value today, August 16, is $1.44, representing a price drop of over 2% in the last 24 hours. With this current price, the asset is almost <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/toncoin" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">19.7%</a> up in the past 14 days, 7% in 30 days, and 17% in the past year. </p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/best-selling-author-buy-xrp-now-but-this-price-crucial/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Best-Selling Author Touts Buy XRP Now, But This Price Is Crucial</a></p>
<h2>Recent Development Within Toncoin Ecosystem Pushes TON’s Value</h2>
<p>There have been a lot of events on Toincoin’s ecosystem attracting massive investor attention and investment. Today August 16, Toincoin <a href="https://twitter.com/ton_blockchain/status/1691742716357464129?ref_src=twsrc%5Egoogle%7Ctwcamp%5Eserp%7Ctwgr%5Etweet" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">shared a post</a> on X about its Indonesia event in Bali slated for August 23, inviting the crypto community to join. </p>
<p>Also, on August 14, Toincoin shared another update on expanding its ecosystem globally through the <a href="https://twitter.com/ton_blockchain/status/1691102487619477507" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">X platform</a>. Toincoin shared that it has taken another step to increase its global reach by launching the network’s website in Ukraine.</p>
<p>This move shows the project&#8217;s commitment to increasing the asset&#8217;s adoption. Also, the team behind the <a href="https://twitter.com/TON_SocietyEU/status/1691137825381429250" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">TON</a> projects wants to discover how Web3 teams could easily sign documents in Telegram. </p>
<p>In its X post, the team behind TON wrote:</p>
<blockquote><p>For those who will be in Lisbon this Thursday, August 17, TON Society Europe is kicking off its journey with an exciting offline event.</p></blockquote>
<img decoding="async" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/xcobL0eN/" alt="TONUSD price chart" width="980" height="589" loading="lazy"/>
<p>Earlier on August 11, the TON community, via its <a href="https://twitter.com/NOWPayments_io/status/1689942726400495616" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">X handle</a>, shared a tweet from a known payment gateway for cryptocurrencies, NOWPayments. </p>
<p>The report noted that the payment service had incorporated TON into its technology to enable a seamless non-fungible token checkout from different marketplaces.</p>
<p>This announcement triggered a rise in the market value of TON, verifiably from historical data on <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/chart/UbXsBwCv/?symbol=OKX%3ATONUSDT" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">TradingView</a>. From the data, the digital asset kick-started its bullish trend on the same day the news was announced. </p>
<p>It recorded a price gain from $1.259 to $1.302, reflecting a positive price change of about 3.4% in 24 hours. As the news spread, investors filled their portfolios with TON, despite the price decline of some other crypto assets.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/altcoin/sei-into-top-100-post-debut-on-major-exchanges/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">SEI Token Breaks Into Top 100 One-Day Post-Debut On Major Exchanges</a></p>
<p>Toncoin entry into the NFT sector could have been the reason for the continued purchase of more TON tokens. Investors are hopeful that the digital asset&#8217;s value will appreciate in the future because of NFTs.</p>
<p>These new updates contributed to the positive market sentiment after the association with NOWPayments triggered the price gains.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Toncoin.jpg?fit=460%2C307" width="460" height="307" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">547546</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Are Bitcoin Whales Selling? This Metric May Suggest So</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-whales-selling-metric-may-suggest-so/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hououin Kyouma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 19:00:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin bearish]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Exchange Whale Ratio]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Selling]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin whales]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=547540</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[On-chain data shows the Bitcoin exchange whale ratio has spiked, a sign that the whales may be selling now. Bitcoin Exchange Whale Ratio Has Gone Up In Recent Days An analyst in a CryptoQuant post explained that the whale inflows have been higher than usual recently. The &#8220;exchange whale ratio&#8221; is an indicator that measures the ratio between the sum of the top 10 inflows to exchanges and the total exchange inflows. Generally, the ten most significant transactions going to exchanges are coming from the whales, so this ratio&#8217;s value can provide hints about how the inflow activity of these humongous investors currently compares with the entire market. When the value of this metric is high, it means that this cohort is making up a significant part of the total market inflows. As one of the main reasons investors deposit their coins to these platforms is for selling-related purposes, this trend can be a sign that the whales are currently applying a large amount of selling pressure. On the other hand, low values imply the whales are making up for a relatively healthy portion of the total inflows. Depending on other market factors, such a trend may be neutral or bullish for the cryptocurrency&#8217;s price. Related Reading: This Dreaded Candlestick Formation Just Printed: Bitcoin To $18k? Now, here is a chart that shows the trend in the Bitcoin exchange whale ratio over the last couple of years: The value of the metric seems to have hit a high peak in recent days &#124; Source: CryptoQuant The above graph shows that the Bitcoin exchange whale ratio has recently registered a spike. In this latest surge, the metric had neared the 0.70 mark, implying that almost 70% of the total exchange inflows had come from these humongous investors alone. If these whales have made these deposits to sell their coins, then BTC could naturally feel a bearish effect from this inflow activity. So far, however, the price hasn&#8217;t seen any significant decline, as it continues to be within the range it has been endlessly consolidating for the past few weeks. Related Reading: Renowned Finance Author Says Bitcoin Price Will Reach $1 Million If This Happens In the chart, the quant has also highlighted the instances during the last couple of years where the Bitcoin exchange whale ratio spiked to similarly high values. It would appear that the BTC price declined shortly after most of these occurrences. In some instances, the bearish effect only occurred with a delay, meaning that even though the recent spike hasn&#8217;t led to a significant price drawdown, it could still do so soon. It remains to be seen how the Bitcoin market copes with this potential high selling pressure from the whales this time. BTC Price At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading around $29,000, down 2% in the last week. Looks like BTC has continued to move sideways recently &#124; Source: BTCUSD on TradingView Featured image from Todd Cravens on Unsplash.com, charts from TradingView.com, CryptoQuant.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On-chain data shows the Bitcoin exchange whale ratio has spiked, a sign that the whales may be selling now.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Exchange Whale Ratio Has Gone Up In Recent Days</h2>
<p>An analyst in a CryptoQuant <a href="https://cryptoquant.com/insights/quicktake/64dc966adcf5141b5e5cfcb5-More-Whale-Inflow-than-Average" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">post</a> explained that the whale inflows have been higher than usual recently. The &#8220;<a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-bullish-signal-exchange-whale-ratio-plunges/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">exchange whale ratio</a>&#8221; is an indicator that measures the ratio between the sum of the top 10 inflows to exchanges and the total <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-exchange-inflow-spikes-is-this-bearish/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">exchange inflows</a>.</p>
<p>Generally, the ten most significant transactions going to exchanges are coming from the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/altcoin/pepe-whales-load-up-bags-memecoin-jumps-13/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">whales</a>, so this ratio&#8217;s value can provide hints about how the inflow activity of these humongous investors currently compares with the entire market.</p>
<p>When the value of this metric is high, it means that this cohort is making up a significant part of the total market inflows. As one of the main reasons investors deposit their coins to these platforms is for selling-related purposes, this trend can be a sign that the whales are currently applying a large amount of selling pressure.</p>
<p>On the other hand, low values imply the whales are making up for a relatively healthy portion of the total inflows. Depending on other market factors, such a trend may be neutral or bullish for the cryptocurrency&#8217;s price.</p>

<p>Now, here is a chart that shows the trend in the Bitcoin exchange whale ratio over the last couple of years:</p>
<p><img decoding="async" class="alignnone aligncenter" src="https://i0.wp.com/img.cryptoquant.com/148277/quicktake/0WYGx_c1143591b3d7c0d9acb264b54f45e29e50085bff020c43315d3370297672677d.png?resize=1280%2C702&#038;ssl=1" alt="Bitcoin Exchange Whale Ratio" width="1280" height="702" loading="lazy" data-recalc-dims="1"/></p>

<p>The above graph shows that the Bitcoin exchange whale ratio has recently registered a spike. In this latest surge, the metric had neared the 0.70 mark, implying that almost 70% of the total exchange inflows had come from these humongous investors alone.</p>
<p>If these whales have made these deposits to sell their coins, then BTC could naturally feel a bearish effect from this inflow activity. So far, however, the price hasn&#8217;t seen any significant decline, as it continues to be within the range it has been endlessly consolidating for the past few weeks.</p>

<p>In the chart, the quant has also highlighted the instances during the last couple of years where the Bitcoin exchange whale ratio spiked to similarly high values.</p>
<p>It would appear that the BTC price declined shortly after most of these occurrences. In some instances, the bearish effect only occurred with a delay, meaning that even though the recent spike hasn&#8217;t led to a significant price drawdown, it could still do so soon.</p>
<p>It remains to be seen how the Bitcoin market copes with this potential high selling pressure from the whales this time.</p>
<h2>BTC Price</h2>
<p>At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading around $29,000, down 2% in the last week.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium aligncenter" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/P8fDpq4D/" alt="Bitcoin Price Chart" width="1534" height="877"/></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/todd-cravens-QnBrjY-nFUs-unsplash.jpg?fit=460%2C306" width="460" height="306" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">547540</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Shiba Inu DAO Gets Serious With New Advisory And Investment Firm</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/shiba-inu-dao-advisory-firm/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 18:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Shiba Inu]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIB]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shiba Inu DAO]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shibarium]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIBUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIBUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=547552</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Shiba Inu, an Ethereum-based cryptocurrency, is bolstering its commitment to driving its ambitious goals in the crypto industry by appointing a new tech advisor. The move will see Alpha Transform Holdings (ATH) providing expertise and advice to the Shiba Inu DAO Foundation.  Strategic Partnership with Alpha Transform Holdings In a Twitter post released by Lucie, a Content Marketer for the Shiba ecosystem, it was revealed that Alpha Transform Holdings, a leading cryptocurrency advisory venture capital firm would be entering a counseling role for the foundation behind Shiba Inu DAO.  Related Reading: Another Crypto Millionaire Has Been Found Dead The update was disclosed on Monday, August 14 in a press release where ATH underlined all the benefits Shiba Inu could potentially gain from decades of experience providing expertise advice to major crypto projects in the industry.  The partnership between Shiba Inu DAO and ATH was enthusiastically welcomed by Alpha Transform Holdings’s Partner, Media, and Entertainment lead, Seth Shapiro. He emphasized Shiba Inu’s pivotal role in transforming the future of the Web3 space and showed full support for the new alliance.   “In the past 15 years, web2 technologies, mobile, streaming, and social, have rewritten the economics of media. We believe that web3 will have a significant impact in the coming years. The Shiba Inu ecosystem is one of the first to offer a 360 strategy for M&#38;E integration at scale. We look forward to working with their team as this next era begins,” Shapiro stated. SHIB price shows strength as ecosystem grows &#124; Source: SHIBUSD on Tradingview.com ATH Contribution To Shiba Inu DAO Growth Alpha Transform Holdings is a new holding company with a team of advisors and strategic partners. According to reports, ATH’s team will provide Shiba Inu DAO with collective experience and knowledge of investments, industry technology, and operations.  The digital asset organization includes a team of professionals in multiple fields including banking, design, and technology, who are said to have deep experience in providing support on topics such as mergers, IPOs, strategic developments, token economics, and more.  ATH has also made partnerships with several high-value organizations, which SHIB potentially stands to benefit from. Some of these organizations include Nasdaq, Disney, and News Corp, veteran companies that have counseled leading blockchain projects like Ethereum and Tether. Related Reading: Institutional XRP Holdings Rise Rapidly Following Ripple’s Win Over SEC Shiba Inu Lead Developer, Shytoshi Kusama has shown ardent support for the new alliance with ATH. He stated his anticipation towards Shiba Inu’s future with ATH guidance especially with Shibarium, Shiba Inu’s upcoming layer 2 Shibarium project almost finalized.   “Now that Shibarium is nearly complete, and our full structure placed at the feet of the world, we couldn’t ask for a better partner to help shepherd this next phase of the Shiba global phenomenon,” Kusama stated. “We look forward to Alpha Transform helping our Foundation swiftly and effectively chart the best course possible for the future of the Shiba Inu Ecosystem.” Featured image from iStock, chart from Tradingview.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Shiba Inu, an Ethereum-based cryptocurrency, is bolstering its commitment to driving its ambitious goals in the crypto industry by appointing a new tech advisor. The move will see Alpha Transform Holdings (ATH) providing expertise and advice to the Shiba Inu DAO Foundation. </p>
<h2>Strategic Partnership with Alpha Transform Holdings</h2>
<p>In a <a href="https://twitter.com/lucieshib/status/1691438772242599936?s=46&amp;t=-3edbsKZ5c-mleGsRUiKUQ" rel="nofollow">Twitter post</a> released by Lucie, a Content Marketer for the Shiba ecosystem, it was revealed that Alpha Transform Holdings, a leading cryptocurrency advisory venture capital firm would be entering a counseling role for the foundation behind Shiba Inu DAO. </p>

<p>The update was disclosed on Monday, August 14 in a <a href="https://www.globenewswire.com/news-release/2023/08/14/2724869/0/en/Alpha-Transform-Holdings-Joins-SHIB-Doggy-DAO-Foundation-as-Advisor.html" rel="nofollow">press release</a> where ATH underlined all the benefits Shiba Inu could potentially gain from decades of experience providing expertise advice to major crypto projects in the industry. </p>
<p>The partnership between Shiba Inu DAO and ATH was enthusiastically welcomed by Alpha Transform Holdings’s Partner, Media, and Entertainment lead, Seth Shapiro. He emphasized Shiba Inu’s pivotal role in transforming the future of the Web3 space and showed full support for the new alliance.  </p>
<p>“In the past 15 years, web2 technologies, mobile, streaming, and social, have rewritten the economics of media. We believe that web3 will have a significant impact in the coming years. The Shiba Inu ecosystem is one of the first to offer a 360 strategy for M&amp;E integration at scale. We look forward to working with their team as this next era begins,” Shapiro stated.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/YEbxi1kg/" alt="Shiba Inu (SHIB) price chart from Tradingview.com (DAO)" width="2884" height="1746"/></p>

<h2>ATH Contribution To Shiba Inu DAO Growth</h2>
<p>Alpha Transform Holdings is a new holding company with a team of advisors and strategic partners. According to reports, ATH’s team will provide Shiba Inu DAO with collective experience and knowledge of investments, industry technology, and operations. </p>
<p>The digital asset organization includes a team of professionals in multiple fields including banking, design, and technology, who are said to have deep experience in providing support on topics such as mergers, IPOs, strategic developments, token economics, and more. </p>
<p>ATH has also made partnerships with several high-value organizations, which SHIB potentially stands to benefit from. Some of these organizations include Nasdaq, Disney, and News Corp, veteran companies that have counseled leading blockchain projects like Ethereum and Tether.</p>

<p>Shiba Inu Lead Developer, <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/shiba-inu-bulls-on-the-horizon-substantial-selling-pressure-seen-dropping/">Shytoshi Kusama</a> has shown ardent support for the new alliance with ATH. He stated his anticipation towards Shiba Inu’s future with ATH guidance especially with Shibarium, Shiba Inu’s upcoming layer 2 <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/shib/shiba-inu-shib-rides-on-bullish-waves-as-shibarium-launch-nears-buy-now/">Shibarium</a> project almost finalized.  </p>
<p>“Now that Shibarium is nearly complete, and our full structure placed at the feet of the world, we couldn’t ask for a better partner to help shepherd this next phase of the Shiba global phenomenon,” Kusama stated. “We look forward to Alpha Transform helping our Foundation swiftly and effectively chart the best course possible for the future of the Shiba Inu Ecosystem.”</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/iStock-1362613000-1.jpg?fit=460%2C307" width="460" height="307" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">547552</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Executives Of Crypto-Friendly Bank Silvergate Step Down As Lawsuits, Liquidation Rages On</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/crypto/crypto-bank-silvergate-executives/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 17:00:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto bank]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto executives]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[silvergate]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[silvergate bank]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=547522</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[In a recent turn of events, multiple executives of the embattled California-based cryptocurrency bank Silvergate Capital have announced that they will be stepping away from their roles at the bank. The announcement comes as the bank remains deep in the throes of liquidation while battling multiple lawsuits linked to its demise. Top Executives Set to Step Down Silvergate Capital Corp announced on Tuesday, August 16, the departure of some of its primary employees working in executive leadership positions in its company. The executives leaving include Chief Financial Officer, Antonia Martino, Chief Legal Officer, John Bonino, and CEO, Alan Lane.  Related Reading: Another Crypto Millionaire Has Been Found Dead Lane and the company’s Chief Legal Officer will be departing on Tuesday, August 16, and according to a financial filing delivered to the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), Silvergate’s Chief Legal Officer is set to step down on September 30.   The executives&#8217; decision to depart from Silvergate follows the bank&#8217;s announcement in March to shut down operations and liquidate its assets. Lane has served as the CEO of Silver Capital Corp and Silvergate Bank since 2008 and played a pivotal role in Silvergate’s development and growth.  In the absence of a CEO, Silvergate has replaced Lane with Silvergate’s Chief Transition Officer, Kathleen M. Fraher. It has also made Andrew Surry, Silvergate’s Accounting Officer, the principal financial offer in the absence of Martino. Silvergate stated in the filing to the SEC that it will provide each executive severance benefits previously offered to employees laid off through the bank&#8217;s liquidation process.  Earlier this year in January, Silvergate laid off over 180 employees, cutting its workforce by 40%. Again, in May, the bank laid off over 250 workers, leaving a group of about 80 to oversee its liquidation and termination process.  The San-Diego-based bank said in a report that it plans to significantly reduce the number of employees in its company and manage its operations using a skeleton crew.  Stock price falls from $20 to $0.2 &#124; Source: Silvergate Capital Corporation on Tradingview.com Silvergate Enveloped in Lawsuits and Liquidations In November 2022, Silvergate collapsed following the FTX failure and embroilment in fraud. Silvergate, which served as one of the two major banks for cryptocurrency companies in the industry, decided to officially shut down all operations and start a liquidation process.  As a result, stocks plunged by 36% and the bank suffered massive customer withdrawals. Toward the end of Q3, Silvergate’s total deposits from crypto customers plummeted by 68%, declining to $3.8 billion from an astonishing $11.9 billion.  Related Reading: US Prosecutors Accuse FTX’s Sam Bankman-Fried Of Using $100M To Curry Political Favors According to reports, FTX was one of Silvergate’s major customers and it was revealed that Silvergate held about $1 billion in deposits from FTX at the time of its failure. Silvergate’s affiliation with FTX has caused severe financial damage to the bank’s reputation and put it on the radar of the regulatory authorities in the United States.  Silvergate was also mentioned in multiple lawsuits due to its association with the bankrupt FTX and allegations of participation in FTX&#8217;s fraudulent activities. Featured image from iStock, chart from Tradingview.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In a recent turn of events, multiple executives of the embattled California-based cryptocurrency bank Silvergate Capital have announced that they will be stepping away from their roles at the bank.</p>
<p>The announcement comes as the bank remains deep in the throes of liquidation while battling multiple lawsuits linked to its demise.</p>
<h2>Top Executives Set to Step Down</h2>
<p>Silvergate Capital Corp announced on Tuesday, August 16, the departure of some of its primary employees working in executive leadership positions in its company. The executives leaving include Chief Financial Officer, Antonia Martino, Chief Legal Officer, John Bonino, and CEO, Alan Lane. </p>

<p>Lane and the company’s Chief Legal Officer will be departing on Tuesday, August 16, and according to a <a href="https://www.sec.gov/Archives/edgar/data/1312109/000095015723000884/form8-k.htm" rel="nofollow">financial filing</a> delivered to the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), Silvergate’s Chief Legal Officer is set to step down on September 30.  </p>
<p>The executives&#8217; decision to depart from Silvergate follows the bank&#8217;s announcement in March to <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/silvergate-to-close-bank-and-wind-down-operations/" rel="nofollow">shut down operations and liquidate its assets</a>. Lane has served as the CEO of Silver Capital Corp and Silvergate Bank since 2008 and played a pivotal role in Silvergate’s development and growth. </p>
<p>In the absence of a CEO, Silvergate has replaced Lane with Silvergate’s Chief Transition Officer, Kathleen M. Fraher. It has also made Andrew Surry, Silvergate’s Accounting Officer, the principal financial offer in the absence of Martino.</p>
<p>Silvergate stated in the filing to the SEC that it will provide each executive severance benefits previously offered to employees laid off through the bank&#8217;s liquidation process. </p>
<p>Earlier this year in January, Silvergate <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/all/crypto-friendly-bank-silvergate-suspends-dividend-payouts/">laid off over 180 employees</a>, cutting its workforce by 40%. Again, in May, the bank laid off over 250 workers, leaving a group of about 80 to oversee its liquidation and termination process. </p>
<p>The San-Diego-based bank said in a report that it plans to significantly reduce the number of employees in its company and manage its operations using a skeleton crew. </p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/5NWW1ECG/" alt="Silvergate bank stock price chart from Tradingview.com" width="2884" height="1746"/></p>

<h2>Silvergate Enveloped in Lawsuits and Liquidations</h2>
<p>In November 2022, Silvergate collapsed following the FTX failure and embroilment in fraud. Silvergate, which served as one of the two major banks for cryptocurrency companies in the industry, decided to officially shut down all operations and start a liquidation process. </p>
<p>As a result, <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/breaking-news-ticker/silvergate-bites-the-dust-down-35-as-crypto-friendly-bank-ceases-operations/">stocks plunged by 36%</a> and the bank suffered massive customer withdrawals. Toward the end of Q3, Silvergate’s total deposits from crypto customers plummeted by 68%, declining to $3.8 billion from an astonishing $11.9 billion. </p>

<p>According to reports, FTX was one of Silvergate’s major customers and it was revealed that Silvergate held about $1 billion in deposits from FTX at the time of its failure. Silvergate’s affiliation with FTX has caused severe financial damage to the bank’s reputation and put it on the radar of the regulatory authorities in the United States. </p>
<p>Silvergate was also <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/silvergate-slapped-with-lawsuit-over-ties-with-ftx-and-alameda/" rel="nofollow">mentioned in multiple lawsuits</a> due to its association with the bankrupt FTX and allegations of participation in FTX&#8217;s fraudulent activities.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/iStock-1473381968.jpg?fit=460%2C345" width="460" height="345" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">547522</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin &#038; Top Assets See High Loss Taking, Is This Bullish?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-other-top-assets-high-loss-taking-bullish/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hououin Kyouma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 16:00:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Bullish]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Lost Taking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Profit To Loss Ratio]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=547491</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[On-chain data shows Bitcoin and the other top assets are observing a high amount of loss-taking currently. Here&#8217;s what this could mean. Investors Of Bitcoin &#38; Other Top Coins Are Capitulating Currently According to data from the on-chain analytics firm Santiment, the current trader capitulation that the largest assets in the market are seeing may be a bottom signal. The indicator of interest here is the &#8220;ratio of daily on-chain transaction volume in profit to loss,&#8221; which, as its name already implies, tells us how the profit-taking volume for any given coin compares with its loss-taking volume right now. When this metric has a positive value, it means that the profit-taking volume is higher than the loss-taking volume currently. Thus, such a trend implies that the market as a whole is harvesting profits at the moment. On the other hand, the indicator having negative values suggests loss taking is the dominant behavior among the traders of the cryptocurrency in question right now. Related Reading: Bitcoin Prediction: Crypto Analyst Forecasts New ATH by 2024 – Can It Happen? In the context of the current discussion, the assets of relevance are Bitcoin (BTC), Ethereum (ETH), XRP (XRP), Litecoin (LTC), and Cardano (ADA). Here is a chart that shows the trend in the ratio of transaction volume in profit to loss for these assets over the last few months: Looks like the value of the metric has been negative for all these assets in recent days &#124; Source: Santiment on X As displayed in the above graph, the indicator&#8217;s value for all these top assets has dipped inside the negative territory recently. This high loss realization from the investors has come as the market as a whole has been unable to amass together any significant rally. From the chart, it&#8217;s visible that these assets have seen the investors capitulate at different points throughout the year, but the current capitulation event has an interesting feature that was missing from these previous instances: the loss-taking is currently happening for all these large cryptocurrencies. It would appear that traders as a whole have finally started to give up on the market after experiencing endless consolidation, as they are ready to take losses in order to make their exit. The scale of the loss-taking itself is also extraordinary, as the only other time this year that the loss volume overtook the profit volume to this degree was way back in March. Historically, capitulation from investors has made bottoms more probable to form. And from the above chart, it&#8217;s visible that the March capitulation also leads to Bitcoin hitting a bottom. Related Reading: Bernstein Predicts Spot ETFs Could Claim 10% Of Bitcoin’s Market If Greenlit The likely reason behind this pattern is that the investors who exit in losses are generally the weak hands, who had a low conviction in the asset, to begin with. In capitulation events, the coins that they sell at losses are picked up by the more resolute investors, and hence, the market gains a stronger foundation for building up rallies. It&#8217;s possible that the high loss taking that Bitcoin and the others are experiencing currently may also lead to a bottom, if the historical precedence is anything to consider. BTC Price At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading around $29,100, down 2% in the last week. BTC continues to move inside a narrow range &#124; Source: BTCUSD on TradingView Featured image from Art Rachen on Unsplash.com, charts from TradingView.com, Santiment.net]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On-chain data shows Bitcoin and the other top assets are observing a high amount of loss-taking currently. Here&#8217;s what this could mean.</p>
<h2>Investors Of Bitcoin &amp; Other Top Coins Are Capitulating Currently</h2>
<p>According to data from the on-chain analytics firm <a href="https://twitter.com/santimentfeed/status/1691664026366095481" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Santiment</a>, the current trader capitulation that the largest assets in the market are seeing may be a bottom signal.</p>
<p>The indicator of interest here is the &#8220;<a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-retraces-back-30000-profit-taking-spikes/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">ratio of daily on-chain transaction volume in profit to loss</a>,&#8221; which, as its name already implies, tells us how the profit-taking volume for any given coin compares with its loss-taking volume right now.</p>
<p>When this metric has a positive value, it means that the profit-taking volume is higher than the loss-taking volume currently. Thus, such a trend implies that the market as a whole is harvesting profits at the moment.</p>
<p>On the other hand, the indicator having negative values suggests loss taking is the dominant behavior among the traders of the cryptocurrency in question right now.</p>

<p>In the context of the current discussion, the assets of relevance are Bitcoin (BTC), Ethereum (ETH), XRP (XRP), Litecoin (LTC), and Cardano (ADA).</p>
<p>Here is a chart that shows the trend in the ratio of transaction volume in profit to loss for these assets over the last few months:</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone aligncenter" src="https://pbs.twimg.com/media/F3n-xFMbUAAuoUC?format=jpg&amp;name=4096x4096" alt="Bitcoin Loss Taking" width="2703" height="1778"/></p>

<p>As displayed in the above graph, the indicator&#8217;s value for all these top assets has dipped inside the negative territory recently. This high loss realization from the investors has come as the market as a whole has been unable to amass together any significant rally.</p>
<p>From the chart, it&#8217;s visible that these assets have seen the investors capitulate at different points throughout the year, but the current <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/altcoin/xrp-traders-show-capitulation-why-could-bullish/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">capitulation event</a> has an interesting feature that was missing from these previous instances: the loss-taking is currently happening for all these large cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p>It would appear that traders as a whole have finally started to give up on the market after experiencing <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/low-bitcoin-volatility-mirrors-2016-bullish-breakout/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">endless consolidation</a>, as they are ready to take losses in order to make their exit.</p>
<p>The scale of the loss-taking itself is also extraordinary, as the only other time this year that the loss volume overtook the profit volume to this degree was way back in March.</p>
<p>Historically, capitulation from investors has made bottoms more probable to form. And from the above chart, it&#8217;s visible that the March capitulation also leads to Bitcoin hitting a bottom.</p>

<p>The likely reason behind this pattern is that the investors who exit in losses are generally the weak hands, who had a low conviction in the asset, to begin with. In capitulation events, the coins that they sell at losses are picked up by the more resolute investors, and hence, the market gains a stronger foundation for building up rallies.</p>
<p>It&#8217;s possible that the high loss taking that Bitcoin and the others are experiencing currently may also lead to a bottom, if the historical precedence is anything to consider.</p>
<h2>BTC Price</h2>
<p>At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading around $29,100, down 2% in the last week.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium aligncenter" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/69q5cxIp/" alt="Bitcoin Price Chart" width="1534" height="877"/></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/art-rachen-yJpjLD3c9bU-unsplash.jpg?fit=307%2C460" width="307" height="460" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">547491</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Is An XRP Spot ETF Coming To The US Soon? Bloomberg Analyst Answers</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/xrp-spot-etf-coming-to-the-us/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 15:00:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Spot XRP ETF]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrp]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP ETF]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrpusdt]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=547521</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Ripple has continued to revel in the glow of Judge Analisa Torres’ ruling in favor of the crypto company, with many use cases being touted for its native token XRP. The most recent use case to surface is a Spot XRP ETF, and Bloomberg analyst James Seyffart has quickly weighed in on the possibility of this happening.  How Possible Is A Spot XRP ETF? Seyffart, during an appearance on Tony Edward’s Thinking Crypto Podcast, explained that XRP would need to be listed on the Chicago Mercantile Exchange (CME) before the SEC can approve a Spot XRP ETF.  Related Reading: Institutional XRP Holdings Rise Rapidly Following Ripple’s Win Over SEC This argument stems from the SEC’s requirement for a regulated market of significant size in the underlying asset. Relatively, exchanges looking to list a Spot Bitcoin ETF are, in hopes of gaining approval, relying on the fact that the CME Bitcoin futures, which happen to be a regulated market, provide significant size to provide necessary data and insights for any spot market.  So Seyffart also believes that any Spot XRP ETF application will also need to fulfill the requirement of the token having a significant market size that can be used to provide any data and insights needed to prevent fraud and market manipulation. To achieve this and easily get the SEC’s approval, listing XRP futures on a prominent derivative exchange like CME would be the way to go, in his opinion.  Despite his remarks, Seyffart isn’t so optimistic about a Spot XRP ETF launching anytime as, according to him, this isn’t something he sees “materializing in the foreseeable future.” Token price continues to fall as euphoria wanes &#124; Source: XRPUSDT on Tradingview.com Little Or No Demand Is A Hindrance Another notable highlight from Seyffart’s remarks was when he suggested that there was little or no demand for an XRP ETF, something which he believes is integral if we are to see any ETF application.  However, there is reason to believe this assumption may not be outrightly correct, as certain figures suggest an increasing demand for XRP, notably among institutional investors.  Related Reading: Renowned Finance Author Says Bitcoin Price Will Reach $1 Million If This Happens Last month, a report stated how XRP’s sales had jumped significantly this year, with over 2.22 billion XRP sold since the beginning of the year. Furthermore, according to a more recent report, the token recorded an institutional inflow of $0.5 million two weeks ago. Ripple’s XRP Ledger is also going head to head with the foremost Bitcoin and Ethereum networks, as it has recorded an increase in daily transactions since the beginning of August. This record has seen it surpass market leader Ethereum in terms of daily transactions conducted on both networks.  Featured image from iStock, chart from Tradingview.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ripple has continued to revel in the glow of Judge Analisa Torres’ ruling in favor of the crypto company, with many use cases being touted for its native token XRP. The most recent use case to surface is a Spot XRP ETF, and Bloomberg analyst James Seyffart has quickly weighed in on the possibility of this happening. </p>
<h2>How Possible Is A Spot XRP ETF?</h2>
<p>Seyffart, during an <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7OEaA9GdIHk" rel="nofollow">appearance</a> on Tony Edward’s Thinking Crypto Podcast, explained that XRP would need to be listed on the Chicago Mercantile Exchange (CME) before the SEC can approve a Spot XRP ETF. </p>

<p>This argument stems from the SEC’s requirement for a regulated market of significant size in the underlying asset. Relatively, exchanges looking to list a Spot Bitcoin ETF are, in hopes of gaining approval, relying on the fact that the CME Bitcoin futures, which happen to be a regulated market, provide significant size to provide necessary data and insights for any spot market. </p>
<p>So Seyffart also believes that any Spot XRP ETF application will also need to fulfill the requirement of the token having a significant market size that can be used to provide any data and insights needed to prevent fraud and market manipulation. To achieve this and easily get the SEC’s approval, listing XRP futures on a prominent derivative exchange like CME would be the way to go, in his opinion. </p>
<p>Despite his remarks, Seyffart isn’t so optimistic about a Spot XRP ETF launching anytime as, according to him, this isn’t something he sees “materializing in the foreseeable future.”</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/bB5Mj1YW/" alt="Ripple (XRP) price chart from Tradingview.com (XRP ETF)" width="2884" height="1746"/></p>

<h2>Little Or No Demand Is A Hindrance</h2>
<p>Another notable highlight from Seyffart’s remarks was when he suggested that there was little or no demand for an XRP ETF, something which he believes is integral if we are to see any ETF application. </p>
<p>However, there is reason to believe this assumption may not be outrightly correct, as certain figures suggest an increasing demand for XRP, notably among institutional investors. </p>

<p>Last month, a <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/ripple-xrp-sales-jump-in-2023/">report</a> stated how XRP’s sales had jumped significantly this year, with over 2.22 billion XRP sold since the beginning of the year. Furthermore, according to a more recent <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-outflows-touch-4-month-high/" rel="nofollow">report</a>, the token recorded an institutional inflow of $0.5 million two weeks ago.</p>
<p>Ripple’s XRP Ledger is also going head to head with the foremost Bitcoin and Ethereum networks, as it has <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/xrp-daily-transactions-surpass-ethereum/">recorded</a> an increase in daily transactions since the beginning of August. This record has seen it surpass market leader Ethereum in terms of daily transactions conducted on both networks. </p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/iStock-1436037805-1.jpg?fit=460%2C307" width="460" height="307" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">547521</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Speculators Retreat As Long-Term Holders Double Down Since $69,000 Peak</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-speculators-retreat-as-long-term-holders-double-down/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samuel Edyme]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 14:00:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[glassnode]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=547516</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Bitcoin market continues to reveal trends and patterns, vital for both long-term holders and short-term speculators. Notably, since Bitcoin reached its all-time high of $69,000, speculators, who play a pivotal role in the market, now hold less of the cryptocurrency. This insight comes from prominent analytics firm Glassnode in its &#8220;The Week On-Chain&#8221; newsletter, which delves into the market&#8217;s dynamics and potential implications. Bitcoin Stagnation And Role Of Short-Term Holders The Bitcoin market has witnessed a prolonged period marked by relatively steady BTC price action. This phase has sown seeds of discontent among market participants, prompting speculation about potential downside risks. Related Reading: Bernstein Predicts Spot ETFs Could Claim 10% Of Bitcoin’s Market If Greenlit So far, the asset only hovers between $29,000 and $25,000 price points creating a tug-of-war between the bulls and bears in that price zones. A noteworthy shift in the Bitcoin market is the dwindling enthusiasm of its short-term traders, commonly referred to as speculators. This group, typically driven by the prospects of swift gains, seems to be re-evaluating its stance, perhaps deterred by the recent lack of significant price movement. Glassnode points out that the market share of these short-term holders has ebbed to a mere 2.56 million BTC. This stands in stark contrast to their presence in October 2021, right before Bitcoin soared to its record high. Yet, while these speculators recede, long-term holders, often viewed as the bedrock of the Bitcoin community, are seemingly undeterred. Their stronghold over the currency is tightening, with a current hold of 14.6M BTC, the highest ever recorded. The report noted: Overall, this suggests that conviction of Bitcoin investors does remain impressively high, and very few are willing to liquidate their holdings. A Market Teetering On Decisions The distinction in purchase prices between the two investor classes has been highlighted as a potential concern. According to the newsletter, Short-term speculators, having bought at a higher average price of $28,600, might be more susceptible to incurring losses with even a modest dip in Bitcoin&#8217;s price. On the other hand, long-term investors, with an aggregate purchase price substantially lower at around $20,300, seem more cushioned against market volatility. This variance in purchasing prices, combined with the contrasting reactions of the two investor groups, paints a picture of a market in flux, divided between those who believe in Bitcoin&#8217;s long-term value and those swayed by its immediate price trajectories. Related Reading: Bitcoin Price Key Indicators Suggest A Strong Case For More Losses Glassnode believes that &#8220;The separation between these two cost basis is an indicator that many recent buyers have a relatively elevated acquisition price.&#8221; Despite the current market uncertainty, an underlying sentiment that remains clear is the confidence of Bitcoin&#8217;s stalwarts. Their increasing hold suggests a steadfast belief in Bitcoin&#8217;s potential, even as speculators seem to waver amid its current price downturn. Featured image from Unsplash, Chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Bitcoin market continues to reveal trends and patterns, vital for both long-term holders and short-term speculators. Notably, since Bitcoin reached its all-time high of $69,000, speculators, who play a pivotal role in the market, now hold less of the cryptocurrency.</p>
<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w g0rxnol2" dir="ltr">This insight comes from prominent analytics firm Glassnode in its &#8220;The Week On-Chain&#8221; <a href="https://insights.glassnode.com/the-week-onchain-week-33-2023/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">newsletter</a>, which delves into the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bernstein-predicts-spot-etfs-bitcoin-market-if-greenlit/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">market&#8217;s dynamics</a> and potential implications.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Stagnation And Role Of Short-Term Holders</h2>
<p>The Bitcoin market has witnessed a prolonged period marked by relatively steady BTC price action. This phase has sown seeds of discontent among market participants, prompting speculation about potential downside risks.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bernstein-predicts-spot-etfs-bitcoin-market-if-greenlit/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Bernstein Predicts Spot ETFs Could Claim 10% Of Bitcoin’s Market If Greenlit</a></p>
<p>So far, the asset only hovers <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/will-bitcoin-price-crash-similarly-to-2019-and-2020/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">between $29,000 and $25,000 price points</a> creating a tug-of-war between the bulls and bears in that price zones.</p>
<p>A noteworthy shift in the Bitcoin market is the dwindling enthusiasm of its short-term traders, commonly referred to as speculators. This group, typically driven by the prospects of swift gains, seems to be re-evaluating its stance, perhaps deterred by the recent lack of <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-price-will-reach-1-million/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">significant price movement</a>.</p>
<p>Glassnode points out that the market share of these short-term holders has ebbed to a mere 2.56 million BTC. This stands in stark contrast to their presence in October 2021, right before Bitcoin soared to its record high.</p>
<p>Yet, while these speculators recede, long-term holders, often viewed as the bedrock of the Bitcoin community, are seemingly undeterred. Their stronghold over the currency is tightening, with a current hold of 14.6M BTC, the highest ever recorded.</p>
<p>The report noted:</p>
<blockquote><p>Overall, this suggests that conviction of Bitcoin investors does remain impressively high, and very few are willing to liquidate their holdings.</p></blockquote>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://i0.wp.com/s3.cointelegraph.com/uploads/2023-08/1b1baec0-9e8c-4d3d-945b-1799d6b763ed.png?resize=1800%2C1013&#038;ssl=1" alt="Bitcoin Holders Threshold chart. " width="1800" height="1013"  data-recalc-dims="1"/>
<h2>A Market Teetering On Decisions</h2>
<p>The distinction in purchase prices between the two investor classes has been highlighted as a potential concern. According to the newsletter, Short-term speculators, having bought at a higher average price of $28,600, might be more susceptible to incurring losses with even a modest dip in Bitcoin&#8217;s price. </p>
<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w g0rxnol2" dir="ltr">On the other hand, long-term investors, with an aggregate purchase price substantially lower at around $20,300, seem more cushioned against <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/this-dreaded-candlestick-formation-just-printed-bitcoin-to-18k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">market volatility</a>.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://i0.wp.com/s3.cointelegraph.com/uploads/2023-08/b9e2046f-9a0e-4ff4-a7f1-d93f00ffc824.png?resize=1194%2C681&#038;ssl=1" alt="Bitcoin Holders On-chain Cost Basis." width="1194" height="681"  data-recalc-dims="1"/>
<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w g0rxnol2" dir="ltr">This variance in purchasing prices, combined with the contrasting reactions of the two investor groups, paints a picture of a market in flux, divided between those who believe in Bitcoin&#8217;s long-term value and those swayed by its immediate price trajectories.</p>

<p dir="ltr">Glassnode believes that &#8220;The separation between these two cost basis is an indicator that many recent buyers have a relatively elevated acquisition price.&#8221;</p>
<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w g0rxnol2" dir="ltr">Despite the current market uncertainty, an underlying sentiment that remains clear is the confidence of Bitcoin&#8217;s stalwarts. Their increasing hold suggests a steadfast belief in Bitcoin&#8217;s potential, even as speculators seem to waver amid its <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-losses-29000/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">current price downturn</a>.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/hcuv36QD/" alt="Bitcoin (BTC)’s price chart on TradingView" width="2770" height="1408"/>
<p dir="ltr">Featured image from Unsplash, Chart from TradingView</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/andre-francois-mckenzie-iGYiBhdNTpE-unsplash-2.jpg?fit=460%2C307" width="460" height="307" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">547516</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Best-Selling Author Touts Buy XRP Now, But This Price Is Crucial</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/best-selling-author-buy-xrp-now-but-this-price-crucial/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jake Simmons]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 12:50:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LindaPJones]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrp]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=547499</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Linda P. Jones has identified a life-changing buying opportunity for XRP, urging investors to capitalize on this moment. Jones, known for her works, &#8220;3 Steps to Quantum Wealth: The Wealth Heiress&#8217; Guide to Financial Freedom by Investing in Cryptocurrencies&#8221; and &#8220;You&#8217;re Already a Wealth Heiress, Now Think and Act Like One: 6 Practical Steps to Make It a Reality Now!&#8221; took to Twitter today, sharing her bullish perspective on several cryptocurrency assets. She fervently states, &#8220;Gave a wake up call to VIP Experience members today: If you&#8217;re not investing in XRP at $0.60, XDC at $0.06, ALGO at $0.10, XLM at $0.10…don&#8217;t come crying to me when they are higher!&#8221; Drawing attention to the present market valuations, she highlighted that many of these assets are currently &#8220;selling at a deep discount&#8221;. She further advised her followers and readers to take a decisive stance on their investments. &#8220;You need to be scooping them up, without a perfectionist mindset of being too afraid to buy if it isn&#8217;t the absolute bottom.&#8221; Related Reading: Institutional XRP Holdings Rise Rapidly Following Ripple’s Win Over SEC While Jones accentuates the potential gains of these assets, she equally emphasizes the investor mindset. Suggesting that the pursuit of the perfect buying point might be a fallacy, she stated, &#8220;You need to be scooping them up, without a perfectionist mindset of being too afraid to buy if it isn&#8217;t the absolute bottom.&#8221; Emphasizing the timely nature of the present market conditions, Jones opines, &#8220;These are life changing prices, but you must take action. The least amount of risk is when prices are low, which is NOW. Could they go lower? Yes. So what, they will likely be a LOT higher in 2 years or sooner, so what are you waiting for?&#8221; XRP Price Analysis A price analysis of the 1-day chart suggests that the XRP price is at a crucial point following the summary judgement in the Ripple vs. SEC case. Related Reading: SEC Asks Court To File Interlocutory Appeal Vs. Ripple, XRP Price Stable At press time, XRP was trading at $0.59, down more than 35% from its yearly high at $0.93 following the summary judgment in the Ripple against the US Securities And Exchange Commission (SEC) case. Before the verdict was announced, XRP was trading at $0.47, meaning that the XRP price has already lost most of its gains following the euphoria over Ripple&#8217;s victory. A look at the 1-day chart shows that XRP found support at the 100-day EMA at $0.5782 yesterday. Subsequently, XRP bulls managed to stage a small recovery. However, XRP is not out of the woods yet as the correction could continue unless the price shows a signal of trend reversal on the shorter timeframes. A first step would be to break above the 61.8% Fibonacci retracement level at $0.6340. A strong confirmation would be a spike above $0.69 where the 50% Fibonacci retracement level is located. In a bearish scenario, XRP also loses the 100-day EMA and falls towards the 200-day EMA at $0.5256. The level can be interpreted as the most crucial support at the moment. If the &#8220;bull line&#8221; fails to hold, the XRP price could face a crash to pre-Ripple ruling levels. Featured image from Outlook India, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Linda P. Jones has identified a life-changing buying opportunity for XRP, urging investors to capitalize on this moment. Jones, known for her works, &#8220;3 Steps to Quantum Wealth: The Wealth Heiress&#8217; Guide to Financial Freedom by Investing in Cryptocurrencies&#8221; and &#8220;You&#8217;re Already a Wealth Heiress, Now Think and Act Like One: 6 Practical Steps to Make It a Reality Now!&#8221; took to Twitter today, sharing her bullish perspective on several cryptocurrency assets.</p>
<p>She fervently <a href="https://twitter.com/LindaPJones/status/1691653081866621062" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">states</a>, &#8220;Gave a wake up call to VIP Experience members today: If you&#8217;re not investing in XRP at $0.60, XDC at $0.06, ALGO at $0.10, XLM at $0.10…don&#8217;t come crying to me when they are higher!&#8221; Drawing attention to the present market valuations, she highlighted that many of these assets are currently &#8220;selling at a deep discount&#8221;.</p>
<p>She further advised her followers and readers to take a decisive stance on their investments. &#8220;You need to be scooping them up, without a perfectionist mindset of being too afraid to buy if it isn&#8217;t the absolute bottom.&#8221;</p>

<p>While Jones accentuates the potential gains of these assets, she equally emphasizes the investor mindset. Suggesting that the pursuit of the perfect buying point might be a fallacy, she stated, &#8220;You need to be scooping them up, without a perfectionist mindset of being too afraid to buy if it isn&#8217;t the absolute bottom.&#8221;</p>
<p>Emphasizing the timely nature of the present market conditions, Jones opines, &#8220;These are life changing prices, but you must take action. The least amount of risk is when prices are low, which is NOW. Could they go lower? Yes. So what, they will likely be a LOT higher in 2 years or sooner, so what are you waiting for?&#8221;</p>
<h2>XRP Price Analysis</h2>
<p>A price analysis of the 1-day chart suggests that the XRP price is at a crucial point following the summary judgement in the Ripple vs. SEC case.</p>

<p>At press time, XRP was trading at $0.59, down more than 35% from its yearly high at $0.93 following the summary judgment in the Ripple against the US Securities And Exchange Commission (SEC) case. Before the verdict was announced, XRP was trading at $0.47, meaning that the XRP price has already lost most of its gains following the euphoria over Ripple&#8217;s victory.</p>
<p>A look at the 1-day chart shows that XRP found support at the 100-day EMA at $0.5782 yesterday. Subsequently, XRP bulls managed to stage a small recovery. However, XRP is not out of the woods yet as the correction could continue unless the price shows a signal of trend reversal on the shorter timeframes.</p>
<p>A first step would be to break above the 61.8% Fibonacci retracement level at $0.6340. A strong confirmation would be a spike above $0.69 where the 50% Fibonacci retracement level is located.</p>
<p>In a bearish scenario, XRP also loses the 100-day EMA and falls towards the 200-day EMA at $0.5256. The level can be interpreted as the most crucial support at the moment. If the &#8220;bull line&#8221; fails to hold, the XRP price could face a crash to pre-Ripple ruling levels.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-547511 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/XRPUSD_2023-08-16_12-17-40.png?resize=3628%2C1672" alt="XRP price" width="3628" height="1672" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/XRPUSD_2023-08-16_12-17-40.png?resize=3628%2C1672?w=3628 3628w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/XRPUSD_2023-08-16_12-17-40.png?resize=3628%2C1672?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/XRPUSD_2023-08-16_12-17-40.png?resize=3628%2C1672?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/XRPUSD_2023-08-16_12-17-40.png?resize=3628%2C1672?w=860 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/XRPUSD_2023-08-16_12-17-40.png?resize=3628%2C1672?w=1536 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/XRPUSD_2023-08-16_12-17-40.png?resize=3628%2C1672?w=2048 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/XRPUSD_2023-08-16_12-17-40.png?resize=3628%2C1672?w=750 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/XRPUSD_2023-08-16_12-17-40.png?resize=3628%2C1672?w=1140 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/XRPUSD_2023-08-16_12-17-40.png?resize=3628%2C1672?w=3000 3000w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" data-recalc-dims="1"/>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/IMAGE_1689591848.jpg?fit=460%2C259" width="460" height="259" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">547499</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>SEI Token Breaks Into Top 100 One Day Post-Debut On Major Exchanges</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/altcoin/sei-into-top-100-post-debut-on-major-exchanges/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Opeyemi Sule]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 11:50:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEI]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sei Foundation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sei Labs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEIUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=547471</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[SEI, the native token of the Sei blockchain, appears to be gaining massive traction a day after its debut on multiple major exchanges. On Tuesday, August 15, Binance, Bybit, Bitget, Kucoin, and Kucoin jointly listed the token on their trading platforms. On the same day, Sei Labs, the company behind the network, announced the launch of the beta mainnet phase after a successful alpha phase. According to the developers, more than 7.5 million unique wallets and 400 million transactions were registered during the testnet phase. The Sei Mainnet beta, Pacific-1, is here. Users may now bridge and stake their $SEI at https://t.co/kllP3XP3dZ pic.twitter.com/dMdocFMba0 — Sei 🚢 (@SeiNetwork) August 15, 2023 Sei network is a layer 1 blockchain built on the Cosmos software development kit. It claims to offer a scaling solution for decentralized exchanges (DEXs) with its matching engine and order front-run prevention tools. SEI Breaks Into Top 100 Crypto Ranking &#8211; Price Overview  SEI experienced a surge in price upon its listing on various exchanges, notching more than a 650% gain within an hour. On Binance, the token opened trading at around $0.0639 before ballooning to a high of $0.4812.  However, SEI has since experienced a slight price correction, trading about 44% beneath the recent high. As of this writing, the token changes hands at $0.2669, with a substantial 16% price jump in the past hour. Related Reading: Shiba Inu Bulls On The Horizon? Substantial Selling Pressure Seen Dropping CoinGecko data shows that SEI has been experiencing a massive surge in market activity, with its trading volume standing at $1,074,696,599. This represents a significant 5,156.5% increase in the last 24 hours. Likewise, the market cap of SEI has been on a steady rise in the past day. With a market cap of roughly $445.4 million, the cryptocurrency sits at the 92nd position on CoinGecko’s crypto ranking. Interestingly, traders seem to have anticipated the current performance of SEI prior to its multiple exchange listings. Data from DEX Aevo’s pre-listing futures revealed that the token could reach nearly half a billion market cap upon debut on centralized exchanges. The initial circulating supply of SEI is 1.8 billion &#8211; 18% of the total supply of 10 billion tokens. The &#8220;Cross-Chain&#8221; Airdrop On Tuesday, August 15, the Sei Foundation unveiled the details of its upcoming &#8220;cross-chain&#8221; airdrop for whitelisted users who bridge qualifying assets into the network. Some of the eligible tokens include USDC, ETH, WBTC (Wrapped Bitcoin), etc. Related Reading: Ethereum Price Prints Bearish Technical Pattern, Why It Could Extend Losses The foundation revealed that active users on just select blockchains, including Solana, Ethereum, Arbitrum, Polygon, Binance Smart Chain, and Osmosis, can participate in the airdrop. According to the announcement, the cross-chain airdrop will be open for claiming at the public mainnet launch. SEIUSDT trading at $0.2450 on the 4-hour timeframe &#124; Source: SEIUSDT chart on TradingView Featured image from The Independent, chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>SEI, the native token of the Sei blockchain, appears to be gaining massive traction a day after its debut on multiple major exchanges. On Tuesday, August 15, Binance, Bybit, Bitget, Kucoin, and Kucoin jointly listed the token on their trading platforms.</p>
<p>On the same day, Sei Labs, the company behind the network, <a href="https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/sei-launches-mainnet-301900263.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">announced</a> the launch of the beta mainnet phase after a successful alpha phase. According to the developers, more than 7.5 million unique wallets and 400 million transactions were registered during the testnet phase.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">The Sei Mainnet beta, Pacific-1, is here.</p>
<p>Users may now bridge and stake their <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24SEI&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$SEI</a> at <a href="https://t.co/kllP3XP3dZ" rel="nofollow">https://t.co/kllP3XP3dZ</a> <a href="https://t.co/dMdocFMba0" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/dMdocFMba0</a></p>
<p>— Sei <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f6a2.png" alt="🚢" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> (@SeiNetwork) <a href="https://twitter.com/SeiNetwork/status/1691428580276752385?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">August 15, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p>Sei network is a layer 1 blockchain built on the Cosmos software development kit. It claims to offer a scaling solution for decentralized exchanges (DEXs) with its matching engine and order front-run prevention tools.</p>
<h2>SEI Breaks Into Top 100 Crypto Ranking &#8211; Price Overview </h2>
<p>SEI experienced a surge in price upon its listing on various exchanges, notching more than a 650% gain within an hour. On Binance, the token opened trading at around $0.0639 before ballooning to a high of $0.4812. </p>
<p>However, SEI has since experienced a slight price correction, trading about 44% beneath the recent high. As of this writing, the token changes hands at $0.2669, with a substantial 16% price jump in the past hour.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/shiba-inu-bulls-on-the-horizon-substantial-selling-pressure-seen-dropping/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Shiba Inu Bulls On The Horizon? Substantial Selling Pressure Seen Dropping</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/sei" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">CoinGecko data</a> shows that SEI has been experiencing a massive surge in market activity, with its trading volume standing at $1,074,696,599. This represents a significant 5,156.5% increase in the last 24 hours.</p>
<p>Likewise, the market cap of SEI has been on a steady rise in the past day. With a market cap of roughly $445.4 million, the cryptocurrency sits at the 92nd position on CoinGecko’s crypto ranking.</p>
<p>Interestingly, traders seem to have anticipated the current performance of SEI prior to its multiple exchange listings. Data from DEX <a href="https://app.aevo.xyz/perpetual/sei" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Aevo’s pre-listing futures</a> revealed that the token could reach nearly half a billion market cap upon debut on centralized exchanges.</p>
<p>The initial circulating supply of SEI is 1.8 billion &#8211; 18% of the total supply of 10 billion tokens.</p>
<h2>The &#8220;Cross-Chain&#8221; Airdrop</h2>
<p>On Tuesday, August 15, the Sei Foundation unveiled the details of its upcoming &#8220;cross-chain&#8221; airdrop for whitelisted users who bridge qualifying assets into the network. Some of the eligible tokens include USDC, ETH, WBTC (Wrapped Bitcoin), etc.</p>

<p>The foundation revealed that active users on just select blockchains, including Solana, Ethereum, Arbitrum, Polygon, Binance Smart Chain, and Osmosis, can participate in the airdrop. According to the announcement, the cross-chain airdrop will be open for claiming at the public mainnet launch.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/uuSO0SZ3/" alt="SEI" width="902" height="587"/></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Price-hike.jpg?fit=460%2C288" width="460" height="288" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">547471</post-id>	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
