<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
>

<channel>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.newsbtc.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<description>Bitcoin &#38; cryptocurrency news today, price &#38; technical analysis</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 02:23:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Active Addresses Sharply Decline Despite Transaction Demand, Why?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-addresses-decline-transaction-demand-why/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hououin Kyouma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 03:00:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin active addresses]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Transaction Demand]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin transactions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=532990</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Data shows that Bitcoin active addresses have sharply dropped despite the high transaction demand; here&#8217;s why this may be happening. Bitcoin Active Addresses Have Seen A Sharp Plunge Recently According to the latest weekly report from Glassnode, the active addresses are around cyclical lows of 566,000. The &#8220;active addresses&#8221; metric measures the daily number of unique Bitcoin addresses participating in some transaction activity on the blockchain. By &#8220;unique,&#8221; what&#8217;s meant here is that the indicator only checks whether an address has been involved in a transfer at least once. This implies that regardless of how many transactions an address might make, its contribution to the active addresses metric will remain just one unit. This restriction exists because the number of unique addresses can serve as an analog to the number of unique users visiting the blockchain, thus providing an estimate for the daily users on the network. Another indicator that&#8217;s made for tracking activity on the Bitcoin blockchain is the &#8220;transaction count,&#8221; which, as its name already suggests, tells us about the daily total number of transfers taking place on the network. When this metric has a high value, it naturally means that many transactions occur on the blockchain. Such indicator values imply a high demand for using the network currently, but the metric can&#8217;t say anything about how the activity is distributed; that&#8217;s where the active addresses indicator comes in. Related Reading: Bitcoin Miners Continue To Sell, Bearish Sign? Now, here is a chart that shows the trend in the Bitcoin transaction count (as well as its 30-day and 365-day simple moving averages) over the entire history of the asset: The value of the metric seems to have sharply surged recently &#124; Source: Glassnode's The Week Onchain - Week 20, 2023 As displayed in the above graph, the Bitcoin transaction count has recently seen a rapid rise and has hit a new all-time high of about 682,000 daily transfers. The reason behind this explosion in the transaction count is the emergence of the BRC-20 tokens, fungible tokens created on the BTC blockchain using the Ordinals protocol (a way to inscribe data like text and images directly into the chain). These BRC-20 tokens have started a new memecoin mania, with PEPE being the largest example of such a coin. The insanely fast popularity of these tokens has meant that the demand for transacting on the network is more than ever before. What about the active addresses, though? Is this indicator also seeing a rise? Looks like the metric has plunged recently &#124; Source: Glassnode's The Week Onchain - Week 20, 2023 From the chart, it&#8217;s apparent that the active addresses observed a rise at first, but then it plunged to a value of 566,000 addresses per day, around the current cyclical low. Related Reading: Stablecoins Interest Spikes As Traders Look To Exit Market This would mean that while the demand for making transactions is super high right now, the demand isn&#8217;t actually coming from a large number of users but a rather small number of them who are constantly making repeat transfers. &#8220;This is a curious scenario, whereby many BRC-20 users appear to have re-used their Bitcoin addresses,&#8221; explains Glassnode. &#8220;Perhaps due to having more familiarity with how account-based chains like Ethereum or Solana operate, and less so with the Bitcoin UTXO system.&#8221; BTC Price At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading around $27,400, down 1% in the last week. BTC has shot up over the last 24 hours &#124; Source: BTCUSD on TradingView Featured image from Kanchanara on Unsplash.com, charts from TradingView.com, Glassnode.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Data shows that Bitcoin active addresses have sharply dropped despite the high transaction demand; here&#8217;s why this may be happening.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Active Addresses Have Seen A Sharp Plunge Recently</h2>
<p>According to the latest weekly report from <a href="https://insights.glassnode.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Glassnode</a>, the active addresses are around cyclical lows of 566,000. The &#8220;<a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/litecoin/litecoin-ltc-records-spike-in-active-addresses-following-launch-of-ltc-20-santiment/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">active addresses</a>&#8221; metric measures the daily number of unique Bitcoin addresses participating in some transaction activity on the blockchain.</p>
<p>By &#8220;unique,&#8221; what&#8217;s meant here is that the indicator only checks whether an address has been involved in a transfer at least once. This implies that regardless of how many transactions an address might make, its contribution to the active addresses metric will remain just one unit.</p>
<p>This restriction exists because the number of unique addresses can serve as an analog to the number of unique users visiting the blockchain, thus providing an estimate for the daily users on the network.</p>
<p>Another indicator that&#8217;s made for tracking activity on the Bitcoin blockchain is the &#8220;<a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/ripple/ripple-transaction-count-down-65-will-this-affect-xrp-prices/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">transaction count</a>,&#8221; which, as its name already suggests, tells us about the daily total number of transfers taking place on the network.</p>
<p>When this metric has a high value, it naturally means that many transactions occur on the blockchain. Such indicator values imply a high demand for using the network currently, but the metric can&#8217;t say anything about how the activity is distributed; that&#8217;s where the active addresses indicator comes in.</p>

<p>Now, here is a chart that shows the trend in the Bitcoin transaction count (as well as its 30-day and 365-day simple moving averages) over the entire history of the asset:</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone aligncenter" src="https://insights.glassnode.com/content/images/2023/05/02_txcountmomentu.png" alt="Bitcoin Transaction Count" width="2000" height="1152"/></p>

<p>As displayed in the above graph, the Bitcoin transaction count has recently seen a rapid rise and has hit a new all-time high of about 682,000 daily transfers.</p>
<p>The reason behind this explosion in the transaction count is the emergence of the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/brc-20-tokens-lose-40-market-cap-in-7-days-heres-why/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">BRC-20 tokens</a>, fungible tokens created on the BTC blockchain using the Ordinals protocol (a way to inscribe data like text and images directly into the chain).</p>
<p>These BRC-20 tokens have started a new memecoin mania, with PEPE being the largest example of such a coin. The insanely fast popularity of these tokens has meant that the demand for transacting on the network is more than ever before.</p>
<p>What about the active addresses, though? Is this indicator also seeing a rise?</p>
<p><img decoding="async" class="aligncenter" src="https://insights.glassnode.com/content/images/2023/05/04_actadrmomentum.png" loading="lazy"/></p>

<p>From the chart, it&#8217;s apparent that the active addresses observed a rise at first, but then it plunged to a value of 566,000 addresses per day, around the current cyclical low.</p>

<p>This would mean that while the demand for making transactions is super high right now, the demand isn&#8217;t actually coming from a large number of users but a rather small number of them who are constantly making repeat transfers.</p>
<p>&#8220;This is a curious scenario, whereby many BRC-20 users appear to have re-used their Bitcoin addresses,&#8221; explains Glassnode. &#8220;Perhaps due to having more familiarity with how account-based chains like Ethereum or Solana operate, and less so with the Bitcoin UTXO system.&#8221;</p>
<h2>BTC Price</h2>
<p>At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading around $27,400, down 1% in the last week.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium aligncenter" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/h7GuLpH8/" alt="Bitcoin Price Chart" width="1533" height="911"/></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/kanchanara-A6a-io0y02o-unsplash-460x306.jpg" width="460" height="306" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Price Just Saw Key Technical Correction But 100 SMA Is Still Strong</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-strong-27k/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 02:23:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xbtusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=533072</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin price is correcting gains and trading below $27,500. BTC must stay above the 100 hourly SMA to start a fresh increase in the near term. Bitcoin struggled to climb above $27,500 and started a downside correction. The price is trading above $26,600 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average. There is a key rising channel forming with support near $27,000 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Kraken). The pair could start a fresh increase if it stays above $26,750 and the 100 hourly SMA. Bitcoin Price Corrects Gains Bitcoin price climbed higher above the $27,200 resistance zone. However, BTC struggled to clear the $27,500 resistance and started a downside correction. The price declined below the $27,250 level and the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $25,827 swing low to the $27,677 high. The price is now approaching key support near $27,000. There is also a key rising channel forming with support near $27,000 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair. Bitcoin price is now trading above $26,600 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average. Immediate resistance is now forming near the $27,250 level. The next major resistance is near the $27,500 level. Source: BTCUSD on TradingView.com A close above the $27,500 resistance might start a decent increase. The next key resistance is near $28,000, above which the price might climb toward the $28,300 resistance. Any more gains might send the price toward the $28,800 level in the coming sessions. More Losses in BTC? If Bitcoin’s price fails to remain stable above $27,000, it could continue to move down. Immediate support on the downside is near the $27,000 level and the channel trend line. The 100 hourly Simple moving average is also below the channel support. The next major support is near the $26,750 zone, below which the price might start a steady decline. In the stated case, it could revisit the $26,200 level. Any more losses might take Bitcoin toward the $26,000 level in the near term. The next major support could be $25,800. Technical indicators: Hourly MACD – The MACD is now gaining pace in the bearish zone. Hourly RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BTC/USD is now below the 50 level. Major Support Levels – $27,000, followed by $26,750. Major Resistance Levels – $27,250, $27,500, and $28,300.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>Bitcoin price is correcting gains and trading below $27,500. BTC must stay above the 100 hourly SMA to start a fresh increase in the near term.</em></p>
<ul>
<li>Bitcoin struggled to climb above $27,500 and started a downside correction.</li>
<li>The price is trading above $26,600 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average.</li>
<li>There is a key rising channel forming with support near $27,000 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could start a fresh increase if it stays above $26,750 and the 100 hourly SMA.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Bitcoin Price Corrects Gains</h2>
<p>Bitcoin price climbed higher above the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-restarts-increase-27k/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">$27,200 resistance zone</a>. However, BTC struggled to clear the $27,500 resistance and started a downside correction.</p>
<p>The price declined below the $27,250 level and the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $25,827 swing low to the $27,677 high. The price is now approaching key support near $27,000. There is also a key rising channel forming with support near $27,000 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair.</p>
<p>Bitcoin price is now trading above $26,600 and the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-breakdown-25k/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">100 hourly Simple moving average</a>. Immediate resistance is now forming near the $27,250 level. The next major resistance is near the $27,500 level.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-11.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-533073" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-11.png" alt="Bitcoin Price" width="1950" height="1109" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-11.png 1950w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-11-460x262.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-11-860x489.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-11-768x437.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-11-1536x874.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-11-750x427.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-11-1140x648.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1950px) 100vw, 1950px"/></a></p>
<p>Source: <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BTCUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">BTCUSD on TradingView.com</a></p>
<p>A close above the $27,500 resistance might start a decent increase. The next key resistance is near $28,000, above which the price might climb toward the $28,300 resistance. Any more gains might send the price toward the $28,800 level in the coming sessions.</p>
<h2>More Losses in BTC?</h2>
<p>If Bitcoin’s price fails to remain stable above $27,000, it could continue to move down. Immediate support on the downside is near the $27,000 level and the channel trend line.</p>
<p>The 100 hourly Simple moving average is also below the channel support. The next major support is near the $26,750 zone, below which the price might start a steady decline. In the stated case, it could revisit the $26,200 level. Any more losses might take Bitcoin toward the $26,000 level in the near term. The next major support could be $25,800.</p>
<p>Technical indicators:</p>
<p>Hourly MACD – The MACD is now gaining pace in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>Hourly RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BTC/USD is now below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Levels – $27,000, followed by $26,750.</p>
<p>Major Resistance Levels – $27,250, $27,500, and $28,300.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/04/shutterstock_638895124-460x264.jpg" width="460" height="264" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Achilles Heel: How The Absence Of Settlement Infrastructure Is Holding Back The Market</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/crypto-achilles-heel-how-the-absence-of-settlement-infrastructure-is-holding-back-the-market/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 02:00:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blockchain technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=533040</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Ram Ahluwalia, the CEO of PeerNova, recently commented on the liquidity challenges the crypto market faces. According to Ahluwalia, the lack of a crypto bank settlement layer has led to a significant drying up of liquidity, hurting market makers and other participants in the industry. Related Reading: South Korea Crypto Exchanges Upbit And Bithumb Probed Over Lawmaker’s Scandal Crypto&#8217;s Biggest Challenge In traditional finance, the solution to this problem is provided by well-capitalized clearinghouse firms such as the Depository Trust and Clearing Corporation (DTCC), Chicago Mercantile Exchange (CME), and Intercontinental Exchange (ICE).  These firms act as the intermediary between buyers and sellers, assuming the role of the seller to every buyer and the buyer to every seller. This allows market makers to settle instantly with counterparties without taking on any counterparty or settlement risk. The role of clearinghouse firms in traditional finance is crucial for ensuring market stability and facilitating efficient trading. By assuming the counterparty risk of every trade, these firms provide confidence and security that encourages market participants to trade with one another.  However, the lack of a similar clearinghouse infrastructure in the crypto market has created significant challenges for market participants. Market makers and other participants are forced to assume counterparty and settlement risk without a centralized clearinghouse, which can be a significant barrier to trading. This has led to a drying up of liquidity in the market, making it more difficult for traders to find counterparties and execute trades. The Importance Of Infrastructure According to Ahluwalia, there is a growing need for a crypto bank settlement layer that can provide the same security and confidence as traditional clearinghouses to address this challenge. This would allow market makers to settle instantly with counterparties without taking on any counterparty or settlement risk. It would also help improve market stability and facilitate efficient trading, which would benefit the crypto market as a whole. However, the emergence of solutions such as Signature Bank’s Signet, a blockchain-based system and a competitor to Silvergate Capital Corp’s now-defunct SEN, has seemingly solved this problem for the crypto market, according to Ahluwalia.  Before the two crypto-friendly bank’s debacle, these solutions provided market makers with instant settlement, allowing them to trade with counterparties without having to tie up capital on multiple exchanges or wait for funds to clear, which is crucial for improving capital efficiency. The lack of it can lead to a drying up of liquidity in the market. On the other hand, Ram Ahluwalia raises an interesting question regarding using a secure high Transaction Per Second (TPS) blockchain to settle transactions instead of the banking settlement layer. While decentralization has grown in popularity, Ahluwalia believes that certain risks are associated with relying solely on blockchain technology for settlement. One major issue is compliance with sanctions screening laws issued by organizations like the Office of Foreign Assets Control (OFAC), a division of the US Treasury. This list includes North Korea, drug cartels, Russian oligarchs, and Iran. Market makers were previously able to rely on banks to ensure compliance with these laws, but without this layer of oversight, market makers would be assuming more risk.  Overall, for Ram Ahluwalia, in the context of a 24&#215;7 crypto market, the need for a 24&#215;7 bank instant settlement layer is critical to unlocking liquidity, and the recent loss of critical market infrastructure like Sen and SigNet has highlighted the importance of having a reliable settlement layer in place. Related Reading: Pro-XRP Lawyer Shares Opinion PEPE Explosion, What Did He Say? Featured image from iStock, a chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ram Ahluwalia, the CEO of PeerNova, recently <a href="https://twitter.com/ramahluwalia/status/1657924211770380290?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">commented </a>on the liquidity challenges the crypto market faces. According to Ahluwalia, the lack of a crypto bank settlement layer has led to a significant drying up of liquidity, hurting market makers and other participants in the industry.</p>

<h2><b>Crypto&#8217;s Biggest Challenge</b></h2>
<p>In traditional finance, the solution to this problem is provided by well-capitalized clearinghouse firms such as the Depository Trust and Clearing Corporation (DTCC), Chicago Mercantile Exchange (CME), and Intercontinental Exchange (ICE). </p>
<p>These firms act as the intermediary between buyers and sellers, assuming the role of the seller to every buyer and the buyer to every seller. This allows market makers to settle instantly with counterparties without taking on any counterparty or settlement risk.</p>
<p>The role of clearinghouse firms in traditional finance is crucial for ensuring market stability and facilitating efficient trading. By assuming the counterparty risk of every trade, these firms provide confidence and security that encourages market participants to trade with one another. </p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">1/ Crypto market liquidity has dried up significantly. </p>
<p>These are the consequences of a lack of a crypto bank settlement layer (SI &amp; Signature). </p>
<p>Market makers need a way to settle instantly with counterparties (eg, exchanges, HFs, other MMs). </p>
<p><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f9f5.png" alt="🧵" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /></p>
<p>&mdash; Ram Ahluwalia, higher for longer crypto CFA (@ramahluwalia) <a href="https://twitter.com/ramahluwalia/status/1657924211770380290?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">May 15, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p></p>
<p>However, the lack of a similar clearinghouse infrastructure in the crypto market has created significant challenges for market participants. Market makers and other participants are forced to assume counterparty and settlement risk without a centralized clearinghouse, which can be a significant barrier to trading. </p>
<p>This has led to a drying up of liquidity in the market, making it more difficult for traders to find counterparties and execute trades.</p>
<b>The Importance Of Infrastructure</b>
<p>According to Ahluwalia, there is a growing need for a crypto bank settlement layer that can provide the same security and confidence as traditional clearinghouses to address this challenge. This would allow market makers to settle instantly with counterparties without taking on any counterparty or settlement risk. </p>
<p>It would also help improve market stability and facilitate efficient trading, which would benefit the crypto market as a whole.</p>
<p>However, the emergence of solutions such as Signature Bank’s Signet, a blockchain-based system and a competitor to Silvergate Capital Corp’s now-defunct SEN, has seemingly solved this problem for the crypto market, according to Ahluwalia. </p>
<p>Before the two crypto-friendly bank’s debacle, these solutions provided market makers with instant settlement, allowing them to trade with counterparties without having to tie up capital on multiple exchanges or wait for funds to clear, which is crucial for improving capital efficiency. The lack of it can lead to a drying up of liquidity in the market.</p>
<p>On the other hand, Ram Ahluwalia raises an interesting question regarding using a secure high Transaction Per Second (TPS) blockchain to settle transactions instead of the banking settlement layer. While decentralization has grown in popularity, Ahluwalia believes that certain risks are associated with relying solely on blockchain technology for settlement.</p>
<p>One major issue is compliance with sanctions screening laws issued by organizations like the Office of Foreign Assets Control (OFAC), a division of the US Treasury. This list includes North Korea, drug cartels, Russian oligarchs, and Iran. Market makers were previously able to rely on banks to ensure compliance with these laws, but without this layer of oversight, market makers would be assuming more risk. </p>
<p>Overall, for Ram Ahluwalia, in the context of a 24&#215;7 crypto market, the need for a 24&#215;7 bank instant settlement layer is critical to unlocking liquidity, and the recent loss of critical market infrastructure like Sen and SigNet has highlighted the importance of having a reliable settlement layer in place.</p>

<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/osl87gL9/" alt="Crypto" width="1813" height="858"/>
<p>Featured image from iStock, a chart from TradingView.com </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/iStock-1294303261-460x345.jpg" width="460" height="345" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Analyst Predicts Altcoins Boom Ahead of Bitcoin Halving &#8211; Is it Time to Invest?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/altcoin/analyst-predicts-altcoins-boom-ahead-of-bitcoin-halving-is-it-time-to-invest/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Edyme]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 01:00:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[doge]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PEPE]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=532957</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Bitcoin and the altcoins market has since been on a rollercoaster ride over the last few months, with investors looking to make gains at every opportunity, especially with the current trend of the creation of meme coins such as PEPE, AIDOGE, TURBO, and so on. Now, with the Bitcoin halving around the corner, renowned crypto analyst Michael van de Poppe believes it is time to accumulate alternative coins. In a tweet, published earlier today, the analyst noted: For altcoins, the time to accumulate them has come. One year before the halving -&#62; time to buy those positions. Reached an important level here, which is also approx. 1 year before the halving. Time To Long The Altcoins Van de Poppe shared his analysis of historical data on altcoins&#8216; market cap dominance and identified crucial areas from 2016, where the altcoin price reaction ahead of a Bitcoin halving has gone according to his prediction. According to the analyst, multiple alternative coins may attract investments, leading to an increase in the altcoins&#8217; market cap dominance. Notably, Bitcoin halving is an event that occurs every 210,000 blocks mined, which is approximately every four years. It is a mechanism put in place to ensure the scarcity of Bitcoin, which helps to maintain its value. Related Reading: Is The Bitcoin Halving The Key For A BTC Price Bottom? During the halving, the block reward is cut in half, which decreases the supply of new Bitcoins being produced. The last Bitcoin halving took place on May 11, 2020, and the next one is expected to occur between April and May 2024. One year before the next Bitcoin halving is the perfect spot to take that buy position on altcoins, according to van de Poppe. His current projection is reinforced by the crucial level of the altcoins market cap dominance, which is approximately one year before the next Bitcoin halving. This is the time when the market experiences a rise in altcoin prices, which leads to an increase in demand for these cryptocurrencies. Though the analyst did not hint at which alternative coins to bag, he went ahead to further ask his nearly 657,000 Twitter followers, “Which ones are you accumulating?” Expected Reaction After The Bitcoin Halving Altcoins have been making significant strides in the crypto market, and their dominance has been on the rise. In the past year, we have seen the dominance of altcoins such as Ethereum (ETH), Binance Coin (BNB), Dogecoin (DOGE), and Cardano (ADA) increase significantly. According to CoinMarketCap, Bitcoin currently holds a market dominance of around 40%, while altcoins hold the remaining 60%. This is a significant shift from a year ago when Bitcoin&#8217;s dominance was close to 70%. Regardless, the altcoins market is expected to see a surge in price following the Bitcoin halving. In the past, altcoins have tended to outperform Bitcoin in the year following a halving event. This is mostly because investors often look for alternative investment opportunities when Bitcoin&#8217;s price becomes too high, and altcoins can provide an attractive alternative. Related Reading: Here Are The Altcoins That Are Outperforming Bitcoin Viewing from Van de Poppe&#8217;s current sentiment, the coming months could be a pivotal time for investors to accumulate altcoins as the Bitcoin halving is set to occur between April and May next year. Following the halving event, the block reward for Bitcoin miners confirming transactions on the network will decrease to 3.125 BTC. Featured image from iStock, Chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w" dir="ltr">The Bitcoin and the altcoins market has since been on a rollercoaster ride over the last few months, with investors looking to make gains at every opportunity, especially with the current trend of the creation of meme coins such as PEPE, AIDOGE, TURBO, and so on. </p>
<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w" dir="ltr">Now, with the Bitcoin halving around the corner, renowned crypto analyst Michael van de Poppe believes it is time to accumulate alternative coins. </p>
<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w" dir="ltr">In a tweet, published earlier today, the analyst <a href="https://twitter.com/CryptoMichNL/status/1658043878388256769?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">noted:</a></p>
<blockquote>
<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w" dir="ltr">For altcoins, the time to accumulate them has come. One year before the halving -&gt; time to buy those positions. Reached an important level here, which is also approx. 1 year before the halving.</p>
</blockquote>
<h2 dir="ltr">Time To Long The Altcoins</h2>
<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w" dir="ltr">Van de Poppe shared his analysis of historical data on <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/altcoin/top-3-altcoins-to-pay-attention-to-over-the-weekend/https://www.newsbtc.com/altcoin/top-3-altcoins-to-pay-attention-to-over-the-weekend/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">altcoins</a>&#8216; market cap dominance and identified crucial areas from 2016, where the altcoin price reaction ahead of a Bitcoin halving has gone according to his prediction.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium wp-image-532998" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/FwKOBJcXoAAYyGz-460x220.png" alt="Historical chart of altcoins market cap dominance" width="460" height="220" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/FwKOBJcXoAAYyGz-460x220.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/FwKOBJcXoAAYyGz-860x411.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/FwKOBJcXoAAYyGz-768x367.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/FwKOBJcXoAAYyGz-750x358.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/FwKOBJcXoAAYyGz-1140x544.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/FwKOBJcXoAAYyGz.png 1200w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px"/>
<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w" dir="ltr">According to the analyst, multiple alternative coins may attract investments, leading to an increase in the altcoins&#8217; market cap dominance.</p>
<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w" dir="ltr">Notably, Bitcoin halving is an event that occurs every 210,000 blocks mined, which is approximately every four years. It is a mechanism put in place to ensure the scarcity of Bitcoin, which helps to maintain its value.</p>

<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w" dir="ltr">During the halving, the block reward is cut in half, which decreases the supply of new Bitcoins being produced. The last Bitcoin halving took place on May 11, 2020, and the next one is expected to occur between April and May 2024.</p>
<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w" dir="ltr">One year before the next<a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/is-the-bitcoin-halving-the-key-for-a-btc-price-bottom/" target="_blank" rel="noopener "> Bitcoin halving</a> is the perfect spot to take that buy position on altcoins, according to van de Poppe. His current projection is reinforced by the crucial level of the altcoins market cap dominance, which is approximately one year before the next Bitcoin halving. </p>
<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w" dir="ltr">This is the time when the market experiences a rise in <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/stacks-stx-makes-10-price-spike/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">altcoin prices</a>, which leads to an increase in demand for these cryptocurrencies. </p>
<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w" dir="ltr">Though the analyst did not hint at which alternative coins to bag, he went ahead to further ask his nearly 657,000 Twitter followers, “Which ones are you accumulating?”</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Expected Reaction After The Bitcoin Halving</h2>
<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w" dir="ltr">Altcoins have been making significant strides in the crypto market, and their dominance has been on the rise. In the past year, we have seen the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/altcoin/here-are-the-altcoins-that-are-outperforming-bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">dominance of altcoins</a> such as Ethereum (ETH), <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/binance-coin/binance-coin-bnb-emerges-top-gainer-larger-altcoins/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Binance Coin (BNB)</a>, Dogecoin (DOGE), and Cardano (ADA) increase significantly.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/U1C3XOgH/" alt="Altcoins market cap price chart on TradingView" width="2768" height="1556"/>
<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w" dir="ltr">According to CoinMarketCap, Bitcoin currently holds a market dominance of around 40%, while altcoins hold the remaining 60%. This is a significant shift from a year ago when <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-btc-dominance-reclaims-june-levels/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Bitcoin&#8217;s dominance</a> was close to 70%. Regardless, the altcoins market is expected to see a surge in price following the Bitcoin halving. </p>
<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w" dir="ltr">In the past, altcoins have tended to outperform Bitcoin in the year following a halving event. This is mostly because investors often look for alternative investment opportunities when Bitcoin&#8217;s price becomes too high, and altcoins can provide an attractive alternative.</p>

<p dir="ltr">Viewing from Van de Poppe&#8217;s current sentiment, the coming months could be a pivotal time for investors to accumulate altcoins as the Bitcoin halving is set to occur between April and May next year. </p>
<p dir="ltr">Following the halving event, the block reward for Bitcoin miners confirming transactions on the network will decrease to 3.125 BTC.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Featured image from iStock, Chart from TradingView</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Altcoins-460x329.jpeg" width="460" height="329" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Shiba Inu Token Burn Hits 1.74 Billion In One Week, What&#8217;s The Current Status?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/shib/shiba-inu-token-burn-hits-1-74-billion-in-one-week-whats-the-current-status/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mike D.]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 00:10:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[SHIB]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[burn rate]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shiba Inu]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ShibBurn]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIBUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=533004</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Shiba Inu community has remained consistent in burning SHIB tokens. In a week, it sent a whopping 1,748,403,277 SHIB tokens to the project’s dead wallet. The burning mechanism is part of the processes that the Shiba Inu uses to maintain stability in its ecosystem. It is a strong measure to reclaim the value of the SHIB token as it removes more coins from circulation.  Community Burns 1.74B Tokens Through 20 Different Transactions According to data from the Shiba Inu burning portal, Shibburn, over 1.74 billion SHIB coins were burned within 7 days. The community completed the burning mechanism for the week through 20 different transactions. Related Reading: Bitcoin Tweets Surpass Dogecoin Despite Meme Coin Craze However, Shibburn disclosed that the Shiba Inu burn rate for the week decreased by 69.48% as against the previous week. The token burning data for the previous week showed that 3.98 billion SHIB tokens were sent to the dead wallet. The process was completed through 19 separate transactions by the community. The 24-hour token burning record has about 11.42 million Shiba Inu coins destroyed. This indicated a drop of 11.21% in the burn rate over the past day. Furthermore, Shibburn highlights the week&#8217;s top 3 SHIB token burners: Mysterious Wallet, Blaze Token, and SHIB Super Store. The Mysterious Wallet is among the top players in SHIB token burn as it destroyed 11.42 million SHIB coins through a single transaction. The wallet has been a major contributor to the SHIB token-burning mechanism. Besides its massive destruction of SHIB tokens, the wallet still holds over 335.79 billion SHIB worth more than $2.96 million. The prominent Shiba Inu Community-led burn project, SHIB Super Store, is the next top token burner. It sent about 10.45 million SHIB tokens to the protocol’s dead wallet on May 8 through a single transaction.  Related Reading: PEPE Outperforms Bitcoin In Social Media Buzz, Triggers Bullish Run For Frog Coin Blaze Token plays the highest contributory role, with the largest number of burned SHIB tokens for the week. The new token destroyed over 1.69 million SHIB coins through a single transaction on May 8.   Shiba Inu (SHIB) Price Action The Shiba Inu community has kept removing lots of SHIB tokens from circulation through the burning process. But SHIB’s value is yet to mark a remarkable recovery.  The entire crypto market has been battling with the influence of the bears pushing most assets’ prices to the bearish zone. At the time of writing, SHIB is trading at around $0.00000886, indicating a slight gain of 0.80% over the past 24 hours. Its market cap is $5.22 billion, with a 24-hour trading volume of $96 million. Its 7-day and 30-day price actions indicated a drop of 1.40% and 20.74%, respectively. Featured image from Pexels, chart from Tradingview.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Shiba Inu community has remained consistent in burning SHIB tokens. In a week, it sent a whopping 1,748,403,277 SHIB tokens to the project’s dead wallet.</p>
<p>The burning mechanism is part of the processes that the Shiba Inu uses to maintain stability in its ecosystem. It is a strong measure to reclaim the value of the SHIB token as it removes more coins from circulation. </p>
<h2>Community Burns 1.74B Tokens Through 20 Different Transactions</h2>
<p>According to data from the Shiba Inu burning portal, <a href="https://twitter.com/shibburn/status/1657596624770588672?" rel="nofollow">Shibburn</a>, over 1.74 billion SHIB coins were burned within 7 days. The community completed the burning mechanism for the week through 20 different transactions.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/dogecoin/bitcoin-tweets-surpass-dogecoin-despite-meme-coin-craze/">Bitcoin Tweets Surpass Dogecoin Despite Meme Coin Craze</a></p>
<p>However, Shibburn disclosed that the Shiba Inu burn rate for the week decreased by 69.48% as against the previous week.</p>
<p>The token burning data for the previous week showed that 3.98 billion SHIB tokens were sent to the dead wallet. The process was completed through 19 separate transactions by the community.</p>
<p>The 24-hour token burning record has about 11.42 million Shiba Inu coins destroyed. This indicated a drop of 11.21% in the burn rate over the past day.</p>
<p>Furthermore, Shibburn highlights the week&#8217;s top 3 SHIB token burners: Mysterious Wallet, Blaze Token, and SHIB Super Store.</p>
<p>The Mysterious Wallet is among the top players in SHIB token burn as it destroyed 11.42 million SHIB coins through a single transaction.</p>
<p>The wallet has been a major contributor to the SHIB token-burning mechanism. Besides its massive destruction of SHIB tokens, the wallet still holds over 335.79 billion SHIB worth more than $2.96 million. </p>
<p>The prominent Shiba Inu Community-led burn project, SHIB Super Store, is the next top token burner. It sent about <a href="https://twitter.com/shib_superstore/status/1655426187672403968?" rel="nofollow">10.45 million SHIB tokens</a> to the protocol’s dead wallet on May 8 through a single transaction. </p>

<p>Blaze Token plays the highest contributory role, with the largest number of burned SHIB tokens for the week. The new token destroyed over <a href="https://twitter.com/blaze_token/status/1655600614448013316?" rel="nofollow">1.69 million SHIB coins</a> through a single transaction on May 8.  </p>
<h2>Shiba Inu (SHIB) Price Action</h2>
<p>The Shiba Inu community has kept removing lots of SHIB tokens from circulation through the burning process. But SHIB’s value is yet to mark a remarkable recovery. </p>
<p>The entire crypto market has been battling with the influence of the bears pushing most assets’ prices to the bearish zone.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-533007 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/SHIBUSDT_2023-05-15_20-17-24-860x370.png" alt="Shiba Inu token Burn Hits 1.74 Billion in Just One Week, What&#039;s The Current Status?" width="860" height="370" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/SHIBUSDT_2023-05-15_20-17-24-860x370.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/SHIBUSDT_2023-05-15_20-17-24-460x198.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/SHIBUSDT_2023-05-15_20-17-24-768x331.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/SHIBUSDT_2023-05-15_20-17-24-1536x661.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/SHIBUSDT_2023-05-15_20-17-24-750x323.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/SHIBUSDT_2023-05-15_20-17-24-1140x491.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/SHIBUSDT_2023-05-15_20-17-24.png 1714w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/>
<p>At the time of writing, SHIB is trading at around $0.00000886, indicating a slight gain of 0.80% over the past 24 hours. Its market cap is $5.22 billion, with a 24-hour trading volume of $96 million. Its 7-day and 30-day price actions indicated a drop of 1.40% and 20.74%, respectively.</p>
<p>Featured image from Pexels, chart from Tradingview.com</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/shiba-inu-g674580f1a_1280-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Why Ethereum&#8217;s Yield Farming May Be The Most Exciting Thing In Crypto Right Now</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/ethereum/why-ethereums-yield-farming-may-be-the-most-exciting-thing-in-crypto-right-now/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 23:35:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=532973</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[As the world of cryptocurrencies evolves, Ethereum (ETH) investors are beginning to take notice of the power of yields and their potential impact on the crypto space. Yields, in essence, are the payments investors receive for holding cryptocurrencies, and they can come in many shapes and forms. How ETH Yields Could Revolutionize The Space One of the most important things to understand about yields is that they exist on a risk curve. This means that the percentage of yield paid out to investors is a function of supply and demand, as well as the perceived risk associated with the cryptocurrency in question.  Related Reading: Only 1,032 Addresses Control Over 60% Of All Litecoin (LTC) In Circulation For example, a cryptocurrency with a limited supply and high demand is likely to have a higher yield than one with a larger supply and lower demand. Similarly, a cryptocurrency that is perceived as less risky is likely to have a higher yield than one that is perceived as more risky. According to the crypto analyst and researcher Adam Cochran, this is where the potential of cryptocurrencies really shines through. By creating non-dilutive yields through the use of fees, cryptocurrencies can offer investors a way to earn passive income without the risk of inflation. This is particularly important in a world where traditional investments like savings accounts and bonds offer little to no yield. One cryptocurrency that is particularly well-positioned to take advantage of the power of yields is Ethereum. With its growing ecosystem of decentralized applications and smart contracts, ETH has the potential to generate significant fees for investors through its use as a platform for decentralized finance (DeFi) applications, according to Cochran.  For example, ETH staking currently offers yields in the 5%-7% range, while Synthtetix (SNX) staking can generate yields of up to 24% in external fees. Similarly, Curve (CRV) staking can generate yields of up to 15% in crvUSD fees. This means that billions of dollars in capital are now able to generate yields of more than 3% annual percentage yield (APY), which is a significant opportunity for investors. This is particularly important in a world where traditional investment opportunities like savings accounts and bonds offer little to no yield. As more investors become aware of the potential of cryptocurrencies to generate high yields with acceptable levels of risk, this can likely drive more interest and investment in the space. From HODLing To Yielding In its recent post, Adam Cochran emphasized the importance of focusing on asset productivity and real yield in the cryptocurrency space. Despite the current narrative that fundamentals don&#8217;t matter and memes and rhetoric dominate the market, Cochran believes that one day, the true value of assets will become apparent. According to Cochran, those who already possess assets have the advantage, as they stand to gain significant capital gains in addition to the 2% APY on the face value of the asset. This is particularly relevant in the cryptocurrency space, where prices can be extremely volatile and subject to sudden fluctuations. Related Reading: Bitcoin Miners Continue To Sell, Bearish Sign? Furthermore, Cochran predicts that as funds of increasing size start to realize the long-term potential of the cryptocurrency space, they will begin to invest heavily. This influx of capital will fundamentally change the finance industry, and those who have acquired a significant number of coins before this shift will reap the benefits. Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com ]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>As the world of cryptocurrencies evolves, Ethereum (ETH) investors are beginning to take notice of the power of yields and their potential impact on the crypto space. Yields, in essence, are the payments investors receive for holding cryptocurrencies, and they can come in many shapes and forms.</p>
<h2>How ETH Yields Could Revolutionize The Space</h2>
<p>One of the most important things to understand about yields is that they exist on a risk curve. This means that the percentage of yield paid out to investors is a function of supply and demand, as well as the perceived risk associated with the cryptocurrency in question. </p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/litecoin/only-1032-addresses-control-over-60-of-all-litecoin-ltc-in-circulation/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Only 1,032 Addresses Control Over 60% Of All Litecoin (LTC) In Circulation</a></p>
<p>For example, a cryptocurrency with a limited supply and high demand is likely to have a higher yield than one with a larger supply and lower demand. Similarly, a cryptocurrency that is perceived as less risky is likely to have a higher yield than one that is perceived as more risky.</p>
<p><a href="https://twitter.com/adamscochran/status/1657901863717548034?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">According</a> to the crypto analyst and researcher Adam Cochran, this is where the potential of cryptocurrencies really shines through.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">1/25</p>
<p>I think most people in crypto don&#39;t fully understand or appreciate yields and what it can mean for the crypto space at large &#8211; as it&#39;s one of the things that gets me incredibly bullish on the space.</p>
<p>And it&#39;s part of why I think ETH still has a 20x+ in its future.</p>
<p>&mdash; Adam Cochran (adamscochran.eth) (@adamscochran) <a href="https://twitter.com/adamscochran/status/1657901863717548034?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">May 15, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p></p>
<p>By creating non-dilutive yields through the use of fees, cryptocurrencies can offer investors a way to earn passive income without the risk of inflation. This is particularly important in a world where traditional investments like savings accounts and bonds offer little to no yield.</p>
<p>One cryptocurrency that is particularly well-positioned to take advantage of the power of yields is Ethereum. With its growing ecosystem of decentralized applications and smart contracts, ETH has the potential to generate significant fees for investors through its use as a platform for decentralized finance (DeFi) applications, according to Cochran. </p>
<p>For example, ETH staking currently offers yields in the 5%-7% range, while Synthtetix (SNX) staking can generate yields of up to 24% in external fees. Similarly, Curve (CRV) staking can generate yields of up to 15% in crvUSD fees. This means that billions of dollars in capital are now able to generate yields of more than 3% annual percentage yield (APY), which is a significant opportunity for investors.</p>
<p>This is particularly important in a world where traditional investment opportunities like savings accounts and bonds offer little to no yield. As more investors become aware of the potential of cryptocurrencies to generate high yields with acceptable levels of risk, this can likely drive more interest and investment in the space.</p>
<h2>From HODLing To Yielding</h2>
<p>In its recent post, Adam Cochran emphasized the importance of focusing on asset productivity and real yield in the cryptocurrency space. Despite the current narrative that fundamentals don&#8217;t matter and memes and rhetoric dominate the market, Cochran believes that one day, the true value of assets will become apparent.</p>
<p>According to Cochran, those who already possess assets have the advantage, as they stand to gain significant capital gains in addition to the 2% APY on the face value of the asset. This is particularly relevant in the cryptocurrency space, where prices can be extremely volatile and subject to sudden fluctuations.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-miners-continue-to-sell-bearish-sign/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Bitcoin Miners Continue To Sell, Bearish Sign?</a></p>
<p>Furthermore, Cochran predicts that as funds of increasing size start to realize the long-term potential of the cryptocurrency space, they will begin to invest heavily. </p>
<p>This influx of capital will fundamentally change the finance industry, and those who have acquired a significant number of coins before this shift will reap the benefits.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/XRIvB4nl/" alt="ETH" width="1814" height="858"/>
<p>Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/bastian-riccardi-trliGkPO7jY-unsplash-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Price Double Fractal Points To “Extended” Parabolic Rally</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-price-double-fractal-extended-parabolic-rally/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tony "The Bull"]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 23:01:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elliott wave principle]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=533068</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin price seems to merely be grinding upwards, with a dusting of chop in between. What corrections have arrived have been minimal, and are shockingly similar in both time and price. This fractal behavior could be a sign of an important Elliott Wave signal, that not only says that BTCUSD is about to go parabolic, but that the rally should be “extended” in its price movement. Bitcoin Price And Time Fractal Discovered After a small recovery from the November 2022 bottom in crypto markets, Bitcoin corrected sharply. The correction was short-lived, due to a sudden banking crisis emerging. BTCUSD then made another run higher to above $30,000 per coin, and is once again correcting after a second, roughly 50% upward move. Related Reading: Check Out This Shocking Pepe Coin Versus Bitcoin Comparison The two similar sized moves took placed in approximately the same amount of time. Superimposing a fractal of one above or below the other demonstrates just how similar they are in time and price. This sort of behavior is a fairly common occurence in Elliott Wave Principle called a 1-2/1-2 setup, and it could mean the crypto market is about to explode higher. Will BTC double after this double fractal? &#124; BTCUSD on TradingView.com All About The 1-2 1-2 Elliott Wave Setup The 1-2/1-2 is a phenomenon when a smaller degree wave 1 and 2 take on a similar shape and length of the previous, larger degree wave 1 and 2. Much like the first 1-2 is a larger degree wave, and the second 1-2 is a smaller degree wave, their appearance suggests an even larger degree wave will be extended. According to a description, a “1-2/1-2 structure is an indication that the larger degree impulse wave in development is extending.” “The 2nd wave 1-2 structure needs to be similar in proportions to that of the first 1-2 structure, not taking much more, if any more, time than the first.  Remember, you are actually seeing the development of a smaller degree impulse wave, so expect it to be a bit smaller than the larger degree structure.” “An extension suggests a massive elongation of the impulse pattern,” a website further reads. Related Reading: Has Bitcoin Completed The Perfect Pullback After a completed wave 2 correction, wave 3 should begin. However, if price stops short of expectations and forms a similar sized pattern as the first waves 1 and 2, it suggests a second set of waves 1 and 2 that help increase the size of the overall wave 3 that was first anticipated. This type of behavior has been spotted in not only Bitcoin. It is also evident in Chainlink, Litecoin, and the Total Crypto Market Cap chart. Several coins exhibiting the pattern could point to full participation across the market in the next more substantial rally. It&#39;s as easy as 1-2 1-2&#8230;#Bitcoin showings signs of an extended larger degree wave 5.https://t.co/4EDcrVn5iS pic.twitter.com/tpdHJnST3p &#8212; Tony &#34;The Bull&#34; (@tonythebullBTC) May 15, 2023 Tony is the author of the CoinChartist (VIP) newsletter. Follow @TonyTheBullBTC &#38; @coinchartist_io on Twitter. Or join the TonyTradesBTC Telegram for exclusive daily market insights and technical analysis education. Please note: Content is educational and should not be considered investment advice. Featured image from iStockPhoto, Charts from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="p1">Bitcoin price seems to merely be grinding upwards, with a dusting of chop in between. What corrections have arrived have been minimal, and are shockingly similar in both time and price. </p>
<p class="p1">This fractal behavior could be a sign of an important Elliott Wave signal, that not only says that BTCUSD is about to go parabolic, but that the rally should be “extended” in its price movement.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Price And Time Fractal Discovered</h2>
<p class="p1">After a small recovery from the November 2022 bottom in crypto markets, Bitcoin corrected sharply. The correction was short-lived, due to a sudden banking crisis emerging. BTCUSD then made another run higher to above $30,000 per coin, and is once again correcting after a second, roughly 50% upward move.</p>

<p class="p1">The two similar sized moves took placed in approximately the same amount of time. Superimposing a fractal of one above or below the other demonstrates just how similar they are in time and price.</p>
<p>This sort of behavior is a fairly common occurence in Elliott Wave Principle called a 1-2/1-2 setup, and it could mean the crypto market is about to explode higher.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large wp-image-533070 aligncenter" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/083234B4-9CE9-4964-B164-EBDAD77C2C52-860x535.jpeg" alt="Bitcoin price double fractal " width="860" height="535" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/083234B4-9CE9-4964-B164-EBDAD77C2C52-860x535.jpeg 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/083234B4-9CE9-4964-B164-EBDAD77C2C52-460x286.jpeg 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/083234B4-9CE9-4964-B164-EBDAD77C2C52-768x478.jpeg 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/083234B4-9CE9-4964-B164-EBDAD77C2C52-750x466.jpeg 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/083234B4-9CE9-4964-B164-EBDAD77C2C52-1140x709.jpeg 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/083234B4-9CE9-4964-B164-EBDAD77C2C52.jpeg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/></p>

<h2>All About The 1-2 1-2 Elliott Wave Setup</h2>
<p class="p1">The 1-2/1-2 is a phenomenon when a smaller degree wave 1 and 2 take on a similar shape and length of the previous, larger degree wave 1 and 2. </p>
<p class="p1">Much like the first 1-2 is a larger degree wave, and the second 1-2 is a smaller degree wave, their appearance suggests an even larger degree wave will be extended. According to a description, a “1-2/1-2 structure is an indication that the larger degree impulse wave in development is extending.” </p>
<blockquote>
<p class="p1">“The 2nd wave 1-2 structure needs to be similar in proportions to that of the first 1-2 structure, not taking much more, if any more, time than the first.  Remember, you are actually seeing the development of a smaller degree impulse wave, so expect it to be a bit smaller than the larger degree structure.”</p>
</blockquote>
<p class="p1">“An extension suggests a massive elongation of the impulse pattern,” a <a href="http://bata4u.com/EW/12_12_elliott_waves.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">website</a> further reads.</p>

<p class="p1">After a completed wave 2 correction, wave 3 should begin. However, if price stops short of expectations and forms a similar sized pattern as the first waves 1 and 2, it suggests a second set of waves 1 and 2 that help increase the size of the overall wave 3 that was first anticipated. </p>
<p class="p1">This type of behavior has been spotted in not only Bitcoin. It is also evident in Chainlink, Litecoin, and the Total Crypto Market Cap chart. Several coins exhibiting the pattern could point to full participation across the market in the next more substantial rally.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">It&#39;s as easy as 1-2 1-2&#8230;<a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Bitcoin?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#Bitcoin</a> showings signs of an extended larger degree wave 5.<a href="https://t.co/4EDcrVn5iS" rel="nofollow">https://t.co/4EDcrVn5iS</a> <a href="https://t.co/tpdHJnST3p" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/tpdHJnST3p</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Tony &quot;The Bull&quot; (@tonythebullBTC) <a href="https://twitter.com/tonythebullBTC/status/1658128498748280833?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">May 15, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p></p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/apollo-bitcoin-moon-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>SEC Reduces LBRY&#8217;s Fine From $22 Million To $111,000 After Revision of Punishment</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/crypto/sec-reduces-lbrys-fine-from-22-million-to-111000-after-revision-of-punishment/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Eli Dambel]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 23:00:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crackdown]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LBRY]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[penalty]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrp]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=532991</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has revised the initial punishment against a blockchain-based content provider, LBRY.  It has significantly reduced the penalty from the previous $22 million to a revised amount of approximately $111,000. SEC Revises Initial Penalty On LBRY The decentralized content-sharing platform that utilizes blockchain technology found itself in legal trouble when the SEC alleged it conducted an unregistered securities offering. The SEC filed a suit against the firm in March 2021, as the agency alleged that LBRY&#8217;s sale of digital tokens, LBC, qualified as the sale of unregistered securities. Related Reading: Bitcoin Tweets Surpass Dogecoin Despite Meme Coin Craze The case sparked a legal battle between LBRY and the SEC. The company contested this, arguing that their tokens were not securities and did not fall under the regulatory framework of traditional securities offerings. However, the case turned out in favor of the SEC in November 2022, with the previous Judge ruling that the tokens were securities. The regulatory body demanded a fine of $22 million as a penalty for the alleged violation and instructed the company to cease such offerings. But LBRY stated in a December 2022 filing that the SEC&#8217;s request for $22 million was unrealistic given that the firm has not made such huge expenses in all its business dealings. It noted that the agency&#8217;s deduction of the sum was simply rough math, and the record does not support the amount. Related Reading: PEPE Outperforms Bitcoin In Social Media Buzz, Triggers Bullish Run For Frog Coin Furthermore, the agency realized the firm lacks adequate funds and may likely shut down its operations if it must pay such an amount. These became the major reasons for revising the initial punishment, according to information that came from a May 12 New Hampshire District Court filing. SEC’s Crackdown On Cryptocurrencies The SEC&#8217;s stance on digital assets can impact investors differently. If the SEC determines that certain digital assets fall under its definition of securities, it may impose trading restrictions on them.  This means that investors may face hurdles in trading their favorite digital currencies as they must comply with additional regulatory requirements, such as using SEC-approved assets and platforms.  These restrictions can limit the liquidity and accessibility of certain digital assets, making it more challenging for investors to engage in the market. This was evidenced in the Ripple case, as the SEC mandated all the crypto platforms in the US to delist XRP. However, the SEC&#8217;s regulatory approach also aims to protect investors. The regulator helps safeguard investors from fraudulent activities, scams, and market manipulations by enforcing regulations and scrutinizing digital asset offerings. featured image from Pixabay and chart from Tradingview]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has <a href="https://twitter.com/Belisarius2020/status/1657152916439060480?" rel="nofollow">revised</a> the initial punishment against a blockchain-based content provider, LBRY. </p>
<p>It has significantly reduced the penalty from the previous $22 million to a revised amount of approximately $111,000.</p>
<h2>SEC Revises Initial Penalty On LBRY</h2>
<p>The decentralized content-sharing platform that utilizes blockchain technology found itself in legal trouble when the SEC alleged it conducted an unregistered securities offering.</p>
<p>The SEC <a href="https://www.sec.gov/litigation/complaints/2021/comp25060.pdf" rel="nofollow">filed</a> a suit against the firm in March 2021, as the agency alleged that LBRY&#8217;s sale of digital tokens, LBC, qualified as the sale of unregistered securities.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/dogecoin/bitcoin-tweets-surpass-dogecoin-despite-meme-coin-craze/">Bitcoin Tweets Surpass Dogecoin Despite Meme Coin Craze</a></p>
<p>The case sparked a legal battle between LBRY and the SEC. The company contested this, arguing that their tokens were not securities and did not fall under the regulatory framework of traditional securities offerings.</p>
<p>However, the case turned out in favor of the SEC in November 2022, with the previous Judge ruling that the tokens were securities.</p>
<p>The regulatory body demanded a fine of $22 million as a penalty for the alleged violation and instructed the company to cease such offerings.</p>
<p>But LBRY stated in a December 2022 <a href="https://www.courtlistener.com/docket/59774584/100/us-securities-and-exchange-commission-v-lbry-inc/" rel="nofollow">filing</a> that the SEC&#8217;s request for $22 million was unrealistic given that the firm has not made such huge expenses in all its business dealings.</p>
<p>It noted that the agency&#8217;s deduction of the sum was simply rough math, and the record does not support the amount.</p>

<p>Furthermore, the agency realized the firm lacks adequate funds and may likely shut down its operations if it must pay such an amount. These became the major reasons for revising the initial punishment, according to information that came from a May 12 New Hampshire District Court filing.</p>
<h2>SEC’s Crackdown On Cryptocurrencies</h2>
<p>The SEC&#8217;s stance on digital assets can impact investors differently. If the SEC determines that certain digital assets fall under its definition of securities, it may impose trading restrictions on them. </p>
<p>This means that investors may face hurdles in <a href="https://www.forbes.com/advisor/investing/sec-crypto-regulation/" rel="nofollow">trading their favorite digital currencies</a> as they must comply with additional regulatory requirements, such as using SEC-approved assets and platforms. </p>
<p>These restrictions can limit the liquidity and accessibility of certain digital assets, making it more challenging for investors to engage in the market. This was evidenced in the Ripple case, as the SEC mandated <a href="https://markets.businessinsider.com/currencies/news/xrp-delisted-ripple-sec-complaint-coinbase-crypto-okcoin-trading-platform-2020-12-1029926814" rel="nofollow">all the crypto platforms</a> in the US to delist XRP.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-532994 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSDT_2023-05-15_19-58-26-860x470.png" alt="SEC Reduces LBRY&#039;s Fine From $22M To $111K After Revision of Punishment" width="860" height="470" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSDT_2023-05-15_19-58-26-860x470.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSDT_2023-05-15_19-58-26-460x252.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSDT_2023-05-15_19-58-26-768x420.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSDT_2023-05-15_19-58-26-750x410.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSDT_2023-05-15_19-58-26-1140x624.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSDT_2023-05-15_19-58-26.png 1530w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/>
<p>However, the SEC&#8217;s regulatory approach <a href="https://www.sec.gov/news/speech/gensler-remarks-crypto-markets-040422" rel="nofollow">also aims to protect</a> investors. The regulator <a href="https://www.sec.gov/oiea/investor-alerts-and-bulletins/exercise-caution-crypto-asset-securities-investor-alert" rel="nofollow">helps safeguard investors</a> from fraudulent activities, scams, and market manipulations by enforcing regulations and scrutinizing digital asset offerings.</p>
<p>featured image from Pixabay and chart from Tradingview</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/gavel-g10a42c87e_1280-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Lido (LDO) Bulls Lock Horns For Rally This Week Ahead Of V2 Update</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/altcoin/lido-ldo-bulls-lock-horns-for-rally-this-week-ahead-of-v2-update/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mudiaga Iritare]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 22:15:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum staking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LDO]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Lido Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Liquid staking]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=532796</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[May 15th marks a new dawn for the Ethereum liquid staking protocol, Lido Finance, as it seeks to launch the highly anticipated V2 update on its platform. According to Lido contributors, the V2 update is its biggest platform update yet and a step in the right direction toward further decentralization in the blockchain industry. The update aims to enhance the user staking experience on  Lido Finance protocol by introducing two new features which achieve this purpose. Related Reading: PEPE Outperforms Bitcoin In Social Media Buzz, Triggers Bullish Run For Frog Coin LDO, the official native token of the Lido finance protocol and liquid staking platform, is seen to soar in price in today&#8217;s trading session as bulls gear up in response to the incoming update. What Is The Lido Finance Protocol V2 Update Earlier in February 2023, an official Lido Finance announcement release introduced a V2 update proposal that brings unique enhancement features to its Ethereum liquid staking platform. Today Lido contributors are proud to present Lido V2 &#8211; Lido’s largest upgrade to date and an important step towards further decentralization. https://t.co/SDxlxCgMNq pic.twitter.com/KJewhEp8rV &#8212; Lido (@LidoFinance) February 7, 2023 Fast forward to May, the team scheduled a final on-chain voting process for its V2 update proposal to take place from the 12th-15th following the success of the Ethereum Shapella upgrade in April. According to a tweet from Lido&#8217;s official handle, if the vote on the proposal passes and is successful, the V2 update will go live on May 15th, which is today, and support direct in-protocol stETH: ETH withdrawals and staking router architecture. So far, the V2 update proposal has been approved as it got the required approval and support rating needed for the update. 👀 https://t.co/GMrXGuLIdT pic.twitter.com/4wfk6zgJbM &#8212; Lido (@LidoFinance) May 15, 2023 The V2 update on the biggest liquid staking platform brings two new core platform features, including a Staking Router and a Withdrawal feature. The Staking Router feature on the V2 update promotes a diverse and decentralized ecosystem of validators by allowing the admission of new node operators. Using a new modular architectural design and framework, the V2 Staking Router enables anyone to develop on-ramps for node operators ranging from Distributed Validator Technology (DVT), solo stakers, and Distributed Autonomous Organizations (DAOs). The second feature on the update, withdrawals, will be a game changer for Lido Finance as it enables stakers on the platform who hold stETH to have access to withdrawals at a 1:1 ratio. LDO Daily Chart Analysis Data reports from Coinmarketcap see the native token of the biggest liquid staking platform, LDO, trading at $2.12, a 9.58% increase in the last 24 hours. LDO market capitalization has also increased by 9.43% at the time of writing. LDO opened with a bullish candle on the daily timeframe and is among the top three gainers in the cryptocurrency markets today. Related Reading: Dogecoin Sees Highest Transactions Count Ever Due DRC20 Madness LDO trades at the strong resistance area at $2.12, with bulls looking to break that level for more upside movements. However, if bulls fail to break that critical area, the asset could experience a retracement in price and trade lower. This resistance line and 50 EMA at $2.13 are major hurdles the asset must break to experience a rally. &#160; Lido (LDO) bulls take charge on the daily timeframe but faces key resistance level &#124; Source: LDOUSD on TradingView.com &#160; Featured image from Istock, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>May 15th marks a new dawn for the Ethereum liquid staking protocol, Lido Finance, as it seeks to launch the highly anticipated V2 update on its platform.</p>
<p>According to Lido contributors, the V2 update is its biggest platform update yet and a step in the right direction toward further decentralization in the blockchain industry.</p>
<p>The update aims to enhance the user staking experience on  Lido Finance protocol by introducing two new features which achieve this purpose.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/pepe-outperforms-bitcoin-in-social-media-buzz-triggers-bullish-run-for-frog-coin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">PEPE Outperforms Bitcoin In Social Media Buzz, Triggers Bullish Run For Frog Coin</a></p>
<p>LDO, the official native token of the Lido finance protocol and liquid staking platform, is seen to soar in price in today&#8217;s trading session as bulls gear up in response to the incoming update.</p>
<h2>What Is The Lido Finance Protocol V2 Update</h2>
<p>Earlier in February 2023, an official Lido Finance <a href="https://www.google.com/amp/s/blog.lido.fi/introducing-lido-v2/amp/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">announcement</a> release introduced a V2 update proposal that brings unique enhancement features to its Ethereum liquid staking platform.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Today Lido contributors are proud to present Lido V2 &#8211; Lido’s largest upgrade to date and an important step towards further decentralization. <a href="https://t.co/SDxlxCgMNq" rel="nofollow">https://t.co/SDxlxCgMNq</a> <a href="https://t.co/KJewhEp8rV" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/KJewhEp8rV</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Lido (@LidoFinance) <a href="https://twitter.com/LidoFinance/status/1622963224898330624?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">February 7, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p></p>
<p>Fast forward to May, the team scheduled a final on-chain voting process for its V2 update proposal to take place from the 12th-15th following the success of the Ethereum Shapella upgrade in April.</p>
<p>According to a tweet from Lido&#8217;s official handle, if the vote on the proposal passes and is successful, the V2 update will go live on May 15th, which is today, and support direct in-protocol stETH: ETH withdrawals and staking router architecture.</p>
<p>So far, the V2 update proposal has been approved as it got the required approval and support rating needed for the update.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="qme" dir="ltr"><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f440.png" alt="👀" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> <a href="https://t.co/GMrXGuLIdT" rel="nofollow">https://t.co/GMrXGuLIdT</a> <a href="https://t.co/4wfk6zgJbM" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/4wfk6zgJbM</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Lido (@LidoFinance) <a href="https://twitter.com/LidoFinance/status/1658039182193827840?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">May 15, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p></p>
<p>The V2 update on the biggest liquid staking platform brings two new core platform features, including a Staking Router and a Withdrawal feature.</p>
<p>The Staking Router feature on the V2 update promotes a diverse and decentralized ecosystem of validators by allowing the admission of new node operators. Using a new modular architectural design and framework, the V2 Staking Router enables anyone to develop on-ramps for node operators ranging from Distributed Validator Technology (DVT), solo stakers, and Distributed Autonomous Organizations (DAOs).</p>
<p>The second feature on the update, withdrawals, will be a game changer for Lido Finance as it enables stakers on the platform who hold stETH to have access to withdrawals at a 1:1 ratio.</p>
<h2>LDO Daily Chart Analysis</h2>
<p>Data <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/lido-dao/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">reports</a> from Coinmarketcap see the native token of the biggest liquid staking platform, LDO, trading at $2.12, a 9.58% increase in the last 24 hours. LDO market capitalization has also increased by 9.43% at the time of writing. LDO opened with a bullish candle on the daily timeframe and is among the top three gainers in the cryptocurrency markets today.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/dogecoin/dogecoin-records-ath-transactions-drc20-madness/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Dogecoin Sees Highest Transactions Count Ever Due DRC20 Madness</a></p>
<p>LDO trades at the strong resistance area at $2.12, with bulls looking to break that level for more upside movements. However, if bulls fail to break that critical area, the asset could experience a retracement in price and trade lower.</p>
<p>This resistance line and 50 EMA at $2.13 are major hurdles the asset must break to experience a rally.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/P5jxtzwh/" alt="Lido" width="1079" height="595"/></p>

<p>&nbsp;</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/iStock-1015828796-460x263.jpg" width="460" height="263" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fantom (FTM) Price Surge Hints At Bullish Trend, What&#8217;s Ahead?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/fantom/fantom-ftm-price-surge-hints-at-bullish-trend-whats-ahead/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Eli Dambel]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 21:40:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Fantom]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bulls]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fantom]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTMUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MACD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Metaverse]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=532980</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Fantom (FTM) has been on a bearish movement since April 19, 2023, resulting in a loss of about 30%. The price decline contributed to the negative market sentiment around the asset, making it hard for any possible retracement. However, these days, some minor green candles indicate a potential bullish trend. This is because the price of Fantom experienced rapid price action recently as the bulls took back control and increased buying pressure. Examining The Bullish Trend of Fantom (FTM) The recent bullish momentum has triggered a significant price action resulting in a price increase in the general FTM market. The price of FTM has increased by 5.09% in the last 24 hours trading session, taking the token to a high of $0.3885. Related Reading: Bitcoin Tweets Surpass Dogecoin Despite Meme Coin Craze Also, with an increase of 57.26% in the 24-hour trading volume, the overall market cap is currently up by 5.09%. This data confirm the bullish momentum present in the asset. Furthermore, the current significant buying and selling activities suggest a surge in market participation, likely leading to heightened price volatility. The current market sentiment of Fantom (FTM) is Neutral, while the Fear &#38; Greed Index is showing 50, meaning Neutral. This indicates that the market is stable, with no pressure from bears or bulls.  The recent development and partnerships with SUPA Foundation also contribute to the bullish sentiment among investors and traders.  As more individuals and institutions recognize the potential and value of the Fantom ecosystem, it’ll drive up buying pressure and support an upward price movement. Fantom (FTM) Technical Analysis Fantom currently trades above the 200-Day Simple Moving Average but below the 50-Day Simple Moving Average. This may indicate a mixed or transitional phase in Fantom’s price action. The asset trading below the 50-Day SMA suggests a short-term weakness or a corrective phase in the price of FTM. Traders may use the 50-Day SMA as a resistance level preventing the FTM from moving higher. The asset is trading above the 200-Day Simple Moving Average, indicating a potential long-term bullish price movement. Related Reading: PEPE Outperforms Bitcoin In Social Media Buzz, Triggers Bullish Run For Frog Coin In general, the asset trading above the 200-Day SMA but below the 50-Day SMA suggests a phase where there&#8217;s a conflict between buyers and sellers. The Relative Strength Index confirms the present market indecision as Fantom is currently at the 44.53 region, which signifies neutral pressure. The Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD) is slightly below the signal line, indicating a low pressure from the bears. FTM trades between its support level of $0.3585 and resistance level of $0.4498, respectively. With increased bullish sentiment and buying pressure, FTM might hit the next significant resistance level of $0.5499. Conversely, if the bears increase selling pressure and the bulls fail to hold their positions, FTM might change the trend and drop sharply to the next support level of $0.3034. Featured image from Pixabay and chart from Tradingview.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Fantom (FTM) has been on a bearish movement since April 19, 2023, resulting in a loss of about 30%. The price decline contributed to the negative market sentiment around the asset, making it hard for any possible retracement. </p>
<p>However, these days, some minor green candles indicate a potential bullish trend. This is because the price of Fantom experienced rapid price action recently as the bulls took back control and increased buying pressure.</p>
<h2>Examining The Bullish Trend of Fantom (FTM)</h2>
<p>The recent bullish momentum has triggered a significant price action resulting in a price increase in the general FTM market. The price of <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/fantom/" rel="nofollow">FTM has increased</a> by 5.09% in the last 24 hours trading session, taking the token to a high of $0.3885.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/dogecoin/bitcoin-tweets-surpass-dogecoin-despite-meme-coin-craze/">Bitcoin Tweets Surpass Dogecoin Despite Meme Coin Craze</a></p>
<p>Also, with an increase of 57.26% in the 24-hour trading volume, the overall market cap is currently up by 5.09%. This data confirm the bullish momentum present in the asset.</p>
<p>Furthermore, the current significant buying and selling activities suggest a surge in market participation, likely leading to heightened price volatility.</p>
<p>The current market sentiment of Fantom (FTM) is Neutral, while the <a href="https://cfgi.io/fantom-fear-greed-index/" rel="nofollow">Fear &amp; Greed Index</a> is showing 50, meaning Neutral. This indicates that the market is stable, with no pressure from bears or bulls. </p>
<p>The recent development and <a href="https://twitter.com/fantom_insider/status/1655100559232471040" rel="nofollow">partnerships</a> with SUPA Foundation also contribute to the bullish sentiment among investors and traders. </p>
<p>As more individuals and institutions recognize the potential and value of the Fantom ecosystem, it’ll drive up buying pressure and support an upward price movement.</p>
<h2>Fantom (FTM) Technical Analysis</h2>
<p>Fantom currently trades above the 200-Day Simple Moving Average but below the 50-Day Simple Moving Average. This may indicate a mixed or transitional phase in Fantom’s price action.</p>
<p>The asset trading below the 50-Day SMA suggests a short-term weakness or a corrective phase in the price of FTM. Traders may use the 50-Day SMA as a resistance level preventing the FTM from moving higher.</p>
<p>The asset is trading above the 200-Day Simple Moving Average, indicating a potential long-term bullish price movement.</p>

<p>In general, the asset trading above the 200-Day SMA but below the 50-Day SMA suggests a phase where there&#8217;s a conflict between buyers and sellers. The Relative Strength Index confirms the present market indecision as Fantom is currently at the 44.53 region, which signifies neutral pressure.</p>
<p>The Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD) is slightly below the signal line, indicating a low pressure from the bears.</p>
<p>FTM trades between its support level of $0.3585 and resistance level of $0.4498, respectively. With increased bullish sentiment and buying pressure, FTM might hit the next significant resistance level of $0.5499.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-532985 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/FTMUSDT_2023-05-15_19-43-51-860x471.png" alt="Fantom (FTM) Price Surges Hinting A Bullish Trend, What&#039;s Ahead?" width="860" height="471" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/FTMUSDT_2023-05-15_19-43-51-860x471.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/FTMUSDT_2023-05-15_19-43-51-460x252.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/FTMUSDT_2023-05-15_19-43-51-768x420.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/FTMUSDT_2023-05-15_19-43-51-750x411.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/FTMUSDT_2023-05-15_19-43-51-1140x624.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/FTMUSDT_2023-05-15_19-43-51.png 1529w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/>
<p>Conversely, if the bears increase selling pressure and the bulls fail to hold their positions, FTM might change the trend and drop sharply to the next support level of $0.3034.</p>
<p>Featured image from Pixabay and chart from Tradingview.com</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/highland-cow-g58a557d37_1280-460x305.jpg" width="460" height="305" />	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
