<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
>

<channel>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.newsbtc.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<description>Bitcoin &#38; cryptocurrency news today, price &#38; technical analysis</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 22:01:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Ripple’s Q1 Report Shows That Investors Are Still Bullish On XRP, Here’s Why</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/ripples-q1-report-shows-that-investors-are-still-bullish-on-xrp-heres-why/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Best Owie]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 23:00:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple users]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrp]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPL]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrpusdt]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=529046</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Ripple is a cryptocurrency firm that has been on the radar of United States regulators for years and its native token XRP has suffered greatly for it. However, despite the legal battle with the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), Ripple has not backed down and it looks like investors are increasingly bullish on the cryptocurrency. Ripple’s Q1 Report Exceeds Expectations In a Q1 report that was posted by Ripple titled ‘Q1 2023 XRP Markets Report’, there has been tremendous growth for the firm in the first three months of 2023. The first thing that stands out from this report is that Ripple has been experiencing rapid adoption during this time period. Related Reading: Bullish Momentum Expected For ARB As Arbitrum Completes DAO Airdrop At a time when other cryptocurrencies were seeing a decline in new users and adoption, the crypto firm reports that over 114,000 new wallets were added in the first quarter of 2023. Furthermore, the number of transactions for this time period also crossed 116 million. The decentralized exchange (DEX) volume for XRP also grew to over $114.5 million compared to the $85.7 million figure recorded in Q4 of 2022. However, transaction fees were higher compared to the previous quarter and its price did not perform as well, closing at an average price of $0.40 compared to $0.42 for Q4 2022. Ripple sees impressive growth in Q1 2023 &#124; Source: ripple.com This rise in transaction fees, as well as the increased number of transactions, saw the total XRP burned for transaction fees reach 140,993 for Q1 2023 compared to 101,968 XRP for Q4 2022. Non-fungible tokens (NFTs) contributed greatly to this volume as the report notes that over 1.2 million NFTs have been minted since XLS-20 went live on mainnet. Thus, Ripple has emerged as a Top 10 chain for NFT trading volume as well. Community Turns Bullish On XRP The expectations of the XRP community have returned to bullish territory given the numbers published in the quarterly report. It has instilled a sense of confidence given that it shows rapid adoption for Ripple despite its troubles over the years. XRP price trending at $0.47 &#124; Source: XRPUSD on TradingView.com XRP’s price has also responded positively with a 2.34% gain in the last 24 hours, data from Coinmarketcap shows. Its trading volume also saw a similar uptrend, rising 2.31% on the day to reach$1.67 billion at the time of this writing. Related Reading: Kaspa (KAS), Render (RNDR), Injective (INJ) See Upside Amid Market Crash, What’s Going On? The token’s current price of $0.47 puts it well above its 50-day and 100-day simple moving averages, making it bullish in the mid to long-term. However, its price is threatened in the short term after falling below its 20-day moving average. The digital asset is now seeing resistance at $0.48, making it the point to beat if bulls are to try to reach $0.5 once again. Follow Best Owie on Twitter for market insights, updates, and the occasional funny tweet… Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="p2">Ripple is a cryptocurrency firm that has been on the radar of United States regulators for years and its native token XRP has suffered greatly for it. However, despite the legal battle with the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), Ripple has not backed down and it looks like investors are increasingly bullish on the cryptocurrency.</p>
<h2 class="p2">Ripple’s Q1 Report Exceeds Expectations</h2>
<p class="p2">In a Q1 report that was <a href="https://ripple.com/insights/q1-2023-xrp-markets-report/?utm_campaign=&amp;utm_medium=organic_social&amp;utm_source=twitter" rel="nofollow">posted</a> by Ripple titled ‘Q1 2023 XRP Markets Report’, there has been tremendous growth for the firm in the first three months of 2023. The first thing that stands out from this report is that Ripple has been experiencing rapid adoption during this time period.</p>

<p class="p2">At a time when other cryptocurrencies were seeing a decline in new users and adoption, the crypto firm reports that over 114,000 new wallets were added in the first quarter of 2023. Furthermore, the number of transactions for this time period also crossed 116 million.</p>
<p class="p2">The decentralized exchange (DEX) volume for XRP also grew to over $114.5 million compared to the $85.7 million figure recorded in Q4 of 2022. However, transaction fees were higher compared to the previous quarter and its price did not perform as well, closing at an average price of $0.40 compared to $0.42 for Q4 2022.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium wp-image-529047 aligncenter" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Ripple-XRP-460x344.png" alt="Ripple (XRP)" width="460" height="344" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Ripple-XRP-460x344.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Ripple-XRP-860x643.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Ripple-XRP-768x574.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Ripple-XRP-1536x1149.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Ripple-XRP-750x561.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Ripple-XRP-1140x853.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Ripple-XRP.png 1824w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px" /></p>

<p class="p2">This rise in transaction fees, as well as the increased number of transactions, saw the total XRP burned for transaction fees reach 140,993 for Q1 2023 compared to 101,968 XRP for Q4 2022.</p>
<p class="p2">Non-fungible tokens (NFTs) contributed greatly to this volume as the report notes that over 1.2 million NFTs have been minted since XLS-20 went live on mainnet. Thus, Ripple has emerged as a Top 10 chain for NFT trading volume as well.</p>
<h2 class="p2">Community Turns Bullish On XRP</h2>
<p class="p2">The expectations of the XRP community have returned to bullish territory given the numbers published in the quarterly report. It has instilled a sense of confidence given that it shows rapid adoption for Ripple despite its troubles over the years.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/8PaLruSn/" alt="Ripple (XRP) price chart from TradingView.com" width="2854" height="1724" /></p>

<p class="p2">XRP’s price has also responded positively with a 2.34% gain in the last 24 hours, data from Coinmarketcap shows. Its trading volume also saw a similar uptrend, rising 2.31% on the day to reach$1.67 billion at the time of this writing.</p>

<p class="p2">The token’s current price of $0.47 puts it well above its 50-day and 100-day simple moving averages, making it bullish in the mid to long-term. However, its price is threatened in the short term after falling below its 20-day moving average. The digital asset is now seeing resistance at $0.48, making it the point to beat if bulls are to try to reach $0.5 once again.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/iStock-148243270-1-460x281.jpg" width="460" height="281" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>XRP May Rally Over 10% Upon Breaching Two Critical Levels</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/xrp-may-rally-over-10-upon-breaching-two-critical-levels/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[anushsamal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 22:00:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrp]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrpusdt]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=529106</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Recently, XRP has been facing significant rejection at its overhead resistance level, including a rejection that occurred just a week ago. On the daily chart, XRP has shown a slight upward movement of 3%. However, over the past week, this altcoin has not made much progress as its price has decreased by 0.4%. This indicates that the XRP price is indecisive over longer time frames. The technical outlook for XRP suggests that the market is bearish. There is a low demand for the altcoin, and accumulation remained less too. However, if XRP manages to move above its overhead resistance, this could trigger a recovery. Related Reading: How Soon Will Litecoin Breach This Psychological Resistance Level? Currently, the BTC price is hovering below the $30,000 mark, and most altcoins have followed a similar trend. If BTC breaks through the $30,000 mark, XRP could attempt to move upwards. At its current level, the altcoin is at a crucial point, as an increase in demand could cause a rally, while a decrease in price could result in a loss of up to 16% of its value. Furthermore, the market capitalization of XRP has decreased, indicating an increase in the number of sellers. XRP Price Analysis: One-Day Chart The altcoin was trading for $0.47 at the time of writing. It is trading underneath its overhead resistance of $0.48. The aforementioned resistance mark is crucial as it has served as a price ceiling previously. A break above the $0,.48 mark can push XRP to $0.50, which might act as another ceiling before the altcoin targets $0.53. A move to $0.53 means over a 10% rally. On the flip side, a fall from the current price level will drag XRP to $0.44 and then to $0.40, thereby bringing bearish influence back. The amount of altcoin traded in the last session was red, indicating a fall in demand. Technical Analysis Since the altcoin dropped below the $0.50 level, demand for the altcoin has failed to recover. The Relative Strength Index (RSI) indicates that selling strength outweighs buying strength, as the RSI is below the half-line. Additionally, the altcoin remains below the 20-Simple Moving Average (SMA) line, which signifies that sellers have control and are driving the price momentum in the market. However, if demand for XRP increases slightly, it could push the coin above the 20-SMA line. This would signal a return of bullish strength on the chart. In line with other indicators, the altcoin is displaying sell signals. The Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD), which indicates price momentum, has formed red histograms, signalling to sell. Related Reading: Ethereum Shark &#38; Whale Addresses Up 5.7% Over Past Year: Santiment Furthermore, the Bollinger Bands, which portray price volatility and fluctuation, have opened up. This suggests that the coin may experience significant price fluctuations over the next few trading sessions. Featured Image From UnSplash, Charts From TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Recently, XRP has been facing significant rejection at its overhead resistance level, including a rejection that occurred just a week ago. On the daily chart, XRP has shown a slight upward movement of 3%. However, over the past week, this altcoin has not made much progress as its price has decreased by 0.4%. This indicates that the XRP price is indecisive over longer time frames.</p>
<p>The technical outlook for XRP suggests that the market is bearish. There is a low demand for the altcoin, and accumulation remained less too. However, if XRP manages to move above its overhead resistance, this could trigger a recovery.</p>

<p>Currently, the BTC price is hovering below the $30,000 mark, and most altcoins have followed a similar trend. If BTC breaks through the $30,000 mark, XRP could attempt to move upwards.</p>
<p>At its current level, the altcoin is at a crucial point, as an increase in demand could cause a rally, while a decrease in price could result in a loss of up to 16% of its value. Furthermore, the market capitalization of XRP has decreased, indicating an increase in the number of sellers.</p>
<h2>XRP Price Analysis: One-Day Chart</h2>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-529112 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/XRPUSD_2023-04-28_18-45-02.png" alt="XRP" width="1816" height="830" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/XRPUSD_2023-04-28_18-45-02.png 1816w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/XRPUSD_2023-04-28_18-45-02-460x210.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/XRPUSD_2023-04-28_18-45-02-860x393.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/XRPUSD_2023-04-28_18-45-02-768x351.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/XRPUSD_2023-04-28_18-45-02-1536x702.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/XRPUSD_2023-04-28_18-45-02-750x343.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/XRPUSD_2023-04-28_18-45-02-1140x521.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1816px) 100vw, 1816px" />
<p>The altcoin was trading for $0.47 at the time of writing. It is trading underneath its overhead resistance of $0.48. The aforementioned resistance mark is crucial as it has served as a price ceiling previously.</p>
<p>A break above the $0,.48 mark can push XRP to $0.50, which might act as another ceiling before the altcoin targets $0.53. A move to $0.53 means over a 10% rally.</p>
<p>On the flip side, a fall from the current price level will drag XRP to $0.44 and then to $0.40, thereby bringing bearish influence back. The amount of altcoin traded in the last session was red, indicating a fall in demand.</p>
<h2>Technical Analysis</h2>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-529114 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/XRPUSD_2023-04-28_18-45-46.png" alt="XRP" width="1816" height="743" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/XRPUSD_2023-04-28_18-45-46.png 1816w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/XRPUSD_2023-04-28_18-45-46-460x188.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/XRPUSD_2023-04-28_18-45-46-860x352.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/XRPUSD_2023-04-28_18-45-46-768x314.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/XRPUSD_2023-04-28_18-45-46-1536x628.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/XRPUSD_2023-04-28_18-45-46-750x307.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/XRPUSD_2023-04-28_18-45-46-1140x466.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1816px) 100vw, 1816px" />
<p>Since the altcoin dropped below the $0.50 level, demand for the altcoin has failed to recover. The Relative Strength Index (RSI) indicates that selling strength outweighs buying strength, as the RSI is below the half-line.</p>
<p>Additionally, the altcoin remains below the 20-Simple Moving Average (SMA) line, which signifies that sellers have control and are driving the price momentum in the market. However, if demand for XRP increases slightly, it could push the coin above the 20-SMA line. This would signal a return of bullish strength on the chart.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-529118 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/XRPUSD_2023-04-28_18-46-09.png" alt="XRP" width="1817" height="743" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/XRPUSD_2023-04-28_18-46-09.png 1817w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/XRPUSD_2023-04-28_18-46-09-460x188.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/XRPUSD_2023-04-28_18-46-09-860x352.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/XRPUSD_2023-04-28_18-46-09-768x314.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/XRPUSD_2023-04-28_18-46-09-1536x628.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/XRPUSD_2023-04-28_18-46-09-750x307.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/XRPUSD_2023-04-28_18-46-09-1140x466.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1817px) 100vw, 1817px" />
<p>In line with other indicators, the altcoin is displaying sell signals. The Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD), which indicates price momentum, has formed red histograms, signalling to sell.</p>

<p>Furthermore, the Bollinger Bands, which portray price volatility and fluctuation, have opened up. This suggests that the coin may experience significant price fluctuations over the next few trading sessions.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/dmitry-demidko-91bKtpRpBfc-unsplash-3-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Emerges As the King Of Assets,10X Growth Over Gold During US Banking Crisis</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-emerges-as-the-king-of-assets10x-growth-over-gold-during-us-banking-crisis/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 20:00:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=529158</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Despite the volatile price action of Bitcoin (BTC), the world&#8217;s largest cryptocurrency has outperformed every other asset, including gold. Although it is trading below its psychological milestone of $30,000 at $29,000, Bitcoin is expected to grow further in 2023, as it acts as a safe haven for investors amidst the US banking crisis. Related Reading: Chainlink Price Slides As The Bear Try To Take Over, Will A Rally Follow?  Bitcoin Reigns Supreme As the Best-Performing Asset Capriole Investment, which provides research and analysis on cryptocurrencies, has reported that the current market cycle favors hard assets like gold, as indicated by the 200-week Gold-to-Stocks ratio. This classic indicator highlights when the market favors safe-haven assets like gold over riskier equity assets. Both gold and Bitcoin have generated some of their best returns during these phases. As the market continues to favor hard assets, Bitcoin has emerged as the preferred safe haven for wealth amidst the US banking crisis and fiat currency weakness. During this period of high correlation, Bitcoin has outperformed gold by 10X in 2023, making it the best-performing asset of the year among major asset classes. The strong positive correlation between Bitcoin and Gold has also increased significantly, making them attractive options for investors looking to diversify their portfolios and hedge against economic uncertainty. With unsustainable tightening, banking crises, and de-dollarization looming, the market is turning to these safe-haven assets to protect their wealth. According to the report by Capriole Investment, the current Bitcoin rally in 2023 is believed to be organic and spot driven. The report highlights a key metric showing total futures Open Interest as a ratio of the total Bitcoin and USDT market cap.  This metric provides insight into the market&#8217;s leverage and shows that the crypto market leverage peaked with the FTX fraud in November 2022. Since then, this ratio has been on a one-way downtrend, despite Bitcoin&#8217;s price rallying over 80% from $16,000 to $30,000. This indicates that there has been little speculation in the market this year. The report suggests that until this ratio spikes or Bitcoin dominance peaks, the foundations for sustainable price appreciation remain in place. This means that the current rally is driven by organic demand rather than speculation, which is a positive sign for the long-term growth of the cryptocurrency market. Furthermore, the report suggests that the decrease in leverage indicates a healthy market less vulnerable to sudden price drops. This is because a high level of leverage can often lead to market instability, causing sharp price swings and potentially resulting in a market crash. BTC&#8217;s $30-32K Dilemma According to the report, Bitcoin is trading within the largest technical resistance block on the chart since $20,000. This region, which ranges from $30,000 to $32,000, represents the bottom of the 2021 range and the breakdown point into the bear market that began in 2022.  Additionally, it is a major weekly order block level and Fibonacci extension level from the prior cycle. $30,000 is also a major round number level, representing a 50% increase from the 2017 cycle all-time-high of $20,000, and $32,000 marks a 100% appreciation in Bitcoin since the FTX Fraud bottom at $16,000. While Bitcoin has shown remarkable resilience in recent months, it is important to note that past performance is not an indicator of future results. However, according to Capriole&#8217;s report, if Bitcoin manages to close above $32,000 weekly, it wouldn&#8217;t be surprising to see a new trend carry its price into the $40,000 mark. Related Reading: Ethereum Shark &#38; Whale Addresses Up 5.7% Over Past Year: Santiment Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Despite the volatile price action of Bitcoin (BTC), the world&#8217;s largest cryptocurrency has outperformed every other asset, including gold. Although it is trading below its psychological milestone of $30,000 at $29,000, Bitcoin is expected to grow further in 2023, as it acts as a safe haven for investors amidst the US banking crisis.</p>

<h2><b> Bitcoin Reigns Supreme As the Best-Performing Asset</b></h2>
<p>Capriole Investment, which provides research and analysis on cryptocurrencies, has <a href="https://capriole.com/issue-31/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">reported</a> that the current market cycle favors hard assets like gold, as indicated by the 200-week Gold-to-Stocks ratio. This classic indicator highlights when the market favors safe-haven assets like gold over riskier equity assets. Both gold and Bitcoin have generated some of their best returns during these phases.</p>
<p>As the market continues to favor hard assets, Bitcoin has emerged as the preferred safe haven for wealth amidst the US banking crisis and fiat currency weakness. During this period of high correlation, Bitcoin has outperformed gold by 10X in 2023, making it the best-performing asset of the year among major asset classes.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large wp-image-529161" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/image-7-1024x567-1-860x476.png" alt="Bitcoin " width="860" height="476" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/image-7-1024x567-1-860x476.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/image-7-1024x567-1-460x255.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/image-7-1024x567-1-768x425.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/image-7-1024x567-1-750x415.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/image-7-1024x567-1.png 1024w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" />
<p>The strong positive correlation between Bitcoin and Gold has also increased significantly, making them attractive options for investors looking to diversify their portfolios and hedge against economic uncertainty. With unsustainable tightening, banking crises, and de-dollarization looming, the market is turning to these safe-haven assets to protect their wealth.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large wp-image-529164" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/kaiko-860x463.jpeg" alt="Bitcoin " width="860" height="463" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/kaiko-860x463.jpeg 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/kaiko-460x248.jpeg 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/kaiko-768x414.jpeg 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/kaiko-750x404.jpeg 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/kaiko-1140x614.jpeg 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/kaiko.jpeg 1310w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" />
<p>According to the report by Capriole Investment, the current Bitcoin rally in 2023 is believed to be organic and spot driven. The report highlights a key metric showing total futures Open Interest as a ratio of the total Bitcoin and USDT market cap. </p>
<p>This metric provides insight into the market&#8217;s leverage and shows that the crypto market leverage peaked with the FTX fraud in November 2022. Since then, this ratio has been on a one-way downtrend, despite Bitcoin&#8217;s price rallying over 80% from $16,000 to $30,000. This indicates that there has been little speculation in the market this year.</p>
<p>The report suggests that until this ratio spikes or Bitcoin dominance peaks, the foundations for sustainable price appreciation remain in place. This means that the current rally is driven by organic demand rather than speculation, which is a positive sign for the long-term growth of the cryptocurrency market.</p>
<p>Furthermore, the report suggests that the decrease in leverage indicates a healthy market less vulnerable to sudden price drops. This is because a high level of leverage can often lead to market instability, causing sharp price swings and potentially resulting in a market crash.</p>
<b>BTC&#8217;s $30-32K Dilemma</b>
<p>According to the report, Bitcoin is trading within the largest technical resistance block on the chart since $20,000. This region, which ranges from $30,000 to $32,000, represents the bottom of the 2021 range and the breakdown point into the bear market that began in 2022. </p>
<p>Additionally, it is a major weekly order block level and Fibonacci extension level from the prior cycle. $30,000 is also a major round number level, representing a 50% increase from the 2017 cycle all-time-high of $20,000, and $32,000 marks a 100% appreciation in Bitcoin since the FTX Fraud bottom at $16,000.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-529160 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/image-5-860x476.png" alt="BTC" width="860" height="476" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/image-5-860x476.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/image-5-460x255.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/image-5-768x425.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/image-5-750x416.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/image-5-1140x632.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/image-5.png 1462w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" />
<p>While Bitcoin has shown remarkable resilience in recent months, it is important to note that past performance is not an indicator of future results. However, according to Capriole&#8217;s report, if Bitcoin manages to close above $32,000 weekly, it wouldn&#8217;t be surprising to see a new trend carry its price into the $40,000 mark.</p>

<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/DpYuEjxE/" alt="Bitcoin " width="1813" height="858" />
<p>Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/crystal-berdion-OPr0ScPETbE-unsplash-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>XRP Could Be Poised For Another Rally, Here Are Key Metrics To Watch Out</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/xrp-could-be-poised-for-another-rally-here-are-key-metrics-to-watch-out/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Edyme]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 18:00:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrp]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=529150</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The cryptocurrency market has been experiencing a period of volatility, but XRP could be poised to break to the upside. As investors and traders gear up for the upcoming potential gains, several key metrics to watch out for could give insights into the future of XRP&#8217;s price. XRP Could Be Poised For A Rally  Over the past week, XRP has shown signs of bullish momentum, with the cryptocurrency price rising from $0.46 on April 21 to $0.47 at the time of writing. The surge in price could be attributed to several factors, including the ubiquitous uptrend in the market. According to the XRP price 4-hour chart, a possible uptrend could occur soon. The asset has formed a double bottom on the 1-day time frame and is now set to shape a W pattern fully. Related Reading: Crypto Analyst Explains Why XRP Will Not Fall To $0.10 The token has major high liquidity at $0.53, which could support an extension in the bullish trend as major players target it. Though the chart appears imprecise, should the asset continue its upward momentum and not invalidate the marked-out W pattern, it could rally and trade at the $0.5 region in the coming weeks.  Key Metrics To Keep An Eye On Alongside the asset validating the W pattern on the chart, XRP trading volume is one of the crucial metrics to watch out for, as it indicates the level of interest among retail traders.  These retail investors have the potential to help solidify the current bullish price action for XRP. According to data from CoinMarketCap, the token&#8217;s daily trading volume has remained consistently high, indicating strong investor interest and potentially foreshadowing a price increase. the token&#8217;s daily trading volume has surged from $1.4 billion seen 5 days ago to $1.6 billion in the last 24 hours. Whale action on XRP&#8217;s is another important metric to watch out for. On the XRPL network, significant whale transactions have been recorded through on-chain data, which can potentially sway the XRP coin&#8217;s price in favor of further profits. Whale transactions refer to large cryptocurrency transactions, typically carried out by institutional investors or high-net-worth individuals. These transactions have the potential to move markets and are closely monitored by traders and investors alike. Related Reading: XRP Dominates The Market: ADV On Centralized Exchanges Surged by 46% In Q1 2023, Report Factors contributing to XRP&#8217;s potential rally include the regulatory environment and its legal battle against the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). As the XRP case continues, any positive news regarding regulation could drive up demand for the cryptocurrency. Featured image from iStock, Chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The cryptocurrency market has been experiencing a period of volatility, but XRP could be poised to break to the upside. As investors and traders gear up for the upcoming potential gains, several key metrics to watch out for could give insights into the future of <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/xrp-price-prediction-ripple-0-4/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">XRP&#8217;s price</a>.</p>
<h2>XRP Could Be Poised For A Rally </h2>
<p>Over the past week, XRP has shown signs of bullish momentum, with the cryptocurrency price <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/xrp-trades-near-crucial-support-of-0-46-will-this-level-hold/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">rising from $0.46</a> on April 21 to $0.47 at the time of writing. The surge in price could be attributed to several factors, including the ubiquitous <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/xrp-dominates-the-market-adv-on-centralized-exchanges-surged-by-46-in-q1-2023-report/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">uptrend in the market</a>.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/GfBl0Qj7/" alt="XRP price chart on TradingView" width="2768" height="1556" />
<p>According to the XRP price 4-hour chart, a possible uptrend could occur soon. The asset has formed a double bottom on the 1-day time frame and is now set to shape a W pattern fully.</p>

<p>The token has major high liquidity at $0.53, which could support an extension in the bullish trend as major players target it. Though the chart appears imprecise, should the asset continue its upward momentum and not invalidate the marked-out W pattern, it could rally and trade at the $0.5 region in the coming weeks. </p>
<h2>Key Metrics To Keep An Eye On</h2>
<p>Alongside the asset validating the W pattern on the chart, XRP trading volume is one of the crucial metrics to watch out for, as it indicates the level of interest among retail traders. </p>
<p>These retail investors have the potential to help solidify the current bullish price action for XRP. According to <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/xrp/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">data</a> from CoinMarketCap, the token&#8217;s daily trading volume has remained consistently high, indicating strong investor interest and potentially foreshadowing a price increase. the token&#8217;s daily trading volume has surged from $1.4 billion seen 5 days ago to $1.6 billion in the last 24 hours.</p>
<p>Whale action on XRP&#8217;s is another important metric to watch out for. On the XRPL network, significant whale transactions have been <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/whales-move-ripple-xrp-holdings-as-the-token-plunges-below-0-46-whats-ahead/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">recorded through on-chain data</a>, which can potentially sway the XRP coin&#8217;s price in favor of further profits.</p>
<p>Whale transactions refer to large cryptocurrency transactions, typically carried out by institutional investors or high-net-worth individuals. These transactions have the potential to move markets and are closely monitored by traders and investors alike.</p>

<p>Factors contributing to XRP&#8217;s potential rally include the regulatory environment and its legal battle against the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). As the XRP case continues, any positive news regarding regulation could <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/crypto-analyst-explains-why-xrp-will-not-fall-to-0-10/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">drive up demand for the cryptocurrency</a>.</p>
<p class="p1">Featured image from iStock, Chart from TradingView</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/XRP-2-460x329.jpeg" width="460" height="329" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Price Targets Fourth Consecutive Bullish Monthly Close, Are We There Yet?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-price-targets-fourth-consecutive-bullish-monthly-close-are-we-there-yet/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mudiaga Iritare]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 16:00:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin bull]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bullrun]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto investment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=529062</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Since the start of the trading year, Bitcoin has maintained a 3-month bullish candle close and is on a path to stealing a fourth. 2023 has been an eventful year for the crypto industry and Bitcoin price, which rallied massively to the surprise of many crypto analysts this month. The significant price movements of Bitcoin, which saw it rally past $30,000 for the first time since June 2022, triggered euphoria and awakened the interests of retail and large cryptocurrency investors. While market sentiments may seem to be positive at the moment, what could have brought about these sentiments? Bitcoin Price Takes The Spotlight Bitcoin has shown grit in its recent price movements and rallies, dragging several altcoins with it as it recorded significant gains. This positive price development of Bitcoin alongside other cryptocurrencies has led to crypto communities calling a start of a bull run and continued price movements. Related Reading: Bitcoin Holds At $29,300 As PCE Comes Out Neutral Recently, crypto expert analysts, celebrities, and even some traditional finance analysts have made BTC a topic of major discussion, dropping bullish price predictions for the cryptocurrency. According to a Reuters report, Geoff Kendrick, head of digital assets research at Standard Chartered, made price predictions for Bitcoin, saying the alpha crypto could reach $100,000 by 2024. Also, Robert Kiyosaki, the famous best-selling author of &#8220;Rich Dad Poor Dad,&#8221; recently called a $100,000 price prediction for BTC on his Twitter handle. BTC&#8217;s sudden price rise and attention could be attributed to several market factors and happenings in the Tradfi and business world. Recent news of the collapse of bank giants such as Silicon Valley and Silvergate caused a stir in the traditional finance world, with users worried about the security of their funds. Concerns of rising inflation and de-dollarization have also resulted in financial experts and analysts looking to Bitcoin as a &#8220;Safe Haven&#8221; asset due to its decentralized nature. While the woes of the traditional finance system continue with recent news of the First Republic Bank potentially failing, Bitcoin price is seen looking to close another month in the bullish territory. Bitcoin Chart Analysis On The Weekly TimeFrame On the monthly chart timeframe, Bitcoin price is heading up to close April on a bullish note after its 3-month consecutive run. The weeks of April have witnessed bullish activity and amazing price action from BTC as it rallied past the $30,000 price region for the first time since last year. &#160; Bitcoin hovers around key support on the weekly chart timeframe &#124;Source: BTCUSD on TradingView.com &#160; However, the previous week saw a huge price dump of BTC below $27,000 after it briefly tested the resistance hanging around the sub $31,000 price level. This week is looking up for Bitcoin as bulls seem to take over. At the time of writing, BTC trades at $29,340, just above a key support level. Related Reading: Dogecoin Bears Unshaken Despite New Trading Pair Addition On Top Exchange A break below the $29,200 support level may see the alpha cryptocurrency looking to find the next support at the sub-$28,000 price level. To the upside, if BTC bulls are able to build momentum and break resistance slightly above $30,000, then it could rally past $31,000 to test the next available resistance level. Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Since the start of the trading year, Bitcoin has maintained a 3-month bullish candle close and is on a path to stealing a fourth. 2023 has been an eventful year for the crypto industry and Bitcoin price, which rallied massively to the surprise of many crypto analysts this month.</p>
<p>The significant price movements of Bitcoin, which saw it rally past $30,000 for the first time since June 2022, triggered euphoria and awakened the interests of retail and large cryptocurrency investors. While market sentiments may seem to be positive at the moment, what could have brought about these sentiments?</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Price Takes The Spotlight</h2>
<p>Bitcoin has shown grit in its recent price movements and rallies, dragging several altcoins with it as it recorded significant gains.</p>
<p>This positive price development of Bitcoin alongside other cryptocurrencies has led to crypto communities calling a start of a bull run and continued price movements.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-holds-at-29300-as-pce-comes-out-neutral/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin Holds At $29,300 As PCE Comes Out Neutral</a></p>
<p>Recently, crypto expert analysts, celebrities, and even some traditional finance analysts have made BTC a topic of major discussion, dropping bullish price predictions for the cryptocurrency.</p>
<p>According to a Reuters <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.reuters.com/technology/bitcoin-could-hit-100000-by-end-2024-standard-chartered-says-2023-04-24/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">report</a>, Geoff Kendrick, head of digital assets research at Standard Chartered, made price predictions for Bitcoin, saying the alpha crypto could reach $100,000 by 2024.</p>
<p>Also, Robert Kiyosaki, the famous best-selling author of &#8220;Rich Dad Poor Dad,&#8221; <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://twitter.com/theRealKiyosaki/status/1649233828517650432?t=9MHHRr4lcBValoSIKx8O8Q&amp;s=19" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">recently called</a> a $100,000 price prediction for BTC on his Twitter handle.</p>
<p>BTC&#8217;s sudden price rise and attention could be attributed to several market factors and happenings in the Tradfi and business world.</p>
<p>Recent news of the <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-rally-m2-money-supply-90-year-low/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">collapse</a> of bank giants such as Silicon Valley and Silvergate caused a stir in the traditional finance world, with users worried about the security of their funds.</p>
<p>Concerns of rising inflation and de-dollarization have also resulted in financial experts and analysts looking to Bitcoin as a &#8220;Safe Haven&#8221; asset due to its decentralized nature.</p>
<p>While the woes of the traditional finance system continue with recent news of the First Republic Bank potentially failing, Bitcoin price is seen looking to close another month in the bullish territory.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Chart Analysis On The Weekly TimeFrame</h2>
<p>On the monthly chart timeframe, Bitcoin price is heading up to close April on a bullish note after its 3-month consecutive run.
The weeks of April have witnessed bullish activity and amazing price action from BTC as it rallied past the $30,000 price region for the first time since last year.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/50s7edrF/" alt="Bitcoin price" width="1280" height="595" /></p>

<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>However, the previous week saw a huge price dump of BTC below $27,000 after it briefly tested the resistance hanging around the sub $31,000 price level.</p>
<p>This week is looking up for Bitcoin as bulls seem to take over. At the time of writing, BTC trades at $29,340, just above a key support level.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/dogecoin/dogecoin-bears-unshaken-despite-new-trading-pair-addition-on-top-exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Dogecoin Bears Unshaken Despite New Trading Pair Addition On Top Exchange</a></p>
<p>A break below the $29,200 support level may see the alpha cryptocurrency looking to find the next support at the sub-$28,000 price level.</p>
<p>To the upside, if BTC bulls are able to build momentum and break resistance slightly above $30,000, then it could rally past $31,000 to test the next available resistance level.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/iStock-921980584-460x250.jpg" width="460" height="250" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Chainlink Price Slides As The Bears Try To Take Over, Will A Rally Follow?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/link/chainlink-price-slides-as-the-bear-try-to-take-over-will-a-rally-follow/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Eli Dambel]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 15:10:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[LINK]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bears]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[chainlink]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[linkusdt]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=529116</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Chainlink (LINK) is experiencing price volatility today despite its slight gains. The bears aim to take control over the price action as LINK dropped from $8.5764 on April 18 to $7.7704 on April 19, 2023.  Its trading volume is up by 97% in the last 24 hours. It also gained 2.27% on its price yesterday. But LINK price shows a decline on today&#8217;s chart representing a bear control. Notably, the overall crypto market cap is down by 0.92%, indicating that bears are in control. Top coins such as BTC and ETH display a bearish trend that is most likely pushing other altcoins to decline. What&#8217;s Ahead For LINK? LINK has formed a red candle on today&#8217;s daily chart, dropping below its 50-day Simple Moving Average (SMA), a short-term bearish sentiment.  Also, it has remained in the sideways trend that began on April 22, 2023, showing that the bears and bulls might be at a stalemate in the market. The price change in this period is slight, but a spike in trading activity is evident for the asset.  Related Reading: Terra Classic Recent Efforts Could Benefit LUNC’s Growth Potential LINK&#8217;s Relative Strength Index (RSI) is 44.58, descending to the oversold region. It implies that further price decline is possible in the coming days. LINK is still above its 200-day SMA despite the price volatility. The 200-day SMA has turned into a support level for the asset at $6.942, indicating a recovery in the long term. Other vital support levels are $6.4 and $6.75. Also, its resistance levels are $7.456, $7.735, $8.8, and $9.48. At the $7.456 resistance, the bears intend to keep LINK&#8217;s price down.  It will likely descend to the $6.942 support level soon, which can act as a pivot point to spark a bullish rally.  Chainlink Upcoming Hackathon Event Sparks Hope Of A Rally The Chainlink Hackathon event promises to bring exciting innovators and developers together. The event will kick off today, April 28, until June 9, 2023. Notably, this event will boost and create awareness in the crypto community. Related Reading: Shiba Inu Whales Unload Billions Amid SHIB Price Retreat The Hackathon Spring 2023 offers developers at different skill levels opportunities to compete in a prize pool of $450,000. Participants must create new decentralized applications (dApps) using Chainlink technology to showcase their potential. Chainlink offers Oracle services enabling hybrid smart contracts to function on any blockchain. Despite the current price slump, LINK has retained most of its gains in 2023. It moved from $5.6224 on January 1, 2023, to its current price of $7.03 at press time. The Hackathon and other developments on the network are vital to its hope of a bull run in 2023 and beyond. Featured image from Pixabay and chart from Tradingview]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Chainlink (LINK) is experiencing price volatility today despite its slight gains. The bears aim to take control over the price action as LINK dropped <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/chainlink/historical-data/" rel="nofollow">from $8.5764 on April 18 to $7.7704</a> on April 19, 2023. </p>
<p>Its trading volume is up by 97% in the last 24 hours. It also gained 2.27% on its price yesterday. But LINK price shows a decline on today&#8217;s chart representing a bear control. </p>
<p>Notably, the overall crypto market cap is down by 0.92%, indicating that bears are in control. Top coins such as BTC and ETH display a bearish trend that is most likely pushing other altcoins to decline.</p>
<h2>What&#8217;s Ahead For LINK?</h2>
<p>LINK has formed a red candle on today&#8217;s daily chart, dropping below its 50-day Simple Moving Average (SMA), a short-term bearish sentiment. </p>
<p>Also, it has remained in the sideways trend that began on April 22, 2023, showing that the bears and bulls might be at a stalemate in the market. The price change in this period is slight, but a spike in trading activity is evident for the asset. </p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/terra-classic-recent-efforts-could-benefit-luncs-growth-potential/?swcfpc=1"> Terra Classic Recent Efforts Could Benefit LUNC’s Growth Potential</a></p>
<p>LINK&#8217;s Relative Strength Index (RSI) is 44.58, descending to the oversold region. It implies that further price decline is possible in the coming days. LINK is still above its 200-day SMA despite the price volatility. The 200-day SMA has turned into a support level for the asset at $6.942, indicating a recovery in the long term.</p>
<p>Other vital support levels are $6.4 and $6.75. Also, its resistance levels are $7.456, $7.735, $8.8, and $9.48. At the $7.456 resistance, the bears intend to keep LINK&#8217;s price down. </p>
<p>It will likely descend to the $6.942 support level soon, which can act as a pivot point to spark a bullish rally. </p>
<h2>Chainlink Upcoming Hackathon Event Sparks Hope Of A Rally</h2>
<p>The <a href="https://chain.link/hackathon?utm_medium=social&amp;utm_source=twitter&amp;utm_campaign=spring-2023-hackathon&amp;agid=sttqzbunpgke" rel="nofollow">Chainlink Hackathon event</a> promises to bring exciting innovators and developers together. The event will kick off today, April 28, until June 9, 2023. Notably, this event will boost and create awareness in the crypto community.</p>

<p>The <a href="https://docs.chain.link/?_ga=2.52769448.1618582368.1682683703-67163498.1681546095" rel="nofollow">Hackathon Spring 2023</a> offers developers at different skill levels opportunities to compete in a prize pool of $450,000. Participants must create new decentralized applications (dApps) using Chainlink technology to showcase their potential. Chainlink offers Oracle services enabling hybrid smart contracts to function on any blockchain.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-529132 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/LINKUSDT_2023-04-28_19-15-23-860x501.png" alt="Chainlink Price Slides As The Bear Try To Take Over, Will A Rally Follow?" width="860" height="501" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/LINKUSDT_2023-04-28_19-15-23-860x501.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/LINKUSDT_2023-04-28_19-15-23-460x268.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/LINKUSDT_2023-04-28_19-15-23-768x447.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/LINKUSDT_2023-04-28_19-15-23-750x437.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/LINKUSDT_2023-04-28_19-15-23-1140x664.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/LINKUSDT_2023-04-28_19-15-23.png 1437w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" />
<p>Despite the current price slump, LINK has retained most of its gains in 2023. It moved from $5.6224 on January 1, 2023, to its current price of $7.03 at press time. The Hackathon and other developments on the network are vital to its hope of a bull run in 2023 and beyond.</p>
<p>Featured image from Pixabay and chart from Tradingview</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/5fa2e075cfcf344baa0e9063_chainlink-open-graph-images_home-with-illustration-460x242.png" width="460" height="242" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum Shark &#038; Whale Addresses Up 5.7% Over Past Year: Santiment</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/ethereum/ethereum-shark-whale-addresses-up-5-7-santiment/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hououin Kyouma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 14:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum Sharks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum Whales]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Santiment]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=529050</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[On-chain data from Santiment shows the Ethereum shark and whale addresses have registered a growth of 5.7% over the past year. Ethereum Sharks &#38; Whales Numbers Have Gone Up During The Past Year According to data from the on-chain analytics firm Santiment, there are now around 380 more sharks and whales in the market compared to 12 months ago. The relevant indicator here is the &#8220;ETH Supply Distribution,&#8221; which tells us about the total amount of Ethereum that each wallet group in the sector is currently holding. Addresses are divided into these &#8220;wallet groups&#8221; based on the number of coins that they are carrying in their balances right now. The 10-100 coins cohort, for instance, includes all wallets that are holding between 10 and 100 ETH at the moment. The Supply Distribution metric for this specific group would measure the sum of the individual balances of all addresses on the network that are satisfying this condition. Related Reading: Bitcoin Accumulation: HODLers Are Buying 15,000 BTC Per Month In the context of the current discussion, the investors of interest are those holding at least 1,000 ETH, meaning that the relevant range here would be 1,000 to infinite coins. Here is a chart that shows the trend in the Ethereum Supply Distribution for such investors over the last couple of years: The value of the metric seems to have been going up in recent days &#124; Source: Santiment on Twitter This wallet range of at least 1,000 ETH (worth about $1.9 million at the current exchange rate) includes two very important cohorts for Ethereum: the sharks and whales. These investors can be quite influential in the market as they hold such large amounts in their wallets (with the whales naturally being more powerful than the sharks since they are the larger of the two. Because of this reason, their behavior may provide hints about where the market may be headed in the long term. As displayed in the above graph, the Supply Distribution for the 1,000+ ETH range had a value of 6,712 a year ago. Since then, the indicator has enjoyed an overall uptrend and its value has risen to 7,092 today. This implies that 380 new addresses belonging to sharks and whales have come up on the network during the last year, representing an increase of about 5.7%. Ethereum saw a decline during most of the past year as the bear market tightly gripped the cryptocurrency. Overall, the asset is still down 35% in this period, meaning that these humongous holders have been buying while the value of the asset has been relatively low. Related Reading: Bitcoin Flash Crash Triggered By Bogus Data? Here’s What Happened From the chart, it&#8217;s visible that the most significant buying spree in this period came just following the collapse of the cryptocurrency exchange FTX. This suggests that the sharks and whales saw the lows following this crash as a profitable buying opportunity. And indeed, their accumulation there looks to have paid off so far, as those lows now appear to be the lowest point for this bear market. These holders have also continued to buy a net amount in the current rally so far, meaning that they are supportive of the price surge. Naturally, this can be a positive sign for bullish momentum in the long term. ETH Price At the time of writing, Ethereum is trading around $1,900, down 1% in the last week. Looks like the asset's value has seen some volatility recently &#124; Source: ETHUSD on TradingView Featured image from Bastian Riccardi on Unsplash.com, charts from TradingView.com, Santiment.net]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On-chain data from Santiment shows the Ethereum shark and whale addresses have registered a growth of 5.7% over the past year.</p>
<h2>Ethereum Sharks &amp; Whales Numbers Have Gone Up During The Past Year</h2>
<p>According to data from the on-chain analytics firm <a href="https://twitter.com/santimentfeed/status/1651707112505090048" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Santiment</a>, there are now around 380 more sharks and whales in the market compared to 12 months ago.</p>
<p>The relevant indicator here is the &#8220;<a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/ethereum/ethereum-breaks-1900-sharks-continue-accumulation/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">ETH Supply Distribution</a>,&#8221; which tells us about the total amount of Ethereum that each wallet group in the sector is currently holding. Addresses are divided into these &#8220;wallet groups&#8221; based on the number of coins that they are carrying in their balances right now.</p>
<p>The 10-100 coins cohort, for instance, includes all wallets that are holding between 10 and 100 ETH at the moment. The Supply Distribution metric for this specific group would measure the sum of the individual balances of all addresses on the network that are satisfying this condition.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-accumulation-hodlers-buying-15000-btc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin Accumulation: HODLers Are Buying 15,000 BTC Per Month</a></p>
<p>In the context of the current discussion, the investors of interest are those holding at least 1,000 ETH, meaning that the relevant range here would be 1,000 to infinite coins.</p>
<p>Here is a chart that shows the trend in the Ethereum Supply Distribution for such investors over the last couple of years:</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone aligncenter" src="https://pbs.twimg.com/media/FuwKJuEaMAAbX5i?format=jpg&amp;name=4096x4096" alt="Ethereum Sharks And Whales" width="2966" height="1834" /></p>

<p>This wallet range of at least 1,000 ETH (worth about $1.9 million at the current exchange rate) includes two very important cohorts for Ethereum: the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-sharks-whales-821-5m-dip-santiment/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">sharks and whales</a>.</p>
<p>These investors can be quite influential in the market as they hold such large amounts in their wallets (with the whales naturally being more powerful than the sharks since they are the larger of the two. Because of this reason, their behavior may provide hints about where the market may be headed in the long term.</p>
<p>As displayed in the above graph, the Supply Distribution for the 1,000+ ETH range had a value of 6,712 a year ago. Since then, the indicator has enjoyed an overall uptrend and its value has risen to 7,092 today.</p>
<p>This implies that 380 new addresses belonging to sharks and whales have come up on the network during the last year, representing an increase of about 5.7%.</p>
<p>Ethereum saw a decline during most of the past year as the bear market tightly gripped the cryptocurrency. Overall, the asset is still down 35% in this period, meaning that these humongous holders have been buying while the value of the asset has been relatively low.</p>



<p>From the chart, it&#8217;s visible that the most significant buying spree in this period came just following the collapse of the cryptocurrency exchange FTX. This suggests that the sharks and whales saw the lows following this crash as a profitable buying opportunity.</p>
<p>And indeed, their accumulation there looks to have paid off so far, as those lows now appear to be the lowest point for this bear market. These holders have also continued to buy a net amount in the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-bulls-keep-pushing-30k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">current rally</a> so far, meaning that they are supportive of the price surge. Naturally, this can be a positive sign for bullish momentum in the long term.</p>
<h2>ETH Price</h2>
<p>At the time of writing, Ethereum is trading around $1,900, down 1% in the last week.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium aligncenter" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/k8BvVcua/" alt="Ethereum Price Chart" width="1533" height="911" /></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/bastian-riccardi-a4Xo_eJ69ps-unsplash-1-460x259.jpg" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Shiba Inu Price Sluggish: Is It A Good Time To Invest Or Cut Losses?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/shiba-inu-price-sluggish-is-it-a-good-time-to-invest-or-cut-losses/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 12:58:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[meme coins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIB]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shiba Inu]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shibarium]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=529070</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Shiba Inu (SHIB) kicked off the year aggressively as it rallied alongside other meme coins. However, as the year progresses, Shiba Inu has experienced a downward trend leaving investors wondering: should they hold or sell?  Shiba Inu coin&#8217;s value on Coingecko is currently at $0.00001027, experiencing a decrease of 3.4% over the last seven days and a more significant slump of 7.8% over the past two weeks. The question on every investor&#8217;s mind now is: what move should they make next with the meme coin? Source: Coingecko Key Levels To Watch For Shiba Inu For traders and investors who want to get a clear grasp of SHIB’s price trajectory, it’s important to remember that there are two key levels to consider: the support level and the resistance level. The support level is currently set at $0.0000095. Alternately, the resistance level, which is now at $0.00001 at the time of writing, signifies the price at which sellers are expected to enter the market and sell their SHIB holdings, hence exerting downward pressure on the price of the meme coin. Related Reading: Terra Classic Recent Efforts Could Benefit LUNC’s Growth Potential The price of SHIB may signify a negative signal and cause traders to sell if it breaks through the support level. On the other hand, if the price rises over the $0.00001 resistance level, it can be a bullish indicator that buyers are flooding the market and pushing the price higher. As such, keeping a close eye on these key levels can help traders make informed decisions when buying or selling SHIB. SHIB&#8217;s Growing Community, Shibarium Dev&#8217;t Could Make It A Good Buy Shiba Inu could be an attractive buy this month because of several reasons. For one, its community is rapidly expanding with many supporters believing in the project&#8217;s long-term potential.  Additionally, the Shiba Inu team has been diligently working on a decentralized ecosystem that includes a non-fungible token (NFT) platform, a decentralized exchange, to mention a few. The Shiba Inu community&#8217;s enthusiasm for Shibarium has been apparent in recent posts on the Telegram group &#8220;Shibarium Tech.&#8221; SHIB total market cap at $5.8 billion on the daily chart at TradingView.com While there have been attempts to obtain information about the latest developments from Shytoshi Kusama, individuals have not heard anything as of April 27 despite Kusama&#8217;s promise of &#8220;big news before May.&#8221; Kusama responded to the community&#8217;s eagerness for Shibarium updates by highlighting the transparency of all activities related to Shibarium, including token transfers. He also emphasized the team&#8217;s dedication to making progress and stated that they are working diligently towards their goals.  Related Reading: Shiba Inu Whales Unload Billions Amid SHIB Price Retreat According to Kusama, the team is currently in &#8220;go mode&#8221; and focused on achieving their objectives rather than just hanging out. Positive updates about Shibarium could have a positive impact on the meme token&#8217;s price during the month of May. (This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk) -Featured image from NorCal Shiba]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Shiba Inu (SHIB) kicked off the year aggressively as it rallied alongside other meme coins. However, as the year progresses, Shiba Inu has experienced a downward trend leaving investors wondering: should they hold or sell? </p>
<p>Shiba Inu coin&#8217;s value on <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Coingecko</a> is currently at $0.00001027, experiencing a decrease of 3.4% over the last seven days and a more significant slump of 7.8% over the past two weeks.</p>
<p>The question on every investor&#8217;s mind now is: what move should they make next with the meme coin?</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-529091 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/a-87.png" alt="" width="750" height="87" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/a-87.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/a-87-460x53.png 460w" sizes="(max-width: 750px) 100vw, 750px" /></p>

<h2><strong>Key Levels To Watch For Shiba Inu</strong></h2>
<p>For traders and investors who want to get a clear grasp of <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/terra-classic-recent-efforts-could-benefit-luncs-growth-potential/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SHIB’s price trajectory</a>, it’s important to remember that there are two key levels to consider: the support level and the resistance level. The support level is currently set at $0.0000095.</p>
<p>Alternately, the resistance level, which is now at $0.00001 at the time of writing, signifies the price at which sellers are expected to enter the market and sell their SHIB holdings, hence exerting downward pressure on the price of the meme coin.</p>

<p>The price of SHIB may signify a negative signal and cause traders to sell if it breaks through the support level. On the other hand, if the price rises over the $0.00001 resistance level, it can be a bullish indicator that buyers are flooding the market and pushing the price higher.</p>
<p>As such, keeping a close eye on these key levels can help traders make informed decisions when buying or selling SHIB.</p>
<h2><strong>SHIB&#8217;s Growing Community, Shibarium Dev&#8217;t Could Make It A Good Buy</strong></h2>
<p>Shiba Inu could be an attractive buy this month because of several reasons. For one, its community is rapidly expanding with many supporters believing in the project&#8217;s long-term potential. </p>
<p>Additionally, the Shiba Inu team has been diligently working on a<a href="https://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20230314005841/en/SHIB-The-Metaverse-To-Launch-On-Shibarium-Layer-2-Blockchain-Setting-New-Standard-for-Web3-Experiences" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow"> decentralized ecosystem </a>that includes a non-fungible token (NFT) platform, a decentralized exchange, to mention a few.</p>
<p>The Shiba Inu community&#8217;s enthusiasm for Shibarium has been apparent in recent posts on the Telegram group &#8220;Shibarium Tech.&#8221; </p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/t4a8PonD/" width="2047" height="979" /></p>

<p>While there have been attempts to obtain information about the latest developments from Shytoshi Kusama, individuals have not heard anything as of April 27 despite Kusama&#8217;s promise of &#8220;big news before May.&#8221;</p>
<p>Kusama responded to the community&#8217;s eagerness for Shibarium updates by highlighting the transparency of all activities related to Shibarium, including token transfers.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-529072 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/a-86.png" alt="" width="655" height="240" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/a-86.png 655w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/a-86-460x169.png 460w" sizes="(max-width: 655px) 100vw, 655px" /></p>
<p>He also emphasized the team&#8217;s dedication to making progress and stated that they are working diligently towards their goals. </p>

<p>According to Kusama, the team is currently in &#8220;go mode&#8221; and focused on achieving their objectives rather than just hanging out. </p>
<p>Positive updates about Shibarium could have a positive impact on the meme token&#8217;s price during the month of May.</p>
<p><em>(This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk)</em></p>
<p><em>-Featured image from NorCal Shiba</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/a-88-460x291.png" width="460" height="291" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Holds At $29,300 As PCE Comes Out Neutral</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-holds-at-29300-as-pce-comes-out-neutral/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jake Simmons]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 12:49:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fed]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[inflation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PCE]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=529055</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[With today&#8217;s release of the Personal Consumption Expenditure (PCE) price index by the Bureau of Economic Analysis, the Bitcoin market just experienced the most important macro event of the week. Ahead of the Federal Open Market Committee (FOMC) of the US Federal Reserve (Fed) on May 2-3, all eyes were on the PCE today. The latter is known as the Fed&#8217;s favorite inflation gauge. (versus CPI). It measures prices paid by consumers for domestic purchases of goods and services and excludes food and energy. The baseline was as follows: February&#8217;s core PCE index was +0.3% on a monthly basis, below the forecast of +0.4%. For March, analysts expected an increase of +0.3%. On an annualized (YoY) basis, an increase of 4.5% was expected, a slight drop from the previous month&#8217;s 4.6%. Hitting expectations or any &#8220;positive&#8221; surprises were expected to be bullish for the Bitcoin market. Renowned analyst Ted (@tedtalksmacro) stated up front: &#8220;Bulls want to continue seeing it trend south!&#8221; and added the chances for a bullish surprise were good: &#8220;CPI + PPI prints earlier in the month, at least for now, suggests that the path of least resistance is for lower inflation numbers.&#8221; PCE Slightly Impacts Bitcoin Price These expectations were not met. As reported by the Bureau of Economic Analysis, core PCE came in at 0.3% on a monthly basis, as expected. On an annual basis, core PCE fell to 4.6%, also delivering the expected number. BREAKING: US PCE data is out! Headline y/y 4.2% vs 4.1% expectation Headline m/m 0.1% vs 0.1% expectation Core y/y 4.6% vs 4.58% expectation Core m/m 0.3% vs 0.3% expectation &#8212; Markets &#38; Mayhem (@Mayhem4Markets) April 28, 2023 Bitcoin price reacted in line with expectations. At the time of writing, BTC was sticking to the price level around $29,300. Related Reading: Bitcoin Wyckoff And Elliott Wave Predict This Next Price Move The big question, however, will be whether progress in fighting inflation is enough for Fed Chairman Jerome Powell. In a phone prank with a fake Ukraine President Volodymyr Zelenskyy yesterday, Powell acknowledged that there are at least two more rate hikes coming, followed by a long period of high interest rates with significant negative effects on the US economy and the US labor market. Powell also stated that a recession in the United States is likely. &#8220;This is what it takes to get inflation down. By cooling off the economy and cooling off the labor market inflation comes down. We don&#8217;t know of any painless way for inflation to come down.&#8221; In a prank call with a fake Zelenskyy Jerome Powell, Chairman of the Federal Reserve, admits at least 2 more upcoming interest rate hikes followed by a long period of high rates with significant negative effects on the US economy and the US labor market. https://t.co/vDb19Ed5ux &#8212; Kim Dotcom (@KimDotcom) April 27, 2023 What Will The Fed Make Of The Data? After the latest macro data, Fed Funds Futures traders expect a probability of more than 80% for a 25 basis points (bps) rate hike next Wednesday. The probability according to the CME FedWatch Tool was at 88% before the release of the PCE and remained at this level afterwards. Related Reading: Why This Top Financial Expert Is Saying ‘Buy Bitcoin’ Amid Looming Bank Failures Still, the market is calling Powell&#8217;s bluff. Liz Young, head of investment strategy at SoFi shared the chart below and stated prior to the PCE release: Market pricing implies 88% odds of a rate hike next week, up from earlier in the month. Some traders are starting to bet on a hike in June as well, but that&#8217;s less certain. Either way, markets still think we&#8217;re going to get multiple cuts later in 2023 &#38; early 2024. Today&#8217;s release is not expected to change this. On the other hand, a second wave of bank failures is currently brewing in the US. Higher interest rates are likely to push more regional banks to their limit. Bitcoin could once again be the beneficiary, as the Fed can&#8217;t hike as high as they would want to. At press time, the Bitcoin price stood at $29,314. Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>With today&#8217;s release of the Personal Consumption Expenditure (PCE) price index by the Bureau of Economic Analysis, the Bitcoin market just experienced the most important macro event of the week. Ahead of the Federal Open Market Committee (FOMC) of the US Federal Reserve (Fed) on May 2-3, all eyes were on the PCE today.</p>
<p>The latter is known as the Fed&#8217;s favorite inflation gauge. (versus CPI). It measures prices paid by consumers for domestic purchases of goods and services and excludes food and energy.</p>
<p>The baseline was as follows: February&#8217;s core PCE index was +0.3% on a monthly basis, below the forecast of +0.4%. For March, analysts expected an increase of +0.3%. On an annualized (YoY) basis, an increase of 4.5% was expected, a slight drop from the previous month&#8217;s 4.6%.</p>
<p>Hitting expectations or any &#8220;positive&#8221; surprises were expected to be bullish for the Bitcoin market. Renowned analyst Ted (@tedtalksmacro) <a href="https://twitter.com/tedtalksmacro/status/1651895148421193730" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">stated</a> up front: &#8220;Bulls want to continue seeing it trend south!&#8221; and added the chances for a bullish surprise were good: &#8220;CPI + PPI prints earlier in the month, at least for now, suggests that the path of least resistance is for lower inflation numbers.&#8221;</p>
<h2>PCE Slightly Impacts Bitcoin Price</h2>
<p>These expectations were not met. As reported by the Bureau of Economic Analysis, core PCE came in at 0.3% on a monthly basis, as expected. On an annual basis, core PCE fell to 4.6%, also delivering the expected number.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">BREAKING: US PCE data is out!</p>
<p>Headline y/y 4.2% vs 4.1% expectation</p>
<p>Headline m/m 0.1% vs 0.1% expectation</p>
<p>Core y/y 4.6% vs 4.58% expectation</p>
<p>Core m/m 0.3% vs 0.3% expectation</p>
<p>&mdash; Markets &amp; Mayhem (@Mayhem4Markets) <a href="https://twitter.com/Mayhem4Markets/status/1651927343353544704?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">April 28, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p></p>
<p>Bitcoin price reacted in line with expectations. At the time of writing, BTC was sticking to the price level around $29,300.</p>

<p>The big question, however, will be whether progress in fighting inflation is enough for Fed Chairman Jerome Powell. In a phone prank with a fake Ukraine President Volodymyr Zelenskyy yesterday, Powell acknowledged that there are at least two more rate hikes coming, followed by a long period of high interest rates with significant negative effects on the US economy and the US labor market.</p>
<p>Powell also stated that a recession in the United States is likely. &#8220;This is what it takes to get inflation down. By cooling off the economy and cooling off the labor market inflation comes down. We don&#8217;t know of any painless way for inflation to come down.&#8221;</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">In a prank call with a fake Zelenskyy Jerome Powell, Chairman of the Federal Reserve, admits at least 2 more upcoming interest rate hikes followed by a long period of high rates with significant negative effects on the US economy and the US labor market. <a href="https://t.co/vDb19Ed5ux" rel="nofollow">https://t.co/vDb19Ed5ux</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Kim Dotcom (@KimDotcom) <a href="https://twitter.com/KimDotcom/status/1651550282449584128?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">April 27, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p></p>
<h2>What Will The Fed Make Of The Data?</h2>
<p>After the latest macro data, Fed Funds Futures traders expect a probability of more than 80% for a 25 basis points (bps) rate hike next Wednesday. The probability according to the CME FedWatch Tool was at 88% before the release of the PCE and remained at this level afterwards.</p>

<p>Still, the market is calling Powell&#8217;s bluff. Liz Young, head of investment strategy at SoFi shared the chart below and <a href="https://twitter.com/LizYoungStrat/status/1651598319695679492" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">stated</a> prior to the PCE release:</p>
<blockquote><p><strong>Market pricing implies 88% odds of a rate hike next week, up from earlier in the month. Some traders are starting to bet on a hike in June as well, but that&#8217;s less certain. Either way, markets still think we&#8217;re going to get multiple cuts later in 2023 &amp; early 2024.</strong></p></blockquote>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-529076 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Fuun6zzXwBY_wrP.jpg" alt="Market-implied rate hikes / cuts" width="1334" height="822" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Fuun6zzXwBY_wrP.jpg 1334w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Fuun6zzXwBY_wrP-460x283.jpg 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Fuun6zzXwBY_wrP-860x530.jpg 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Fuun6zzXwBY_wrP-768x473.jpg 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Fuun6zzXwBY_wrP-750x462.jpg 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Fuun6zzXwBY_wrP-1140x702.jpg 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1334px) 100vw, 1334px" />
<p>Today&#8217;s release is not expected to change this. On the other hand, a second wave of bank failures is currently <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/all/banking-crisis-redux-bitcoin-first-republic-bank-shares/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">brewing</a> in the US. Higher interest rates are likely to push more regional banks to their limit. Bitcoin could once again be the beneficiary, as the Fed can&#8217;t hike as high as they would want to.</p>
<p>At press time, the Bitcoin price stood at $29,314.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-529084 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/BTCUSD_2023-04-28_14-43-59.png" alt="Bitcoin price" width="3625" height="1672" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/BTCUSD_2023-04-28_14-43-59.png 3625w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/BTCUSD_2023-04-28_14-43-59-460x212.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/BTCUSD_2023-04-28_14-43-59-860x397.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/BTCUSD_2023-04-28_14-43-59-768x354.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/BTCUSD_2023-04-28_14-43-59-1536x708.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/BTCUSD_2023-04-28_14-43-59-2048x945.png 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/BTCUSD_2023-04-28_14-43-59-750x346.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/BTCUSD_2023-04-28_14-43-59-1140x526.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 3625px) 100vw, 3625px" />

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/iStock-1316231784-460x339.jpg" width="460" height="339" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>How Soon Will Litecoin Breach This Psychological Resistance Level?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/litecoin/how-soon-will-litecoin-breach-this-psychological-resistance-level/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[anushsamal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 11:52:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Litecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ltc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ltc/usd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LTCUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=529043</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[In recent trading sessions, the price of Litecoin has remained stagnant below a significant resistance level while Bitcoin has experienced consistent fluctuations. Although Litecoin showed a slight increase of 2% in the last 24 hours, it lost 1% over the week, indicating consolidation. The altcoin&#8217;s technical outlook suggests a potential bearish takeover, as demand and accumulation for the altcoin have both declined. The crucial overhead resistance level of Litecoin has been a barrier that the coin has failed to surpass previously. In the event of another rejection over the coming trading sessions, bears could successfully take over. Related Reading: Terra Classic Recent Efforts Could Benefit LUNC’s Growth Potential As Bitcoin approaches the $30,000 mark, major altcoins are following a similar price trend. If BTC successfully crosses this resistance level, Litecoin could experience a rally. However, the market capitalization of LTC has decreased in the last 24 hours, indicating a decline in buying strength. Litecoin Price Analysis: One-Day Chart At the time of writing, LTC was trading at $89.58, and the overhead resistance level was at $90, which the coin has attempted to break through over the past few weeks. If LTC manages to surpass this level, it could potentially trade near the $100 mark. However, for a recovery on the chart to occur, selling pressure needs to decrease. On the flip side, if LTC falls from the $89 mark, it could reach $88. Failing to stay above that level could drag the price down to $84. The last trading session showed a red volume of LTC traded, indicating that sellers were dominating the market. Technical Analysis Following the formation of a tall bearish engulfing candlestick, the price of LTC has been steadily decreasing, and demand has also diminished. The Relative Strength Index (RSI) remains below the 50-mark, indicating that there is more selling pressure than buying strength. Additionally, LTC has fallen below the 20-Simple Moving Average line, indicating that sellers are driving the price momentum. However, the price has moved above the 50-SMA line (yellow), suggesting that LTC might attempt to recover over the next trading session. In line with other indicators, LTC has shown sell signals associated with negative price action. The Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD), which indicates price momentum and reversals, has continued to form red histograms, signaling sellers to the table. Related Reading: Why Coinbase CEO Believes SEC’s Crypto Warning Is Harmful To The US The Directional Movement Index has also been negative, with the +DI line (blue) below the -DI line (orange). Furthermore, the Average Directional Index has fallen below the 20-mark, indicating that the current price trend lacks strength. However, with an increase in demand and broader market strength, LTC may be able to break through its overhead resistance level in the coming trading sessions. Featured Image From UnSplash, Charts From TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In recent trading sessions, the price of Litecoin has remained stagnant below a significant resistance level while Bitcoin has experienced consistent fluctuations. Although Litecoin showed a slight increase of 2% in the last 24 hours, it lost 1% over the week, indicating consolidation.</p>
<p>The altcoin&#8217;s technical outlook suggests a potential bearish takeover, as demand and accumulation for the altcoin have both declined. The crucial overhead resistance level of Litecoin has been a barrier that the coin has failed to surpass previously. In the event of another rejection over the coming trading sessions, bears could successfully take over.</p>

<p>As Bitcoin approaches the $30,000 mark, major altcoins are following a similar price trend. If BTC successfully crosses this resistance level, Litecoin could experience a rally. However, the market capitalization of LTC has decreased in the last 24 hours, indicating a decline in buying strength.</p>
<h2>Litecoin Price Analysis: One-Day Chart</h2>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-529054 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/LTCUSD_2023-04-28_16-11-23.png" alt="Litecoin" width="1816" height="830" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/LTCUSD_2023-04-28_16-11-23.png 1816w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/LTCUSD_2023-04-28_16-11-23-460x210.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/LTCUSD_2023-04-28_16-11-23-860x393.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/LTCUSD_2023-04-28_16-11-23-768x351.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/LTCUSD_2023-04-28_16-11-23-1536x702.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/LTCUSD_2023-04-28_16-11-23-750x343.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/LTCUSD_2023-04-28_16-11-23-1140x521.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1816px) 100vw, 1816px" />






<p>At the time of writing, LTC was trading at $89.58, and the overhead resistance level was at $90, which the coin has attempted to break through over the past few weeks. If LTC manages to surpass this level, it could potentially trade near the $100 mark.</p>
<p>However, for a recovery on the chart to occur, selling pressure needs to decrease. On the flip side, if LTC falls from the $89 mark, it could reach $88. Failing to stay above that level could drag the price down to $84. The last trading session showed a red volume of LTC traded, indicating that sellers were dominating the market.</p>




<h2 class="text-gray-400 flex self-end lg:self-center justify-center mt-2 gap-2 md:gap-3 lg:gap-1 lg:absolute lg:top-0 lg:translate-x-full lg:right-0 lg:mt-0 lg:pl-2 visible">Technical Analysis</h2>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-529056 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/LTCUSD_2023-04-28_16-11-56-1.png" alt="Litecoin" width="1816" height="743" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/LTCUSD_2023-04-28_16-11-56-1.png 1816w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/LTCUSD_2023-04-28_16-11-56-1-460x188.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/LTCUSD_2023-04-28_16-11-56-1-860x352.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/LTCUSD_2023-04-28_16-11-56-1-768x314.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/LTCUSD_2023-04-28_16-11-56-1-1536x628.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/LTCUSD_2023-04-28_16-11-56-1-750x307.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/LTCUSD_2023-04-28_16-11-56-1-1140x466.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1816px) 100vw, 1816px" />






<p>Following the formation of a tall bearish engulfing candlestick, the price of LTC has been steadily decreasing, and demand has also diminished. The Relative Strength Index (RSI) remains below the 50-mark, indicating that there is more selling pressure than buying strength.</p>
<p>Additionally, LTC has fallen below the 20-Simple Moving Average line, indicating that sellers are driving the price momentum. However, the price has moved above the 50-SMA line (yellow), suggesting that LTC might attempt to recover over the next trading session.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-529061 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/LTCUSD_2023-04-28_16-38-44.png" alt="Litecoin" width="1816" height="743" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/LTCUSD_2023-04-28_16-38-44.png 1816w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/LTCUSD_2023-04-28_16-38-44-460x188.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/LTCUSD_2023-04-28_16-38-44-860x352.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/LTCUSD_2023-04-28_16-38-44-768x314.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/LTCUSD_2023-04-28_16-38-44-1536x628.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/LTCUSD_2023-04-28_16-38-44-750x307.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/LTCUSD_2023-04-28_16-38-44-1140x466.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1816px) 100vw, 1816px" />





<p>In line with other indicators, LTC has shown sell signals associated with negative price action. The Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD), which indicates price momentum and reversals, has continued to form red histograms, signaling sellers to the table.</p>

<p>The Directional Movement Index has also been negative, with the +DI line (blue) below the -DI line (orange). Furthermore, the Average Directional Index has fallen below the 20-mark, indicating that the current price trend lacks strength. However, with an increase in demand and broader market strength, LTC may be able to break through its overhead resistance level in the coming trading sessions.</p>










]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/kanchanara-PxGgCR0IZ80-unsplash-460x306.jpg" width="460" height="306" />	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
