<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
>

<channel>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.newsbtc.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<description>Bitcoin &#38; Cryptocurrency News Today</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 22:20:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Bearish Signal: BNB Open Interest Skyrockets To New Highs</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/bnb/bnb-open-interest-new-highs/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Best Owie]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 23:30:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BNB]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance Coin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BNBUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bnbusdt]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=542965</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Crypto exchange Binance has been the subject of intense regulatory scrutiny over the last few months and BNB has suffered as a result. Even now, as it seems the crypto exchange is beginning to find its footing once more amid regulatory wolves circling, its native token is still under immense selling pressure. This is evidenced by the BNB open interest, which has now skyrocketed to new all-time highs. BNB Open Interest Reaches New All-Time High In an interesting turn of events, BNB shorts are ramping up even at a time when the crypto market seems to be on a recovery trend. According to a Twitter post by analyst Dylan LeClair, this has caused the open interest in the digital asset to rise exponentially. Related Reading: Crypto Liquidations Cross $300 Million Amid Massive Market Recovery The chart shared by LeClair shows that BNB&#8217;s open interest is now sitting at $400 million. This is over four times higher than the previous all-time high for the digital asset which was $50 million back in 2020. And unlike then, the surge in open interest right now is more bearish than it is bullish. Hmmm, some interesting flow in $BNB futures: &#8211; Perpetual futures open interest is seeing new highs as funding rates have gone deeply negative (-200% APR for next funding period) (Chart #1) &#8211; looks as if someone is getting ahead of some bad news flow. &#8211; The last time BNB… pic.twitter.com/1B27OkjvPx — Dylan LeClair 🟠 (@DylanLeClair_) July 17, 2023 This current increase has seen funding rates move above negative 200% and yet traders continue to short the altcoin. The fact that traders are choosing this route despite the high cost to do so points to the expectations of a massive crash coming for the digital asset. As LeClair points out, this could mean that the United States Department of Justice (DoJ) is finally leveling charges against the crypto exchange. “And people in the know are positioning accordingly.” Will The Altcoin Survive a DoJ Lawsuit? As already demonstrated by the Securities and Exchange Commission’s (SEC) lawsuit against the Binance crypto exchange, a lawsuit from regulators would have an adverse impact on the price of BNB. When the SEC sued the exchange in early June, the price of BNB plummeted by over 20% over a few days period.  BNB price continues to hold above $240 &#124; Source: BNBUSD on TradingView.com Given such a response, a lawsuit from the DoJ would be even worse because of its implications. And if this were to happen this week, then another 20% decline from here would see the digital asset lose its footing above $200. Related Reading: Polygon Upgrade Proposal Pushes Price Over 5%, Is It Too Late To Buy? For right now, the price of BNB is still holding up nicely above $240. One reason for this could be the Arkham sale being carried out on the Binance launchpad. As this sale requires BNB for subscriptions to participate, it has provided temporary buy pressure for investors to participate. However, once the sale ends on July 18, this temporary plug would be eliminated and the cryptocurrency will likely fall back to the $230 territory. Follow Best Owie on Twitter for market insights, updates, and the occasional funny tweet… Featured image from Currency.com, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="p2">Crypto exchange Binance has been the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/fud-or-real-binance-selling-bitcoin-to-prop-up-bnb/">subject</a> of intense regulatory scrutiny over the last few months and BNB has suffered as a result. Even now, as it seems the crypto exchange is beginning to find its footing once more amid regulatory wolves circling, its native token is still under immense selling pressure. This is evidenced by the BNB open interest, which has now skyrocketed to new all-time highs.</p>
<h2 class="p2">BNB Open Interest Reaches New All-Time High</h2>
<p class="p2">In an interesting turn of events, BNB shorts are ramping up even at a time when the crypto market seems to be on a recovery trend. According to a Twitter <a href="https://twitter.com/DylanLeClair_/status/1680749844170784769?s=20" rel="nofollow">post</a> by analyst Dylan LeClair, this has caused the open interest in the digital asset to rise exponentially.</p>

<p class="p2">The chart shared by LeClair shows that BNB&#8217;s open interest is now sitting at $400 million. This is over four times higher than the previous all-time high for the digital asset which was $50 million back in 2020. And unlike then, the surge in open interest right now is more bearish than it is bullish.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Hmmm, some interesting flow in <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24BNB&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$BNB</a> futures:</p>
<p>&#8211; Perpetual futures open interest is seeing new highs as funding rates have gone deeply negative (-200% APR for next funding period) (Chart #1) &#8211; looks as if someone is getting ahead of some bad news flow.</p>
<p>&#8211; The last time BNB… <a href="https://t.co/1B27OkjvPx" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/1B27OkjvPx</a></p>
<p>— Dylan LeClair <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f7e0.png" alt="🟠" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> (@DylanLeClair_) <a href="https://twitter.com/DylanLeClair_/status/1680749844170784769?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">July 17, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p class="p2">This current increase has seen funding rates move above negative 200% and yet traders continue to short the altcoin. The fact that traders are choosing this route despite the high cost to do so points to the expectations of a massive crash coming for the digital asset.</p>
<p class="p2">As LeClair points out, this could mean that the United States Department of Justice (DoJ) is finally leveling charges against the crypto exchange. “And people in the know are positioning accordingly.”</p>
<h2 class="p2">Will The Altcoin Survive a DoJ Lawsuit?</h2>
<p class="p2">As already <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/bnb/bnb-market-cap-down-by-25-in-june-amidst-binance-regulatory-pressure/">demonstrated</a> by the Securities and Exchange Commission’s (SEC) lawsuit against the Binance crypto exchange, a lawsuit from regulators would have an adverse impact on the price of BNB. When the SEC sued the exchange in early June, the price of BNB plummeted by over 20% over a few days period.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/iwSP16O4/" alt="Binance Coin (BNB) price chart from TradingView.com" width="2884" height="1758"/></p>

<p class="p2">Given such a response, a lawsuit from the DoJ would be even worse because of its implications. And if this were to happen this week, then another 20% decline from here would see the digital asset lose its footing above $200.</p>

<p class="p2">For right now, the price of BNB is still holding up nicely above $240. One reason for this could be the Arkham sale being carried out on the Binance launchpad. As this sale requires BNB for subscriptions to participate, it has provided temporary buy pressure for investors to participate. However, once the sale ends on July 18, this temporary plug would be eliminated and the cryptocurrency will likely fall back to the $230 territory.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BNB-1-460x268.jpeg" width="460" height="268" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>This Bitcoin Continuation Pattern Points To 3-6 Months Of Uptrend Ahead</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/this-bitcoin-continuation-pattern-points-to-3-6-months-of-uptrend-ahead/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tony "The Bull"]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 22:19:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=543029</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin price is pulling back after a strong finish in the crypto market last week. However, this past Sunday night’s weekend close was also the close of the 4-week BTCUSD chart, which has potentially confirmed a high timeframe continuation pattern. If the continuation pattern is indeed valid, it could point to 3-6 months of an extended uptrend, making 2023 an extremely bullish year in the end. Here is everything you need to know about the bullish continuation pattern and what it could mean for the crypto market. Bullish Candlestick Continuation Pattern To Light Up Second Half Of 2023 2023 has been an interesting year in the cryptocurrency market. Bitcoin has been mostly bullish, but nothing compared to what we’ve witnessed in the past — as recently as 2020. Meanwhile, altcoins have been long suffering an onslaught from the US SEC. This has kept Bitcoin further at bay against the US Dollar, while eating up altcoin capital on the BTC pair. Despite an important week for the industry and BTCUSD setting a new high for the year, Bitcoin lost some momentum and is now trading below $30,000 per coin. However, before the correction happened, the 4-week BTCUSD candle also closed on Sunday night. Related Reading: Perfect Storm: Why Bitcoin &#38; Crypto Are Poised For A Dramatic Recovery The 4-week timeframe is slightly more sensitive than the monthly at between 2 to 3 days less, sometimes offering unique signals from the 1-month. Sunday night’s close forever marked the chart with the last candle necessary for a completed Rising Three Method pattern. The Rising Three Method is a bullish Japanese candlesticks continuation pattern. It consists of a large white candle, followed by three small-bodied candles in a row. After the period of consolidation, a large white candle closes above the trio of black candles, engulfing them all. The Rising Three Method pattern &#124; BTCUSD on TradingView.com Bitcoin Buyers Make A Statement: Rising Three Method Pattern Completes The pattern shows that after a pause, buyers resume control. By making this statement, bulls could gain control of Bitcoin over the next 3 to 6 months. The reason for the timing, is due to the length of each candle’s session. After a Japanese candlestick pattern confirms, its expected results should appear within the next 3-5 candlesticks. 3-5 sessions of 4 weeks total, equals roughly 12 to 20 weeks, or around 3-5 months. That timing would take any potential bull rally through the end of the year. For further validation of the fact upside should appear within 3-5 candles after a confirmed signal, we can see that a morning star pattern completed during the first candlestick close of the year. The second candle of the year was a doji, then this bullish continuation pattern formed. All of this combined tells a possible story of a continued bull market for the rest of the calendar year. Related Reading: The One Ingredient Missing From A Full-Bore Bitcoin Bull Run The Japanese candlestick continuation pattern also comes with plenty of confluence through a confirmed bullish crossover of the LMACD. The technical indicator suggests a momentum shift supportive of more upside in Bitcoin. Will this continuation pattern result in a strong bull market breakout? This chart originally appeared in issue #12 of CoinChartist (VIP) alongside a dozen exclusive XRP, Bitcoin, and other charts. Subscribe for free. Tony is the author of the CoinChartist (VIP) newsletter. Follow @TonyTheBullBTC &#38; @coinchartist_io on Twitter. Or join the TonyTradesBTC Telegram for daily market insights and technical analysis education. Please note: Content is educational and should not be considered investment advice. Featured image from iStockPhoto, Charts from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin price is pulling back after a strong finish in the crypto market last week. However, this past Sunday night’s weekend close was also the close of the 4-week BTCUSD chart, which has potentially confirmed a high timeframe continuation pattern.</p>
<p>If the continuation pattern is indeed valid, it could point to 3-6 months of an extended uptrend, making 2023 an extremely bullish year in the end. Here is everything you need to know about the bullish continuation pattern and what it could mean for the crypto market.</p>
<h2>Bullish Candlestick Continuation Pattern To Light Up Second Half Of 2023</h2>
<p>2023 has been an interesting year in the cryptocurrency market. Bitcoin has been mostly bullish, but nothing compared to what we’ve witnessed in the past — as recently as 2020. Meanwhile, altcoins have been long suffering an onslaught from the US SEC. This has kept Bitcoin further at bay against the US Dollar, while eating up altcoin capital on the BTC pair.</p>
<p>Despite an important week for the industry and BTCUSD setting a new high for the year, Bitcoin lost some momentum and is now trading below $30,000 per coin. However, before the correction happened, the 4-week BTCUSD candle also closed on Sunday night.</p>

<p>The 4-week timeframe is slightly more sensitive than the monthly at between 2 to 3 days less, sometimes offering unique signals from the 1-month. Sunday night’s close forever marked the chart with the last candle necessary for a completed <a href="https://coinchartist.io/rising-three-methods/education/japanese-candlesticks/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Rising Three Method</a> pattern.</p>
<p>The Rising Three Method is a bullish Japanese candlesticks continuation pattern. It consists of a large white candle, followed by three small-bodied candles in a row. After the period of consolidation, a large white candle closes above the trio of black candles, engulfing them all.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large wp-image-543031 aligncenter" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/1489EC1D-BBB8-450B-8189-3D6E41ECBF54-860x535.png" alt="Bitcoin Rising Three Method" width="860" height="535" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/1489EC1D-BBB8-450B-8189-3D6E41ECBF54-860x535.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/1489EC1D-BBB8-450B-8189-3D6E41ECBF54-460x286.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/1489EC1D-BBB8-450B-8189-3D6E41ECBF54-768x478.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/1489EC1D-BBB8-450B-8189-3D6E41ECBF54-1536x955.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/1489EC1D-BBB8-450B-8189-3D6E41ECBF54-2048x1274.png 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/1489EC1D-BBB8-450B-8189-3D6E41ECBF54-750x466.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/1489EC1D-BBB8-450B-8189-3D6E41ECBF54-1140x709.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/></p>

<h2>Bitcoin Buyers Make A Statement: Rising Three Method Pattern Completes</h2>
<p>The pattern shows that after a pause, buyers resume control. By making this statement, bulls could gain control of Bitcoin over the next 3 to 6 months. The reason for the timing, is due to the length of each candle’s session. After a Japanese candlestick pattern confirms, its expected results should appear within the next 3-5 candlesticks. 3-5 sessions of 4 weeks total, equals roughly 12 to 20 weeks, or around 3-5 months.</p>
<p>That timing would take any potential bull rally through the end of the year. For further validation of the fact upside should appear within 3-5 candles after a confirmed signal, we can see that a morning star pattern completed during the first candlestick close of the year. The second candle of the year was a doji, then this bullish continuation pattern formed. All of this combined tells a possible story of a continued bull market for the rest of the calendar year.</p>

<p>The Japanese candlestick continuation pattern also comes with plenty of confluence through a confirmed bullish crossover of the LMACD. The technical indicator suggests a momentum shift supportive of more upside in Bitcoin.</p>
<p>Will this continuation pattern result in a strong bull market breakout?</p>
<p>This chart originally appeared in <a href="https://coinchartist.substack.com/p/issue-12-patience-for-the-grand-finale" rel="nofollow">issue #12 of CoinChartist (VIP)</a> alongside a dozen exclusive XRP, Bitcoin, and other charts. Subscribe for <a href="https://coinchartist.substack.com/p/issue-12-patience-for-the-grand-finale" rel="nofollow">free</a>.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/C9D0C50F-7BB5-4547-9DBB-0ECAE62360FF-460x330.jpeg" width="460" height="330" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Uniswap Launches UniswapX Protocol, Sparking 3% Surge In UNI&#8217;s Price</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/uni/uniswap-launches-uniswapx-protocol-sparking-3-surge-in-unis-price/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 21:30:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[UNI]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Uniswap]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Uniswap (UNI)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[UNIUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=543004</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Uniswap, the leading decentralized exchange (DEX), has announced the launch of UniswapX, a permissionless and open-source protocol for trading across automated market makers (AMMs) and other liquidity sources.  According to the announcement, UniswapX aims to improve self-custody swapping and grow on-chain trading by offering better prices through the aggregation of liquidity sources, gas-free swapping, protection against maximal extractable value (MEV), and no cost for failed transactions.  Uniswap Latest Protocol Launch  UniswapX addresses the growing complexity of on-chain routing and the fragmentation of liquidity pools resulting from the increasing number of customized pool designs.  The protocol outsources routing complexity to a network of third-party fillers who compete to fill swaps using on-chain liquidity like AMM pools or their private inventory. This allows swappers to use the Uniswap interface without worrying about getting the best price and ensures that transactions are always transparently recorded and settled on-chain. Related Reading: zkSync Unveils Boojum Upgrade: The Ultimate Solution For Scalability And Security? Per the announcement, gas-free swapping is a key feature of UniswapX. Swappers sign a unique off-chain order, which is then submitted on-chain by fillers who pay gas on the swappers&#8217; behalf.  This eliminates the need for swappers to pay gas or hold a chain&#8217;s native network token to trade. MEV protection is also provided by UniswapX, which returns MEV that would be left on the table to be captured by an arbitrage transaction to swappers through improved prices. UniswapX also has plans to launch a cross-chain version later this year that combines swapping and bridging into one seamless action.  This will provide users with the ability to exchange between different blockchain networks in a seamless and trustless manner. This is made possible through the use of bridges, which are specialized smart contracts that enable the transfer of assets between different blockchain networks. In addition, instead of receiving a bridge-specific token, users can choose which assets to receive on the destination chain.  Strong Resistance Causes UNI To Retract After the announcement of the launch of the UniswapX protocol, the price of Uniswap&#8217;s native token, UNI, experienced a surge of around 3%. UNI reached a high of $6.152, a level not seen since April 2023. The excitement generated by the launch of this new protocol led to a surge in demand for UNI, as traders anticipated improved user experience and better prices for on-chain trading. Related Reading: XRP Crosses 1 Million Trades Per Minute Following Court Ruling However, UNI faced a strong resistance line at this same level, causing the token to retrace and lose all the gains generated by the announcement. At present, UNI is trading at $5.738, down by 1.4% in the last 24 hours. Despite this recent dip, UNI has posted significant gains in the 30-day timeframe, with a staggering 28% profit. On the flip side, according to Token Terminal data, Uniswap&#8217;s market cap (circulating) currently stands at $4.76 billion, representing a 28.3% increase over the past 30 days. The market cap (fully diluted) is $5.77 billion, up 26.01% over the same period. Uniswap&#8217;s total value locked (TVL) is currently $3.67 billion, a decrease of 0.54% over the past 30 days. The price fees (P/F) ratio (fully diluted) stands at 17.50x, indicating that the market values Uniswap&#8217;s future earnings potential at a premium. Uniswap&#8217;s trading volume (annualized) is $349.19 billion, representing a decrease of 8.05%. In terms of user activity, Uniswap has had an average of 69.640 daily active users over the past 30 days, representing an increase of 2.7%.  Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com ]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Uniswap, the leading decentralized exchange (DEX), has <a href="https://blog.uniswap.org/uniswapx-protocol" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">announced </a>the launch of UniswapX, a permissionless and open-source protocol for trading across automated market makers (AMMs) and other liquidity sources. </p>
<p>According to the announcement, UniswapX aims to improve self-custody swapping and grow on-chain trading by offering better prices through the aggregation of liquidity sources, gas-free swapping, protection against maximal extractable value (MEV), and no cost for failed transactions. </p>
<h2>Uniswap Latest Protocol Launch </h2>
<p>UniswapX addresses the growing complexity of on-chain routing and the fragmentation of liquidity pools resulting from the increasing number of customized pool designs. </p>
<p>The protocol outsources routing complexity to a network of third-party fillers who compete to fill swaps using on-chain liquidity like AMM pools or their private inventory. This allows swappers to use the Uniswap interface without worrying about getting the best price and ensures that transactions are always transparently recorded and settled on-chain.</p>

<p>Per the announcement, gas-free swapping is a key feature of UniswapX. Swappers sign a unique off-chain order, which is then submitted on-chain by fillers who pay gas on the swappers&#8217; behalf. </p>
<p>This eliminates the need for swappers to pay gas or hold a chain&#8217;s native network token to trade. MEV protection is also provided by UniswapX, which returns MEV that would be left on the table to be captured by an arbitrage transaction to swappers through improved prices.</p>
<p>UniswapX also has plans to launch a cross-chain version later this year that combines swapping and bridging into one seamless action. </p>
<p>This will provide users with the ability to exchange between different blockchain networks in a seamless and trustless manner. This is made possible through the use of bridges, which are specialized smart contracts that enable the transfer of assets between different blockchain networks.</p>
<p>In addition, instead of receiving a bridge-specific token, users can choose which assets to receive on the destination chain. </p>
Strong Resistance Causes UNI To Retract
<p>After the announcement of the launch of the UniswapX protocol, the price of Uniswap&#8217;s native token, UNI, experienced a surge of around 3%. UNI reached a high of $6.152, a level not seen since April 2023. The excitement generated by the launch of this new protocol led to a surge in demand for UNI, as traders anticipated improved user experience and better prices for on-chain trading.</p>

<p>However, UNI faced a strong resistance line at this same level, causing the token to retrace and lose all the gains generated by the announcement. At present, UNI is trading at $5.738, down by 1.4% in the last 24 hours. Despite this recent dip, UNI has posted significant gains in the 30-day timeframe, with a staggering 28% profit.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/hQLEAaXy/" alt="Uniswap" width="1814" height="858"/>
<p>On the flip side, according to Token Terminal <a href="https://tokenterminal.com/terminal/projects/uniswap" rel="nofollow">data</a>, Uniswap&#8217;s market cap (circulating) currently stands at $4.76 billion, representing a 28.3% increase over the past 30 days. The market cap (fully diluted) is $5.77 billion, up 26.01% over the same period.</p>
<p>Uniswap&#8217;s total value locked (TVL) is currently $3.67 billion, a decrease of 0.54% over the past 30 days. The price fees (P/F) ratio (fully diluted) stands at 17.50x, indicating that the market values Uniswap&#8217;s future earnings potential at a premium. Uniswap&#8217;s trading volume (annualized) is $349.19 billion, representing a decrease of 8.05%.</p>
<p>In terms of user activity, Uniswap has had an average of 69.640 daily active users over the past 30 days, representing an increase of 2.7%. </p>
<p>Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/nik-Geu-i5VvI1A-unsplash-308x460.jpg" width="308" height="460" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>SUI Continues Rally As Sui 8192 Web3 Game Fuels Blockchain Activity To Hit New Peak</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/altcoin/sui-continues-rally-as-sui-8192-web3-game-fuels-blockchain-activity-to-hit-new-peak/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samuel Edyme]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 20:00:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SUI]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SUIUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=542980</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Sui blockchain platform is witnessing a surge of activity, mainly due to its new Web3 game, Sui 8192. Not only is this game boosting blockchain engagement, but it&#8217;s also contributing to the bullish run of Sui&#8217;s native token, SUI. SUI scan has shown Sui 8192 contributed to the transaction spike on the network. In the past 24 hours alone, the game has drawn 258 million transactions on the Sui blockchain. Developed by Ethos, a Sui wallet maker, the game is intended to spark interest in Web3. In the past 24 hours, the number of transactions on the Sui blockchain exceeded 29 million (transaction blocks), a record high. This growth was mainly driven by a casual game called Sui 8192 launched by Ethos Wallet, which is the first on-chain game on the Sui, and its gameplay… — Wu Blockchain (@WuBlockchain) July 17, 2023 New Era Of Web3 Gaming On Sui Blockchain? The mechanics of Sui 8192 includes Players accruing points by matching two similar tiles on a grid. When they amass 8192 points, the game ends, and a non-fungible token (NFT) is minted on the blockchain, a testimony to their achievement. Related Reading: Sui Foundation Refutes Claims Of Dumping Locked Staking Rewards On Binance This experience introduces more and more people to the world of blockchain and NFTs in an accessible way. However, Sui 8192 is not the only game in town; Sui also hosts other notable titles like the high fantasy action games Abyss World, Cosmocadia, and Orange Comet. Riding The Bullish Trend: SUI Token Climbs To New Heights Sui&#8217;s blockchain native token, SUI, is seeing an upward trajectory, with a 10.5% value gain in just a week, leaping from $0.63 on July 10 to a high of $0.72, a near 2% increase in the past 24 hours alone. Simultaneously, the trading volume of SUI has nearly doubled in the past week, escalating from $33 million to a towering $76 million in just 24 hours. SUI&#8217;s market capitalization is rising from $426 million to $461 million today. With the steady growth of Sui&#8217;s blockchain platform and the rising popularity of its gaming universe, the upward trend of SUI could be more than a temporary spike. Related Reading: ZachXBT Slapped With Defamation Lawsuit For MachiBigBrother Exposé Featured image from iStock, Chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w" dir="ltr">The Sui blockchain platform is witnessing a surge of activity, mainly due to its new Web3 game, Sui 8192. Not only is this game boosting blockchain engagement, but it&#8217;s also contributing to the bullish run of Sui&#8217;s native token, SUI.</p>
<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w" dir="ltr"><a href="https://suiscan.xyz/mainnet/analytics/transactions" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">SUI scan </a>has shown Sui 8192 contributed to the transaction spike on the network. In the past 24 hours alone, the game has drawn 258 million transactions on the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/altcoin/sui-foundation-refutes-claims-of-dumping-locked-staking-rewards-on-binance/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Sui blockchain</a>. </p>
<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w" dir="ltr">Developed by Ethos, a Sui wallet maker, the game is intended to spark interest in Web3.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">In the past 24 hours, the number of transactions on the Sui blockchain exceeded 29 million (transaction blocks), a record high. This growth was mainly driven by a casual game called Sui 8192 launched by Ethos Wallet, which is the first on-chain game on the Sui, and its gameplay…</p>
<p>— Wu Blockchain (@WuBlockchain) <a href="https://twitter.com/WuBlockchain/status/1680832107692822529?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">July 17, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<h2 dir="ltr">New Era Of Web3 Gaming On Sui Blockchain?</h2>
<p>The mechanics of Sui 8192 includes Players accruing points by matching two similar tiles on a grid. When they amass 8192 points, the game ends, and a non-fungible token (NFT) is minted on the blockchain, a testimony to their achievement.</p>

<p>This experience introduces more and more people to the world of blockchain and NFTs in an accessible way. However, Sui 8192 is not the only game in town; Sui also hosts other notable titles like the high fantasy action games Abyss World, Cosmocadia, and Orange Comet.</p>
<h2>Riding The Bullish Trend: SUI Token Climbs To New Heights</h2>
<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w" dir="ltr">Sui&#8217;s blockchain <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/ripple-set-to-hit-30-if-it-comes-out-victorious-in-sec-lawsuit-hedge-fund-manager-predicts/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">native token, SUI, </a>is seeing an upward trajectory, with a 10.5% value gain in just a week, leaping from $0.63 on July 10 to a high of $0.72, a near 2% increase in the past 24 hours alone.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/BobJ341G/" alt="SUI price chart on TradingView" width="2770" height="1556"/>
<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w" dir="ltr">Simultaneously, the trading volume of SUI has nearly <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/altcoin/sui-defies-bear-market-with-15-rally-is-a-return-to-1-imminent/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">doubled in the past week</a>, escalating from $33 million to a towering $76 million in just 24 hours.</p>
<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w" dir="ltr"><a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/altcoin/sui-price-plummets-by-38/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">SUI&#8217;s market capitalization</a> is rising from $426 million to $461 million today. With the steady growth of Sui&#8217;s blockchain platform and the rising popularity of its gaming universe, the upward trend of SUI could be more than a temporary spike.</p>

<p dir="ltr">Featured image from iStock, Chart from TradingView</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/HUOBI-460x230.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>29% Of Bitcoin’s Circulating Supply Is Now Presumed Lost Forever</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-presumed-lost-forever/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 19:00:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dormant BTC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=542992</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[According to recent findings from blockchain analytics company IntoTheBlock, around 29% of the total Bitcoin circulating supply is now presumed lost forever after remaining stagnant for over five years. Bitcoin was designed to be scarce, with only 21 million coins ever to be mined, but the very features that make the cryptocurrency so attractive to investors can sometimes lead to investors losing their assets forever, especially in cases where private keys are forgotten.  Related Reading: Why Ripple’s Victory Against The SEC May Be Short-Lived: Legal Expert Stagnant BTC Addresses Are Growing Over Time In a recent tweet by IntoTheBlock, the company called attention to the high number of dormant bitcoin addresses. &#8220;Our data shows that 29% of $BTC hasn&#8217;t moved in over 5 years. It&#8217;s possible that a large part of this concerns lost coins,&#8221; the tweet said.  BTC presumed lost crosses 7.7 million &#124; Source: Glassnode Similar data has been supplied by Glassnode Alerts, an on-chain metrics monitor. According to Glassnode, on-chain data shows that the total quantity of HODLed or lost bitcoins just hit a new all-time high of 7,781,224.168 BTC. Given that the price of a single Bitcoin is currently about $30,000, this equates to more than $235 billion in BTC that has now been lost.  What Does This Mean For Bitcoin? Institutional interest in Bitcoin has grown in the past year, with companies like MicroStrategy doubling down on their bitcoin holdings. Hence, the increase in dormant addresses can show more people are holding Bitcoin as a long-term investment rather than trading or spending it. However, it can also signal the amount of BTC lost forever, especially by early investors.  BTC price trending at $30,100 &#124; Source: BTCUSD on TradingView.com Taking into account that early investors are more likely to cash out on the huge gains made by the price of bitcoin, the latter is more likely. The price of Bitcoin has skyrocketed over the years and small amounts of Bitcoin from the early days are now worth a fortune. So if investors still had access to these dormant BTC, then they would likely have been moved already.  As Bitcoin gained mainstream popularity, many people have also bought in without fully understanding how to secure their private keys properly. A good example is the case of Stefan Thomas, a San Francisco-based programmer who is unable to asses his holdings of about 7,002 bitcoins. Thomas&#8217; holdings are currently worth $216 million, but he can&#8217;t remember the password containing the private keys to his digital wallet.  Related Reading: Ark Invest Sells Over $50 Million Worth of Coinbase Shares Amidst Stock Rally With bitcoin having a fixed supply, its increasing scarcity due to lost coins can also enhance its appeal as a store of value. This could drive the price up due to increasing demand for the fewer bitcoins in circulation.  Bitcoin has seen a surge in price in recent months fueled by spot ETF applications filed by major investment companies like BlackRock and Valkyrie. The cryptocurrency is up by 43% this year and is currently ranging around $30,000 for the past few weeks. Featured image from Futurism, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p style="font-weight: 400">According to recent findings from blockchain analytics company IntoTheBlock, around 29% of the total Bitcoin circulating supply is now presumed lost forever after remaining stagnant for over five years. </p>
<p style="font-weight: 400">Bitcoin was designed to be scarce, with only 21 million coins ever to be mined, but the very features that make the cryptocurrency so attractive to investors can sometimes lead to investors losing their assets forever, especially in cases where private keys are forgotten. </p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="Legal Expert" rel="nofollow">Why Ripple’s Victory Against The SEC May Be Short-Lived: Legal Expert</a></p>
<h2 style="font-weight: 400">Stagnant BTC Addresses Are Growing Over Time</h2>
<p style="font-weight: 400">In a recent <a href="https://twitter.com/intotheblock/status/1680834832601939968?s=20" rel="nofollow">tweet </a>by IntoTheBlock, the company called attention to the high number of dormant bitcoin addresses. &#8220;Our data shows that 29% of $BTC hasn&#8217;t moved in over 5 years. It&#8217;s possible that a large part of this concerns lost coins,&#8221; the tweet said. </p>


<p style="font-weight: 400">Similar <a href="https://twitter.com/glassnodealerts/status/1680823505976279041?s=20" rel="nofollow">data </a>has been supplied by Glassnode Alerts, an on-chain metrics monitor. According to Glassnode, on-chain data shows that the total quantity of HODLed or lost bitcoins just hit a new all-time high of 7,781,224.168 BTC. Given that the price of a single Bitcoin is currently about $30,000, this equates to more than $235 billion in BTC that has now been lost. </p>
<h2 style="font-weight: 400">What Does This Mean For Bitcoin?</h2>
<p style="font-weight: 400">Institutional interest in Bitcoin has grown in the past year, with companies like MicroStrategy doubling down on their bitcoin holdings. Hence, the increase in dormant addresses can show more people are holding Bitcoin as a long-term investment rather than trading or spending it. However, it can also signal the amount of BTC lost forever, especially by early investors. </p>
<p style="text-align: center"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/XcF1QvUE/" alt="Bitcoin (BTC) price chart from TradingView.com" width="2160" height="1686"/></p>

<p style="font-weight: 400">Taking into account that early investors are more likely to cash out on the huge gains made by the price of bitcoin, the latter is more likely. The price of Bitcoin has skyrocketed over the years and small amounts of Bitcoin from the early days are now worth a fortune. So if investors still had access to these dormant BTC, then they would likely have been moved already. </p>
<p style="font-weight: 400">As Bitcoin gained mainstream popularity, many people have also bought in without fully understanding how to secure their private keys properly. A good example is the case of Stefan Thomas, a San Francisco-based programmer who is unable to asses his holdings of about 7,002 bitcoins. Thomas&#8217; holdings are currently worth $216 million, but he can&#8217;t remember the password containing the private keys to his digital wallet. </p>

<p style="font-weight: 400">With bitcoin having a fixed supply, its increasing scarcity due to lost coins can also enhance its appeal as a store of value. This could drive the price up due to increasing demand for the fewer bitcoins in circulation. </p>
<p style="font-weight: 400">Bitcoin has seen a surge in price in recent months fueled by spot ETF applications filed by major investment companies like BlackRock and Valkyrie. The cryptocurrency is up by 43% this year and is currently ranging around $30,000 for the past few weeks.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/IMG_0018-460x265.jpeg" width="460" height="265" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>XRP Crosses 1 Million Trades Per Minute Following Court Ruling</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/xrp-crosses-1-million-trades/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 17:30:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrp]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP volume]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrpusdt]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=542979</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[In the wake of a favorable court ruling in the Ripple vs. SEC case, XRP has witnessed an extraordinary surge in demand and trading activity. With over 1 million trades per minute globally, XRP has become the center of attention for investors worldwide.  This unprecedented growth comes after a period of legal uncertainty and trading restrictions, positioning XRP for potential success in the cryptocurrency market. XRP&#8217;s Milestone: Over 1 Million Trades Per Minute Sparks Growth Visionary entrepreneur and self-proclaimed &#8220;Crypto Crusader,&#8221; known as Nick on Twitter,  swiftly recognized the unparalleled growth potential inherent in XRP. Related Reading: Why Ripple’s Victory Against The SEC May Be Short-Lived: Legal Expert Taking to social media, Nick expressed his awe at the surging demand for XRP, emphasizing its relentless upward trajectory in a tweet. With unwavering confidence, Nick firmly believes that this remarkable milestone is merely the inception of XRP&#8217;s extraordinary journey. Also, XRP experienced a significant surge in trading volume, reaching $10.4 billion on July 13. However, while this figure appears impressive, it is worth noting that it only ranks as the 76th largest volume in XRP&#8217;s history.  This observation highlights the immense potential that XRP possesses, suggesting that the recent surge in volume may be just the beginning. A tweet from Leonidas, the host of the popular crypto YouTube channel XRPArcade, underscores this point, stating, &#8220;On July 13th, XRP&#8217;s volume spiked to $10.4 billion. Even though this seems like a big number, historically, this was XRP&#8217;s 76th largest daily trading volume recorded on CoinMarketCap (CMC). The highest was almost $37 billion on April 6th, 2021.&#8221;  This historical context emphasizes that XRP has achieved even higher trading volumes in the past, indicating the potential for further growth.  XRP price sitting at $0.73 &#124; Source: XRPUSD on TradingView.com Daily Volume Surges 18-Fold Following Court Ruling And Exchange Relisting The court ruling that declared XRP as not a Security favored the altcoin as XRP witnessed a dramatic surge in trading volume, increasing from $613 million to $11.2 billion within a single day.  The ruling by the Southern District Court of New York has reignited investor interest in XRP, leading major exchange platforms such as Coinbase, Kraken, and Crypto.com to relist the asset.  The market responded with XRP&#8217;s value soaring by 85% from $0.47 to $0.87, with the token currently trading at $0.78 despite the market drawdown. Related Reading: Ark Invest Sells Over $50 Million Worth of Coinbase Shares Amidst Stock Rally Moreover, XRP&#8217;s market capitalization also experienced a substantial boost, reaching $40.8 billion within the past 24 hours. This surge propelled XRP to become the fourth largest cryptocurrency in terms of market capitalization, trailing only Bitcoin (BTC), Ether (ETH), and Tether USD (USDT).  The derivatives market also witnessed increased interest, with funding rates and open interest for XRP derivatives reaching the highest levels of the year, indicating growing confidence among traders. Featured image from Outlook India, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In the wake of a favorable court ruling in the Ripple vs. SEC case, XRP has witnessed an extraordinary surge in demand and trading activity. With over 1 million trades per minute globally, XRP has become the center of attention for investors worldwide. </p>
<p>This unprecedented growth comes after a period of legal uncertainty and trading restrictions, positioning XRP for potential success in the cryptocurrency market.</p>
<h2>XRP&#8217;s Milestone: Over 1 Million Trades Per Minute Sparks Growth</h2>
<p>Visionary entrepreneur and self-proclaimed &#8220;Crypto Crusader,&#8221; known as Nick on Twitter,  swiftly recognized the unparalleled growth potential inherent in XRP.</p>

<p>Taking to social media, Nick expressed his awe at the surging demand for XRP, emphasizing its relentless upward trajectory in a <a href="https://twitter.com/NCashOfficial/status/1680633846822236161?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw%7Ctwcamp%5Etweetembed%7Ctwterm%5E1680633846822236161%7Ctwgr%5Eb8abeb7f9c7535c558c4eff033e21dbf31f5dbb1%7Ctwcon%5Es1_c10&amp;ref_url=https%3A%2F%2Fthecryptobasic.com%2F2023%2F07%2F17%2Fxrp-demand-skyrockets-with-over-1-million-trades-per-minute-globally%2F" rel="nofollow">tweet</a>. With unwavering confidence, Nick firmly believes that this remarkable milestone is merely the inception of XRP&#8217;s extraordinary journey.</p>
<p>Also, XRP experienced a significant surge in trading volume, reaching $10.4 billion on July 13. However, while this figure appears impressive, it is worth noting that it only ranks as the 76th largest volume in XRP&#8217;s history. </p>
<p>This observation highlights the immense potential that XRP possesses, suggesting that the recent surge in volume may be just the beginning.</p>
<p>A <a href="https://twitter.com/LeoHadjiloizou/status/1680595490185023488?s=20" rel="nofollow">tweet</a> from Leonidas, the host of the popular crypto YouTube channel XRPArcade, underscores this point, stating, &#8220;On July 13th, XRP&#8217;s volume spiked to $10.4 billion. Even though this seems like a big number, historically, this was XRP&#8217;s 76th largest daily trading volume recorded on CoinMarketCap (CMC). The highest was almost $37 billion on April 6th, 2021.&#8221; </p>
<p>This historical context emphasizes that XRP has achieved even higher trading volumes in the past, indicating the potential for further growth. </p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/xOptrzwf/" alt="Ripple (XRP) price chart on TradingView.com" width="2884" height="1758"/></p>

<h2>Daily Volume Surges 18-Fold Following Court Ruling And Exchange Relisting</h2>
<p>The court ruling that declared XRP as not a Security favored the altcoin as XRP witnessed a dramatic surge in trading volume, increasing from $613 million to $11.2 billion within a single day. </p>
<p>The ruling by the Southern District Court of New York has reignited investor interest in XRP, leading major exchange platforms such as Coinbase, Kraken, and Crypto.com to <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/large-exchanges-relist-xrp/?swcfpc=1">relist the asset</a>. </p>
<p>The market responded with XRP&#8217;s value soaring by 85% from $0.47 to $0.87, with the token currently trading at $0.78 despite the market drawdown.</p>

<p>Moreover, XRP&#8217;s market capitalization also experienced a substantial boost, reaching $40.8 billion within the past 24 hours. This surge propelled XRP to become the fourth largest cryptocurrency in terms of market capitalization, trailing only Bitcoin (BTC), Ether (ETH), and Tether USD (USDT). </p>
<p>The derivatives market also witnessed increased interest, with funding rates and open interest for XRP derivatives reaching the highest levels of the year, indicating growing confidence among traders.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRP-460x259.jpeg" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>zkSync Unveils Boojum Upgrade: The Ultimate Solution For Scalability And Security?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/blockchain/zksync-unveils-boojum-upgrade-the-ultimate-solution-for-scalability-and-security/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 16:30:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blockchain technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DeFi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[zkSync]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=542973</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[zkSync, a blockchain network that aims to make digital self-ownership universally accessible, has announced a major cryptographic upgrade to its proof system.  The upgrade involves transitioning to a new STARK-based proof system called Boojum, which, according to the announcement, offers world-class proving performance and reduces hardware requirements for decentralization. zkSync Era Moves To Boojum Boojum is a Rust-based arithmetization and constraint library that implements the upgraded version of the ZK circuits for zkSync Era and the ZK Stack. The library offers several compelling properties, including PLONK-style arithmetization. PLONK-style arithmetization refers to the use of PLONK (Permutation-based Linear-based SNARKs for transparent, universal, and upgradable proofs) as the underlying zero-knowledge proof system.  PLONK is a relatively new proof system that provides several advantages over previous systems, such as Sonic and Halo. Specifically, PLONK is designed to be more transparent, universal, and upgradeable, making it a good choice for zkSync&#8217;s upgraded proof system. Related Reading: Celsius Is Selling, More Pain For BNB, LINK, And SNX? According to the announcement, the move to a STARK-based proof system represents a dramatic performance improvement and will help ensure low latency for finality and support for increased levels of activity on zkSync Era and other ZK Stack-based systems.  The GPU provers used for Boojum require just 16 GB (GygaByte) of RAM, a significant reduction from the hundreds of GBs of RAM needed by prevalent proof systems.  By reducing the amount of RAM required to run the GPU provers from hundreds of GBs to just 16 GB, zkSync will be able to use cheaper machines for increased horizontal scalability. This will likely have a positive impact on the cost of using zkSync. This means that more people will be able to participate in the network and contribute to its decentralization, ultimately leading to a healthier and more robust network. Furthermore, to ensure a smooth transition, zkSync is running the new proof system alongside the existing one in a testing phase called mainnet shadow mode.  The network is generating and verifying &#8220;shadow proofs&#8221; for Mainnet blocks to further test and optimize the system with real production data from zkSync Era&#8217;s user activity. This testing is being done off-chain to find edge cases and bugs, and to continue reviewing the implementation. zkSync is also open-sourcing the Boojum codebase to allow anyone to use the new proofs and verify them using a command-line interface (CLI) tool.  Related Reading: Polkadot (DOT) Price Momentum Builds As Open Interest Climbs – Details The network is confident that Boojum and its commitment to innovation and user-first design are the next steps forward for a more secure, scalable, and efficient zkEVM. However, according to the announcement, the migration to the new proof system will only happen after further audits and security reviews are completed. Overall, the move to Boojum is a significant step towards a future of user-powered, decentralized proof generation. The increased performance and reduced hardware requirements will help zkSync and other ZK Stack-based systems achieve greater scalability and accessibility, making digital self-ownership more accessible to everyone. Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com ]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>zkSync, a blockchain network that aims to make digital self-ownership universally accessible, has <a href="https://zksync.mirror.xyz/HJ2Pj45EJkRdt5Pau-ZXwkV2ctPx8qFL19STM5jdYhc" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">announced </a>a major cryptographic upgrade to its proof system. </p>
<p>The upgrade involves transitioning to a new STARK-based proof system called Boojum, which, according to the announcement, offers world-class proving performance and reduces hardware requirements for decentralization.</p>
<h2>zkSync Era Moves To Boojum</h2>
<p>Boojum is a Rust-based arithmetization and constraint library that implements the upgraded version of the ZK circuits for zkSync Era and the ZK Stack. The library offers several compelling properties, including PLONK-style arithmetization.</p>
<p>PLONK-style arithmetization refers to the use of PLONK (Permutation-based Linear-based SNARKs for transparent, universal, and upgradable proofs) as the underlying zero-knowledge proof system. </p>
<p>PLONK is a relatively new proof system that provides several advantages over previous systems, such as Sonic and Halo. Specifically, PLONK is designed to be more transparent, universal, and upgradeable, making it a good choice for zkSync&#8217;s upgraded proof system.</p>

<p>According to the announcement, the move to a STARK-based proof system represents a dramatic performance improvement and will help ensure low latency for finality and support for increased levels of activity on zkSync Era and other ZK Stack-based systems. </p>
<p>The GPU provers used for Boojum require just 16 GB (GygaByte) of RAM, a significant reduction from the hundreds of GBs of RAM needed by prevalent proof systems. </p>
<p>By reducing the amount of RAM required to run the GPU provers from hundreds of GBs to just 16 GB, zkSync will be able to use cheaper machines for increased horizontal scalability. This will likely have a positive impact on the cost of using zkSync.</p>
<p>This means that more people will be able to participate in the network and contribute to its decentralization, ultimately leading to a healthier and more robust network.</p>
<p>Furthermore, to ensure a smooth transition, zkSync is running the new proof system alongside the existing one in a testing phase called mainnet shadow mode. </p>
<p>The network is generating and verifying &#8220;shadow proofs&#8221; for Mainnet blocks to further test and optimize the system with real production data from zkSync Era&#8217;s user activity. This testing is being done off-chain to find edge cases and bugs, and to continue reviewing the implementation.</p>
<p>zkSync is also open-sourcing the Boojum codebase to allow anyone to use the new proofs and verify them using a command-line interface (CLI) tool. </p>

<p>The network is confident that Boojum and its commitment to innovation and user-first design are the next steps forward for a more secure, scalable, and efficient zkEVM. </p>
<p>However, according to the announcement, the migration to the new proof system will only happen after further audits and security reviews are completed.</p>
<p>Overall, the move to Boojum is a significant step towards a future of user-powered, decentralized proof generation. The increased performance and reduced hardware requirements will help zkSync and other ZK Stack-based systems achieve greater scalability and accessibility, making digital self-ownership more accessible to everyone.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/8QtCNAZV/" alt="zkSync" width="1814" height="858"/>
<p>Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/hitesh-choudhary-JNxTZzpHmsI-unsplash-460x259.jpg" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Miners Selling Again, Will Price Crash Again?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-miners-selling-again-will-price-crash-again/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hououin Kyouma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 15:30:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin bearish]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Miner Selling]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin miners]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=542955</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[On-chain data shows that Bitcoin miners may have once again been participating in selling recently, something that could lead to the asset declining. Bitcoin Miner Reserve Has Been Declining In The Last Two Weeks As pointed out by an analyst in a CryptoQuant post, the BTC miner reserve has been observing outflows recently. The &#8220;miner reserve&#8221; here refers to the total amount of Bitcoin that the miners as a whole are holding in their wallets right now. When the value of this metric goes up, it means that these chain validators are transferring coins into their addresses currently. This kind of trend can be a sign that the miners are accumulating, and hence, can be bullish for the price of the asset. On the other hand, the indicator trending down suggests the miners are taking BTC out of their wallets at the moment. Generally, these investors withdraw coins from their reserve for selling-related purposes, so such a trend can have bearish consequences for the cryptocurrency&#8217;s value. In the context of the current discussion, the miner reserve itself isn&#8217;t of interest, but rather its &#8220;rate of change&#8221; (ROC) is. This metric keeps track of the percentage changes in the miner reserve over a specific period. Here, the relevant period is the 14-day one. Related Reading: Bitcoin MVRV At Critical Level: Will A Break Happen? Now, below is a chart that shows the trend in the 14-day ROC of the Bitcoin miner reserves over the last few months: Looks like the value of the metric seems to have been negative in recent days &#124; Source: CryptoQuant As shown in the above graph, the 14-day ROC of the miner reserve had been green last month as Bitcoin had rallied above the $30,000 level. These positive values of the indicator imply that the miner reserve had been rapidly going up. The timing of these positive ROC values could suggest that the accumulation from the miners might have provided support for the surge in the cryptocurrency&#8217;s price. Related Reading: Stablecoin Exchange Deposits Remain Low, What Does It Mean For Bitcoin? In the first week of this month, though, the metric turned negative, implying that the miner reserve started to decline. The miners look to have continued to withdraw coins from their wallets since then, as the indicator&#8217;s value has remained red. The Bitcoin price has been struggling in this period, as it hasn&#8217;t been able to mount up any significant moves. It would appear that this selling from the miners (if the withdrawals are indeed happening for selling) might be one of the factors behind the asset stalling in the past couple of weeks. Since the 14-day ROC of the miner reserve has continued to be at notable red values recently, it&#8217;s possible that these chain validators aren&#8217;t letting up their selling just yet. So far, the price has continued to hold on above the $30,000 level, implying that there may be enough demand in the market to absorb any selling from the miners for now. However, if the miners continue to sell into the near future, it&#8217;s possible the asset may buckle and the price could face a drawdown. BTC Price At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading around $30,000, down 1% in the last week. BTC has been moving sideways recently &#124; Source: BTCUSD on TradingView Featured image from Kanchanara on Unsplash.com, charts from TradingView.com, CryptoQuant.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On-chain data shows that Bitcoin miners may have once again been participating in selling recently, something that could lead to the asset declining.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Miner Reserve Has Been Declining In The Last Two Weeks</h2>
<p>As pointed out by an analyst in a CryptoQuant <a href="https://cryptoquant.com/insights/quicktake/64b522b041768f4ed3151978-Bitcoin-is-under-pressure-from-miners-again" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">post</a>, the BTC miner reserve has been observing outflows recently. The &#8220;<a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-miner-reserve-plunges-bearish-price/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">miner reserve</a>&#8221; here refers to the total amount of Bitcoin that the miners as a whole are holding in their wallets right now.</p>
<p>When the value of this metric goes up, it means that these chain validators are transferring coins into their addresses currently. This kind of trend can be a sign that the miners are accumulating, and hence, can be bullish for the price of the asset.</p>
<p>On the other hand, the indicator trending down suggests the miners are taking BTC out of their wallets at the moment. Generally, these investors withdraw coins from their reserve for selling-related purposes, so such a trend can have bearish consequences for the cryptocurrency&#8217;s value.</p>
<p>In the context of the current discussion, the miner reserve itself isn&#8217;t of interest, but rather its &#8220;rate of change&#8221; (ROC) is. This metric keeps track of the percentage changes in the miner reserve over a specific period. Here, the relevant period is the 14-day one.</p>

<p>Now, below is a chart that shows the trend in the 14-day ROC of the Bitcoin miner reserves over the last few months:</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone aligncenter" src="https://img.cryptoquant.com/35304/quicktake/smjvSB0_4efb40142bc6206cb55ba68e973cbd24b17b4ed0819ff240e22350e3083b56e5.png" alt="Bitcoin miner reserve ROC" width="1192" height="505"/></p>

<p>As shown in the above graph, the 14-day ROC of the miner reserve had been green last month as Bitcoin had rallied above the $30,000 level. These positive values of the indicator imply that the miner reserve had been rapidly going up.</p>
<p>The timing of these positive ROC values could suggest that the accumulation from the miners might have provided support for the surge in the cryptocurrency&#8217;s price.</p>

<p>In the first week of this month, though, the metric turned negative, implying that the miner reserve started to decline. The miners look to have continued to withdraw coins from their wallets since then, as the indicator&#8217;s value has remained red.</p>
<p>The Bitcoin price has been <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/big-bitcoin-move-ahead-bollinger-bands-see-extreme-squeeze/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">struggling</a> in this period, as it hasn&#8217;t been able to mount up any significant moves. It would appear that this selling from the miners (if the withdrawals are indeed happening for selling) might be one of the factors behind the asset stalling in the past couple of weeks.</p>
<p>Since the 14-day ROC of the miner reserve has continued to be at notable red values recently, it&#8217;s possible that these chain validators aren&#8217;t letting up their selling just yet.</p>
<p>So far, the price has continued to hold on above the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/520000-bitcoin-accumulated-at-30000-btc-bull-run/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">$30,000 level</a>, implying that there may be enough demand in the market to absorb any selling from the miners for now. However, if the miners continue to sell into the near future, it&#8217;s possible the asset may buckle and the price could face a drawdown.</p>
<h2>BTC Price</h2>
<p>At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading around $30,000, down 1% in the last week.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium aligncenter" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/ipieXj6U/" alt="Bitcoin Price Chart" width="1534" height="877"/></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/iStock-906872048-460x319.jpg" width="460" height="319" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Stablecoin Exchange Deposits Remain Low, What Does It Mean For Bitcoin?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/stablecoin/stablecoin-exchange-deposits-remain-low-mean-bitcoin/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hououin Kyouma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 14:30:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Stablecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[stablecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stablecoin Exchange Deposits]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stablecoin Exchange Withdrawals]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=542899</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[On-chain data shows the stablecoin exchange deposits have remained low recently. Here&#8217;s what this may mean for Bitcoin. Stablecoin Exchange Deposits Stay Low, While Withdrawals Jump As pointed out by an analyst in a CryptoQuant post, the fact that the stablecoin exchange withdrawals have spiked while deposits have stayed low may be slightly alarming for BTC. There are two indicators of relevance here: the &#8220;stablecoin exchange withdrawing transactions&#8221; and the &#8220;stablecoin exchange depositing transactions.&#8221; As their names already imply, these metrics track the total number of withdrawals and deposit transfers, respectively, that investors of the ERC-20 stables are making right now. Generally, investors seek the safety of these fiat-tied tokens whenever they want to escape the volatility associated with the other assets in the sector. Eventually, when these holders think that the prices are right to jump back into the volatile markets, they swap their stables back for their desired cryptocurrency. These investors usually make use of centralized exchanges for this purpose. So, when the exchange withdrawing transactions are high, it can be a sign that holders are exchanging coins like Bitcoin for stablecoins right now. Related Reading: Here’s What On-Chain Data Reveals About XRP Rally On the other hand, the deposits being high can imply these investors are looking to buy volatile assets using their stables. Naturally, in the former case, Bitcoin and others may feel a bearish effect from the selling, while in the latter case, the prices might see a bullish boost. Now, here is a chart that shows the trend in the stablecoin exchange withdrawing and depositing transactions over the past couple of years: Looks like only one of these two metrics has had a high value recently &#124; Source: CryptoQuant As displayed in the above graph, the stablecoin exchange depositing transactions metric has been relatively low for a while now. This would suggest that there may not be enough demand for converting stables into other assets right now. From the graph, it&#8217;s visible that the last time the indicator spiked was back in March of this year. Following the deposits back then, Bitcoin observed a sharp rebound in its price as the rally saw a revival. The timing of these inflows might mean that it was the buying from these stablecoin holders that had provided the fuel for the BTC surge. Related Reading: Bitcoin MVRV At Critical Level: Will A Break Happen? In the graph, the quant has marked other similar past instances as well. It looks like the BTC price generally observes a rise after stablecoin deposits spike, given that the withdrawals are low at the same time. Recently, however, only the stablecoin withdrawals have observed a spike, implying that investors are taking these tokens away from exchanges, likely to hold onto them for extended periods in self-custody. As there aren&#8217;t any deposits happening to counteract this, the BTC price has been struggling recently. If the trend continues and more stablecoin withdrawals continue to take place, it&#8217;s possible that the cryptocurrency could take a hit in the short term. Bitcoin Price At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading around $30,200, up 1% in the last week. BTC has taken a hit recently &#124; Source: BTCUSD on TradingView Featured image from iStock.com, charts from TradingView.com, CryptoQuant.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On-chain data shows the stablecoin exchange deposits have remained low recently. Here&#8217;s what this may mean for Bitcoin.</p>
<h2>Stablecoin Exchange Deposits Stay Low, While Withdrawals Jump</h2>
<p>As pointed out by an analyst in a CryptoQuant <a href="https://cryptoquant.com/insights/quicktake/64b48531d3b74754036d682e-Retail-Demand-Weakening" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">post</a>, the fact that the stablecoin exchange withdrawals have spiked while deposits have stayed low may be slightly alarming for BTC.</p>
<p>There are two indicators of relevance here: the &#8220;stablecoin exchange withdrawing transactions&#8221; and the &#8220;stablecoin exchange depositing transactions.&#8221; As their names already imply, these metrics track the total number of withdrawals and deposit transfers, respectively, that investors of the ERC-20 stables are making right now.</p>
<p>Generally, investors seek the safety of these <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/stablecoin/stablecoins-market-cap-shows-rise-why-bullish-bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">fiat-tied tokens</a> whenever they want to escape the volatility associated with the other assets in the sector. Eventually, when these holders think that the prices are right to jump back into the volatile markets, they swap their stables back for their desired cryptocurrency.</p>
<p>These investors usually make use of centralized exchanges for this purpose. So, when the exchange withdrawing transactions are high, it can be a sign that holders are exchanging coins like Bitcoin for stablecoins right now.</p>

<p>On the other hand, the deposits being high can imply these investors are looking to buy volatile assets using their stables. Naturally, in the former case, Bitcoin and others may feel a bearish effect from the selling, while in the latter case, the prices might see a <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/exchanges-large-stablecoin-inflows-what-bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">bullish boost</a>.</p>
<p>Now, here is a chart that shows the trend in the stablecoin exchange withdrawing and depositing transactions over the past couple of years:</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone aligncenter" src="https://img.cryptoquant.com/148277/quicktake/QNL53ERXk_3be09f44191d25a3cc63140518c3bd97943329e7792b60a59df90872cbddb6a8.png" alt="Stablecoin Deposits And Bitcoin" width="1280" height="527"/></p>

<p>As displayed in the above graph, the stablecoin exchange depositing transactions metric has been relatively low for a while now. This would suggest that there may not be enough demand for converting stables into other assets right now.</p>
<p>From the graph, it&#8217;s visible that the last time the indicator spiked was back in March of this year. Following the deposits back then, Bitcoin observed a sharp rebound in its price as the rally saw a revival. The timing of these inflows might mean that it was the buying from these stablecoin holders that had provided the fuel for the BTC surge.</p>

<p>In the graph, the quant has marked other similar past instances as well. It looks like the BTC price generally observes a rise after stablecoin deposits spike, given that the withdrawals are low at the same time.</p>
<p>Recently, however, only the stablecoin withdrawals have observed a spike, implying that investors are taking these tokens away from exchanges, likely to hold onto them for extended periods in self-custody.</p>
<p>As there aren&#8217;t any deposits happening to counteract this, the BTC price has been <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-stuck-tight-range-btc-decompress-big-move/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">struggling</a> recently. If the trend continues and more stablecoin withdrawals continue to take place, it&#8217;s possible that the cryptocurrency could take a hit in the short term.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Price</h2>
<p>At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading around $30,200, up 1% in the last week.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium aligncenter" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/pbJn5tNc/" alt="Bitcoin Price Chart" width="1534" height="877"/></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/iStock-1359416693-460x259.jpg" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Celsius Is Selling, More Pain For BNB, LINK, And SNX?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/celsius-is-selling-more-pain-for-bnb-link-and-snx/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dalmas Ngetich]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 13:30:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BNB]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BONE]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[celsius]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FalconX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[OKX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ZRX]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=542947</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Celsius, the bankrupt crypto lender, has started selling its non-Bitcoin and non-Ethereum crypto assets, records on July 17 indicate. According to on-chain data from Lookonchain, Celsius has transferred approximately $23.5 million of various cryptocurrencies, including BNB, ZRX, LINK, BONE, and SNX, to FalconX and OKX, respectively. Different amounts of these tokens were transferred by Celsius, a move that, while it could be positive for creditors, may impact the token valuations of those projects. Celsius Selling Altcoins  Lookonchain revealed that Celsius moved $8.5 million worth of LINK, the native currency of Chainlink, a middleware protocol linking on-chain smart contracts to external but verified data. At the same time, it also moved $7.84 million worth of SNX, the native token of Synthetix, a protocol allowing users to trade derivatives called synths, was transferred. Celsius also went on to move $3 million worth of BNB, the coin behind the sprawling Binance ecosystem, $2.26 million worth of 1INCH, the token aggregator, and $1.9 million worth of ZRX, the token behind one of the first decentralized finance platforms, Ox Protocol. The bankrupt lender also moved $709,678 worth of FTT, the token behind the collapsed FTX exchange, to FalconX. In response, FalconX has started depositing these tokens to Binance for selling. Related Reading: $18 Billion Worth Of Bitcoin Accumulated At $30,200 – BTC Bull Run Incoming? The only token moved to a different exchange was BONE, where Celsius moved $235,000 of the meme token to the popular cryptocurrency exchange, OKX. While OKX caters to retail and institutional investors, FalconX serves institutional investors, offering diverse services, including liquidity provision and risk management. So far, a large tranche of tokens held by Celsius has moved through FalconX. In late June, Judge Martin Glenn of the Southern District of New York allowed Celsius to start converting all their tokens to either Bitcoin or Ethereum, the two currencies that would be allowed to pay back creditors. All conversions were set to begin on July 1. Altcoins Taking A Hit The transfer also comes amid a favorable ruling that saw a US Judge say XRP, one of the major altcoins, is not a security and can be traded like a commodity, just like Bitcoin. However, even though news pumped altcoins, mostly XRP, momentum tapered during the weekend, and most altcoins fell back from last week&#8217;s highs. Related Reading: XRP Whales Ride The Crypto Surge, As Ripple Token Notches 62% Price Spike Among the impacted tokens included BNB, the native currency behind Binance, the world&#8217;s largest ecosystem. The coin currently oscillates within a $30 range as bears dominate price action. From the daily chart, BNB has resistance at $260 and is down over 30% from April 2023 highs.  LINK and SNX are seeing similar price actions, both recording losses on the 24-hour chart. LINK is down 2.97% to be trading at $6.63, while SNX is nursing 3.94% losses, bringing its price to $2.64. Feature image from Canva, chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Celsius, the bankrupt crypto lender, has started selling its non-Bitcoin and non-Ethereum crypto assets, records on July 17 indicate. According to on-chain data from Lookonchain, Celsius has transferred approximately $23.5 million of various cryptocurrencies, including BNB, ZRX, LINK, BONE, and SNX, to FalconX and OKX, respectively. </p>
<p>Different amounts of these tokens were transferred by Celsius, a move that, while it could be positive for creditors, may impact the token valuations of those projects.</p>
<h2>Celsius Selling Altcoins </h2>
<p>Lookonchain <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://twitter.com/lookonchain/status/1680790940842340357?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">revealed</a> that Celsius moved $8.5 million worth of LINK, the native currency of Chainlink, a middleware protocol linking on-chain smart contracts to external but verified data. At the same time, it also moved $7.84 million worth of SNX, the native token of Synthetix, a protocol allowing users to trade derivatives called synths, was transferred. </p>
<p>Celsius also went on to move $3 million worth of BNB, the coin behind the sprawling Binance ecosystem, $2.26 million worth of 1INCH, the token aggregator, and $1.9 million worth of ZRX, the token behind one of the first decentralized finance platforms, Ox Protocol. </p>
<p>The bankrupt lender also moved $709,678 worth of FTT, the token behind the collapsed FTX exchange, to FalconX. In response, FalconX has <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://twitter.com/lookonchain/status/1680793493701292033" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">started</a> depositing these tokens to Binance for selling.</p>

<p>The only token moved to a different exchange was BONE, where Celsius moved $235,000 of the meme token to the popular cryptocurrency exchange, OKX. </p>
<p>While OKX caters to retail and institutional investors, FalconX serves institutional investors, offering diverse services, including liquidity provision and risk management. So far, a large tranche of tokens held by Celsius has moved through FalconX.</p>
<p>In late June, Judge Martin Glenn of the Southern District of New York <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cases.stretto.com/public/x191/11749/PLEADINGS/1174906302380000000027.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">allowed</a> Celsius to start converting all their tokens to either Bitcoin or Ethereum, the two currencies that would be allowed to pay back creditors. All conversions were set to begin on July 1.</p>
<h2>Altcoins Taking A Hit</h2>
<p>The transfer also comes amid a favorable ruling that saw a US Judge say XRP, one of the major altcoins, is not a security and can be traded like a commodity, just like Bitcoin. However, even though news pumped altcoins, mostly XRP, momentum tapered during the weekend, and most altcoins fell back from last week&#8217;s highs.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/xrp-whales-ride-the-crypto-surge-as-ripple-token-notches-62-price-spike/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">XRP Whales Ride The Crypto Surge, As Ripple Token Notches 62% Price Spike</a></p>
<p>Among the impacted tokens included BNB, the native currency behind Binance, the world&#8217;s largest ecosystem. The coin currently oscillates within a $30 range as bears dominate price action. From the daily chart, BNB has resistance at $260 and is down over 30% from April 2023 highs. </p>
<p>LINK and SNX are seeing similar price actions, both recording losses on the 24-hour chart. LINK is down 2.97% to be trading at $6.63, while SNX is nursing 3.94% losses, bringing its price to $2.64.</p>
<a href="https://www.tradingview.com/x/DdcSOCjJ/" rel="nofollow"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/DdcSOCjJ/" alt="BNB price on July 17| Source: BNBUSDT on Binance, TradingView" width="1226" height="595"/></a>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Celsius-BNB-Bitcoin-Ethereum-460x260.jpg" width="460" height="260" />	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
