<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0" xmlns:cc="http://cyber.law.harvard.edu/rss/creativeCommonsRssModule.html">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Stories by OjirehPrime on Medium]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Stories by OjirehPrime on Medium]]></description>
        <link>https://medium.com/@ojirehprime?source=rss-e4ead21b461f------2</link>
        <image>
            <url>https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/fit/c/150/150/1*5Dti-D1e9-0UtF3YdSwxdA.png</url>
            <title>Stories by OjirehPrime on Medium</title>
            <link>https://medium.com/@ojirehprime?source=rss-e4ead21b461f------2</link>
        </image>
        <generator>Medium</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2022 02:15:59 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://medium.com/@ojirehprime/feed" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <webMaster><![CDATA[yourfriends@medium.com]]></webMaster>
        <atom:link href="http://medium.superfeedr.com" rel="hub"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[OjirehPrime raised $1,240,000 backed by Ex-Interswitch Board Chairman]]></title>
            <link>https://ojirehprime.medium.com/ojirehprime-raised-1-240-000-backed-by-ex-interswitch-board-chairman-7ab11704ee41?source=rss-e4ead21b461f------2</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://medium.com/p/7ab11704ee41</guid>
            <category><![CDATA[angel-investors]]></category>
            <category><![CDATA[fintech-startups]]></category>
            <category><![CDATA[fintech]]></category>
            <category><![CDATA[venture-capital]]></category>
            <category><![CDATA[preseed]]></category>
            <dc:creator><![CDATA[OjirehPrime]]></dc:creator>
            <pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2022 14:39:35 GMT</pubDate>
            <atom:updated>2022-11-08T14:39:35.685Z</atom:updated>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<figure><img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/1024/1*NLpGy3aunMSd9_5z1zllHg.png" /></figure><p>I am super excited to inform you that we have just closed our pre-seed round and raised $1,240,000 in funding from some of the finest investors any startup could ask for. This round was led by former Interswitch Board Chairman Adedotun Sulaiman, with participation from former Heritage Bank Director Mrs. Mary Akpobome, as well as UK-based accelerator CPRES203 and a number of angel investors.</p><p>It’s been a long and exciting journey for us at OjirehPrime, bootstrapping every milestone from operating as a prepaid card focused fintech, organically scaling to 40,000 users of our prepaid card, acquiring a microfinance bank, launching our mobile app, scaling to 450,000 users, and now closing our pre-seed funding.</p><p>The journey itself taught me the value of tenacity, as the old adage goes, “where there is a will, there is a way.” This opens us up to a whole new phase as we would be able to attract more talents, drive increased marketing, create better experience and better position the brand for scale. Thank you to everyone who has helped make this possible. Thank you to our customers who believed in us despite our bumpy start.</p><p>For us, we’re just getting started.</p><p>With thanks</p><p>Edoka Idoko</p><p>For: OjirehPrime</p><img src="https://medium.com/_/stat?event=post.clientViewed&referrerSource=full_rss&postId=7ab11704ee41" width="1" height="1" alt="">]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[OjirehPrime app and Android app hibernation coming Feature]]></title>
            <link>https://ojirehprime.medium.com/ojirehprime-app-and-android-app-hibernation-coming-feature-a7592c2222a4?source=rss-e4ead21b461f------2</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://medium.com/p/a7592c2222a4</guid>
            <dc:creator><![CDATA[OjirehPrime]]></dc:creator>
            <pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2022 07:38:03 GMT</pubDate>
            <atom:updated>2022-10-08T07:40:00.617Z</atom:updated>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<figure><img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/1024/1*18BIKCpyZJI3Eo34sIv_lA.png" /></figure><p>Soon, a feature of Android’s operating system (OS) will go live that could interfere with important notifications from apps you only sometimes use. It’s important that we provide information about this impending upgrade because our app is presently available to users of Android phones, ensuring that you don’t miss any important notifications</p><h3>What is the update about and how it affects OjirehPrime?</h3><p>Android OS will roll out a feature starting in November 2022 that will stop any apps you don’t use frequently by deleting temporary files and turning off any notifications for apps you haven’t used in the last 90 days. App hibernation is a feature that is available on devices running OS 12 or higher.</p><p>Imagine missing an important notification from us on a product you enjoy, like Boxes, Spaces, or even a special offer. By using your app more frequently for transactions, you can help us by stopping our app from going into hibernation after 90 days, which will prevent us from sharing important updates about your accounts or regulatory information through push notifications.</p><h3>How to disable this feature</h3><p>The steps below should work on most Android devices:</p><ol><li>Open Settings on your device (the cog icon)</li><li>Go to “Apps”</li><li>Tap “See all apps”</li><li>Find the Atom bank app in the list</li><li>Disable either “Pause app activity if unused” (Android 13) or “Remove permissions and free up space” (Android 12)</li></ol><p>This will disable Android’s app hibernation feature, allowing you to continue using the OjirehPrime app at your own pace without missing any notifications. Some manufacturers (such as Samsung or Xiaomi) manage your options in a unique way. Please refer to the manufacturer’s instructions for your specific device.</p><img src="https://medium.com/_/stat?event=post.clientViewed&referrerSource=full_rss&postId=a7592c2222a4" width="1" height="1" alt="">]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How to survive the 21st century as a gen z]]></title>
            <link>https://ojirehprime.medium.com/how-to-survive-the-21st-century-as-a-gen-z-8ac090b5307f?source=rss-e4ead21b461f------2</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://medium.com/p/8ac090b5307f</guid>
            <category><![CDATA[knowledge]]></category>
            <category><![CDATA[banking]]></category>
            <category><![CDATA[fintech]]></category>
            <category><![CDATA[savings-tips]]></category>
            <category><![CDATA[saving]]></category>
            <dc:creator><![CDATA[OjirehPrime]]></dc:creator>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 23:32:47 GMT</pubDate>
            <atom:updated>2022-06-30T23:32:47.458Z</atom:updated>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<figure><img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/1024/1*BG-j8gUlqizHP9NJxc3PTA.png" /></figure><p>The way each generation pays for goods and services around the world is changing. However, one generation in particular shines out. People born between the late 1990s and the early 2010s are referred to as “generation Z.” In comparison to previous generations, they have developed a variety of habits and behaviors ranging from payment preferences, financial attitudes, and spending habits to educational techniques.</p><p>Three simple ways to survive being a gen-z</p><ul><li>Education</li><li>Value</li><li>Transferable skills</li></ul><p>Education gives people a sense of security and empowerment. Generation z’s are climbing a longer academic ladder, and with so many options for free or paid schooling, <a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.ojirehprime.mobile.android">OjirehPrime</a> has developed a secure payment way to assist you in accomplishing these goals. Remember that greater information equals more riches.</p><p>Values provide us a feeling of direction and a distinct sense of identity that we develop through our own actions and decisions. As the most innovative and resourceful generation in history, Generation Z must be mindful of their experimental phase and spending habits if financial stability is the end goal. With Boxes, by <a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.ojirehprime.mobile.android">OjirehPrime</a>, your saving goals can be achieved ranging from saving for that new investment, property, emergency fund, vacation, and so on, and these sustainable values can be shared with family and friends, and we also create a mutual funding element for your loved ones to achieve their goals.</p><p>Transferable skills are intrinsic abilities that can be applied to a new profession or work setting. The pandemic has altered the workplace in numerous ways, some of which are likely to be permanent. Transferable skills can help you find a new job, no matter how “unmatched” your skill set appears to be, whether you’re looking for a new job because you have to or because you’ve decided it’s time for a career move. Communication, analytical reasoning, teamwork, business acumen, and management are examples of such abilities.</p><p>With these three elements, the twenty-first century becomes less of a survival struggle and more of an impactful process, and the future, while unknown, becomes much more manageable. Until next time, <a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.ojirehprime.mobile.android">Ojirehprime</a> finance nuggets.</p><img src="https://medium.com/_/stat?event=post.clientViewed&referrerSource=full_rss&postId=8ac090b5307f" width="1" height="1" alt="">]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The future is BOXES]]></title>
            <link>https://ojirehprime.medium.com/the-future-is-boxes-4c6ec7e7b47e?source=rss-e4ead21b461f------2</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://medium.com/p/4c6ec7e7b47e</guid>
            <category><![CDATA[digital-marketing]]></category>
            <category><![CDATA[savings-tips]]></category>
            <category><![CDATA[fintech]]></category>
            <category><![CDATA[banking]]></category>
            <category><![CDATA[digital]]></category>
            <dc:creator><![CDATA[OjirehPrime]]></dc:creator>
            <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 10:07:01 GMT</pubDate>
            <atom:updated>2022-06-06T10:21:10.839Z</atom:updated>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<figure><img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/600/1*QyBnjXO-89nzwaaUVqvKEQ.png" /></figure><p>We challenged you to share your kolo story as part of our ongoing savings challenge, and the responses have been both stunning and hilarious. Some of you shared your experience of how money mysteriously disappeared from your kolo and others also talked about how charges deplete their savings with traditional banks. This is a case of being trapped between the devil and the deep blue sea.</p><p>To some of us, saving isn’t an easy journey. A follower shared his first experience saving with kolo and explained how regularly he would use a piece of a broomstick to pick out money, hilarious right? But a lot of us are guilty of the same attitude and lack of financial commitment especially when they aren’t any fundamental return on investment or accountability. But in recent times with have seen traditional banks use the “broomstick” method and we have all been victims of this. At <a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.ojirehprime.mobile.android&amp;hl=en">OjirehPrime</a> we have cracked the code to give you a Kolo with zero disappearing act and broomstick method.</p><figure><img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/1024/1*kMLGxWDOx5VRro0jQ2GbKg.jpeg" /></figure><p>Here are 5 ways Boxes is building a future for your finance</p><ol><li><a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.ojirehprime.mobile.android&amp;hl=en">Flexible and fixed box</a>: you get to decide how long you invest in yourself financially with a flexible or fixed box, with a flexible box you get a 12% return on investment (ROI) and the option to withdraw at your selected time. Fixed boxes have an ROI of 15% offering a long investment time. The longer your money stays in the account earning interest, the faster it will grow.</li><li><a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.ojirehprime.mobile.android&amp;hl=en">Automated payment to yourself</a>: think of saving as a method of paying yourself because in the closest future it will be paying you. set up an automatic transfer into either your flexible or fixed box account and commit to saving a certain amount so you won’t be tempted to spend the money.</li><li>Emergency fund creation: If there’s anything the pandemic thought us it’s that you can never go wrong with creating an emergency fund and the amazing thing about boxes is that it doesn’t have to be just one. Your first savings goal should be to set up your emergency fund to cover unexpected things like medical bills, car repairs or even a zombie apocalypse. Our experts at <a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.ojirehprime.mobile.android&amp;hl=en">OjirehPrime</a> usually recommend putting aside up to three months of rent and expenses, but even one month is a good start.</li><li>Breaking the paycheck cycle: The problem, when it comes to money, is that we just aren’t planning and putting away enough. Saving with boxes means allowing a break from the paycheck-to-paycheck cycle or allowing for a big purchase down the road, like a vehicle, vacation, or house. Creating a budget and following it, strategizing about the income we make now to devise plans for the future is one of the best things we can do with our hard-earned money.</li><li>Enjoy life: we’ve preached discipline and resisting instant gratification. But everyone is only human. Understanding the importance of saving simple also means that you can now and again spend on things for fun, relaxation and celebrations But be sure to build the occasional splurge into your <a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.ojirehprime.mobile.android&amp;hl=en">OjirehPrime</a> app budget plan with boxes.</li></ol><p>Get into the habit of saving remember it’s never too early to become a saver, start your saving journey today And more importantly, trust the bank you’re proud to call family to also prepare a protection plan for your finance and savings against any unexpected risks. Until next time with <a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.ojirehprime.mobile.android&amp;hl=en">OjirehPrime </a>nuggets of finance.</p><p>Download <a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.ojirehprime.mobile.android&amp;hl=en">OjirehPrime</a> and enjoy transparent banking and innovative savings</p><img src="https://medium.com/_/stat?event=post.clientViewed&referrerSource=full_rss&postId=4c6ec7e7b47e" width="1" height="1" alt="">]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How to start and Build your Emergency Fund.]]></title>
            <link>https://ojirehprime.medium.com/how-to-start-and-build-your-emergency-fund-13412e1fb543?source=rss-e4ead21b461f------2</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://medium.com/p/13412e1fb543</guid>
            <category><![CDATA[money]]></category>
            <category><![CDATA[savings-tips]]></category>
            <category><![CDATA[fintech]]></category>
            <category><![CDATA[savings-plan]]></category>
            <category><![CDATA[banking]]></category>
            <dc:creator><![CDATA[OjirehPrime]]></dc:creator>
            <pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 10:33:05 GMT</pubDate>
            <atom:updated>2022-05-25T10:35:13.258Z</atom:updated>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<figure><img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/1024/0*PwhnpnDiOXyshwM2" /><figcaption>Build your Emergency Fund</figcaption></figure><p>Emergency funds provide a cash reserve that allows you to stay afloat in an emergency without depending on credit cards or high-interest loans. establishing an emergency fund is extremely crucial because it can save you from borrowing more.</p><p><strong>How much should I save?</strong></p><p><strong>The short answer: </strong>Start small and establish a savings pattern, then progressively expand your goal over time.</p><p><strong>The long answer: </strong>The amount that is appropriate for you depends on your financial situation, but a reasonable rule of thumb is to have enough money to cover three to six months of living expenses. (If you freelance or work seasonally, or if your job is difficult to replace, you could need more.) If you lose your job, you can use the money to cover basic expenses while you look for a new one, or you can use it to enhance your unemployment payments. Start small and grow</p><h3>Where do I put my emergency fund?</h3><p>An emergency can happen at any point, having fast and easy access is important therefore it should not be placed in a long-term fund however, the account should be kept separate from the one you use on a regular basis so you don’t have to tap into your reserves. When developing an emergency fund, one of the most crucial factors to consider is the security of your cash, which should take precedence over the interest rate offered. Build your emergency fund directly with banks, fintechs, finance/investment houses that are fully licensed and regulated or have shown a strong partnership with one.</p><p>At OjirehPrime we understand the importance of building an emergency fund, this is why we’ve built Boxes for you. Boxes represent a more innovative way to save. With the OjirehPrime app, you can create a box, name it and set a timeline to it. You also get the chance to choose between a flexible and permanent lock style. The permanent lock affords you the opportunity to save on a secured lock with up to 15% interest Pa while the flexible lock affords you the window to break your save at any time you wish. OjirehPrime is available to android users as <a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.ojirehprime.mobile.android">OjirehPrime</a>.</p><img src="https://medium.com/_/stat?event=post.clientViewed&referrerSource=full_rss&postId=13412e1fb543" width="1" height="1" alt="">]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How OjirehPrime is helping Millennials Save Money]]></title>
            <link>https://ojirehprime.medium.com/how-ojirehprime-is-helping-millennials-save-money-c5f09dc63bd?source=rss-e4ead21b461f------2</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://medium.com/p/c5f09dc63bd</guid>
            <category><![CDATA[money]]></category>
            <category><![CDATA[money-management]]></category>
            <category><![CDATA[saving]]></category>
            <category><![CDATA[millennials]]></category>
            <category><![CDATA[generation-y]]></category>
            <dc:creator><![CDATA[OjirehPrime]]></dc:creator>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jul 2021 12:18:22 GMT</pubDate>
            <atom:updated>2021-07-06T12:25:15.241Z</atom:updated>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A major challenge that Millennials face is the constant worry of not being able to meet key financial goals such as buying a house or saving for retirement with a pandemic that has emphasized the need for a behavioral change and here is how OjirehPrime is delivering on her promise to enable a saving culture with Millenials in Sub-Saharan Africa.</p><figure><img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/1024/1*xZjFMa4DUa0AaLtoRnmr9w.png" /></figure><p>Although Millenials have frequently been labelled as materialistic, spoiled, and engulfed with a sense of entitlement, many millennials still have a lingering feeling of not being able to achieve material goals like finding their dream job, buying a house, or retiring until much later in their lives which have become increasingly difficult for many who are struggling with unemployment and low-paying jobs. The pandemic left more than 15% of millennials in their early 20s out of work, many of whom are still struggling to find suitable jobs, according to <a href="https://www.investopedia.com/articles/personal-finance/021914/money-habits-millennials.asp">Investopedia</a>.</p><p>Owing to the impact of social media and the increasing amount of pressure that millennials feel to conform to the financial habits of their peers comes from social media, where financial milestones such as home and car purchases are routinely posted, millennials divert funds meant to be saved into non-profitable engagements. Research by <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2017/06/30/heres-how-millennials-spend-their-money-compared-to-their-parents.html">CNBC</a> revealed that 69% of the 7.000 millennials do not save regularly and a mountain of debt due to excessive spending and a constant repayment of loans making it harder to save. Most millennials’ monthly salary is always used up before they consider setting out an amount.</p><h3>The Way Around, OjirehPrime Boxes and Transparent Banking</h3><figure><img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/287/1*rCx5GZIJa1pZv9nkLHWyUA.png" /><figcaption>OjirehPrime Boxes</figcaption></figure><p>The solution is, set the budget at the beginning of the month as soon as you receive your salary. Assign expenditure items as needed with the Ojirehprime boxes Then, set aside at least 10%-30% of the money for savings which can be named accordingly for proper and easy savings method. Ojirehprime’s boxes are suitable for millennials due to their technologically advanced saving method that includes automation, interest building, and the ability to liquidate without hassle or make unavailable until maturity based on the type of box selected on initiation. Even though you regularly save money, you can still have a modern lifestyle.</p><p>The Ojirehprime boxes can be opened via the bank app at your convenience so you don’t have to make a physical visit to the bank. Ojirehprime coming mobile app will help you keep track of all your finances and create tailor-made budgets based on control and savings methods on your earning/inflow and spending habits. Then on security? Finances are secured with military-grade encryption as revealed by the engineering lead for OjirehPrime, Wale Shotobi in one of the Wednesday <a href="http://bit.ly/ojirehprimeclub">Clubhouse</a> sessions.</p><h3>Final Thoughts</h3><p>A lot of millennials feel like the deck is stacked against them when working a lot, making a little, and still trying to piece together some semblance of financial stability. To get yourself on the right track toward financial success, start small, be consistent — and remain realistic. Challenge yourself with an Ojirehprime savings method but don’t set yourself up for failure and acknowledge what living within your means really looks like, although Ojirehprime has successfully made it easier, we encourage you to set goals on all boxes.</p><p>Where to begin? Join the waitlist now, on the <a href="https://www.ojirehprime.com">OjirehPrime website</a>.</p><h3>Do you know and agree that you can save and invest your way to millionaire status?</h3><img src="https://medium.com/_/stat?event=post.clientViewed&referrerSource=full_rss&postId=c5f09dc63bd" width="1" height="1" alt="">]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact Investing and Importance in achieving SDG Goals in Africa]]></title>
            <link>https://ojirehprime.medium.com/impact-investing-and-importance-in-achieving-sdg-goals-in-africa-ecd678062d2c?source=rss-e4ead21b461f------2</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://medium.com/p/ecd678062d2c</guid>
            <category><![CDATA[sustainable-development]]></category>
            <category><![CDATA[impact-investing]]></category>
            <category><![CDATA[africa]]></category>
            <category><![CDATA[green-energy]]></category>
            <category><![CDATA[investing]]></category>
            <dc:creator><![CDATA[OjirehPrime]]></dc:creator>
            <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jun 2021 08:02:35 GMT</pubDate>
            <atom:updated>2021-06-24T08:45:12.110Z</atom:updated>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>How Impact Investing could sustainably galvanize the achievement of the Sustainable Development Goals, an OjirehPrime call-to-action special.</p><figure><img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/1024/1*vloNWUAwrMFI7asxEV8Frg.jpeg" /><figcaption>Image: Emmanuel Ben-Paul</figcaption></figure><p>Impact investing is an investment strategy made to generate positive, measurable social and environmental impact alongside a financial gain. One of its major aims is to use money and investment capital for positive social results, taking the form of numerous asset classes which may result in many specific outcomes. Investors using impact investing as a strategy consider a company’s commitment to corporate social responsibility evaluating their sense of duty before becoming fully involved with that company. The growing impact investment market provides capital to address the world’s most pressing challenges such as microfinance, affordable and accessible basic services including housing, good healthcare, education, affordable and clean energy. Impact investment has constantly challenged the long-held views that social and environmental issues should be addressed only by philanthropic donations, and those market investments should focus exclusively on achieving financial returns. Impact investing offers diverse and viable opportunities for investors to advance social and environmental solutions through investments.</p><figure><img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/1024/1*JGGhvSeJrDrdcb5kuymVrA.jpeg" /></figure><p>When looking at the SDGs, there are such categories as providing access to clean and affordable energy, reducing poverty, creating more sustainable cities and communities, reducing poverty et al. Every goal has targets that require some sort of financial investment. It was estimated by the UN that developing countries alone face a USD 2.5 trillion gap in financing. Impact investment plays a pivotal contributing role as it has unlocked private capital to address societal issues. Impact investors raise and direct new capital to address pressing social and environmental challenges such as ending poverty, protecting the planet, and ensuring that all people enjoy peace and prosperity by 2030 directly targeting progress toward the SDGs. The massive growth in the scale, breadth and public recognition of the emerging transformative investment market is gradually changing and making traditional entrepreneurial, investment, and charitable activities adapt to creating new opportunities not only for profit but also for achieving sustainable development goals.</p><figure><img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/1024/1*iuhtg0G6tlsHY9B7ovTjrw.jpeg" /><figcaption>Image: Patrick Hendry</figcaption></figure><p>Our future is interdependent, impact investing has been an agent of social change, redefining our notions of value allowing us to be a part of social change that makes a measurable difference for our planet and future generations driving positive change. It has so changed the culture of investing today investors position themselves to take advantage of this energy and to further bring impact investing into the mainstream. The private capital is constantly filling the financial gap in assistance to government grants just to meet the Sustainable Development Goals (SDGs) in developing countries.</p><p>Barclays, a British multinational universal bank set precedence in June 2020 with the launch of Impact Agora that Digital Banks and Fintech on the continent can champion this — a platform to bring together the investors and intermediaries who are working with directly entrepreneurs seeking to promote impact investing. Impact Agora provides shared technology and builds a community of member institutions, thereby reducing barriers to investment and raising the profile of impact investing intermediaries and entrepreneurs. Startups like OjirehPrime are stepping up with investment initiatives that impact investors or prospective could drive this through, powered by Solid Allianze Microfinance Banks — Interested investors can indicate interest and request a call <a href="https://mailchi.mp/ojirehprime/invest">here</a>.</p><p>The time for impact investing to scale in Africa is now!</p><h4>What are your thoughts?</h4><p><em>Written by Ameh Ujah and Jessica Fetun</em></p><img src="https://medium.com/_/stat?event=post.clientViewed&referrerSource=full_rss&postId=ecd678062d2c" width="1" height="1" alt="">]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Who will finally hack the Nigerian Customer Service situation?]]></title>
            <link>https://ojirehprime.medium.com/who-will-finally-hack-the-nigerian-customer-service-situation-89840dd4e029?source=rss-e4ead21b461f------2</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://medium.com/p/89840dd4e029</guid>
            <category><![CDATA[fintech]]></category>
            <category><![CDATA[ojirehprime]]></category>
            <category><![CDATA[customer-experience]]></category>
            <category><![CDATA[customer-engagement]]></category>
            <category><![CDATA[customer-service]]></category>
            <dc:creator><![CDATA[OjirehPrime]]></dc:creator>
            <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jun 2021 19:02:02 GMT</pubDate>
            <atom:updated>2021-06-22T10:00:07.861Z</atom:updated>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>With over $9 billion in value pools and being an attractive sector banking in Nigeria despite the high level of competition and foreign investments old habits are being rekindled that see neglecting of customers complaints add to the large percentage of customers that are underserved.</p><figure><img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/770/1*0PxxTQFv_IM5mkstGISIrQ.jpeg" /></figure><p>Recently, fintech companies in Nigeria have been known to focus on innovative technology neglecting their duties to customers which contributes to the rising frustration customers experience. Jeff Bezos, CEO of Amazon, one of the world’s biggest tech companies describes the company’s focus on customer experience as an “obsession” and what Amazon has done better than their peer tech. In Nigeria, many fintech companies will do anything except being less focused on customer service which cannot thrive without accountability and has gotten worse after the Twitter ban which was a major force for fintech companies to respond in real-time which allowed both customers and competitors to see what they are doing wrong.</p><p>Digital banks have in recent times neglected complaints owing to Twitter not being banned by the government and the absence of real-time accountability. Prior to the ban, there have been a rising number of customers alleging fintech companies’ poor customer experience and in most cases, a lack of transparency evident from the several comments on official pages for most Fintech companies.</p><figure><img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/1024/1*6vhgjg0g1ekEw3ZmudJ1Ug.png" /><figcaption>Complaint from the comment section of some Fintech Banks where some have resorted to closing their comment</figcaption></figure><p>Some notable fintech companies including OjirehPrime positioned as ‘the first bank customers will be proud to call family’ have recently adopted the use of other platforms such as Clubhouse to keep its customers engaged and receive real-time complaints while troubleshooting. “If there is one reason we have done better than our peers in the internet space over the last six years, it is because we have focused like a laser on customer experience, and that really does matter, I think, in any business. It certainly matters online, where word-of-mouth is so very very powerful, ” Jeff Bezos said. It points to the fact that OjirehPrime has successfully integrated this alongside innovative technology.</p><p>The productivity of Fintech companies is on the verge of breakthrough from the traditional banks assisting them with infrastructures which for a while has been a dependent limitation as traditional banks aiming to maintain their hold deny them full access. Bolaji Akinboro, the co-founder of Cellulant and chairman of Voriancorelli clarified that the major component of the infrastructure is data stating that “It’s a bit like the banking version of social media data, anyone who has access to that data can build a comprehensive profile of human behaviour that is very valuation” in a chat with BusinessDay.</p><p>Ojirehprime and a few Fintech companies have been able to crack through that data using multiple platforms to reach their customers, encouraging real-time access to the company and resolving both emergencies, and feeding the customers with transparent information.</p><h3>The question? Who will finally hack the Customer Service situation? When will a typical Nigerian bank customer not have to settle?</h3><img src="https://medium.com/_/stat?event=post.clientViewed&referrerSource=full_rss&postId=89840dd4e029" width="1" height="1" alt="">]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Using Microfinance Banks’ Service — The Underappreciated Underdogs]]></title>
            <link>https://ojirehprime.medium.com/using-microfinance-banks-service-the-underappreciated-underdogs-17af8f26fe9a?source=rss-e4ead21b461f------2</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://medium.com/p/17af8f26fe9a</guid>
            <category><![CDATA[microfinance-bank]]></category>
            <category><![CDATA[microfinanc]]></category>
            <category><![CDATA[financial-services]]></category>
            <category><![CDATA[ojirehprime]]></category>
            <category><![CDATA[solid-allianze]]></category>
            <dc:creator><![CDATA[OjirehPrime]]></dc:creator>
            <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2021 08:12:29 GMT</pubDate>
            <atom:updated>2021-06-16T15:52:38.434Z</atom:updated>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<h3>Using Microfinance Banks’ Service — The Underappreciated Underdogs</h3><p>Microfinance is synonymous with microcredit. As an institution, Microfinance banks provide small business owners and entrepreneurs access to capital which often they are unable to acquire through traditional financial resources and major institutions. This consequently means harder to access loans, insurance, and investments to assist the growth of their businesses. This is where Microfinance Banks pick the ball.</p><figure><img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/1024/1*3MZfdYiQkCeENcV063w40g.png" /></figure><p>Many Microfinance banks offer additional services such as checking and savings accounts as well as micro-insurance products, and some even provide financial and business education to the small business owner and entrepreneur. There are quite a number of Microfinance banks in Nigeria including <a href="https://techpoint.africa/2021/04/01/solid-allianze-mfb-announces-ojirehprime-as-a-new-investor/">Solid Allianze which was acquired by OjirehPrime months ago</a> and The goal of microfinance is to ultimately give low-income individuals an opportunity to become self-sufficient who otherwise might have no other access to financial services.</p><p><strong>UNDERSTANDING MICRO-FINANCING</strong></p><p>Microfinance services are provided to help bridge the gap of financial insufficiency of unemployed to low-income earners providing them with the necessary safe capital to start a business and work toward financial independence. Unlike typical financing situations which focus on the borrower having enough collateral to cover the loan, many microfinance organizations focus on helping entrepreneurs succeed; however, the interest rates of these loans are often high due to the appetite of risk they have to take and risk of default.</p><figure><img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/512/1*OcU9EtRPcM5kvnEnoDd6IQ.png" /><figcaption>Solid Allianze MFB</figcaption></figure><p>Microfinance organizations often require you to take a basic money-management class, cover understanding interest rates, the concept of cash flow, how financing agreements and savings accounts work, how to budget, and how to manage debt afterward small loans and other resources are provided to business owners and entrepreneurs to help them easily start their businesses. Microfinance encompasses microloans, micro-savings, and microinsurance. Micro savings accounts allow entrepreneurs to have a savings account with no minimum balance and microinsurance provides borrowers with insurance at a lower rate.</p><p><strong>BENEFITS OF MICROFINANCING</strong></p><p>Although microfinance banks must charge interest on loans, they are generally lower than conventional banks. As of 2014, The International Finance Corporation (IFC), part of the larger World Bank Group, estimates that more than 130 million people have directly benefited from microfinance-related operations. The benefits of microfinance extend giving people a source for capital. Entrepreneurs who create successful businesses, in turn, create jobs, trade, and overall economic improvement within a community.</p><p>Entrepreneurs with no collateral can take out loans to jump-start their business. Microfinance banks have been known to assist more women to break the cycle of financial insufficiency. Women in 2018 made up 80% of loans according to the 2019 Microfinance Barometer. The microfinance industry is also growing rapidly. In 2018, there were 139.9 million microfinance borrowers, for a total of $124 billion in loans. Nigeria accounted for most of these borrowers, followed by India, Bangladesh, and Vietnam.</p><p>Microfinance serves as a valuable tool for the financially underserved when used properly. Also citing the industry’s high repayment rate as proof of its effectiveness.</p><figure><img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/1000/1*8_9bjhUtw27K0KAjUl7OQg.jpeg" /></figure><p><strong>KEY TAKEAWAY</strong></p><p>•Like conventional lenders, micro financiers charge interest on loans and institute specific repayment plans but on lesser interest rates.</p><p>•Microfinance banks operate majorly in developing countries like Nigeria, Uganda, Indonesia, Serbia and India.</p><p>• It was estimated by the World Bank that more than 500 million people have benefited from microfinance-related operations.</p><p>•Microfinance is a banking service provided to unemployed or low-income individuals or groups who would have no other access to financial services.</p><ul><li>Microfinance allows people to take reasonably safe small business loans that are consistent with ethical lending practices.</li></ul><p>We have a Clubhouse virtual chat series scheduled for tonight at 8PM [WAT] — RSVP and add to your calendar <a href="https://bit.ly/ojirehprimeclub">here</a>.</p><p>In conclusion, will you open a Microfinance bank account after reading this? If still no, kindly share reasons in the comment box.</p><img src="https://medium.com/_/stat?event=post.clientViewed&referrerSource=full_rss&postId=17af8f26fe9a" width="1" height="1" alt="">]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Stop the Cycle of Living Pay Check to Pay Check]]></title>
            <link>https://ojirehprime.medium.com/stop-the-cycle-of-living-pay-check-to-pay-check-10b4e0a2d019?source=rss-e4ead21b461f------2</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://medium.com/p/10b4e0a2d019</guid>
            <category><![CDATA[money-management]]></category>
            <category><![CDATA[personal-development]]></category>
            <category><![CDATA[finance]]></category>
            <category><![CDATA[personal-financ]]></category>
            <category><![CDATA[finance-management]]></category>
            <dc:creator><![CDATA[OjirehPrime]]></dc:creator>
            <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jun 2021 13:17:01 GMT</pubDate>
            <atom:updated>2021-06-15T13:25:52.808Z</atom:updated>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Are you stuck in the cycle of living from paycheck to paycheck? Constantly stressed, anxious, afraid, and overwhelmed about your finances? These emotions are making it hard for you to carefully look into your finances and take bold steps into gaining control and achieving your financial goals. Here is an <a href="https://ojirehprime.com/join">OjirehPrime</a> guide from the <a href="https://www.instagram.com/stories/highlights/17903949742947870/">Ask Ojireh series</a>.</p><figure><img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/1024/1*MT8mTqMaO5HM05cdGD1-oA.jpeg" /></figure><p><strong>BECOME DEBT FREE</strong>: You can’t get ahead if you keep piling up on debt, opt on living within your means. Pay off old debts and avoid any catchy deals that might mean repaying over time with interest especially on things that do not yield profit.</p><p><strong>MAKE SAVINGS PAINLESS</strong>: Everyone has goals, especially financial goals like launching a business, having a comfortable retirement, kids university tuition, buying a new home or car etc that dream will need to be thoughtfully translated into savings to make the process easy and less tedious. It is important to channel your money and know where it is going tangibly, once you know how much you are spending you can easily direct a portion of your money into saving. When money goes out of your pay without you seeing it, there is less chance that you’re going to spend it and the <a href="https://ojirehprime.com/join">OjirehPrime</a> boxes help you achieve this sole process making budgeting and saving less painful.</p><figure><img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/1024/1*ah_hBY3mik10F4_DNExjqA.jpeg" /><figcaption>Focus and there’ll be no worries</figcaption></figure><p><strong>FOCUS ON YOUR PRIMARY NEEDS</strong>: The need to focus on your immediate survival needs is a top priority if you live waiting for your next paycheck. Pay for these things before anything else:</p><ul><li>Food</li><li>Shelter</li><li>Utilities</li><li>Transportation</li></ul><p>Make a list of what to pay according to an order of importance. When you run out of money you will be fed and have a roof over your head no matter what.</p><p><strong>HAVE AN EMERGENCY FUND</strong>: Skip that new restaurant that offers throat-cutting prices. It’s not the right time especially when an Emergency Fund is not in your financial lifestyle. With just 50 naira you can start a safety net with OjirehPrime. Once an Emergency Fund is set up you’ll be amazed at how much peace it’ll give up. Most people wonder why they might need an emergency fund but knowing you don’t need to spend from your entire next paycheck when you get into an unforeseen situation will keep you from getting into debt and give you a financially stable lifestyle.</p><figure><img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/1024/1*BOCqhy9oxPVa-mJSIv5zfA.png" /><figcaption>With OjirehPrime Boxes you could automate saving for your boxes</figcaption></figure><p><strong>BUDGETING/SIDE HUSTLE</strong>: I know you’ve heard a lot of “create a budget” advice and it can get frustrating when your paycheck isn’t even enough to cover your primary needs. An increase in income will not just give you an extra edge but will make budgeting a whole lot easier. You can either request a salary raise, find another job, or start a simple side hustle to help cover your bills and a little more financial stability.</p><p><a href="https://www.instagram.com/p/CP8JBsMpVc2/">https://www.instagram.com/p/CP8JBsMpVc2/</a></p><p><strong>FINANCIAL EDUCATION</strong>: Develop the habit of taking out 15–20 minutes to expand your financial knowledge not just to fit in your current financial level but also to create more wealth and learn how to manage it this can include checking the OjirehPrime blog, listening to a podcast, following reputable financial experts on social media, reading a book on money management, The more you learn about finance, the easier it’ll become to make positive choices and adopt healthier habits. Stop guessing/ wishing for a financially stable future and start educating yourself about it.</p><p>Remember if you need practical advice on dealing with any personal finance matter, simply drop us a comment with the hashtag — #ASKOjireh and your topic will be next on the series. Keep up with us on <a href="https://www.instagram.com/stories/highlights/17903949742947870/">social media</a>.</p><figure><img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/1024/1*7IdQ7Bws62Xnp5-EbasdDg.png" /></figure><img src="https://medium.com/_/stat?event=post.clientViewed&referrerSource=full_rss&postId=10b4e0a2d019" width="1" height="1" alt="">]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>