<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>News Archives &#8902; ZyCrypto</title>
	<atom:link href="https://zycrypto.com/category/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://zycrypto.com/category/news/</link>
	<description>ZyCrypto Is A Cryptocurrency News Media, Focusing On Daily News, Expert Opinions, Analysis, Reviews, And So Much More.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 21:10:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/cropped-ZyCrypto-Site-Logo-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News Archives &#8902; ZyCrypto</title>
	<link>https://zycrypto.com/category/news/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Ripple Mulls Making Key Acquisitions in Crypto-Friendly Countries — Can It Boost XRP To $1?</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/ripple-mulls-making-key-acquisitions-in-crypto-friendly-countries-can-it-boost-xrp-to-1/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/ripple-mulls-making-key-acquisitions-in-crypto-friendly-countries-can-it-boost-xrp-to-1/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Newton Gitonga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 21:10:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=81431</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Legal-Expert-Has-‘No-Doubt-Ripple-Will-Win-Legal-War-Against-SEC-—-Can-It-Supercharge-XRP-To-1.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Legal Expert Has ‘No Doubt’ Ripple Will Win Legal War Against SEC — Can It Supercharge XRP To $1?" decoding="async" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Legal-Expert-Has-‘No-Doubt-Ripple-Will-Win-Legal-War-Against-SEC-—-Can-It-Supercharge-XRP-To-1.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Legal-Expert-Has-‘No-Doubt-Ripple-Will-Win-Legal-War-Against-SEC-—-Can-It-Supercharge-XRP-To-1-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Legal-Expert-Has-‘No-Doubt-Ripple-Will-Win-Legal-War-Against-SEC-—-Can-It-Supercharge-XRP-To-1-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Legal-Expert-Has-‘No-Doubt-Ripple-Will-Win-Legal-War-Against-SEC-—-Can-It-Supercharge-XRP-To-1-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>Prominent blockchain-based payment solutions company, Ripple, is contemplating making strategic acquisitions in crypto-friendly countries in a bid to expand its business model.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Legal-Expert-Has-‘No-Doubt-Ripple-Will-Win-Legal-War-Against-SEC-—-Can-It-Supercharge-XRP-To-1.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Legal Expert Has ‘No Doubt’ Ripple Will Win Legal War Against SEC — Can It Supercharge XRP To $1?" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Legal-Expert-Has-‘No-Doubt-Ripple-Will-Win-Legal-War-Against-SEC-—-Can-It-Supercharge-XRP-To-1.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Legal-Expert-Has-‘No-Doubt-Ripple-Will-Win-Legal-War-Against-SEC-—-Can-It-Supercharge-XRP-To-1-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Legal-Expert-Has-‘No-Doubt-Ripple-Will-Win-Legal-War-Against-SEC-—-Can-It-Supercharge-XRP-To-1-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Legal-Expert-Has-‘No-Doubt-Ripple-Will-Win-Legal-War-Against-SEC-—-Can-It-Supercharge-XRP-To-1-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>Prominent blockchain-based payment solutions company, Ripple, is contemplating making strategic acquisitions in crypto-friendly countries in a bid to expand its business model.</p>



<p>Ripple CEO Brad Garlinghouse unveiled this information during a live interview at last week&#8217;s Dubai Fintech Summit. In his remarks, the Ripple boss noted that Ripple&#8217;s aspirations <a href="https://zycrypto.com/ripple-expands-into-the-institutional-crypto-custody-market-following-250-million-acquisition-of-metaco/">go beyond</a> its existing emphasis on cross-border payments for businesses and encompass various other aspects of the blockchain technology sector.</p>



<p><em>“What I think will be next is certainly something Ripple thinks about. We started with enterprise-based cross-border payments. We talked about there being four primitive pieces to blockchain-based technologies; liquidity, compliance, custody and tokenization. Ripple aspires to be more than just that…I think you’d expect that we will expand into some of those other areas either organically or through acquisitions,”</em> said Garlinghouse.</p>



<p>The CEO then emphasized the significance of operating in countries that support blockchain technologies, citing the <a href="https://zycrypto.com/ripple-debuts-first-ever-in-market-on-demand-liquidity-odl-deployment-in-the-middle-east/">United Arab Emirates (UAE)</a> and Switzerland as prime examples of nations that offer an encouraging environment for entrepreneurs in the crypto space.</p>



<p><em>“I think we will look at making acquisitions in markets that are friendly to these technologies,” </em>he said, adding <em>“In the previous panel, you had representations from UAE, Switzerland. These are countries that are providing the clarity for entrepreneurs to invest and that allows a company like Ripple that is larger.”&nbsp;</em></p>



<p>Furthermore, to back his statements, Garlinghouse disclosed that Ripple had over $1 billion in cash reserves positioned to be allocated towards the said strategic acquisitions.</p>



<p><em>“We have more than $1 billion of cash on our balance sheet. We want to deploy that to grow both organically and also inorganically through acquisition,” </em>he went on.&nbsp;</p>



<p>Garlinghouse&#8217;s remarks came amid heightened concerns over the regulatory environment in the United States. During the interview, he expressed his frustration at the US, stating that the country is falling behind significantly due to the prioritization of politics over policy.&nbsp;</p>



<p>According to him, investment and growth potential in blockchain technologies risked being pursued outside the United States of America due to the country’s apparent anti-crypto ideologies.</p>



<p>He went on to state that Ripple expects to spend approximately $200 million defending itself against the <a href="https://zycrypto.com/xrp-lawsuit-sec-may-have-just-bitten-off-more-than-it-can-chew-as-ripple-eyes-very-big-win-in-case/">ongoing lawsuit</a> with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), asserting that the case lacks a solid foundation.</p>



<p>That said, despite the difficulties encountered in the United States, Ripple&#8217;s ambitions for expansion, which include the possibility of acquiring companies in crypto-friendly regions, have the potential to establish the company as a frontrunner in the global blockchain industry.</p>



<p>This strategic move would boost the utilization of Ripple&#8217;s ecosystem and ultimately drive the value of XRP towards the coveted $1 price level. At press time, the cryptocurrency was trading at $0.4672, up 3.39% in the past 24 hours.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/ripple-mulls-making-key-acquisitions-in-crypto-friendly-countries-can-it-boost-xrp-to-1/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>DLT Viable Solution For Cross-border, Multi-currency Payments &#8211; New York Fed/MAS Study</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/dlt-viable-solution-for-cross-border-multi-currency-payments-new-york-fed-mas-study/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/dlt-viable-solution-for-cross-border-multi-currency-payments-new-york-fed-mas-study/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Isa Nsereko]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 20:59:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=81425</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/FTX-Forges-New-Partnership-With-Visa-To-Enable-Crypto-Payments-In-40-Countries.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="FTX Forges New Partnership With Visa To Enable Crypto Payments In 40 Countries" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/FTX-Forges-New-Partnership-With-Visa-To-Enable-Crypto-Payments-In-40-Countries.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/FTX-Forges-New-Partnership-With-Visa-To-Enable-Crypto-Payments-In-40-Countries-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/FTX-Forges-New-Partnership-With-Visa-To-Enable-Crypto-Payments-In-40-Countries-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/FTX-Forges-New-Partnership-With-Visa-To-Enable-Crypto-Payments-In-40-Countries-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>In a May 18, 2023 press release, the New York Fed and the Monetary Authority of Singapore (MAS) published the results of a research study, known as Project Cedar Phase II x Ubin+. Project Cedar is a Federal Reserve Bank of New York’s New York Innovation Center initiative that seeks to develop a technical framework [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/FTX-Forges-New-Partnership-With-Visa-To-Enable-Crypto-Payments-In-40-Countries.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="FTX Forges New Partnership With Visa To Enable Crypto Payments In 40 Countries" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/FTX-Forges-New-Partnership-With-Visa-To-Enable-Crypto-Payments-In-40-Countries.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/FTX-Forges-New-Partnership-With-Visa-To-Enable-Crypto-Payments-In-40-Countries-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/FTX-Forges-New-Partnership-With-Visa-To-Enable-Crypto-Payments-In-40-Countries-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/FTX-Forges-New-Partnership-With-Visa-To-Enable-Crypto-Payments-In-40-Countries-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>In a May 18, 2023 press release, the New York Fed and the Monetary Authority of Singapore (MAS) published the results of a research study, known as Project Cedar Phase II x Ubin+.</p>



<p>Project Cedar is a Federal Reserve Bank of New York’s New York Innovation Center initiative that seeks to develop a technical framework for a theoretical wholesale central bank digital currency (CBDC) and contribute to the CBDCs dialogue.</p>



<p>Phase I of Project Cedar revealed that using a wholesale CBDC to facilitate blockchain technology transactions could improve the speed and safety of wholesale cross-border payments.</p>



<p>Ubin+ is a MAS initiative to improve the efficiency of cross-border settlement using distributed ledger technology (DLT) and non-DLT financial networks.</p>



<p>The collaboration to investigate whether wholesale central bank digital currencies (wCBDCs) could improve the efficiency of cross-border, multi-currency payments was announced by the New York Fed and the MAS in November 2022.</p>



<p>Project Cedar Phase II x Ubin+ examined whether DLT could improve the efficiency of cross-border wholesale payments and settlements involving multiple currencies.</p>



<p>As stated by the released Project Cedar Phase II x Ubin+ report, the study was aimed at contributing to the ongoing innovation in the financial sector and not to advance any specific policy outcome. Neither was the study intended to signal any imminent decisions about the appropriateness of issuing a CBDC nor indicating how one would be designed.</p>



<p>The hypotheses tested in the study aimed to establish whether wholesale CBDC systems developed using DLT could be technically interoperable with other payment systems across different jurisdictions, could facilitate cross-border payments across illiquid currency corridors, or could shorten the processing time of cross-border, cross-currency payments initiated in different jurisdictions.</p>



<p>Project Cedar Phase II x Ubin+ has shown that payments can be safely made across multiple ledgers without a central clearing authority or the establishment of a shared central network. The results also showed that simulated payments could be settled atomically, in near real-time, addressing concerns of counterparty risks.</p>



<p>Project Cedar Phase II x Ubin+ also demonstrated that DLT could support enhancements to cross-border multi-currency payments and settlements relating to network interoperability and autonomy, settlement, and speed. The study noted that alternative technical designs other than DLT may also provide viable solutions.</p>



<p>“Cross-border payments are a major railway for facilitating the functioning of the global economy,” said Michelle Neal, New York Fed’s Head of the Markets Group.</p>



<p>Areas for future experimentation and analysis identified by the study include the viability of the network scalability, the involvement of additional currencies supported by their corresponding central bank ledgers, and privacy limitations and liquidity optimization.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/dlt-viable-solution-for-cross-border-multi-currency-payments-new-york-fed-mas-study/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Suitability Of Crypto Products To Be Included In Regulatory Frameworks &#8211; IOSCO Recommendation</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/suitability-of-crypto-products-to-be-included-in-regulatory-frameworks-iosco-recommendation/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/suitability-of-crypto-products-to-be-included-in-regulatory-frameworks-iosco-recommendation/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Isa Nsereko]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 20:40:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=81422</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/White-House-Finally-Publishes-A-Framework-For-Crypto-Regulation.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="White House Finally Publishes A Framework For Crypto Regulation" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/White-House-Finally-Publishes-A-Framework-For-Crypto-Regulation.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/White-House-Finally-Publishes-A-Framework-For-Crypto-Regulation-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/White-House-Finally-Publishes-A-Framework-For-Crypto-Regulation-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/White-House-Finally-Publishes-A-Framework-For-Crypto-Regulation-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>According to a May 23, 2023 media release, the International Organization of Securities Commissions (IOSCO) issued global recommendations to jurisdictions on the regulation of crypto and digital asset markets. IOSCO has requested comments on its recommendations through public consultation by July 31, 2023. ‘Retail access, suitability, and distribution’ of crypto assets is one of the [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/White-House-Finally-Publishes-A-Framework-For-Crypto-Regulation.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="White House Finally Publishes A Framework For Crypto Regulation" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/White-House-Finally-Publishes-A-Framework-For-Crypto-Regulation.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/White-House-Finally-Publishes-A-Framework-For-Crypto-Regulation-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/White-House-Finally-Publishes-A-Framework-For-Crypto-Regulation-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/White-House-Finally-Publishes-A-Framework-For-Crypto-Regulation-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>According to a May 23, 2023 media release, the International Organization of Securities Commissions (IOSCO) issued global recommendations to jurisdictions on the regulation of crypto and digital asset markets. IOSCO has requested comments on its recommendations through public consultation by July 31, 2023.</p>



<p>‘Retail access, suitability, and distribution’ of crypto assets is one of the key areas covered by IOSCO’s recommendations. IOSCO proposed that regulators should require crypto-asset service providers (CASPs) to operate in a manner consistent with its standards regarding interactions and dealings with retail clients.</p>



<p>This includes assessing the appropriateness and/or suitability of particular crypto-asset products and services offered to each retail client. In developing new frameworks for crypto and digital asset markets, regulators should consider imposing requirements related to suitability/ appropriateness assessments.</p>



<p>Client Suitability Assessment enables CASPs to profile potential clients to choose the best investments aligned to their objectives, risk tolerance, preferences, experiences, specific needs and circumstances, among other factors.</p>



<p>As per IOSCO recommendations, If CSAPs use suitability assessments, regulators should require that the assessments are robust enough not to give clients the impression that they fully understand the operations and the related risks of crypto asset markets.</p>



<p>IOSCO further proposes that where a prospective client does not demonstrate sufficient knowledge, the CASP should not permit that client to trade crypto assets.</p>



<p>On the retail distribution of crypto-assets, IOSCO has requested public feedback on what other safeguards should be adopted, whether regulators should take steps, and to what extent to restrict advertisements and endorsements promoting crypto-assets.</p>



<p>Following the crypto market bankruptcies in 2022 and events surrounding the collapse of the FTX crypto exchange, the technical committee of IOSCO published a consultation report in February 2023 on the suitability requirements for complex financial products.</p>



<p>The report set out proposed principles relating to customer protection, including suitability and disclosure obligations relating to the distribution of complex financial products to retail and non-retail customers by intermediaries.</p>



<p>Following the issuance of its recommendations, IOSCO has requested jurisdictions to review them against their current regulatory frameworks to ensure compliance with its standards and to fix any gaps as soon as possible. IOSCO aims to finalize its recommendations by the end of the year.&nbsp;</p>



<p>In an April 2023 media release, IOSCO published its work program for 2023-24. The work program called for IOSCO to maintain the momentum from its July 2022 crypto-asset roadmap and to assess and respond to the risks associated with crypto-asset market activities and decentralized finance.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/suitability-of-crypto-products-to-be-included-in-regulatory-frameworks-iosco-recommendation/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hoskinson: Cardano to Achieve Unrivaled Decentralization in Crypto After Major Project Developments</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/hoskinson-cardano-to-achieve-unrivaled-decentralization-in-crypto-after-major-project-developments/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/hoskinson-cardano-to-achieve-unrivaled-decentralization-in-crypto-after-major-project-developments/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Newton Gitonga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 17:19:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADAUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=81409</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Cardano-Is-Buzzing-With-Super-Bullish-Activity-As-ADA-Adoption-Expands-To-New-Realms.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Cardano Is Buzzing With Super Bullish Activity As ADA Adoption Expands To New Realms" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Cardano-Is-Buzzing-With-Super-Bullish-Activity-As-ADA-Adoption-Expands-To-New-Realms.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Cardano-Is-Buzzing-With-Super-Bullish-Activity-As-ADA-Adoption-Expands-To-New-Realms-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Cardano-Is-Buzzing-With-Super-Bullish-Activity-As-ADA-Adoption-Expands-To-New-Realms-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Cardano-Is-Buzzing-With-Super-Bullish-Activity-As-ADA-Adoption-Expands-To-New-Realms-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>Cardano founder Charles Hoskinson has expressed confidence in Cardano making substantial strides in its mission to create a truly decentralized and inclusive blockchain ecosystem.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Cardano-Is-Buzzing-With-Super-Bullish-Activity-As-ADA-Adoption-Expands-To-New-Realms.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Cardano Is Buzzing With Super Bullish Activity As ADA Adoption Expands To New Realms" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Cardano-Is-Buzzing-With-Super-Bullish-Activity-As-ADA-Adoption-Expands-To-New-Realms.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Cardano-Is-Buzzing-With-Super-Bullish-Activity-As-ADA-Adoption-Expands-To-New-Realms-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Cardano-Is-Buzzing-With-Super-Bullish-Activity-As-ADA-Adoption-Expands-To-New-Realms-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Cardano-Is-Buzzing-With-Super-Bullish-Activity-As-ADA-Adoption-Expands-To-New-Realms-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>Cardano founder Charles Hoskinson has expressed confidence in Cardano making substantial strides in its mission to create a truly decentralized and inclusive blockchain ecosystem.</p>



<p>In a Thursday, May 25 video on his YouTube channel, Hoskinson provided an update on the project&#8217;s progress and outlined the significant developments that will contribute to the platform&#8217;s unrivalled decentralization in the cryptocurrency space.</p>



<p>First, Hoskinson highlighted CIP 1694, an important project which aims to bring a new way of governing <a href="https://zycrypto.com/cardano-ada-staking-value-surpasses-400-million-ada-reaching-161-million-in-tvl/">Cardano</a>. Currently, most major decisions on how things are done on the network are decided by the Cardano Foundation and a small group of people. However, according to Hoskinson, with CIP 1694, more people from the community will be able to have a say and be involved in making decisions.</p>



<p><em>“You should have a say, not people you&#8217;ve never met not people that aren&#8217;t accountable to you and not people who don&#8217;t have your best interest at heart and I&#8217;d like to believe we can get there. That&#8217;s why we built Cardano,”</em> said Hoskinson.</p>



<p>He further mentioned that the team behind this project was working hard to build and test it on node 8.0, adding that they plan to release node 8.1 soon.</p>



<p>To further encourage community involvement, Charles Hoskinson announced the launch of a grant and Request for Proposal (RFP) program. According to him, these initiatives will provide interested individuals and organizations opportunities to contribute to the Cardano ecosystem by developing tools, infrastructure, and voting accountability mechanisms. He noted that these programs&#8217; details will be unveiled in June and July.</p>



<p>In addition, the crypto guru revealed that Cardano is collaborating with the University of Edinburgh&#8217;s decentralization index lab to measure the project&#8217;s level of decentralization compared to other major cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin and Ethereum. This collaboration aims to showcase Cardano&#8217;s significant progress in decentralization, aligning with the project&#8217;s primary goal of building decentralized protocols.</p>



<p>He also mentioned various other <a href="https://zycrypto.com/cardanos-explosive-network-developments-fuel-speculation-for-1-ada-price-milestone/">ongoing projects</a> within the Cardano ecosystem. These include advancements in peer-to-peer mechanics, signature support, and the development of the Hydra open-source program. According to him, these developments further contribute to Cardano&#8217;s journey towards unrivalled decentralization.</p>



<p><em>&nbsp;“My belief is that we&#8217;ll actually be substantially more decentralized than all cryptocurrencies on Market which is one of the primary goals of these types of protocols,”</em> he added.</p>



<p>Notably, Charles Hoskinson once again stressed the significance of focusing on moving forward even when facing criticism from others in the industry. That said, as Cardano prepares to enter the age of Voltaire, the network can anticipate a surge of projects and people joining, which will positively impact its overall growth and that of ADA, its native token.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/hoskinson-cardano-to-achieve-unrivaled-decentralization-in-crypto-after-major-project-developments/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>VISA Explores the Potential of Smart Contracts for Payments with Ethereum</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/visa-explores-the-potential-of-smart-contracts-for-payments-with-ethereum/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/visa-explores-the-potential-of-smart-contracts-for-payments-with-ethereum/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Newton Gitonga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 16:58:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=81405</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/Visa-Looking-to-Enable-the-Purchase-of-Bitcoin-on-its-Credentials-Says-CEO-Al-Kelly.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Visa Looking to Enable the Purchase of Bitcoin on its Credentials, Says CEO Al Kelly" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/Visa-Looking-to-Enable-the-Purchase-of-Bitcoin-on-its-Credentials-Says-CEO-Al-Kelly.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/Visa-Looking-to-Enable-the-Purchase-of-Bitcoin-on-its-Credentials-Says-CEO-Al-Kelly-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/Visa-Looking-to-Enable-the-Purchase-of-Bitcoin-on-its-Credentials-Says-CEO-Al-Kelly-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/Visa-Looking-to-Enable-the-Purchase-of-Bitcoin-on-its-Credentials-Says-CEO-Al-Kelly-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>Global financial services behemoth VISA recently shared a range of significant milestones in its ongoing pursuit of digital asset payments and seamless crypto onboarding. In a blog titled &#8220;Rethinking Digital Transactions with Account Abstraction” earlier this week, the firm disclosed it is now exploring how gas fees can be redesigned using Account Abstraction on the [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/Visa-Looking-to-Enable-the-Purchase-of-Bitcoin-on-its-Credentials-Says-CEO-Al-Kelly.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Visa Looking to Enable the Purchase of Bitcoin on its Credentials, Says CEO Al Kelly" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/Visa-Looking-to-Enable-the-Purchase-of-Bitcoin-on-its-Credentials-Says-CEO-Al-Kelly.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/Visa-Looking-to-Enable-the-Purchase-of-Bitcoin-on-its-Credentials-Says-CEO-Al-Kelly-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/Visa-Looking-to-Enable-the-Purchase-of-Bitcoin-on-its-Credentials-Says-CEO-Al-Kelly-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/Visa-Looking-to-Enable-the-Purchase-of-Bitcoin-on-its-Credentials-Says-CEO-Al-Kelly-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>Global financial services behemoth VISA recently shared a range of significant milestones in its ongoing pursuit of digital asset payments and seamless crypto onboarding.</p>



<p>In a <a href="https://usa.visa.com/solutions/crypto/rethink-digital-transactions-with-account-abstraction.html">blog</a> titled &#8220;Rethinking Digital Transactions with Account Abstraction” earlier this week, the firm disclosed it is now exploring how gas fees can be redesigned using Account Abstraction on the Ethereum blockchain, enabling secure and automatic payments for self-custodial wallets. It then added that it is deeply engaged in studying Ethereum&#8217;s proposal ERC-4337 for digital payments.</p>



<p>Rolled out on the Ethereum mainnet in early March, ERC-4337 is a key component of VISA’s exploration, as it adds the ability for smart contracts to transact on behalf of the user.</p>



<p>The firm also noted that it has successfully deployed two sets of Paymaster contracts on the Ethereum Goerli testnet, a move aimed at showcasing the potential for redesigning gas fees on the blockchain to improve user convenience. Mustafa Bedawala of Visa’s crypto department <a href="https://twitter.com/digitalmustafa/status/1658710491613761536">observed</a> that the firm’s first paymaster contract is focused on investigating whether users can pay transaction fees with alternative tokens, like dollar stablecoins or, potentially, CBDCs apart from ETH.</p>



<p><em>“To transact on the Ethereum blockchain today, a user needs to acquire ETH to pay for gas fees; similarly, to transact on Polygon blockchain, a user needs to acquire the native token MATIC. Is there a solution that eliminates the need to accumulate a different range of native blockchain tokens solely for the purpose of paying for gas?</em>” wrote Visa.</p>



<p>The other paymaster contract is aimed at completely covering gas fees for user transactions, addressing a major pain point in the crypto space.</p>



<p><em>“Account Abstraction offers a solution by allowing users to bypass these costs if a third party, such as a fintech wallet provider, is willing to cover them. In this case, the wallet provider or dApps can act as Paymasters, covering gas fees for users and significantly reducing friction. The ERC-4337 Paymaster concept can be a potential way to incentivize user adoption by making it free for users to transact through their wallet platform,” </em>the firm added.</p>



<p>Ethereum co-founder Vitalik Buterin has previously expressed his longstanding interest in gas fees Account Abstraction, calling it a dream of the Ethereum developer community. Buterin recommends the use of social recovery wallets and multi-signature wallets for crypto investors to achieve self-custody of their assets.</p>



<p>Thus, with the imminent implementation of ERC-4337 and the emergence of smart contract wallets, wallet security, as well as payments, are expected to improve significantly for VISA users opening doors to <a href="https://zycrypto.com/visa-wants-to-create-an-ecosystem-to-make-crypto-more-accessible-like-other-currencies/">wider adoption</a> of cryptocurrencies.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/visa-explores-the-potential-of-smart-contracts-for-payments-with-ethereum/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance Assists US Law Enforcement in Seizing $4.4M Linked to North Korean Organized Crime, Freezes Accounts</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/binance-assists-us-law-enforcement-in-seizing-4-4m-linked-to-north-korean-organized-crime-freezes-accounts/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/binance-assists-us-law-enforcement-in-seizing-4-4m-linked-to-north-korean-organized-crime-freezes-accounts/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Newton Gitonga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 16:46:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=81403</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Binance-Introduces-Crypto-Tax-Calculator-for-Users-in-Canada-and-France-BNB-up-7.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Binance Introduces Crypto Tax Calculator for Users in Canada and France, BNB up 7%" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Binance-Introduces-Crypto-Tax-Calculator-for-Users-in-Canada-and-France-BNB-up-7.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Binance-Introduces-Crypto-Tax-Calculator-for-Users-in-Canada-and-France-BNB-up-7-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Binance-Introduces-Crypto-Tax-Calculator-for-Users-in-Canada-and-France-BNB-up-7-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Binance-Introduces-Crypto-Tax-Calculator-for-Users-in-Canada-and-France-BNB-up-7-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>In the latest development in the fight against cybercrime, Binance, the world&#8217;s leading cryptocurrency exchange, has collaborated with US law enforcement to seize $4.4 million and freeze accounts connected to North Korean organized crime. On Wednesday, May 24, Binance took to Twitter to express its fulfilment in its collaboration with US law enforcement agencies, highlighting [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Binance-Introduces-Crypto-Tax-Calculator-for-Users-in-Canada-and-France-BNB-up-7.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Binance Introduces Crypto Tax Calculator for Users in Canada and France, BNB up 7%" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Binance-Introduces-Crypto-Tax-Calculator-for-Users-in-Canada-and-France-BNB-up-7.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Binance-Introduces-Crypto-Tax-Calculator-for-Users-in-Canada-and-France-BNB-up-7-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Binance-Introduces-Crypto-Tax-Calculator-for-Users-in-Canada-and-France-BNB-up-7-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Binance-Introduces-Crypto-Tax-Calculator-for-Users-in-Canada-and-France-BNB-up-7-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>In the latest development in the fight against cybercrime, Binance, the world&#8217;s leading cryptocurrency exchange, has collaborated with US law enforcement to seize $4.4 million and freeze accounts connected to North Korean organized crime.</p>



<p>On Wednesday, May 24, Binance took to Twitter to express its fulfilment in its collaboration with US law enforcement agencies, highlighting the crucial role played by its investigations team in uncovering and taking action against North Korean criminal entities.</p>



<p><em>“We are proud to have assisted US law enforcement in seizing $4.4M and freezing accounts linked to North Korean organized crime,” the </em>exchange <a href="https://twitter.com/binance/status/1661474788370690049">wrote</a>.</p>



<p><em>“We proactively took action against accounts connected to these individuals over a year ago, in compliance with lawfully served warrants and in collaboration with law enforcement,” </em>it added.</p>



<p>Binance’s statement follows a Tuesday announcement by the US Department of the Treasury&#8217;s Office of Foreign Assets Control (OFAC) that it had sanctioned five entities involved in malicious cyber activities supporting the Democratic People&#8217;s Republic of Korea (DPRK).</p>



<p><em>“The DPRK conducts malicious cyber activities and deploys information technology (IT), workers who fraudulently obtain employment to generate revenue, including in virtual currency, to support the Kim regime and its priorities, such as its unlawful weapons of mass destruction and ballistic missile programs</em>,” wrote OFAC.</p>



<p>As previously reported, the DPRK has been engaging in cyber activities worldwide, primarily aimed at stealing funds to support its <a href="https://zycrypto.com/north-korea-is-stealing-your-crypto-to-fund-its-ballistic-missile-program-un-report/">illicit programs</a>. According to the OFAC, the Pyongyang University of Automation, recognized as one of the DPRK&#8217;s top cyber training institutions, has been responsible for nurturing malicious cyber actors, many of whom operate under the Reconnaissance General Bureau (RGB), the primary intelligence agency behind the DPRK&#8217;s cyber operations.</p>



<p>The RGB, a controlled entity of the North Korean government and previously sanctioned by OFAC, oversees the activities of several cybercriminal groups, including the <a href="https://zycrypto.com/norway-recovers-5-9-million-out-of-axie-infinity-loot-from-notorious-lazarus-group/">Lazarus Group</a> which is responsible for several significant cryptocurrency heists in 2022. In March 2023, a UN Panel of Experts revealed in a report that DPRK cyber actors stole a record amount of virtual currency in 2022, surpassing previous years.</p>



<p>That said, while this is not the first time Binance has collaborated with US law enforcement in combating cybercrime, the US government has remained tight-lipped on such claims, perhaps due to its restrained relationship with the exchange. In January and February, the exchange <a href="https://zycrypto.com/binance-and-huobi-freeze-funds-linked-to-100m-harmony-one-hack-124-btc-recovered/">announced</a> the freezing of more than $100 million linked to the Harmony One hack last year in collaboration with Huobi. </p>



<p>Despite the lack of proper recognition, Binance reaffirmed its commitment to promoting a safe and secure environment for cryptocurrency transactions, noting that it will continue to “work closely with authorities around the world every day to help prevent crimes and take action against bad actors.”</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/binance-assists-us-law-enforcement-in-seizing-4-4m-linked-to-north-korean-organized-crime-freezes-accounts/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Exchange Inflows Tap 6-Year Low as Investors Take Flight to Self-Custody</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/bitcoin-exchange-inflows-tap-6-year-low-as-investors-take-flight-to-self-custody/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/bitcoin-exchange-inflows-tap-6-year-low-as-investors-take-flight-to-self-custody/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Newton Gitonga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 16:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XBTUSD]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=81397</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-Predicted-To-Soar-Past-35000-By-Summer-As-Wallets-Holding-At-Least-1-BTC-Hits-The-1-Million-Mark.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Bitcoin Predicted To Soar Past $35,000 By Summer As Wallets Holding At Least 1 BTC Hits The 1 Million Mark" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-Predicted-To-Soar-Past-35000-By-Summer-As-Wallets-Holding-At-Least-1-BTC-Hits-The-1-Million-Mark.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-Predicted-To-Soar-Past-35000-By-Summer-As-Wallets-Holding-At-Least-1-BTC-Hits-The-1-Million-Mark-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-Predicted-To-Soar-Past-35000-By-Summer-As-Wallets-Holding-At-Least-1-BTC-Hits-The-1-Million-Mark-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-Predicted-To-Soar-Past-35000-By-Summer-As-Wallets-Holding-At-Least-1-BTC-Hits-The-1-Million-Mark-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>It has been a relatively stable week for Bitcoin, with the leading cryptocurrency by market capitalization witnessing minimal fluctuations in its price. ]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-Predicted-To-Soar-Past-35000-By-Summer-As-Wallets-Holding-At-Least-1-BTC-Hits-The-1-Million-Mark.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Bitcoin Predicted To Soar Past $35,000 By Summer As Wallets Holding At Least 1 BTC Hits The 1 Million Mark" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-Predicted-To-Soar-Past-35000-By-Summer-As-Wallets-Holding-At-Least-1-BTC-Hits-The-1-Million-Mark.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-Predicted-To-Soar-Past-35000-By-Summer-As-Wallets-Holding-At-Least-1-BTC-Hits-The-1-Million-Mark-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-Predicted-To-Soar-Past-35000-By-Summer-As-Wallets-Holding-At-Least-1-BTC-Hits-The-1-Million-Mark-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-Predicted-To-Soar-Past-35000-By-Summer-As-Wallets-Holding-At-Least-1-BTC-Hits-The-1-Million-Mark-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>It has been a relatively stable week for Bitcoin, with the leading cryptocurrency by market capitalization witnessing minimal fluctuations in its price.&nbsp;</p>



<p>Bitcoin saw its largest red day on Wednesday after dropping around 3% amid worries over US debt uncertainties and President <a href="https://zycrypto.com/joe-biden-slams-wealthy-crypto-traders-what-you-need-to-know-on-the-presidents-anti-bitcoin-stance/">Biden’s stance</a> against tax waivers for crypto traders. However, the price managed to regain ground late Thursday after a brief dip to $25,995, pushing past the key resistance level of $26,000 and closing at $26,500.</p>



<p>Overall, while the price has not moved much since mid-May, a key metric exchange metric has emerged, allowing investors to gauge potential shifts within a price range that has held over the past two or so weeks.</p>



<p>On Thursday, May 25, Tomáš Hančar, an analyst at on-chain analytics firm Cryptoquant highlighted that <a href="https://zycrypto.com/key-bitcoin-metric-reaches-crucial-support-level-can-price-pull-a-2021-like-rally/">Bitcoin</a> had seen a significant drop in exchange inflows, reaching a six-year low. According to the pundit, the trend, which began in early May 2023, has continued at a rapid pace, with the current levels not witnessed since mid-January 2017.</p>



<p>&#8220;<em>Exchange depositing transactions have been breaking historical lows since early May &#8217;23,”</em> the pundit wrote.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="409" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-28-1024x409.png" alt="" class="wp-image-81398" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-28-1024x409.png 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-28-300x120.png 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-28-768x307.png 768w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-28.png 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>One potential reason for this shift has been the lingering distrust among speculators and investors following the FTX controversy. According to the pundit, the fallout from the FTX revelation as an actual Ponzi scheme has led to a &#8220;flight to safety&#8221; in the form of self-custody. As a result, many individuals have been opting for self-storage as the preferred method for long-term asset preservation.</p>



<p>“<em>The message of &#8220;not your keys, not your coins&#8221; has simply been getting traction,”</em> he added.</p>



<p>Furthermore, the analyst also pointed out a delay in new investors entering the market, whom he referred to as &#8220;tourists.&#8221; These individuals have yet to recognize the potential of the current upward market trend. According to him, these investors are unaware of the opportunities because they are not keeping up with the current market conditions. For this reason, he noted that it may take a few more weeks or even months for them to realize that the “<em>bull market has basically been in its early phase since the FTX capitulation candle back in early Nov last year.”</em></p>



<p>That said, while the decline in exchange depositing transactions could indicate the early signs of a new bull market, Tomáš Hančar emphasized the need to consider other on-chain indicators. Notably, the overall network activity, the rising number of wallets, including the general downward trend of miners to exchange flow support this hypothesis.</p>



<p>Meanwhile, as the cryptocurrency market continues to evolve, investors&#8217; growing inclination towards self-custody for assets such as Bitcoin demonstrates a desire for greater control and security and is positive for Bitcoin&#8217;s price.</p>



<p>At press time on Friday, Bitcoin was trading at $26,829, up 2.21% in the past 24 hours. In the past week, the cryptocurrency has lost a mere 1.56%, according to CoinMarketCap data.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/bitcoin-exchange-inflows-tap-6-year-low-as-investors-take-flight-to-self-custody/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>South Korea Passes Law Requiring Disclosure of Cryptocurrency Holdings by Officials</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/south-korea-passes-law-requiring-disclosure-of-cryptocurrency-holdings-by-officials/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/south-korea-passes-law-requiring-disclosure-of-cryptocurrency-holdings-by-officials/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Marco Tulio]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 10:29:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[South Korea]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=81394</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/04/South-Korea’s-Central-Bank-Initiates-Pilot-Scheme-For-Trialing-Digital-Won.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="South Korea’s Central Bank Initiates Pilot Scheme For Trialing Digital Won" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/04/South-Korea’s-Central-Bank-Initiates-Pilot-Scheme-For-Trialing-Digital-Won.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/04/South-Korea’s-Central-Bank-Initiates-Pilot-Scheme-For-Trialing-Digital-Won-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/04/South-Korea’s-Central-Bank-Initiates-Pilot-Scheme-For-Trialing-Digital-Won-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/04/South-Korea’s-Central-Bank-Initiates-Pilot-Scheme-For-Trialing-Digital-Won-768x448.jpg 768w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/04/South-Korea’s-Central-Bank-Initiates-Pilot-Scheme-For-Trialing-Digital-Won-610x356.jpg 610w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>On May 25, the South Korean National Assembly passed the "Kim Nam Guk Prevention Law," which requires legislators and high-ranking government officials to disclose their cryptocurrency holdings.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/04/South-Korea’s-Central-Bank-Initiates-Pilot-Scheme-For-Trialing-Digital-Won.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="South Korea’s Central Bank Initiates Pilot Scheme For Trialing Digital Won" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/04/South-Korea’s-Central-Bank-Initiates-Pilot-Scheme-For-Trialing-Digital-Won.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/04/South-Korea’s-Central-Bank-Initiates-Pilot-Scheme-For-Trialing-Digital-Won-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/04/South-Korea’s-Central-Bank-Initiates-Pilot-Scheme-For-Trialing-Digital-Won-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/04/South-Korea’s-Central-Bank-Initiates-Pilot-Scheme-For-Trialing-Digital-Won-768x448.jpg 768w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/04/South-Korea’s-Central-Bank-Initiates-Pilot-Scheme-For-Trialing-Digital-Won-610x356.jpg 610w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>On May 25, the South Korean National Assembly passed the &#8220;Kim Nam Guk Prevention Law,&#8221; which requires legislators and high-ranking government officials to disclose their cryptocurrency holdings.</p>



<p>According to <a href="https://www.news1.kr/articles/5058538">News1</a>, the amendments to the National Assembly Law were approved with broad support, ensuring that cryptocurrencies are included in the legislators&#8217; register of private interests.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-the-new-law-aims-to-promote-transparency-and-prevent-abuses-of-authority"><strong>The new law aims to promote transparency and prevent abuses of authority</strong></h2>



<p>This new law aims to promote integrity and transparency in the government by addressing concerns about the potential misuse of cryptocurrencies by lawmakers and public officials.</p>



<p>Furthermore, the Public Officials Ethics Act amendment also mandates high-ranking public officials, including legislators, to register their cryptocurrency assets.</p>



<p>These measures were taken in response to suspicions and controversies surrounding Representative Kim Nam Guk, a member of the Democratic Party, who was accused of owning cryptocurrencies valued at up to 6 billion won (over $4.5 million). This raised concerns about possible conflicts of interest and insider trading activities.</p>



<p>Leaders from different political parties, including the People Power Party and the Democratic Party of Korea, expressed agreement on the need to pass this law during a meeting with the Speaker of the National Assembly.</p>



<p>Therefore, it is expected that with the approval of this law, transparency regarding the cryptocurrency holdings of public officials will become a reality in South Korea, strengthening public trust in institutions while enhancing cryptocurrency regulation.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>South Korea continues to make progress in cryptocurrency regulation</strong></h2>



<p>In April 2023, the South Korean National Assembly passed the cryptocurrency regulation bill, overcoming the most significant initial obstacle before becoming law.</p>



<p>Hwang Suk-jin, a Special Committee on Digital Assets of the People Power Party member, stated that following the National Assembly&#8217;s approval, he expects it to become law in the first half of the year. It only requires approval from the legislative and judicial committees.</p>



<p>The bill requires cryptocurrency <a href="https://zycrypto.com/south-koreas-aml-watchdog-goes-after-16-crypto-exchanges-operating-without-registration/">service providers</a> to keep users&#8217; funds separate and secure, avoiding mixing them with their own funds. This has been a controversial issue that several countries are including in their regulations following the <a href="https://zycrypto.com/revealed-sam-bankman-fried-secretly-loaned-crypto-news-site-the-block-and-its-ceo-43-million/">alleged embezzlement</a> by <a href="https://zycrypto.com/binance-ceo-cz-calls-sam-bankman-fried-a-fraudster-reveals-the-real-reason-behind-ftx-crash/">Sam Bank-Fried</a> at the now-bankrupt exchange, FTX.</p>



<p>Likewise, the bill establishes penalties such as imprisonment and fines up to five times the illicit gains for those who fail to comply with the new regulations. Additionally, courts could impose maximum sentences such as life imprisonment in cases where reported losses to victims exceed $3.73 million.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/south-korea-passes-law-requiring-disclosure-of-cryptocurrency-holdings-by-officials/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Circle Launches Euro Coin on Avalanche: Expanding Stablecoin Support Beyond Ethereum</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/circle-launches-euro-coin-on-avalanche-expanding-stablecoin-support-beyond-ethereum/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/circle-launches-euro-coin-on-avalanche-expanding-stablecoin-support-beyond-ethereum/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aaron Feuerstein]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 10:04:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Avalanche]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Circle]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=81385</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Circle-Launches-Euro-Coin-on-Avalanche-Expanding-Stablecoin-Support-Beyond-Ethereum.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Circle Launches Euro Coin on Avalanche: Expanding Stablecoin Support Beyond Ethereum" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Circle-Launches-Euro-Coin-on-Avalanche-Expanding-Stablecoin-Support-Beyond-Ethereum.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Circle-Launches-Euro-Coin-on-Avalanche-Expanding-Stablecoin-Support-Beyond-Ethereum-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Circle-Launches-Euro-Coin-on-Avalanche-Expanding-Stablecoin-Support-Beyond-Ethereum-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Circle-Launches-Euro-Coin-on-Avalanche-Expanding-Stablecoin-Support-Beyond-Ethereum-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>Circle, a well-known stablecoin issuer, has released the Euro Coin on the Avalanche network, marking a huge extension beyond its Ethereum basis, in a bold move intended to increase stablecoin accessibility.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Circle-Launches-Euro-Coin-on-Avalanche-Expanding-Stablecoin-Support-Beyond-Ethereum.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Circle Launches Euro Coin on Avalanche: Expanding Stablecoin Support Beyond Ethereum" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Circle-Launches-Euro-Coin-on-Avalanche-Expanding-Stablecoin-Support-Beyond-Ethereum.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Circle-Launches-Euro-Coin-on-Avalanche-Expanding-Stablecoin-Support-Beyond-Ethereum-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Circle-Launches-Euro-Coin-on-Avalanche-Expanding-Stablecoin-Support-Beyond-Ethereum-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Circle-Launches-Euro-Coin-on-Avalanche-Expanding-Stablecoin-Support-Beyond-Ethereum-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>Circle, a well-known stablecoin issuer, has released the Euro Coin on the <a href="https://zycrypto.com/circle-rolls-out-usdc-cross-chain-transfer-protocol-for-ethereum-and-avalanche-networks/">Avalanche network</a>, marking a huge extension beyond its Ethereum basis, in a bold move intended to increase stablecoin accessibility.</p>



<p>Circle hopes to develop a multi-chain presence for its Euro Coin by utilising the Avalanche blockchain, giving consumers more alternatives and boosting the stablecoin&#8217;s acceptance. The selection of Avalanche, a platform renowned for its scalability and low transaction costs, demonstrates Circle&#8217;s drive to innovation and its commitment to offering customers a wide variety of options.</p>



<p>The partnership between Circle and Avalanche is an important point in the evolution of stablecoin ecosystems. The technical team at Circle worked closely with Avalanche to make sure that the Euro Coin was integrated into the new blockchain without any issues. The safe connection between the Avalanche blockchain and the Euro Coin allows for quick transactions while preserving the usefulness and stability of the digital asset.</p>



<p>The cryptocurrency community has paid close attention to the introduction of the Euro Coin on Avalanche. This action not only solidifies Circle&#8217;s position as a market leader in stablecoins but also demonstrates its commitment to going beyond Ethereum.</p>



<p>In a press release, Joao Reginatto, VP of Product at Circle, stated: “By launching Euro Coin on Avalanche’s fast and efficient platform, we can help developers and their users experience near-instant, more cost-effective financial transactions and unlock new possibilities for payments, remittances and 24/7 FX.”</p>



<p>As a result of its expansion onto Avalanche, Circle now has access to the fast-expanding Avalanche ecosystem, enabling strategic alliances with ongoing initiatives and encouraging fresh partnerships. The Euro Coin is widely accepted inside the Avalanche network and is interoperable, positioning it as a reliable medium of trade and piquing interest from both businesses and investors.</p>



<p>Other stablecoin issuers will be inspired to venture beyond their initial blockchain foundations by Circle&#8217;s ground-breaking action, which serves as a model for others. The introduction of the Euro Coin on Avalanche highlights the sector&#8217;s dedication to innovation and blockchain compatibility.</p>



<p>The development of the Euro Coin on the Avalanche network sets the path for a more durable and connected future for stablecoins. With more options for users and a drive towards a multi-chain ecosystem, this development pushes the limits of stablecoin acceptance.</p>



<p>With increasing collaboration, innovation, and more opportunities within the cryptocurrency environment, Circle&#8217;s Euro Coin on Avalanche represents a significant development in the stablecoin market. This revelation reverberates as evidence of the persistent pursuit of advancement within the digital asset space, where limitations are persistently pushed to create a more inclusive and stable financial ecosystem.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/circle-launches-euro-coin-on-avalanche-expanding-stablecoin-support-beyond-ethereum/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>XRP Lawsuit: Ripple Boss Confident Groundbreaking Verdict Is Coming ‘In Weeks’ After Hinman Speech Docs Win</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/xrp-lawsuit-ripple-boss-confident-groundbreaking-verdict-is-coming-in-weeks-after-hinman-speech-docs-win/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/xrp-lawsuit-ripple-boss-confident-groundbreaking-verdict-is-coming-in-weeks-after-hinman-speech-docs-win/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Brenda Ngari]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 20:24:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=81355</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Garlinghouse-Reveals-Ripple-Will-Spend-200M-Defending-Itself-Against-The-SEC-Even-As-Case-Worries-XRP-Holders.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Garlinghouse Reveals Ripple Will Spend $200M Defending Itself Against The SEC Even As Case Worries XRP Holders" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Garlinghouse-Reveals-Ripple-Will-Spend-200M-Defending-Itself-Against-The-SEC-Even-As-Case-Worries-XRP-Holders.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Garlinghouse-Reveals-Ripple-Will-Spend-200M-Defending-Itself-Against-The-SEC-Even-As-Case-Worries-XRP-Holders-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Garlinghouse-Reveals-Ripple-Will-Spend-200M-Defending-Itself-Against-The-SEC-Even-As-Case-Worries-XRP-Holders-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Garlinghouse-Reveals-Ripple-Will-Spend-200M-Defending-Itself-Against-The-SEC-Even-As-Case-Worries-XRP-Holders-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>Garlinghouse expects a verdict in weeks and not months after the recent court news concerning the Hinman documents.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Garlinghouse-Reveals-Ripple-Will-Spend-200M-Defending-Itself-Against-The-SEC-Even-As-Case-Worries-XRP-Holders.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Garlinghouse Reveals Ripple Will Spend $200M Defending Itself Against The SEC Even As Case Worries XRP Holders" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Garlinghouse-Reveals-Ripple-Will-Spend-200M-Defending-Itself-Against-The-SEC-Even-As-Case-Worries-XRP-Holders.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Garlinghouse-Reveals-Ripple-Will-Spend-200M-Defending-Itself-Against-The-SEC-Even-As-Case-Worries-XRP-Holders-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Garlinghouse-Reveals-Ripple-Will-Spend-200M-Defending-Itself-Against-The-SEC-Even-As-Case-Worries-XRP-Holders-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Garlinghouse-Reveals-Ripple-Will-Spend-200M-Defending-Itself-Against-The-SEC-Even-As-Case-Worries-XRP-Holders-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>Ripple chief executive officer Brad Garlinghouse believes a ruling in its costly lawsuit with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) is coming soon. Garlinghouse expects a verdict in weeks and not months after the recent court news concerning the Hinman documents.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-xrp-suit-could-be-over-sooner-than-you-think"><strong>XRP Suit Could Be Over Sooner Than You Think</strong></h2>



<p>Bradley Garlinghouse has hinted that a court case resolution is coming immediately after the release of the infamous William Hinman materials.</p>



<p>In a recent <a href="https://twitter.com/XRPnewt/status/1661547535062769669">interview </a>at Redefine Tomorrow 2023 summit, Garlinghouse revealed that in terms of where things currently stand in the courtroom war with the SEC, he is confident of getting a decision in the coming weeks.&nbsp;</p>



<p>The Ripple CEO pointed to the recent court ruling where the SEC’s motion to keep Hinman documents under wraps was rejected by a federal judge.</p>



<p>Back in 2021, Ripple cited the landmark Hinman speech as an indication that the SEC does not deem Bitcoin or Ethereum as a security, contending that XRP should not be classified as a security either. The crypto payments firm then<a href="https://twitter.com/s_alderoty/status/1355212300861513728"> filed for Freedom of Information Act request</a> which would uncover docs explaining how Hinman came to this conclusion.</p>



<p>At the time, the SEC responded by claiming Hinman&#8217;s speech represented his personal opinions and not the agency’s policy. To that end, the SEC wanted to shield the documents relating to this speech from the public eye while also arguing that the materials are protected by a statute that grants privacy for internal deliberations. </p>



<p>But as <em>ZyCrypto </em><a href="https://zycrypto.com/groundbreaking-ripple-win-in-xrp-case-looking-likely-as-court-rejects-secs-request-to-keep-hinman-docs-hidden/">reported </a>recently, the court believes that these speech drafts and emails are judicial documents and should be made public. The move was viewed as a key win for Ripple, which believes that these internal deliberations and discussions are key evidence in its ongoing litigation.&nbsp;</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Hinman Emails To Give Ripple The Upper Hand?</strong></h2>



<p>Commenting on the upcoming unmasking of the Hinman materials, pro-Ripple attorney John E Deaton <a href="https://twitter.com/JohnEDeaton1/status/1660061091525787650">noted</a>:</p>



<p>“I can’t wait for these emails to be released. I predict even non-XRP holders, including Ripple critics, will have to objectively say that what the SEC did is flat-out wrong. The inquiry about the motive behind this lawsuit will go into a higher gear — mark my words.”&nbsp;</p>



<p>Spectators are now waiting for the summary judgment decision after completing all the briefings. Garlinghouse’s comment that he expects a verdict in weeks’ time is being interpreted by some in the XRP community as an indication that he anticipates a favourable decision by the presiding judge.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/xrp-lawsuit-ripple-boss-confident-groundbreaking-verdict-is-coming-in-weeks-after-hinman-speech-docs-win/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Shiba Inu’s Shibarium Triggers Explosive Momentum For ‘$0.001 SHIB’ Price Following Burn Portal Reveal</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/shiba-inus-shibarium-triggers-explosive-momentum-for-0-001-shib-price-following-burn-portal-reveal/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/shiba-inus-shibarium-triggers-explosive-momentum-for-0-001-shib-price-following-burn-portal-reveal/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Newton Gitonga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 18:25:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIB]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIBA INU]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIBUSD]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=81336</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Shiba-Inus-Shibarium-Renews-Bullish-Momentum-For-0.001-SHIB-As-Massive-Token-Burn-Expected.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Shiba Inu&#039;s Shibarium Renews Bullish Momentum For &#039;$0.001 SHIB&#039; As Massive Token Burn Expected" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Shiba-Inus-Shibarium-Renews-Bullish-Momentum-For-0.001-SHIB-As-Massive-Token-Burn-Expected.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Shiba-Inus-Shibarium-Renews-Bullish-Momentum-For-0.001-SHIB-As-Massive-Token-Burn-Expected-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Shiba-Inus-Shibarium-Renews-Bullish-Momentum-For-0.001-SHIB-As-Massive-Token-Burn-Expected-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Shiba-Inus-Shibarium-Renews-Bullish-Momentum-For-0.001-SHIB-As-Massive-Token-Burn-Expected-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>The Shiba Inu (SHIB) community has been buzzing with excitement following the leak of the SHIB burn portal on Shibarium, the ecosystem's upcoming layer-2 network.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Shiba-Inus-Shibarium-Renews-Bullish-Momentum-For-0.001-SHIB-As-Massive-Token-Burn-Expected.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Shiba Inu&#039;s Shibarium Renews Bullish Momentum For &#039;$0.001 SHIB&#039; As Massive Token Burn Expected" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Shiba-Inus-Shibarium-Renews-Bullish-Momentum-For-0.001-SHIB-As-Massive-Token-Burn-Expected.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Shiba-Inus-Shibarium-Renews-Bullish-Momentum-For-0.001-SHIB-As-Massive-Token-Burn-Expected-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Shiba-Inus-Shibarium-Renews-Bullish-Momentum-For-0.001-SHIB-As-Massive-Token-Burn-Expected-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Shiba-Inus-Shibarium-Renews-Bullish-Momentum-For-0.001-SHIB-As-Massive-Token-Burn-Expected-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>The Shiba Inu (SHIB) community has been buzzing with excitement following the leak of the SHIB burn portal on Shibarium, the ecosystem&#8217;s upcoming layer-2 network.</p>



<p>On Sunday, May 21, the pseudonymous Twitter user “SHIB INFORMER” shared a preview of the user interface of the burn mechanism in Shibarium, giving the Shib army a glimpse into what&#8217;s to come.</p>



<p>According to the leaked information, the burn portal&#8217;s interface suggests that <a href="https://zycrypto.com/0-001-shiba-inu-price-beckons-as-shibarium-launch-proves-to-be-a-game-changer-for-shib/">Shibarium</a> will facilitate swapping accumulated BONE tokens for Shiba Inu (SHIB) tokens, which will then be sent to the burn address. This aligns with the original concept of charging transaction fees in BONE tokens. Notably, these fees will be accumulated until a certain threshold is reached, at which point any user will be able to initiate the burn transaction.</p>



<p><em>“The transaction fees destined to burn will be accumulated up to a certain amount and then the Burn will be triggered. My current understanding is that anyone will be able to trigger it after the threshold is reached,”</em> tweeted SHIB INFORMER, sharing the image below.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="747" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-27-1024x747.png" alt="" class="wp-image-81328" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-27-1024x747.png 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-27-300x219.png 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-27-768x560.png 768w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-27-324x235.png 324w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-27.png 1080w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>It&#8217;s important to note that the burn process will be manual rather than automatic. Users will play an essential role in triggering the burn transaction once the accumulated threshold is met. The leaked interface is currently in the alpha testing stage, indicating changes may occur before the public <a href="https://zycrypto.com/0-001-shib-price-beckons-as-shiba-inus-shibarium-public-beta-finally-set-to-go-live-this-week/">beta phase</a>.</p>



<p>The burning mechanism aims to support the burning campaign of SHIB tokens. According to documentation by the Shiba Inu team, Shibarium plans to burn 70% of its base transaction fees in SHIB, with the remaining 30% allocated to network maintenance. This approach is expected to significantly impact the token&#8217;s supply, which is theoretically expected to boost SHIB’s value to the much-coveted $0.001 price point.</p>



<p>Meanwhile, LucieSHIB, a content marketing specialist within the Shiba ecosystem, acknowledged the authenticity of the leaked images and clarified that they represent the alpha version of the mechanism, with the possibility of changes being implemented upon its official launch.&nbsp;</p>



<p>“<em>Note that it is only the alpha version (not beta yet), So the final version may be different, but it&#8217;s good for a look. BONE will convert to SHIB and burn SHIB,”</em> tweeted Lucie, adding, “<em>Each transaction will add to the burn pool. Then anyone will be able to trigger the burn.”</em></p>



<p>Notably, as the Shibarium team continues to make significant developments ahead of its official release, whales have begun accumulating SHIB tokens in the hope that Shibarium&#8217;s developments have the potential to make a significant impact on the token&#8217;s price. According to data from IntoTheBlock, whales have amassed over 26 trillion SHIB tokens in the past week.</p>



<p>That said, the notable progress made on Shibarium has been a boon for the SHIB token, which was trading at $0.000008459 at press time, down 0.49%&nbsp;over the past last 24 hours, according to CoinMarketCap data.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/shiba-inus-shibarium-triggers-explosive-momentum-for-0-001-shib-price-following-burn-portal-reveal/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Huobi Ordered To Suspend Operations In Malaysia In Latest Crypto Hit</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/huobi-ordered-to-suspend-operations-in-malaysia-in-latest-crypto-hit/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/huobi-ordered-to-suspend-operations-in-malaysia-in-latest-crypto-hit/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Brenda Ngari]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 18:18:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[HUOBI]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[malaysia]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=81330</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Bankman-Fried-And-Justin-Sun-Reportedly-Eyeing-Purchase-Of-Majority-Stake-In-Crypto-Exchange-Giant-Huobi.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Bankman-Fried And Justin Sun Reportedly Eyeing Purchase Of Majority Stake In Crypto Exchange Giant Huobi" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Bankman-Fried-And-Justin-Sun-Reportedly-Eyeing-Purchase-Of-Majority-Stake-In-Crypto-Exchange-Giant-Huobi.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Bankman-Fried-And-Justin-Sun-Reportedly-Eyeing-Purchase-Of-Majority-Stake-In-Crypto-Exchange-Giant-Huobi-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Bankman-Fried-And-Justin-Sun-Reportedly-Eyeing-Purchase-Of-Majority-Stake-In-Crypto-Exchange-Giant-Huobi-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Bankman-Fried-And-Justin-Sun-Reportedly-Eyeing-Purchase-Of-Majority-Stake-In-Crypto-Exchange-Giant-Huobi-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>On Monday, the Malaysian Securities Commission (SC) ordered Seychelles-headquartered cryptocurrency exchange Huobi Global to cease activities in the country. The regulator said Huobi was operating a digital asset exchange in Malaysia without the appropriate registration. Operating a crypto exchange without a Recognised Market Operator (RMO) license is a crime under the Capital Markets and Services [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Bankman-Fried-And-Justin-Sun-Reportedly-Eyeing-Purchase-Of-Majority-Stake-In-Crypto-Exchange-Giant-Huobi.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Bankman-Fried And Justin Sun Reportedly Eyeing Purchase Of Majority Stake In Crypto Exchange Giant Huobi" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Bankman-Fried-And-Justin-Sun-Reportedly-Eyeing-Purchase-Of-Majority-Stake-In-Crypto-Exchange-Giant-Huobi.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Bankman-Fried-And-Justin-Sun-Reportedly-Eyeing-Purchase-Of-Majority-Stake-In-Crypto-Exchange-Giant-Huobi-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Bankman-Fried-And-Justin-Sun-Reportedly-Eyeing-Purchase-Of-Majority-Stake-In-Crypto-Exchange-Giant-Huobi-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Bankman-Fried-And-Justin-Sun-Reportedly-Eyeing-Purchase-Of-Majority-Stake-In-Crypto-Exchange-Giant-Huobi-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>On Monday, the Malaysian Securities Commission (SC) <a href="https://www.sc.com.my/resources/media/media-release/sc-takes-enforcement-action-against-huobi-global-for-illegally-operating-dax-in-malaysia">ordered </a>Seychelles-headquartered cryptocurrency exchange Huobi Global to cease activities in the country.</p>



<p>The regulator said Huobi was operating a digital asset exchange in Malaysia without the appropriate registration. Operating a crypto exchange without a Recognised Market Operator (RMO) license is a crime under the Capital Markets and Services Act 2007.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-huobi-terminates-crypto-services-in-malaysia"><strong>Huobi Terminates Crypto Services In Malaysia</strong></h2>



<p>The SC has served a public reprimand against one of the largest and most trusted crypto exchanges globally, Huobi, and its founder Leon Li. As the company’s CEO, Li has been mandated to supervise the process of winding down local activities, discontinuing any advertisements to Malaysian investors, disabling the website, and removing the mobile application from app stores.&nbsp;</p>



<p>Huobi&#8217;s Malaysian investors have been urged to withdraw all their investments from the platform and close their accounts.</p>



<p>The SC’s statement says the enforcement action against Huobi was driven by “concerns about the platform’s compliance with local regulatory requirements and protecting investors’ interests.”</p>



<p>Malaysia&#8217;s securities regulator further encouraged citizens to stop trading with cryptocurrency exchanges in the country illegally.</p>



<p>At the press time, the native token of Huobi Global, Huobi Token (HT), is trading hands at $2.95, up by 1.21% in the last 24 hours.&nbsp;</p>



<p>Huobi is presently the fourth-largest crypto exchange in the world by trading volume, according to CoinGecko. The exchange has fallen foul of Malaysia&#8217;s markets regulator in the past. Back in August 2022, the Securities Commission Malaysia warned Huobi of operating without a license and <a href="https://twitter.com/SecComMalaysia/status/1561662707572822017">added </a>it to a list of companies not permitted to operate in the country. At the time, Huobi claimed that it was in talks with Malaysian regulators about its regional operations.</p>



<p>The Malaysian regulator’s action marks the latest blow to the crypto industry, which has been facing regulatory pressure from various countries in the world — most notably the United States. The U.S.’s lack of clarity and regulation by enforcement has spooked many crypto companies and investors, who are already looking to relocate to other friendlier jurisdictions.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/huobi-ordered-to-suspend-operations-in-malaysia-in-latest-crypto-hit/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum Continues System Stability Upgrades Despite Recent Block Finality Incidents</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/ethereum-continues-system-stability-upgrades-despite-recent-block-finality-incidents/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/ethereum-continues-system-stability-upgrades-despite-recent-block-finality-incidents/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Isa Nsereko]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 18:01:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=81327</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Vitalik-Buterin-Uncovers-‘Missing-Link-For-Creating-Transaction-Privacy-on-Ethereum.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Vitalik Buterin Uncovers ‘Missing Link’ For Creating Transaction Privacy on Ethereum" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Vitalik-Buterin-Uncovers-‘Missing-Link-For-Creating-Transaction-Privacy-on-Ethereum.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Vitalik-Buterin-Uncovers-‘Missing-Link-For-Creating-Transaction-Privacy-on-Ethereum-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Vitalik-Buterin-Uncovers-‘Missing-Link-For-Creating-Transaction-Privacy-on-Ethereum-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Vitalik-Buterin-Uncovers-‘Missing-Link-For-Creating-Transaction-Privacy-on-Ethereum-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>The Ethereum protocol recently experienced two incidents in which its Beacon Chain stopped finalizing blocks. This occurred on May 11, 2023, when the network was unable to fully confirm transactions for about 20 minutes and again on May 12, 2023, for over an hour. Generally, block finality refers to a state where a supermajority of [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Vitalik-Buterin-Uncovers-‘Missing-Link-For-Creating-Transaction-Privacy-on-Ethereum.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Vitalik Buterin Uncovers ‘Missing Link’ For Creating Transaction Privacy on Ethereum" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Vitalik-Buterin-Uncovers-‘Missing-Link-For-Creating-Transaction-Privacy-on-Ethereum.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Vitalik-Buterin-Uncovers-‘Missing-Link-For-Creating-Transaction-Privacy-on-Ethereum-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Vitalik-Buterin-Uncovers-‘Missing-Link-For-Creating-Transaction-Privacy-on-Ethereum-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Vitalik-Buterin-Uncovers-‘Missing-Link-For-Creating-Transaction-Privacy-on-Ethereum-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>The Ethereum protocol recently experienced two incidents in which its Beacon Chain stopped finalizing blocks. This occurred on May 11, 2023, when the network was unable to fully confirm transactions for about 20 minutes and again on May 12, 2023, for over an hour.</p>



<p>Generally, block finality refers to a state where a supermajority of validators have attested to the final state of the blockchain, guaranteeing that a block and its processed transactions cannot be modified or eliminated from the blockchain.</p>



<p>Block finality implies that a block of data has been added to a blockchain with some negligible probability of being reversed or altered. Blockchains like Bitcoin and Ethereum show probabilistic transaction finality in that transactions are not automatically or instantly final, but the probability of being reversed decreases as more blocks are added to the chain.</p>



<p>During the two finality incidents, Ethereum end users successfully continued to transact on-chain through the incident. Ethereum Developers released patches to resolve the block finality incidents but said an analysis was underway to determine the root cause of the problem.&nbsp;</p>



<p>In a May 21, 2023 blog, Ethereum co-founder Vitalik Buterin cautioned against overloading Ethereum consensus beyond its core functions of validating blocks and securing the network, as this could bring high systemic risks to the ecosystem. In the same blog, Buterin called for preserving the chain’s minimalism and helping developers find alternate strategies to achieve their security goals.</p>



<p>The Ethereum protocol has undergone several major upgrades and improvement plans to make it more robust and reliable.</p>



<p>In September 2022, the Merge upgrade was implemented. In the Merge, the Ethereum protocol moved from its original proof-of-work mechanism to a proof-of-stake mechanism. The merge aimed to make the Ethereum protocol less energy-intensive, more secure, and better suited to implementing new scaling solutions.</p>



<p>In November 2022, Buterin outlined an updated Ethereum protocol roadmap in line with its vision of enhancing scalability, security, and sustainability. Buterin said that the Ethereum protocol is undergoing several system upgrades and will ultimately enter a state of relative stability that optimizes safety and predictability.</p>



<p>According to Buterin, the Ethereum protocol roadmap consists of six parallel running upgrades: the Merge, the Surge, the Scourge, the Verge, the Purge, and the Splurge.</p>



<p>Another upgrade known as the Ethereum ‘Shapella’ upgrade was implemented in April 2023. The Shapella upgrade enabled stakers to unstake ETH and validators to withdraw previously staked ETH. The Shapella upgrade was implemented with other Ethereum Improvement Proposals, including reducing gas fees during peak network periods.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/ethereum-continues-system-stability-upgrades-despite-recent-block-finality-incidents/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>One Of Ripple’s Defense Lawyers Drops Out Of SEC Lawsuit — Does It Spell Doom For XRP?</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/one-of-ripples-defense-lawyers-drops-out-of-sec-lawsuit-does-it-spell-doom-for-xrp/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/one-of-ripples-defense-lawyers-drops-out-of-sec-lawsuit-does-it-spell-doom-for-xrp/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Brenda Ngari]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 10:26:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=81310</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Legal-Expert-Has-‘No-Doubt-Ripple-Will-Win-Legal-War-Against-SEC-—-Can-It-Supercharge-XRP-To-1.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Legal Expert Has ‘No Doubt’ Ripple Will Win Legal War Against SEC — Can It Supercharge XRP To $1?" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Legal-Expert-Has-‘No-Doubt-Ripple-Will-Win-Legal-War-Against-SEC-—-Can-It-Supercharge-XRP-To-1.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Legal-Expert-Has-‘No-Doubt-Ripple-Will-Win-Legal-War-Against-SEC-—-Can-It-Supercharge-XRP-To-1-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Legal-Expert-Has-‘No-Doubt-Ripple-Will-Win-Legal-War-Against-SEC-—-Can-It-Supercharge-XRP-To-1-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Legal-Expert-Has-‘No-Doubt-Ripple-Will-Win-Legal-War-Against-SEC-—-Can-It-Supercharge-XRP-To-1-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>This departure comes as the XRP community expects a summary judgment ruling any day now.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Legal-Expert-Has-‘No-Doubt-Ripple-Will-Win-Legal-War-Against-SEC-—-Can-It-Supercharge-XRP-To-1.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Legal Expert Has ‘No Doubt’ Ripple Will Win Legal War Against SEC — Can It Supercharge XRP To $1?" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Legal-Expert-Has-‘No-Doubt-Ripple-Will-Win-Legal-War-Against-SEC-—-Can-It-Supercharge-XRP-To-1.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Legal-Expert-Has-‘No-Doubt-Ripple-Will-Win-Legal-War-Against-SEC-—-Can-It-Supercharge-XRP-To-1-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Legal-Expert-Has-‘No-Doubt-Ripple-Will-Win-Legal-War-Against-SEC-—-Can-It-Supercharge-XRP-To-1-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Legal-Expert-Has-‘No-Doubt-Ripple-Will-Win-Legal-War-Against-SEC-—-Can-It-Supercharge-XRP-To-1-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>In a blow to Ripple, one of its attorneys in the long-running legal dispute with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), Kylie Chiseul Kim, has called it quits. This departure comes as the XRP community expects a summary judgment ruling any day now.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-what-does-the-departure-mean-for-the-case"><strong>What Does The Departure Mean For The Case?</strong></h2>



<p>Attorney Kylie Chiseul Kim has left Ripple Lab’s legal team as the case drags on.</p>



<p>According to the letter filed in the Southern District of New York, Kylie noted that she would no longer have any association with Kellogg, Hansen, Todd, Figel &amp; Frederick, P.L.L.C., the law firm presently representing Ripple. The filing indicated that other lawyers from the same law firm and those from Debevoise &amp; Plimpton LLP would continue being counsel for the defendants. Notably, Kylie’s motion was granted by the court.</p>



<p>Kylie has long been a key member of the team representing Ripple since July 2022. She was hired alongside Clayton J. Masterman as Ripple was still battling the 2020 XRP lawsuit with the SEC. The U.S. regulator <a href="https://zycrypto.com/xrp-holders-are-completely-fcked-messari-founder-predicts-drop-to-0-10-as-the-sec-sues-ripple/">accused </a>Ripple, co-founder and former CEO Chris Larsen, and current CEO Brad Garlinghouse of misleading investors by raising over $1.3 billion in unregistered securities offerings of the XRP token. The onboarding of these two attorneys at the time was viewed as a move to bolster Ripple’s legal team for an expected lengthy legal fight.</p>



<p>Kylie’s surprising departure has left many wondering whether it seals Ripple’s fate in the case. There were mixed reactions to the news of her leaving Ripple’s defence team. Nonetheless, the majority believe her exit had nothing to do with Ripple and did not reflect her view of Ripple’s stakes in the lawsuit but was related to her quitting her former law firm.</p>



<p>The departure, nonetheless, comes as the crypto community anxiously awaits the <a href="https://zycrypto.com/groundbreaking-ripple-win-in-xrp-case-looking-likely-as-court-rejects-secs-request-to-keep-hinman-docs-hidden/">unsealing</a> of the “Hinman documents” on June 13. These docs relate to a 2018 speech given by former SEC Director William Hinman and emails associated with writing it. In the speech, Hinman declared that Ether was not a security due to its decentralized nature. These documents are believed to tip the scales in Ripple’s favour as the company endeavours to prove that XRP should not be considered a security.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/one-of-ripples-defense-lawyers-drops-out-of-sec-lawsuit-does-it-spell-doom-for-xrp/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
