<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>News Archives &#8902; ZyCrypto</title>
	<atom:link href="https://zycrypto.com/category/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://zycrypto.com/category/news/</link>
	<description>ZyCrypto Is A Cryptocurrency News Media, Focusing On Daily News, Expert Opinions, Analysis, Reviews, And So Much More.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 21:22:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/cropped-ZyCrypto-Site-Logo-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News Archives &#8902; ZyCrypto</title>
	<link>https://zycrypto.com/category/news/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>SEC To Win An Appeal Against Ripple? Former SEC Official Cautions XRP Celebrations</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/sec-to-win-an-appeal-against-ripple-former-sec-official-cautions-xrp-celebrations/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/sec-to-win-an-appeal-against-ripple-former-sec-official-cautions-xrp-celebrations/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aaron Feuerstein]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 21:22:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=83013</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/06/Ripples-Brad-Garlinghouse-Isnt-Taking-His-Feet-Off-SECs-Neck-Anytime-Soon-For-XRPs-Struggles.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Ripple&#039;s Brad Garlinghouse Isn&#039;t Taking His Feet Off SEC&#039;s Neck Anytime Soon For XRP’s Struggles" decoding="async" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/06/Ripples-Brad-Garlinghouse-Isnt-Taking-His-Feet-Off-SECs-Neck-Anytime-Soon-For-XRPs-Struggles.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/06/Ripples-Brad-Garlinghouse-Isnt-Taking-His-Feet-Off-SECs-Neck-Anytime-Soon-For-XRPs-Struggles-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/06/Ripples-Brad-Garlinghouse-Isnt-Taking-His-Feet-Off-SECs-Neck-Anytime-Soon-For-XRPs-Struggles-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/06/Ripples-Brad-Garlinghouse-Isnt-Taking-His-Feet-Off-SECs-Neck-Anytime-Soon-For-XRPs-Struggles-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>Last week’s highly publicized decision in the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) case against Ripple, touted by many as a significant victory against the SEC and Chairman Gary Gensler, may not be the end of the story.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/06/Ripples-Brad-Garlinghouse-Isnt-Taking-His-Feet-Off-SECs-Neck-Anytime-Soon-For-XRPs-Struggles.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Ripple&#039;s Brad Garlinghouse Isn&#039;t Taking His Feet Off SEC&#039;s Neck Anytime Soon For XRP’s Struggles" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/06/Ripples-Brad-Garlinghouse-Isnt-Taking-His-Feet-Off-SECs-Neck-Anytime-Soon-For-XRPs-Struggles.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/06/Ripples-Brad-Garlinghouse-Isnt-Taking-His-Feet-Off-SECs-Neck-Anytime-Soon-For-XRPs-Struggles-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/06/Ripples-Brad-Garlinghouse-Isnt-Taking-His-Feet-Off-SECs-Neck-Anytime-Soon-For-XRPs-Struggles-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/06/Ripples-Brad-Garlinghouse-Isnt-Taking-His-Feet-Off-SECs-Neck-Anytime-Soon-For-XRPs-Struggles-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>Last week’s highly publicized decision in the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) case against Ripple, touted by many as a significant <a href="https://zycrypto.com/major-ripple-victory-xrp-pops-in-ballistic-rally-as-judge-finally-rules-it-isnt-a-security/">victory against the SEC</a> and Chairman Gary Gensler, may not be the end of the story. </p>



<p>Former SEC attorney, John Reed Stark, cautions against premature celebrations, pointing out the decision&#8217;s shaky ground and the likelihood of an appeal that could result in a reversal. Stark&#8217;s perspective challenges the prevailing narrative surrounding the ruling.</p>



<p>The court ruling on the Ripple case categorizes the company&#8217;s offering of securities into three distinct categories: institutional sales, programmatic sales, and other sales. The court&#8217;s ruling on each category is critical in determining the legal implications for Ripple and its investors.</p>



<p>Regarding institutional sales, the court deemed Ripple&#8217;s sale of XRP to sophisticated individuals and entities a violation of securities laws. The court ruled that XRP was a security during these transactions, entitling investors to rescission and imposing penalties on Ripple.</p>



<p>In addition, the court dismissed Ripple&#8217;s attempt to reimagine the conventional Howey test by introducing a new test known as the &#8220;Essential Ingredients Test.&#8221; Additionally, it rejected Ripple&#8217;s claim that, according to the Howey framework, an &#8220;investment of money&#8221; differs from &#8220;merely payment of money.&#8221;</p>



<p>In the case of programmatic sales, where XRP was sold to the public on digital asset exchanges, the court ruled that XRP ceased to be a security once it was sold anonymously to exchanges. The court concluded that the sources of programmatic buyers&#8217; profit expectations were independent of Ripple&#8217;s efforts.</p>



<p>According to Stark, this presumption ignores the possibility that many programmatic buyers purchased XRP, expecting to profit from Ripple&#8217;s endeavours, undermining investor protection principles.</p>



<p>The last category, &#8220;Other Distributions,&#8221; involved written contracts with Ripple, where $609 million in non-cash consideration was recorded in Ripple&#8217;s audited financial statements. These distributions included compensation for employees and support for Ripple&#8217;s Xpring initiative.</p>



<p>Stark expresses his concerns regarding the Ripple decision, highlighting several troubling aspects. Firstly, the decision grants full SEC protection and remedies to institutional investors while leaving retail investors without any SEC protection, a seemingly backward approach, according to Stark.</p>



<p>Secondly, he argues that the ruling implies that securities regulations do not apply if tokens are sold through exchanges, based on the presumption that exchange customers are ignorant of the token issuer&#8217;s identity. However, Stark finds this argument contradicts established principles of securities law.</p>



<p>Stark argues that even if retail investors are uninformed or refuse to conduct research, their investments should still be considered securities. Retail investors speculatively buy tokens, banking on the &#8220;Greater Fool Theory.&#8221; Stark argues that the court&#8217;s decision seems to transform tokens from securities when sold to institutional investors into &#8220;not securities&#8221; when sold on exchanges, an inconsistent stance with basic investing principles.</p>



<p>He finds the court&#8217;s distinction between tokens awarded to employees and third parties also problematic. Stark points out that these distributions should be considered compensation, similar to restricted stock units or stock options, and therefore subject to securities laws.</p>



<p>Additionally, the ruling seems to go against SEC precedent regarding the volume of consideration required to bring on registration requirements. Stark references past SEC cases involving &#8220;free stock&#8221; offerings, where a nominal review was sufficient to require registration. The court&#8217;s refusal to consider the employee and third-party distributions as securities due to a lack of consideration contradicts this precedent.</p>



<p>Stark said, <em>“The trial order in the Ripple case is a partial summary judgment from a single district court judge. While important and certainly worthy of study, the decision is not binding precedent on other courts.”</em></p>



<p>Appeals and future cases could yield different interpretations and outcomes, highlighting the complexity of crypto-related legal matters.</p>



<p>Stark predicts that <em>“the SEC will likely appeal the Ripple decision to the 2nd Circuit, where the District Court&#8217;s rulings on ‘programmatic’ and ‘other sales’ may be overturned.”</em> Otherwise, the ruling could set a precedent that exempts specific tokens from securities regulations based on investor sophistication and ignorance.</p>



<p>In conclusion, the <a href="https://zycrypto.com/u-s-banks-could-be-exploring-xrp-for-cross-border-payments-following-ripples-legal-victory/">Ripple decision</a> raises issues surrounding investor protection, the distinction between institutional and retail investors, and the classification of tokens as securities. The future of the case remains uncertain, and the broader implications of this ruling could shape the regulatory landscape for cryptocurrency offerings.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/sec-to-win-an-appeal-against-ripple-former-sec-official-cautions-xrp-celebrations/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>46% of Investors Believe Ether Will Outdo Bitcoin, Survey Finds</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/46-of-investors-believe-ether-will-outdo-bitcoin-survey-finds/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/46-of-investors-believe-ether-will-outdo-bitcoin-survey-finds/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aaron Feuerstein]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 19:17:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XBTUSD]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=83008</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Bitcoin-Ethereum-Primed-For-Bullish-Boost-As-Brazils-Largest-Broker-Opens-Trading.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Bitcoin, Ethereum Primed For Bullish Boost As Brazil’s Largest Broker Opens Trading" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Bitcoin-Ethereum-Primed-For-Bullish-Boost-As-Brazils-Largest-Broker-Opens-Trading.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Bitcoin-Ethereum-Primed-For-Bullish-Boost-As-Brazils-Largest-Broker-Opens-Trading-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Bitcoin-Ethereum-Primed-For-Bullish-Boost-As-Brazils-Largest-Broker-Opens-Trading-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Bitcoin-Ethereum-Primed-For-Bullish-Boost-As-Brazils-Largest-Broker-Opens-Trading-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>A recent survey by the online cryptocurrency portal CryptoVantage focused on American attitudes toward cryptocurrencies and produced some intriguing findings.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Bitcoin-Ethereum-Primed-For-Bullish-Boost-As-Brazils-Largest-Broker-Opens-Trading.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Bitcoin, Ethereum Primed For Bullish Boost As Brazil’s Largest Broker Opens Trading" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Bitcoin-Ethereum-Primed-For-Bullish-Boost-As-Brazils-Largest-Broker-Opens-Trading.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Bitcoin-Ethereum-Primed-For-Bullish-Boost-As-Brazils-Largest-Broker-Opens-Trading-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Bitcoin-Ethereum-Primed-For-Bullish-Boost-As-Brazils-Largest-Broker-Opens-Trading-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Bitcoin-Ethereum-Primed-For-Bullish-Boost-As-Brazils-Largest-Broker-Opens-Trading-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>A recent survey by the online cryptocurrency portal CryptoVantage focused on American attitudes toward cryptocurrencies and produced some intriguing findings. According to the study, 78% of respondents think <a href="https://zycrypto.com/nydig-predicts-spot-bitcoin-etfs-could-unlock-30-billion-in-fresh-demand/">Bitcoin</a> will surpass its previous record high, but only 23% think it will peak in the upcoming year, and 47% think it will happen over the next five years. Only 8% of people believe Bitcoin will never hit its all-time high again.</p>



<p>Interestingly, 21% of respondents think Dogecoin (DOGE) has the highest chance of ever outpacing Bitcoin in market value, while 46% of Americans think Ethereum (ETH) has the best chance.</p>



<p>The &#8220;Q2 2023 Signals Report&#8221; from Fidelity Digital Assets, which was released on July 18, 2023, also contained some intriguing data on the development and prospects for Bitcoin and Ethereum.</p>



<p>According to the research, Bitcoin and Ether have a solid growth path ahead. With a gain of about 85% year-to-date (YTD), Bitcoin has maintained significant price levels as on-chain indicators stabilize post-speculative activity. With a YTD increase of almost 62%, Ether displays potentially positive price signals and growing on-chain metrics.</p>



<p>There has been a net decrease in the supply of more than 700,000 Ether since the eagerly anticipated &#8220;Merge&#8221; in September 2022, suggesting less issuance. The growing number of Ethereum addresses performing their first transaction indicates a healthy network adoption.</p>



<p>Additionally, there were 15% more active Ethereum validators in the second quarter, indicating a rise in network security awareness.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-growth-beyond-2023"><strong>Growth Beyond 2023</strong></h2>



<p>However, a lot is happening in the Ethereum ecosystem regarding new developments, and the community is eagerly anticipating significant changes predicted to increase platform usage and user interest. Two crucial actions that will soon be implemented and are projected to improve the <a href="https://zycrypto.com/ethereum-ico-whale-reawakens-after-8-years-of-dormancy-moves-116-million/">Ethereum ecosystem</a> considerably are the adoption of EIP4844 and the launch of the base mainnet.</p>



<p>The much-anticipated improvement EIP4844, which is expected to be operational by the end of the year, seeks to significantly lower costs related to rollups. To boost Ethereum&#8217;s transaction throughput while retaining its security, rollups are a layer 2 scaling solution. This change will probably improve user experience and entice more developers to the platform by lowering rollup expenses.</p>



<p>With the potential to bring millions of additional users to the ecosystem, launching the basic mainnet is another crucial milestone for Ethereum. The mainnet&#8217;s extension will enable easier onboarding and participation in the Ethereum network as the popularity of decentralized finance (DeFi) and blockchain applications soars. This improved accessibility may lead to a major rise in the acceptance and usage of Ethereum.</p>



<p>Ethereum&#8217;s rollup solutions are undergoing general enhancements in addition to these essential ones, which will help users and developers. These improvements are anticipated to improve the platform&#8217;s layer 2 solutions&#8217; general performance, effectiveness, and usability, encouraging more usage and innovation within the ecosystem.</p>



<p>Additionally, the Ethereum community is anticipating the vibrant growth of new applications on rollups, layer 2s, and layer 3. Through these developments, novel DeFi platforms, autonomous worlds, and the tokenization of physical assets are all predicted to emerge. It is anticipated that the Ethereum ecosystem will experience a surge of innovative and disruptive applications as developers explore the potential of these new capabilities.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/46-of-investors-believe-ether-will-outdo-bitcoin-survey-finds/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>NYDIG Predicts Spot Bitcoin ETFs Could Unlock $30 Billion In Fresh Demand</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/nydig-predicts-spot-bitcoin-etfs-could-unlock-30-billion-in-fresh-demand/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/nydig-predicts-spot-bitcoin-etfs-could-unlock-30-billion-in-fresh-demand/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Brenda Ngari]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 18:41:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XBTUSD]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=83004</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/NYDIG-Predicts-Spot-Bitcoin-ETFs-Could-Unlock-30-Billion-In-Fresh-Demand.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="NYDIG Predicts Spot Bitcoin ETFs Could Unlock $30 Billion In Fresh Demand" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/NYDIG-Predicts-Spot-Bitcoin-ETFs-Could-Unlock-30-Billion-In-Fresh-Demand.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/NYDIG-Predicts-Spot-Bitcoin-ETFs-Could-Unlock-30-Billion-In-Fresh-Demand-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/NYDIG-Predicts-Spot-Bitcoin-ETFs-Could-Unlock-30-Billion-In-Fresh-Demand-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/NYDIG-Predicts-Spot-Bitcoin-ETFs-Could-Unlock-30-Billion-In-Fresh-Demand-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>Bitcoin spot exchange-traded funds (ETFs) could attract $30 billion in fresh demand for the flagship cryptocurrency, a new prediction says.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/NYDIG-Predicts-Spot-Bitcoin-ETFs-Could-Unlock-30-Billion-In-Fresh-Demand.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="NYDIG Predicts Spot Bitcoin ETFs Could Unlock $30 Billion In Fresh Demand" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/NYDIG-Predicts-Spot-Bitcoin-ETFs-Could-Unlock-30-Billion-In-Fresh-Demand.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/NYDIG-Predicts-Spot-Bitcoin-ETFs-Could-Unlock-30-Billion-In-Fresh-Demand-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/NYDIG-Predicts-Spot-Bitcoin-ETFs-Could-Unlock-30-Billion-In-Fresh-Demand-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/NYDIG-Predicts-Spot-Bitcoin-ETFs-Could-Unlock-30-Billion-In-Fresh-Demand-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>Bitcoin spot exchange-traded funds (ETFs) could attract $30 billion in fresh demand for the flagship cryptocurrency, a new prediction says.</p>



<p>In a recent research report, the Global Head of Research at Crypto investment firm NYDIG, Greg Cipolaro, delivered a bold vision of how the arrival of a spot Bitcoin ETF would be a game changer for the world’s oldest and largest crypto.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-a-spot-bitcoin-etf-will-open-door-to-30-billion-inflows"><strong>A Spot Bitcoin ETF Will Open Door To $30 Billion Inflows</strong></h2>



<p>$10 billion in new demand could suddenly unlock for the Bitcoin market if a spot ETF is approved by the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission, according to NYDIG.</p>



<p><a href="https://zycrypto.com/btc-primed-for-trillion-dollar-boost-as-blackrock-expects-landmark-bitcoin-etf-approval/">BlackRock&#8217;s filing</a> for a spot crypto ETF last month sparked a new wave of optimism in the crypto space, which prompted other large Wall Street institutions, including ARK Invest, Valkyrie, and Fidelity to <a href="https://zycrypto.com/bitcoin-etfs-in-motion-an-analysis-of-open-spot-btc-etf-applications-in-the-market/">file </a>their applications for a physically settled Bitcoin ETF. </p>



<p>The SEC has capsized all previous applicants looking to offer spot investment vehicles with direct exposure to BTC but started<a href="https://zycrypto.com/as-the-first-u-s-bitcoin-etf-debuts-grayscale-ceo-sees-an-ethereum-etf-rolling-out/"> greenlighting ETFs linked to BTC futures</a> in 2021. In June, the SEC gave its regulatory blessing to a leveraged Bitcoin futures ETF, one of the first of its kind in the U.S.</p>



<p>While a spot ETF has not yet hit the market in the U.S., NYDIG estimates that a total of $28.8 billion in Bitcoin assets under management already exists across the globe. Of these, $27.6 billion has been allocated to spot-like investment products.</p>



<p>NYDIG’s Greg Cipolaro notes that a spot Bitcoin ETF with the SEC’s approval would be a safer bet for investors and act as a reliable choice of investment especially because of BlackRock and iShares brand recognition.</p>



<p>Cipolaro then went on to present an interesting analogy between Bitcoin and gold — two assets that are oftentimes compared to each other. Gold ETFs around the world reportedly hold roughly $210 billion in AUM, NYIG notes. Remarkably, a bigger portion of Bitcoin’s supply (4.9%) is held in various fund formats compared to gold (1.6%). When considering private investments, the ratio is more favorable for Bitcoin compared to the yellow metal, which entails coins and bars.</p>



<p>NYDIG further uses a volatility equivalent basis to estimate potential demand for a spot Bitcoin ETF.&nbsp;</p>



<p>“Bitcoin is about 3.6x more volatile than gold, meaning that on a volatility equivalent basis, investors would require 3.6x less bitcoin than gold on a dollar basis to get as much risk exposure. Still, that would result in nearly $30B of incremental demand for a bitcoin ETF,” Cipolaro writes.</p>



<p>So, as the trend goes, Bitcoin is looking optimistic in both value and regulation as institutional trust returns to the crypto industry.&nbsp;</p>



<p>While NYDIG thinks having spot Bitcoin ETFs in the market could herald a new stage of institutional investors getting involved with the cryptocurrency, not everyone is convinced such a product would be of great benefit to the nascent industry. JPMorgan <a href="https://zycrypto.com/secs-approval-of-spot-bitcoin-etfs-wont-be-a-game-changer-for-crypto-industry-jpmorgan-strategists-opine/">said </a>earlier this month that Bitcoin spot ETFs have not seen any substantial success in overseas markets like Canada and Europe, where they have existed for years. As such, there is no reason for them to gain much traction in the U.S. if they do receive the SEC’s seal of approval.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/nydig-predicts-spot-bitcoin-etfs-could-unlock-30-billion-in-fresh-demand/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>XRP Set for Price Explosion Amid Ripple&#8217;s Expectations for $250 Trillion Cross-Border Payments</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/xrp-set-for-price-explosion-amid-ripples-expectations-for-250-trillion-cross-border-payments/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/xrp-set-for-price-explosion-amid-ripples-expectations-for-250-trillion-cross-border-payments/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aaron Feuerstein]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 11:23:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=82992</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/XRP-Poised-To-Break-New-Ground-As-Ripple-Unveils-This-New-Trillion-Dollar-Worth-ODL-Corridor.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="XRP Poised To Break New Ground As Ripple Unveils This New Trillion-Dollar Worth ODL Corridor" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/XRP-Poised-To-Break-New-Ground-As-Ripple-Unveils-This-New-Trillion-Dollar-Worth-ODL-Corridor.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/XRP-Poised-To-Break-New-Ground-As-Ripple-Unveils-This-New-Trillion-Dollar-Worth-ODL-Corridor-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/XRP-Poised-To-Break-New-Ground-As-Ripple-Unveils-This-New-Trillion-Dollar-Worth-ODL-Corridor-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/XRP-Poised-To-Break-New-Ground-As-Ripple-Unveils-This-New-Trillion-Dollar-Worth-ODL-Corridor-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>According to Ripple, blockchain and crypto technologies are attracting the interest of global financial executives as they present a potential solution to modernize the underlying infrastructure of international payments.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/XRP-Poised-To-Break-New-Ground-As-Ripple-Unveils-This-New-Trillion-Dollar-Worth-ODL-Corridor.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="XRP Poised To Break New Ground As Ripple Unveils This New Trillion-Dollar Worth ODL Corridor" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/XRP-Poised-To-Break-New-Ground-As-Ripple-Unveils-This-New-Trillion-Dollar-Worth-ODL-Corridor.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/XRP-Poised-To-Break-New-Ground-As-Ripple-Unveils-This-New-Trillion-Dollar-Worth-ODL-Corridor-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/XRP-Poised-To-Break-New-Ground-As-Ripple-Unveils-This-New-Trillion-Dollar-Worth-ODL-Corridor-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/XRP-Poised-To-Break-New-Ground-As-Ripple-Unveils-This-New-Trillion-Dollar-Worth-ODL-Corridor-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>According to <a href="https://zycrypto.com/tag/ripple">Ripple</a>, blockchain and crypto technologies are attracting the interest of global financial executives as they present a potential solution to modernize the underlying infrastructure of international payments. A recent report by Ripple Labs reveals that 44% of survey respondents expect payments to be the biggest driver of crypto adoption, with cross-border payments being a top use case for <a href="https://zycrypto.com/tag/xrp">XRP</a>.</p>



<p>Traditional payments, especially cross-border ones, often rely on legacy rails that can take days to settle transactions.</p>



<p>“In contrast, blockchain and digital asset technologies provide a seamless global infrastructure in which payments can be sent and received anytime, anywhere, instantly with lower fees and 360 visibility”, the <a href="https://ripple.com/insights/how-finance-leaders-believe-crypto-is-reshaping-payments">report</a> by Ripple states.</p>



<p>Digital-first finance is expanding rapidly; by 2025, it&#8217;s estimated that over 65% of Americans will use mobile banking, and by 2024, internet banking in Asia will have about 1 billion users. Despite these digital banking services&#8217; user-friendly interfaces, the underlying technology is still out-of-date.</p>



<p>Beneath the modern apps lie an old-fashioned payment rail system built before the internet and mobile phones. The complexity of legacy systems and the need for intermediaries introduce delays and inefficiencies, hindering real-time transactions. Moving funds internationally is even more cumbersome due to regulatory requirements, currency exchanges, time zones, and limited hours of operation, resulting in slow and expensive processes.</p>



<p>According to the Ripple report, cross-border payments are vital to the global economy, underpinning international trade, supply chains, corporate treasury flows, and funding non-governmental organizations. However, the frictions in the current system inflate the time and costs for these transactions.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-crypto-payments-fuel-shift-in-finance"><strong>Crypto Payments Fuel Shift in Finance</strong></h2>



<p>Fortunately, cross-border payments have emerged as a robust use case for crypto and blockchain technology because they facilitate interoperability between tokens or chains. Crypto-enabled payments allow for the quick movement of digital assets between chains, liquidating them into fiat currencies for faster, affordable, and transparent transactions.</p>



<p>And the market is by no means small, as global payments powered by crypto assets like XRP are projected to reach $250 trillion by 2027. The advantages of using crypto for cross-border payments are evident, with over half of global payments and treasury professionals seeing faster payments and cost savings as critical reasons for adoption.</p>



<p>More than 80% of top financial executives worldwide predict that their companies will embrace cryptocurrencies over the next three years. Blockchain technology is paving the way for seamless global payments by solving the drawbacks of conventional payment systems, enabling instantaneous transactions for people, companies, and banks anywhere.</p>



<p>Financial institutions, regulators, and companies are collaborating to unleash the potential of blockchain to create a new and effective payment environment as the world proceeds toward this seismic upheaval in finance.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/xrp-set-for-price-explosion-amid-ripples-expectations-for-250-trillion-cross-border-payments/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>XRP Sometimes a Security, Sometimes Not? Here’s Why Even Lawyers Seem Confused About SEC vs Ripple Outcome</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/xrp-sometimes-a-security-sometimes-not-heres-why-even-lawyers-seem-confused-about-sec-vs-ripple-outcome/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/xrp-sometimes-a-security-sometimes-not-heres-why-even-lawyers-seem-confused-about-sec-vs-ripple-outcome/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aaron Feuerstein]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 11:05:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=82990</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRP-Lawsuit-Ripple-And-SEC-Request-Additional-Time-to-Disclose-Hinman-Files-—-Is-A-Settlement-Looming.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="XRP Lawsuit: Ripple And SEC Request Additional Time to Disclose Hinman Files — Is A Settlement Looming?" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRP-Lawsuit-Ripple-And-SEC-Request-Additional-Time-to-Disclose-Hinman-Files-—-Is-A-Settlement-Looming.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRP-Lawsuit-Ripple-And-SEC-Request-Additional-Time-to-Disclose-Hinman-Files-—-Is-A-Settlement-Looming-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRP-Lawsuit-Ripple-And-SEC-Request-Additional-Time-to-Disclose-Hinman-Files-—-Is-A-Settlement-Looming-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRP-Lawsuit-Ripple-And-SEC-Request-Additional-Time-to-Disclose-Hinman-Files-—-Is-A-Settlement-Looming-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>After Judge Torres handed down her verdict in the SEC vs Ripple lawsuit last Thursday, a lot has been said about what the ruling actually means. The reactions have been very mixed, perhaps rightfully so, reflecting the case&#8217;s complexity and importance. Not surprisingly, the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) tried to put a positive spin [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRP-Lawsuit-Ripple-And-SEC-Request-Additional-Time-to-Disclose-Hinman-Files-—-Is-A-Settlement-Looming.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="XRP Lawsuit: Ripple And SEC Request Additional Time to Disclose Hinman Files — Is A Settlement Looming?" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRP-Lawsuit-Ripple-And-SEC-Request-Additional-Time-to-Disclose-Hinman-Files-—-Is-A-Settlement-Looming.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRP-Lawsuit-Ripple-And-SEC-Request-Additional-Time-to-Disclose-Hinman-Files-—-Is-A-Settlement-Looming-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRP-Lawsuit-Ripple-And-SEC-Request-Additional-Time-to-Disclose-Hinman-Files-—-Is-A-Settlement-Looming-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRP-Lawsuit-Ripple-And-SEC-Request-Additional-Time-to-Disclose-Hinman-Files-—-Is-A-Settlement-Looming-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>After Judge Torres handed down her <a href="https://zycrypto.com/major-ripple-victory-xrp-pops-in-ballistic-rally-as-judge-finally-rules-it-isnt-a-security/">verdict in the SEC vs Ripple lawsuit</a> last Thursday, a lot has been said about what the ruling actually means. The reactions have been very mixed, perhaps rightfully so, reflecting the case&#8217;s complexity and importance.</p>



<p>Not surprisingly, the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) tried to put a positive spin on the outcome by claiming victory. The SEC stated it was <em>“pleased that the court has found that XRP tokens were offered and sold by Ripple as investment contracts in certain circumstances, in violation of securities laws.”</em></p>



<p>However, rather than a win for the SEC or Ripple, the decision was a split one, with each of the parties having a win. In a nutshell, the judge delivered a divided verdict, partially ruling on both parties&#8217; motions for summary judgment, which had asked the court to decide without consulting a jury of peers.</p>



<p>Some crypto community members have questioned the judgment, with former SEC lawyer John Reed Stark voicing his concerns about the ruling and advising against hasty celebrations among the cryptocurrency community. He claimed that the court had turned investor protection on its head.</p>



<p>However, Coinbase Chief Legal Officer Paul Grewal commented, <em>“Don’t be misled that Judge Torres ruled that sometimes XRP is a security and sometimes it isn’t. That’s exactly the opposite of what she ruled: XRP itself is NEVER a security.”</em></p>



<p>Judge Torres found that <em>“XRP, as a digital token, is not in and of itself a ‘contract, transaction [,] or scheme’ that embodies the Howey requirements of an investment contract.”</em></p>



<p>According to the judge, XRP programmatic sales are not unregistered securities offerings. The judge made it clear that because it was unrelated to the case, the decision did not examine whether XRP&#8217;s secondary market sales constituted offers and sales of investment contracts. Rather, the judge ruled that institutional XRP sales were unlawful because they were unregistered securities transactions.</p>



<p>When buying XRP from Ripple, institutions received investment papers and signed contracts on paper. Despite being required by law, Ripple never reported the sales. Consequently, the court ruled against Ripple here.</p>



<p>However, programmatic sales and other XRP distribution methods were recognized as legitimate. The judge ruled that no one had paid money to obtain these distributions; thus, there were no unregistered investment contracts. Programmatic sales involved anonymous bid/ask exchanges carried out by algorithms, with buyers being unaware of the identity of the sellers.</p>



<p>This is probably seen as the biggest win for XRP retail investors and the 75000 holders represented by lawyer John E. Deaton as Amicus or friends to the court.</p>



<p>Judge Torres referred to the Amicus and their Affidavits in her ruling, citing that it was impossible to know why people had bought XRP on exchanges, which means the decision could have been easily very different if not for the 75000 Amicus’.</p>



<p>In the end, while individual defendants wait for their trials to determine whether the two Ripple executives aided and abetted Ripple concerning Institutional sales, the question is: Will Judge Torres&#8217; summary ruling be appealed? Either party may appeal the decision; however, such a request is known as an interlocutory appeal, and only very seldom are they granted, according to a lawyer and a close observer of the case, Jeremy Hogan.</p>



<p>The likelihood of appeals occurring after the trial is higher, according to Hogan, and as appeals naturally take a long time to resolve, the judgment will likely stand through and into 2025, which is a considerable amount of time and may give the US Congress time to carve out more transparent regulations.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/xrp-sometimes-a-security-sometimes-not-heres-why-even-lawyers-seem-confused-about-sec-vs-ripple-outcome/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Elon Musk’s Tesla Still HODLing $184 Million In Bitcoin</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/elon-musks-tesla-still-hodling-184-million-in-bitcoin/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/elon-musks-tesla-still-hodling-184-million-in-bitcoin/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Brenda Ngari]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 10:41:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elon Musk]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tesla]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XBTUSD]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=82988</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Heres-The-Crucial-Silver-Lining-To-Teslas-Bombshell-936-Million-Bitcoin-Sale.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Here’s The Crucial Silver Lining To Tesla’s Bombshell $936 Million Bitcoin Sale" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Heres-The-Crucial-Silver-Lining-To-Teslas-Bombshell-936-Million-Bitcoin-Sale.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Heres-The-Crucial-Silver-Lining-To-Teslas-Bombshell-936-Million-Bitcoin-Sale-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Heres-The-Crucial-Silver-Lining-To-Teslas-Bombshell-936-Million-Bitcoin-Sale-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Heres-The-Crucial-Silver-Lining-To-Teslas-Bombshell-936-Million-Bitcoin-Sale-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>It’s been a year since Elon Musk’s electric car company Tesla sold 75% of its Bitcoin stash. However, Tesla remains one of the largest corporate holders of Bitcoin.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Heres-The-Crucial-Silver-Lining-To-Teslas-Bombshell-936-Million-Bitcoin-Sale.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Here’s The Crucial Silver Lining To Tesla’s Bombshell $936 Million Bitcoin Sale" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Heres-The-Crucial-Silver-Lining-To-Teslas-Bombshell-936-Million-Bitcoin-Sale.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Heres-The-Crucial-Silver-Lining-To-Teslas-Bombshell-936-Million-Bitcoin-Sale-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Heres-The-Crucial-Silver-Lining-To-Teslas-Bombshell-936-Million-Bitcoin-Sale-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Heres-The-Crucial-Silver-Lining-To-Teslas-Bombshell-936-Million-Bitcoin-Sale-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>It&#8217;s been a year since Elon Musk&#8217;s electric car company Tesla <a href="https://zycrypto.com/bitcoin-holds-steady-above-22k-even-as-elon-musks-tesla-dumps-75-of-its-btc-holdings/">sold 75% of its Bitcoin stash</a>. However, Tesla remains one of the largest corporate holders of Bitcoin. The company&#8217;s BTC holdings remain unchanged for the straight quarter in Q2 2023.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-tesla-s-diamond-hands"><strong>Tesla’s Diamond Hands</strong></h2>



<p>In its <a href="https://digitalassets.tesla.com/tesla-contents/image/upload/TSLA-Q2-2023-Update.pdf">latest earnings report</a> released Wednesday, Tesla revealed it had neither sold nor bought any Bitcoin in the second quarter of 2023.</p>



<p>The value of its Bitcoin cache at the end of the quarter stood at $184 million, the same as it has been for the past three quarters. The valuation of the stockpile remained flat even as BTC rose to about $30,500 at the end of Q2 from $27,900 three months earlier, as existing accounting laws don&#8217;t permit such gains to be booked.</p>



<p>Tesla had not sold any more Bitcoin since July last year when it infamously offloaded $936 million worth of BTC, with Musk <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=kwpYe1Empwo&amp;ab_channel=Tesla">pointing to </a>uncertainty surrounding lockdowns in China and the need to maximize the company&#8217;s cash to justify the sale.</p>



<p>The sell-off in July 2022 left the electric car manufacturer with approximately 10,725 Bitcoins on its balance sheet. Despite all the turmoil and uncertainty in the markets, Tesla has continued to hold on to its remaining BTC, leaving crypto fans wondering whether the Musk-helmed company plans to buy more bitcoin soon.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Tesla And Bitcoin</strong></h2>



<p>In February 2021, Tesla <a href="https://zycrypto.com/elon-musk-takes-crypto-enthusiasm-to-a-whole-new-level-as-tesla-invests-1-5-billion-in-bitcoin/">invested an astounding $1.5 billion in Bitcoin</a>, making it one of the biggest corporate holders of the premier crypto — second only to Michael Saylor&#8217;s MicroStrategy. At the time, Bitcoin traded at around $45,000 per coin, and Tesla had also started accepting Bitcoin payments. By November of the same year, Bitcoin posted its lifetime high of $69,044.</p>



<p>However, the love affair between Tesla and Bitcoin ended in May 2021 after the company <a href="https://zycrypto.com/elon-musk-pokes-massive-hole-in-the-bitcoin-market-after-halting-bitcoin-payments-at-tesla/">suspended </a>BTC as a payment option, with Musk <a href="https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1392602041025843203">citing </a>concerns &#8220;about rapidly increasing use of fossil fuels for bitcoin mining and transactions.&#8221;</p>



<p>This year, Bitcoin has noticeably outperformed most traditional stocks and bonds and has recouped the losses incurred from the cryptocurrency contagions induced by FTX and Terra-Luna catastrophe.</p>



<p>Besides Bitcoin, Tesla is also believed to hold Dogecoin, as it <a href="https://zycrypto.com/dogecoin-set-to-break-new-grounds-as-elon-musk-announces-tesla-will-accept-doge-for-merchandise/">accepts </a>the canine-themed crypto as payment for merchandise, and Musk is a<a href="https://zycrypto.com/keen-on-dogecoin-beating-bitcoin-hands-down-elon-musk-backs-new-doge-upgrade/"> self-avowed evangelist</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/elon-musks-tesla-still-hodling-184-million-in-bitcoin/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Coast Not Clear For Coinbase Despite XRP&#8217;s Victory Over The SEC — Here&#8217;s Why</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/coast-not-clear-for-coinbase-despite-xrps-victory-over-the-sec-heres-why/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/coast-not-clear-for-coinbase-despite-xrps-victory-over-the-sec-heres-why/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aliyu Pokima]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 22:12:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=82984</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Coast-Not-Clear-For-Coinbase-Despite-XRPs-Victory-Over-The-SEC-—-Heres-Why.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Coast Not Clear For Coinbase Despite XRP&#039;s Victory Over The SEC — Here&#039;s Why" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Coast-Not-Clear-For-Coinbase-Despite-XRPs-Victory-Over-The-SEC-—-Heres-Why.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Coast-Not-Clear-For-Coinbase-Despite-XRPs-Victory-Over-The-SEC-—-Heres-Why-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Coast-Not-Clear-For-Coinbase-Despite-XRPs-Victory-Over-The-SEC-—-Heres-Why-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Coast-Not-Clear-For-Coinbase-Despite-XRPs-Victory-Over-The-SEC-—-Heres-Why-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>Ripple Labs’ split victory over the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) elicited waves of optimism for Coinbase in its case against the regulator. However, analysts have warned that the exchange still faces an uphill climb.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Coast-Not-Clear-For-Coinbase-Despite-XRPs-Victory-Over-The-SEC-—-Heres-Why.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Coast Not Clear For Coinbase Despite XRP&#039;s Victory Over The SEC — Here&#039;s Why" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Coast-Not-Clear-For-Coinbase-Despite-XRPs-Victory-Over-The-SEC-—-Heres-Why.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Coast-Not-Clear-For-Coinbase-Despite-XRPs-Victory-Over-The-SEC-—-Heres-Why-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Coast-Not-Clear-For-Coinbase-Despite-XRPs-Victory-Over-The-SEC-—-Heres-Why-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Coast-Not-Clear-For-Coinbase-Despite-XRPs-Victory-Over-The-SEC-—-Heres-Why-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>Ripple Labs’ <a href="https://zycrypto.com/the-good-bad-and-the-complicated-from-the-sec-vs-ripple-verdict-as-bulls-envision-10-xrp-price/">split victory</a> over the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) elicited waves of optimism for Coinbase in its case against the regulator. However, analysts have warned that the exchange still faces an uphill climb.</p>



<p>Berenberg Capital Markets noted in a new report that the SEC still has a strong case against Coinbase regarding the status of several offerings. According to the report, the allegations of Coinbase offering unregistered securities to the public hold substance as evidence in the exchange’s recent move.</p>



<p>Barely a day after the court ruled that XRP did not amount to a security, Coinbase moved to suspend the operations of its staking service in four U.S. states. Coinbase stated in its announcement that pausing its staking service is not an admission of guilt but is designed to allow the legal proceedings to run their full course.</p>



<p>However, Berenberg warned that halting the staking service “serves as a reminder to investors that Coinbase is far from being in the clear” The analysts cited a statement from Coinbase that although no customer has lost assets through staking, there are several risks associated with the offering.</p>



<p>Experts have pointed out that the SEC will be pinning the bulk of its argument on Coinbase’s submission that staking poses a measure of risk to investors.</p>



<p>Back in March, the SEC <a href="https://zycrypto.com/sec-action-against-coinbase-triggers-ballistic-reaction-from-crypto-community/">issued</a> a Wells notice to Coinbase confirming the start of enforcement action against the U.S.-based exchange. The SEC is accusing the exchange of running an unregistered securities exchange and offering the public unregistered securities through Coinbase Earn, its staking service.</p>



<p>Despite Berenberg’s warning, a number of Wall Street Banks have hailed XRP’s ruling as a net positive for Coinbase, expecting the exchange to include it in its defense.</p>



<p><em>“We view the ruling as incrementally positive for Coinbase, given the interpretation that in some cases a token may not be a security,”</em> said U.K.-based Barclays Bank. <em>“This may also provide incremental clarity for future token issuances.”</em></p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-coinbase-faults-the-sec"><strong>Coinbase faults the SEC</strong></h2>



<p>While both parties head to court, Coinbase has made some scathing allegations against the SEC, eliminating a settlement option.</p>



<p>Coinbase refuted all allegations of breaching securities laws, saying that it had sought the SEC’s feedback on its crypto rules but received “none” from the commission.</p>



<p><em>“We also reiterated that we stand by our listings process &#8211; we don’t list securities today &#8211; and repeatedly invited the SEC to raise any questions about any asset at all on our platform,” </em><a href="https://www.coinbase.com/blog/we-asked-the-sec-for-reasonable-crypto-rules-for-americans-we-got-legal">said</a> Coinbase. <em>“We met with the SEC more than 30 times over nine months, but we were doing all of the talking.”</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/coast-not-clear-for-coinbase-despite-xrps-victory-over-the-sec-heres-why/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Big Blow To Crypto As Nasdaq Scraps Plans To Enter Custody Business Amid U.S. Regulatory Turmoil</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/big-blow-to-crypto-as-nasdaq-scraps-plans-to-enter-custody-business-amid-u-s-regulatory-turmoil/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/big-blow-to-crypto-as-nasdaq-scraps-plans-to-enter-custody-business-amid-u-s-regulatory-turmoil/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Brenda Ngari]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 20:44:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Featured]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NASDAQ]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=82977</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Big-Blow-To-Crypto-As-Nasdaq-Scraps-Plans-To-Enter-Custody-Business-Amid-U.S.-Regulatory-Turmoil.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Big Blow To Crypto As Nasdaq Scraps Plans To Enter Custody Business Amid U.S. Regulatory Turmoil" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Big-Blow-To-Crypto-As-Nasdaq-Scraps-Plans-To-Enter-Custody-Business-Amid-U.S.-Regulatory-Turmoil.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Big-Blow-To-Crypto-As-Nasdaq-Scraps-Plans-To-Enter-Custody-Business-Amid-U.S.-Regulatory-Turmoil-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Big-Blow-To-Crypto-As-Nasdaq-Scraps-Plans-To-Enter-Custody-Business-Amid-U.S.-Regulatory-Turmoil-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Big-Blow-To-Crypto-As-Nasdaq-Scraps-Plans-To-Enter-Custody-Business-Amid-U.S.-Regulatory-Turmoil-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>Stock market operator Nasdaq has ended its plans to provide its highly-anticipated crypto custody service, citing the ongoing regulatory conditions in the United States as the key reason for their decision.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Big-Blow-To-Crypto-As-Nasdaq-Scraps-Plans-To-Enter-Custody-Business-Amid-U.S.-Regulatory-Turmoil.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Big Blow To Crypto As Nasdaq Scraps Plans To Enter Custody Business Amid U.S. Regulatory Turmoil" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Big-Blow-To-Crypto-As-Nasdaq-Scraps-Plans-To-Enter-Custody-Business-Amid-U.S.-Regulatory-Turmoil.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Big-Blow-To-Crypto-As-Nasdaq-Scraps-Plans-To-Enter-Custody-Business-Amid-U.S.-Regulatory-Turmoil-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Big-Blow-To-Crypto-As-Nasdaq-Scraps-Plans-To-Enter-Custody-Business-Amid-U.S.-Regulatory-Turmoil-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Big-Blow-To-Crypto-As-Nasdaq-Scraps-Plans-To-Enter-Custody-Business-Amid-U.S.-Regulatory-Turmoil-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>Stock market operator Nasdaq has ended its plans to provide its highly-anticipated crypto custody service, citing the ongoing regulatory conditions in the United States as the key reason for their decision. The service was scheduled to go live in the second quarter of this year. The sudden reversal of the custody plans marks a notable setback to the institutional adoption of crypto in the U.S.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-nasdaq-halts-plan-for-institutional-crypto-custody-service"><strong>Nasdaq Halts Plan For Institutional Crypto Custody Service</strong></h2>



<p>CEO Adena Friedman announced that Nasdaq has dropped its plans for a Bitcoin custody service during the company’s Q2 results call.</p>



<p><em>“This quarter, considering the shifting business and regulatory environment in the United States, we have made the decision to halt our launch of the U.S. digital assets custodian business and our related efforts to pursue relevant license,” Friedman indicated.</em></p>



<p>The Nasdaq boss stressed that the firm would “remain committed to supporting the evolution of the digital asset ecosystem.” Friedman highlighted intentions to pursue collaborations with potential ETF issuers:</p>



<p>“We continue to build and deliver technology capabilities that position Nasdaq as a leading digital assets software solutions provider to the broader global industry.”</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>A Bane For Crypto</strong></h2>



<p>News <a href="https://zycrypto.com/nasdaq-scales-up-crypto-ambitions-by-introducing-custody-service-for-institutional-players/">emerged </a>last year that Nasdaq was intending to roll out a crypto custody service in a bid to capture institutional investor interest. However, regulators in the U.S. have embarked on their most harrowing crackdown on crypto yet — initiating lawsuits against a number of high-profile companies.</p>



<p>The exchange operator had been awaiting permission from the New York Department of Financial Services (NYDFS) by the end of June to start offering custodial services to customers. Nasdaq was targeting a launch by the end of this month.</p>



<p>But the company has decided to rethink its involvement in the crypto custody business and its efforts to seek the requisite licenses for the service amid the regulatory uncertainty and heightened scrutiny of crypto-related offerings.</p>



<p>This surprising turnabout is a big blow to greater institutional adoption as concerns of a possible exodus of crypto firms to more friendly jurisdictions arise. Sadly, the U.S. is becoming a hostile place for the crypto industry to do business. The actions of the SEC and its chair Gary Gensler against the world&#8217;s foremost exchanges, <a href="https://zycrypto.com/coinbase-suffers-double-whammy-as-sec-and-state-regulators-act-against-exchange-for-unregistered-securities/">Coinbase </a>and <a href="https://zycrypto.com/us-sec-files-fresh-charges-against-binance-and-ceo-changpeng-zhao/">Binance</a>, have the crypto sector reeling.</p>



<p>Even so, there does seem to be institutional demand in the industry: BlackRock — and a slew of other prominent asset management firms — have <a href="https://zycrypto.com/bitcoin-etfs-in-motion-an-analysis-of-open-spot-btc-etf-applications-in-the-market/">submitted </a>applications to launch spot Bitcoin ETF products. In fact, Nasdaq has partnered with BlackRock— the world’s largest asset manager — for the application, which is presently being <a href="https://zycrypto.com/approval-incoming-sec-officially-acknowledges-blackrocks-spot-bitcoin-etf-application/">examined </a>by the SEC.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/big-blow-to-crypto-as-nasdaq-scraps-plans-to-enter-custody-business-amid-u-s-regulatory-turmoil/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>U.S. Banks Could Be Exploring XRP for Cross-Border Payments Following Ripple&#8217;s Legal Victory</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/u-s-banks-could-be-exploring-xrp-for-cross-border-payments-following-ripples-legal-victory/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/u-s-banks-could-be-exploring-xrp-for-cross-border-payments-following-ripples-legal-victory/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aaron Feuerstein]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 15:07:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=82970</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/XRP-Adoption-Boost_-Bank-Of-America-Applauds-Ripple’s-Innovative-Cross-Border-Solution.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="XRP Adoption Boost: Bank Of America Applauds Ripple’s Innovative Cross-Border Solution" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/XRP-Adoption-Boost_-Bank-Of-America-Applauds-Ripple’s-Innovative-Cross-Border-Solution.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/XRP-Adoption-Boost_-Bank-Of-America-Applauds-Ripple’s-Innovative-Cross-Border-Solution-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/XRP-Adoption-Boost_-Bank-Of-America-Applauds-Ripple’s-Innovative-Cross-Border-Solution-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/XRP-Adoption-Boost_-Bank-Of-America-Applauds-Ripple’s-Innovative-Cross-Border-Solution-768x448.jpg 768w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/XRP-Adoption-Boost_-Bank-Of-America-Applauds-Ripple’s-Innovative-Cross-Border-Solution-610x356.jpg 610w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>...the company anticipates starting discussions with American financial institutions about adopting its...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/XRP-Adoption-Boost_-Bank-Of-America-Applauds-Ripple’s-Innovative-Cross-Border-Solution.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="XRP Adoption Boost: Bank Of America Applauds Ripple’s Innovative Cross-Border Solution" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/XRP-Adoption-Boost_-Bank-Of-America-Applauds-Ripple’s-Innovative-Cross-Border-Solution.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/XRP-Adoption-Boost_-Bank-Of-America-Applauds-Ripple’s-Innovative-Cross-Border-Solution-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/XRP-Adoption-Boost_-Bank-Of-America-Applauds-Ripple’s-Innovative-Cross-Border-Solution-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/XRP-Adoption-Boost_-Bank-Of-America-Applauds-Ripple’s-Innovative-Cross-Border-Solution-768x448.jpg 768w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/XRP-Adoption-Boost_-Bank-Of-America-Applauds-Ripple’s-Innovative-Cross-Border-Solution-610x356.jpg 610w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>In a landmark ruling, Judge Analisa Torres of the United States District Court for the Southern District of New York sided with Fintech company Ripple and decided that <a href="https://zycrypto.com/major-ripple-victory-xrp-pops-in-ballistic-rally-as-judge-finally-rules-it-isnt-a-security/">XRP was not necessarily a security</a>. Ripple, the company behind the cryptocurrency, now expects U.S. banks and financial institutions to use XRP for cross-border payments.</p>



<p>In an interview with CNBC, Ripple&#8217;s Chief Legal Officer, Stuart Alderoty, said the company anticipates starting discussions with American financial institutions about adopting its On-Demand Liquidity (ODL) product. According to the San Francisco firm, XRP enables ODL to provide near-instantaneous money movement across borders.</p>



<p>The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) sued Ripple and its executives CEO Brad Garlinghouse and Executive Chair Chris Larsen, in December 2020, <a href="https://zycrypto.com/xrp-holders-are-completely-fcked-messari-founder-predicts-drop-to-0-10-as-the-sec-sues-ripple/">alleging the illegal sale of $1.3 billion worth of XRP</a>. Contrary to several of the SEC&#8217;s allegations against Ripple, the New York judge recently ruled that XRP was not, in essence, a security.</p>



<p>Stuart Alderoty was optimistic about the ruling prompting American banks to return to Ripple and utilize its ODL product, further stating, “I think we’re hopeful that this decision would give financial institution customers or potential customers comfort to at least come in and start having the conversation about what problems they are experiencing in their business, real-world problems in terms of moving value across borders without incurring obscene fees.”</p>



<p>Ripple uses ODL, which utilizes XRP as an intermediary currency, enabling instant liquidity sourcing and real-time fund transfers. ODL is used by various businesses, including payment service providers, fintech companies involved in business-to-business transactions, and organizations seeking to transfer internal treasury payments to foreign accounts.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-ripple-s-customer-base"><strong>Ripple&#8217;s Customer Base</strong></h2>



<p>Interestingly while both Ripple and the SEC claim victory in the case, Judge Torres did make a split decision, granting that XRP itself was not a security. She also acknowledged that certain token sales qualified as securities transactions to institutional investors. The judge stated that approximately $728.9 million of such XRP sales did meet the criteria of securities, citing the ‘presence of a common enterprise and an expectation of profit’.</p>



<p>With Ripple&#8217;s core business operating outside the United States, most of its customers and revenue originate internationally. Although Ripple, which has approximately 900 employees globally, maintains a significant presence in the United States, Alderoty explained that since Ripple&#8217;s primary customer base is outside the United States, this aspect of the ruling would not immediately impact the company&#8217;s existing operations.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/u-s-banks-could-be-exploring-xrp-for-cross-border-payments-following-ripples-legal-victory/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum ICO Whale Reawakens After 8 Years Of Dormancy, Moves $116 Million</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/ethereum-ico-whale-reawakens-after-8-years-of-dormancy-moves-116-million/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/ethereum-ico-whale-reawakens-after-8-years-of-dormancy-moves-116-million/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Brenda Ngari]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 14:13:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=82967</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ethereum-ICO-Whale-Reawakens-After-8-Years-Of-Dormancy-Moves-116-Million.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Ethereum ICO Whale Reawakens After 8 Years Of Dormancy, Moves $116 Million" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ethereum-ICO-Whale-Reawakens-After-8-Years-Of-Dormancy-Moves-116-Million.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ethereum-ICO-Whale-Reawakens-After-8-Years-Of-Dormancy-Moves-116-Million-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ethereum-ICO-Whale-Reawakens-After-8-Years-Of-Dormancy-Moves-116-Million-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ethereum-ICO-Whale-Reawakens-After-8-Years-Of-Dormancy-Moves-116-Million-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>An extremely old Ether wallet has suddenly resurrected after eight long years of dormancy, moving pre-mined ETH worth...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ethereum-ICO-Whale-Reawakens-After-8-Years-Of-Dormancy-Moves-116-Million.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Ethereum ICO Whale Reawakens After 8 Years Of Dormancy, Moves $116 Million" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ethereum-ICO-Whale-Reawakens-After-8-Years-Of-Dormancy-Moves-116-Million.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ethereum-ICO-Whale-Reawakens-After-8-Years-Of-Dormancy-Moves-116-Million-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ethereum-ICO-Whale-Reawakens-After-8-Years-Of-Dormancy-Moves-116-Million-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ethereum-ICO-Whale-Reawakens-After-8-Years-Of-Dormancy-Moves-116-Million-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>An extremely old Ether wallet has suddenly resurrected after eight long years of dormancy, moving pre-mined ETH worth $116 million to a Kraken wallet address. The tokens were accumulated during a sale event in June 2014 and have greatly increased in value over the years.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-ethereum-ico-participant-wakes-from-8-year-slumber"><strong>Ethereum ICO Participant Wakes From 8-Year Slumber</strong></h2>



<p>Pre-mining era Ether, worth an eye-popping $116 million, moved wallets on July 18 after laying dormant for eight years, Etherscan <a href="https://etherscan.io/address/0x828d32346ae445ce058923642dd467261e69adae">data </a>shows. The wallet transferred all of its 61,216 ETH to an address on the Kraken exchange. On that day, its owner began with a cautionary transfer of 0.05 ETH to the Kraken address before proceeding to make the large-scale transfer.</p>



<p>Notably, moving $116 million worth of ETH required a mere transaction fee of $1.68 and 25.475673161 Gwei in gas price.</p>



<p>The Ethereum network held a sale event back in June 2014, allowing co-founders and early participants to purchase pre-mined Ether. This event was necessary because the Ethereum ecosystem couldn’t generate tokens on its own during this time and was also not being utilized for real use cases.</p>



<p>During the pre-mine period, the 61,216 Ether was bought at a price of between $300 and $400, which places the initial investment amount at around $20 million. At today’s price of $1,908, the value of those tokens has risen to over $116 million within the eight-year period.</p>



<p>The owner of the wallet remains unknown as of publication time. Still, holding his stash for eight whole years demonstrates the extent of hodling —  a popular investment strategy in the crypto community that prioritizes the long-term accumulation of crypto tokens. </p>



<p><a href="https://zycrypto.com/10-year-dormant-bitcoin-whale-emerges-rakes-in-astonishing-38-million-profit/">Dormant wallets</a> with huge sums of crypto can resurrect for a string of reasons. Sometimes they have decided to cash in on big price increases. Other times, it&#8217;s simply because the owner may have been hacked. Nevertheless, such dormant whales&#8217; actions can substantially impact the market and investor sentiment. Monitoring any possible ripple effects from this latest multi-million-dollar transaction will be fascinating.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/ethereum-ico-whale-reawakens-after-8-years-of-dormancy-moves-116-million/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bridging the Gap: Chainlink Unveils Cross-Chain Interoperability Protocol to Connect TradFi with Crypto</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/bridging-the-gap-chainlink-unveils-cross-chain-interoperability-protocol-to-connect-tradfi-with-crypto/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/bridging-the-gap-chainlink-unveils-cross-chain-interoperability-protocol-to-connect-tradfi-with-crypto/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aaron Feuerstein]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 14:08:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ChainLink]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Link]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LINKUSD]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=82965</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Chainlink-Targets-New-Highs-After-Release-Of-Updated-Roadmap-For-Introduction-Of-Staking.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Chainlink Targets New Highs After Release Of Updated Roadmap For Introduction Of Staking" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Chainlink-Targets-New-Highs-After-Release-Of-Updated-Roadmap-For-Introduction-Of-Staking.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Chainlink-Targets-New-Highs-After-Release-Of-Updated-Roadmap-For-Introduction-Of-Staking-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Chainlink-Targets-New-Highs-After-Release-Of-Updated-Roadmap-For-Introduction-Of-Staking-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Chainlink-Targets-New-Highs-After-Release-Of-Updated-Roadmap-For-Introduction-Of-Staking-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>The eagerly awaited Cross-Chain Interoperability Protocol (CCIP), which seeks to transform communication between the traditional finance (TradFi) and cryptocurrency ecosystems, has been made official by data provider Chainlink.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Chainlink-Targets-New-Highs-After-Release-Of-Updated-Roadmap-For-Introduction-Of-Staking.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Chainlink Targets New Highs After Release Of Updated Roadmap For Introduction Of Staking" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Chainlink-Targets-New-Highs-After-Release-Of-Updated-Roadmap-For-Introduction-Of-Staking.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Chainlink-Targets-New-Highs-After-Release-Of-Updated-Roadmap-For-Introduction-Of-Staking-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Chainlink-Targets-New-Highs-After-Release-Of-Updated-Roadmap-For-Introduction-Of-Staking-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Chainlink-Targets-New-Highs-After-Release-Of-Updated-Roadmap-For-Introduction-Of-Staking-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>The eagerly awaited Cross-Chain Interoperability Protocol (CCIP), which seeks to transform communication between the traditional finance (TradFi) and cryptocurrency ecosystems, has been made official by data provider <a href="https://zycrypto.com/tag/chainlink">Chainlink</a>. According to a Chainlink blog post, the protocol will make it possible for smooth cross-chain communication, encourage cooperation, and open up a wide range of opportunities for the decentralized finance (DeFi) industry. It is now accessible for early-access users on the Avalanche, Ethereum, Optimism, and Polygon blockchains.</p>



<p>With over 25 partner projects, including well-known players like the decentralized banking protocol Aave and the decentralized liquidity platform Synthetix, the CCIP, designed to create cross-chain apps and services, has been through rigorous testing. These early adopters set the bar for using CCIP&#8217;s capabilities because they understand its disruptive potential.</p>



<p>The relationship between Chainlink and SWIFT, the closed network banks use for international money transfers, has also been greatly aided by Chainlink&#8217;s CCIP. Chainlink and SWIFT recently announced plans to link various financial institutions to blockchain networks, with CCIP as the primary connector. Co-founder of Chainlink Sergey Nazarov voiced enthusiasm for this partnership&#8217;s pilot phase, saying that CCIP &#8220;could connect all of the blockchains and all of the bank chains.&#8221;</p>



<p>Chainlink has made CCIP accessible to all developers across five testnets, including Arbitrum Goerli, Avalanche Fuji, Ethereum Sepolia, Optimism Goerli, and Polygon Mumbai, as a sign of its dedication to supporting innovation and broad adoption. This starts the process of moving the protocol to mainnet general availability, where it will be available to users and developers everywhere.</p>



<p>The foundation of Chainlink&#8217;s CCIP is a strong security model that has supported the company&#8217;s renowned pricing oracles, recognized for their resilience against flash-loan assaults and other typical risks. The importance of CCIP was compared to the fundamental design of the internet by Sergey Nazarov, who said it aims to be the &#8220;TCP/IP of finance.&#8221;</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-major-finance-players-coming-on-board"><strong>Major Finance Players Coming on Board</strong></h2>



<p>In a statement to the online publication, DeCrypt, Nazarov stressed that the protocol&#8217;s promise extends beyond the world of cryptocurrencies and can help close the gap between traditional finance and digital assets. Major participants in the traditional finance industry, such as SWIFT, BNY Mellon, Citigroup, and BNP Paribas, have already started working with Chainlink.</p>



<p>“Through CCIP, we will create a private-public dynamic that will give access to traditional finance to digital assets and the cryptocurrency space to trillions of dollars”, Nazarov added.</p>



<p>According to Nazarov, this fusion of traditional banking with the blockchain industry marks a paradigm change. This market cycle is fueled by clients&#8217; persistent demand for crypto assets within conventional financial institutions, as opposed to earlier cycles entirely driven by token pricing. According to Nazarov, CCIP can revolutionize global banking, much like TCP/IP did when forming a unified internet architecture.</p>



<p>The CCIP protocol from Chainlink, which is currently operational and gathering support from pioneers and titans of the sector, can close the gap between traditional banking and the cryptocurrency ecosystem. The CCIP will transform the financial landscape and open the door for increased cooperation and innovation in the DeFi arena by enabling seamless communication and new opportunities.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/bridging-the-gap-chainlink-unveils-cross-chain-interoperability-protocol-to-connect-tradfi-with-crypto/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Booster Robert F. Kennedy Jr. Promises To Use Bitcoin To Stabilize US Dollar If He Becomes President</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/crypto-booster-robert-f-kennedy-jr-promises-to-use-bitcoin-to-stabilize-us-dollar-if-he-becomes-president/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/crypto-booster-robert-f-kennedy-jr-promises-to-use-bitcoin-to-stabilize-us-dollar-if-he-becomes-president/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Brenda Ngari]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 13:52:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XBTUSD]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=82962</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Crypto-Booster-Robert-F.-Kennedy-Jr.-Promises-To-Use-Bitcoin-To-Stabilize-US-Dollar-If-He-Becomes-President.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Crypto Booster Robert F. Kennedy Jr. Promises To Use Bitcoin To Stabilize US Dollar If He Becomes President" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Crypto-Booster-Robert-F.-Kennedy-Jr.-Promises-To-Use-Bitcoin-To-Stabilize-US-Dollar-If-He-Becomes-President.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Crypto-Booster-Robert-F.-Kennedy-Jr.-Promises-To-Use-Bitcoin-To-Stabilize-US-Dollar-If-He-Becomes-President-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Crypto-Booster-Robert-F.-Kennedy-Jr.-Promises-To-Use-Bitcoin-To-Stabilize-US-Dollar-If-He-Becomes-President-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Crypto-Booster-Robert-F.-Kennedy-Jr.-Promises-To-Use-Bitcoin-To-Stabilize-US-Dollar-If-He-Becomes-President-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>Democratic presidential hopeful Robert F. Kennedy Jr. has pledged to restore strength to the United States dollar using Bitcoin. The Kennedy family scion also plans to exempt Bitcoin profits from capital gains tax.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Crypto-Booster-Robert-F.-Kennedy-Jr.-Promises-To-Use-Bitcoin-To-Stabilize-US-Dollar-If-He-Becomes-President.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Crypto Booster Robert F. Kennedy Jr. Promises To Use Bitcoin To Stabilize US Dollar If He Becomes President" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Crypto-Booster-Robert-F.-Kennedy-Jr.-Promises-To-Use-Bitcoin-To-Stabilize-US-Dollar-If-He-Becomes-President.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Crypto-Booster-Robert-F.-Kennedy-Jr.-Promises-To-Use-Bitcoin-To-Stabilize-US-Dollar-If-He-Becomes-President-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Crypto-Booster-Robert-F.-Kennedy-Jr.-Promises-To-Use-Bitcoin-To-Stabilize-US-Dollar-If-He-Becomes-President-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Crypto-Booster-Robert-F.-Kennedy-Jr.-Promises-To-Use-Bitcoin-To-Stabilize-US-Dollar-If-He-Becomes-President-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>Democratic presidential hopeful Robert F. Kennedy Jr. has pledged to restore strength to the United States dollar using <a href="https://zycrypto.com/tag/bitcoin">Bitcoin</a>. The Kennedy family scion also plans to exempt Bitcoin profits from capital gains tax.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-backing-the-dollar-with-bitcoin"><strong>Backing The Dollar With Bitcoin</strong></h2>



<p>Presidential candidate Robert F. Kennedy Jr has unveiled an ambitious plan that seeks to revolutionize the financial landscape of the U.S.</p>



<p>Speaking during the Heal-the-Divide PAC event on Wednesday, RFK claimed that backing the U.S. dollar with what he deemed “real finite assets” such as gold, silver, or Bitcoin, could help breathe life into the struggling economy and guarantee the status of the dollar as the world reserve currency.</p>



<p>“Backing dollars and U.S. debt obligations with hard assets could help restore strength back to the dollar, rein in inflation, and usher in a new era of American financial stability, peace, and prosperity.”</p>



<p>He noted that the process would be gradual and that he would revise the amount of backing for the dollar depending on the success of the audacious plan. “My plan would be to start very, very small, perhaps 1% of issued T-bills would be backed by hard currency, by gold, silver platinum or bitcoin,”<em> </em>he posited.</p>



<p>“Ironically we will be able to use bitcoin to save the U.S. dollar,&#8221; Kennedy added.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>RFK Vows To Exempt Bitcoin Profits From Capital Gains Tax</strong></h2>



<p>RFK has previously made waves in the cryptoverse, including when he made a pit stop at the biggest annual industry conference Bitcoin Miami where he declared that he’d “defend the right of self-custody of bitcoin and other digital assets.” He also revealed that his campaign is accepting BTC donations. It was also recently reported that Kennedy holds downwards of $250,000 in crypto.</p>



<p>The high-profile presidential challenger in the July 19 event that he would also exempt Bitcoin to U.S. dollar conversions from capital gains taxes. He said the proposed tax exemption would stimulate investment and encourage startups to establish their businesses within the United States instead of moving to other crypto-friendly jurisdictions like Singapore and Switzerland. In Kennedy’s view, making Bitcoin conversion a non-taxable event would foster innovation, safeguard privacy, and make it more difficult for governments to use digital currency against free speech.</p>



<p>FFK, who has been accused of circulating anti-vaxxer disinformation, has also been noted for his crypto enthusiasm in the past. The high-profile presidential challenger has been outspoken in his evangelism of crypto, including <a href="https://twitter.com/RobertKennedyJr/status/1653808786577010697">bashing </a>a proposed 30% tax on crypto mining, describing the recent avalanche of regulatory enforcement actions against the sector as “an extra-legal war” that has harmed the U.S.’s economic prospects, and <a href="https://zycrypto.com/pro-crypto-presidential-candidate-robert-kennedy-jr-lauds-bitcoin-throws-shade-at-oppressive-cbdcs/">speaking against </a>“oppressive” central bank digital currencies (CBDCs).</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/crypto-booster-robert-f-kennedy-jr-promises-to-use-bitcoin-to-stabilize-us-dollar-if-he-becomes-president/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cathie Wood Strongly Believes Bitcoin Price Is Going To $1.5 Million If This Scenario Unfolds</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/cathie-wood-strongly-believes-bitcoin-price-is-going-to-1-5-million-if-this-scenario-unfolds/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/cathie-wood-strongly-believes-bitcoin-price-is-going-to-1-5-million-if-this-scenario-unfolds/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Brenda Ngari]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 21:50:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XBTUSD]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=82957</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/1-BTC-to-1-Million-Cathie-Wood-Doubles-Down-On-Decade-long-Bitcoin-Price-Prediction.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="1 BTC to $1 Million: Cathie Wood Doubles Down On Decade-long Bitcoin Price Prediction" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/1-BTC-to-1-Million-Cathie-Wood-Doubles-Down-On-Decade-long-Bitcoin-Price-Prediction.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/1-BTC-to-1-Million-Cathie-Wood-Doubles-Down-On-Decade-long-Bitcoin-Price-Prediction-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/1-BTC-to-1-Million-Cathie-Wood-Doubles-Down-On-Decade-long-Bitcoin-Price-Prediction-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/1-BTC-to-1-Million-Cathie-Wood-Doubles-Down-On-Decade-long-Bitcoin-Price-Prediction-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>Cathie Wood of Ark Invest — known for her previously controversial $1 million price target for Bitcoin— has just upped the ante. ]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/1-BTC-to-1-Million-Cathie-Wood-Doubles-Down-On-Decade-long-Bitcoin-Price-Prediction.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="1 BTC to $1 Million: Cathie Wood Doubles Down On Decade-long Bitcoin Price Prediction" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/1-BTC-to-1-Million-Cathie-Wood-Doubles-Down-On-Decade-long-Bitcoin-Price-Prediction.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/1-BTC-to-1-Million-Cathie-Wood-Doubles-Down-On-Decade-long-Bitcoin-Price-Prediction-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/1-BTC-to-1-Million-Cathie-Wood-Doubles-Down-On-Decade-long-Bitcoin-Price-Prediction-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/1-BTC-to-1-Million-Cathie-Wood-Doubles-Down-On-Decade-long-Bitcoin-Price-Prediction-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>ARK Invest CEO Cathie Wood has updated her lofty Bitcoin price forecast. Wood now thinks the premier is going to $1.5 million by 2030. That&#8217;s under its bull-case scenario, while its base case sees BTC hitting $625,000 by that time.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-cathie-wood-says-her-confidence-in-btc-racing-toward-1-5-million-has-risen"><strong>Cathie Wood Says Her Confidence In BTC Racing Toward $1.5 Million Has Risen</strong></h2>



<p>Cathie Wood of Ark Invest — known for her previously <a href="https://zycrypto.com/cathie-wood-sticks-with-1-million-bitcoin-prediction-amid-maelstrom-of-regulatory-crackdowns-heres-why/">controversial $1 million price target</a> for Bitcoin— has just upped the ante.&nbsp;</p>



<p>Wood highlighted her firm’s internal analysis during her latest <a href="https://twitter.com/DocumentingBTC/status/1681277645768540161">interview </a>with <em>Bloomberg </em>to explain her bullish outlook. “Our bull case, I think it&#8217;s $1,500,000 per coin, the best case is $625,000 (something like that),” the asset management titan posited.</p>



<p>As far as why her confidence in Bitcoin has increased, her reasoning boils down to this: the U.S. banking system turmoil that happened in March reinforced the flagship crypto’s long-term outlook to the upside. For Wood, Bitcoin acts as a great hedge against counterparty risk.</p>



<p>&#8220;Bitcoin is an insurance policy. We won&#8217;t have another &#8217;08-&#8217;09 crisis with Bitcoin. It&#8217;s decentralized and transparent,” she opined.</p>



<p>Wood has made no secret of her ultra-bullish stance. She made her first bold prediction in early 2021, <a href="https://zycrypto.com/amid-crypto-market-armageddon-ark-invests-cathie-wood-still-thinks-bitcoin-can-go-to-500000/">forecasting that BTC would reach $500,000 by 2026</a>, owing to the fact that more institutional investors would be moving into the digital asset. Early last year, she ratcheted up her prediction to $1 million per coin by 2030. At the time, ARK based its long-term call on the argument that the top crypto had the potential to “usurp 50% of gold’s role”.</p>



<p>ARK Invest offers several actively managed exchange-traded funds and holds $15 billion in assets under management. It’s hoping to <a href="https://zycrypto.com/ark-invest-gains-edge-in-spot-bitcoin-etf-race-with-epic-surveillance-sharing-maneuver/">roll out a spot Bitcoin ETF product </a>in the near future.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Is Wood’s $1.5 Million Target Realistic Or Outlandish?</strong></h2>



<p>In this scenario, the market capitalization of Bitcoin — already the biggest token — would balloon to around $30 trillion from about $578 billion today, according to <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/bitcoin">CoinGecko</a>. For comparison, the total value of the physical gold supply in the world is estimated to be around $12 trillion. This means that Bitcoin would be roughly 2.5 times more valuable than the entire gold market.</p>



<p>For now, BTC is trading hands at $29,753 after rallying to a new 13-month high of $31,800 on Thursday in the wake of the <a href="https://zycrypto.com/major-ripple-victory-xrp-pops-in-ballistic-rally-as-judge-finally-rules-it-isnt-a-security/">favorable court ruling for Ripple&#8217;s XRP</a>. The crypto is still 56.91% down from its all-time high of $69,044 recorded in November 2021.</p>



<p>It’s hard to say whether or not Wood’s pie-in-the-sky figure of $1.5 million can be considered well justified. Nonetheless, even a $1 million price target seems to be a bit too rosy for BTC bulls. That would indicate a market capitalization of circa $22 trillion, which is nearly 10x the current market value of Apple.</p>



<p>Time will tell whether Wood’s $1.5 million price prediction comes to fruition.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/cathie-wood-strongly-believes-bitcoin-price-is-going-to-1-5-million-if-this-scenario-unfolds/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>SEC vs. Binance: Clash of Titans in the Crypto World</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/sec-vs-binance-clash-of-titans-in-the-crypto-world/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/sec-vs-binance-clash-of-titans-in-the-crypto-world/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Marco Tulio]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 21:40:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=82952</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/Changpeng-Zhao-Says-Binance-Is-10x-Bigger-Than-Its-Closest-Competition-Speaks-On-Regulatory-Challenges.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Changpeng Zhao Says Binance Is 10x Bigger Than Its Closest Competition, Speaks On Regulatory Challenges" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/Changpeng-Zhao-Says-Binance-Is-10x-Bigger-Than-Its-Closest-Competition-Speaks-On-Regulatory-Challenges.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/Changpeng-Zhao-Says-Binance-Is-10x-Bigger-Than-Its-Closest-Competition-Speaks-On-Regulatory-Challenges-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/Changpeng-Zhao-Says-Binance-Is-10x-Bigger-Than-Its-Closest-Competition-Speaks-On-Regulatory-Challenges-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/Changpeng-Zhao-Says-Binance-Is-10x-Bigger-Than-Its-Closest-Competition-Speaks-On-Regulatory-Challenges-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>Binance, the world&#8217;s largest cryptocurrency exchange, expressed disappointment and dissatisfaction with the recent complaint filed by the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), alleging non-compliance issues by the exchange and its affiliated platform, Binance.US. According to Binance, they were taken by surprise by the SEC&#8217;s unilateral decision as the company was engaged in discussions [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/Changpeng-Zhao-Says-Binance-Is-10x-Bigger-Than-Its-Closest-Competition-Speaks-On-Regulatory-Challenges.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Changpeng Zhao Says Binance Is 10x Bigger Than Its Closest Competition, Speaks On Regulatory Challenges" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/Changpeng-Zhao-Says-Binance-Is-10x-Bigger-Than-Its-Closest-Competition-Speaks-On-Regulatory-Challenges.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/Changpeng-Zhao-Says-Binance-Is-10x-Bigger-Than-Its-Closest-Competition-Speaks-On-Regulatory-Challenges-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/Changpeng-Zhao-Says-Binance-Is-10x-Bigger-Than-Its-Closest-Competition-Speaks-On-Regulatory-Challenges-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/Changpeng-Zhao-Says-Binance-Is-10x-Bigger-Than-Its-Closest-Competition-Speaks-On-Regulatory-Challenges-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>Binance, the world&#8217;s largest cryptocurrency exchange, expressed disappointment and dissatisfaction with the recent complaint filed by the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), alleging non-compliance issues by the exchange and its affiliated platform, Binance.US.</p>



<p>According to <a href="https://www.binance.com/en/blog/ecosystem/sec-complaint-aims-to-unilaterally-define-crypto-market-structure-8707489117122437402">Binance</a>, they were taken by surprise by the SEC&#8217;s unilateral decision as the company was engaged in discussions with regulators to reach a negotiated agreement that would resolve the ongoing investigations.</p>



<p>However, the regulators chose to close those doors and proceed with <a href="https://zycrypto.com/us-sec-files-fresh-charges-against-binance-and-ceo-changpeng-zhao/">legal actions</a>. Binance considers this tactic &#8220;regrettable&#8221; given their collaborative efforts.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-binance-vs-sec-a-battle-for-the-future-of-the-crypto-industry"><strong>Binance vs. SEC: A Battle For The Future of The Crypto Industry</strong></h2>



<p>Binance indicated that despite the SEC&#8217;s limited jurisdiction over them as a non-U.S. exchange, they are ready to vigorously defend their platform and protect the interests of their users. Binance believes that the accusations brought forth by the SEC, under the guise of &#8220;emergency,&#8221; lack justification.</p>



<p>&#8220;Because Binance is not a U.S. exchange, the SEC&#8217;s actions are limited in reach. Still, we stand with digital asset market participants in the U.S., opposing the SEC&#8217;s latest overreach, and we are fully prepared to fight it within the boundaries of the law.&#8221;</p>



<p>Furthermore, Binance has highlighted the lack of clarity and guidance within the <a href="https://zycrypto.com/cz-refutes-report-binance-is-considering-delisting-u-s-based-projects-in-face-of-crypto-regulatory-storm/">U.S. regulatory environment</a> for cryptocurrencies. They argue that this situation is hindering the country&#8217;s role as a global technological center by impeding progress and sector development.</p>



<p>Binance has emphasized that all user assets on their platforms, including Binance.US, remain secure and protected. They categorically refute any claims suggesting otherwise. These reassurances come in response to recent allegations published by Reuters, indicating that Binance commingled client funds with company revenue, thereby violating U.S. financial regulations.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Hoskinson Warns of SEC&#8217;s Accusation For State-controlled CBDC</strong></h2>



<p>Charles Hoskinson, founder of Cardano and co-founder of Ethereum, indicated that the SEC&#8217;s accusation &#8220;seems like the next step in a series of measures to implement chokepoint 2.0 in the United States.&#8221; The ultimate goal, according to Hoskinson, is the launch of a state-controlled central bank digital currency (CBDC).</p>



<p>He further added that although this situation is not entirely unprecedented, it presents a perfect opportunity for the &#8220;fragmented&#8221; crypto industry to unite and confront regulators. Their aim is to prevent the country from falling into a dystopian state that would make the 1984 banking crisis look like a vacation.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/sec-vs-binance-clash-of-titans-in-the-crypto-world/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
