<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>News Archives &#8902; ZyCrypto</title>
	<atom:link href="https://zycrypto.com/category/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://zycrypto.com/category/news/</link>
	<description>ZyCrypto Is A Cryptocurrency News Media, Focusing On Daily News, Expert Opinions, Analysis, Reviews, And So Much More.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 21:50:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/cropped-ZyCrypto-Site-Logo-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News Archives &#8902; ZyCrypto</title>
	<link>https://zycrypto.com/category/news/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Cardano-Centered Stablecoin Djed Set to Debut in January — ADA Poised For Rapid Adoption</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/cardano-centered-stablecoin-djed-set-to-debut-in-january-ada-poised-for-rapid-adoption/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/cardano-centered-stablecoin-djed-set-to-debut-in-january-ada-poised-for-rapid-adoption/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Olivia Brooke]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 21:50:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADAUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=76624</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Major-Bullish-Milestone-For-ADA-As-First-USD-Backed-Stablecoin-On-Cardano-Goes-Live.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Major Bullish Milestone For ADA As First USD-Backed Stablecoin On Cardano Goes Live" decoding="async" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Major-Bullish-Milestone-For-ADA-As-First-USD-Backed-Stablecoin-On-Cardano-Goes-Live.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Major-Bullish-Milestone-For-ADA-As-First-USD-Backed-Stablecoin-On-Cardano-Goes-Live-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Major-Bullish-Milestone-For-ADA-As-First-USD-Backed-Stablecoin-On-Cardano-Goes-Live-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Major-Bullish-Milestone-For-ADA-As-First-USD-Backed-Stablecoin-On-Cardano-Goes-Live-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>The Cardano blockchain gears up to see the launch of one of its most anticipated stablecoin projects, Djed.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Major-Bullish-Milestone-For-ADA-As-First-USD-Backed-Stablecoin-On-Cardano-Goes-Live.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Major Bullish Milestone For ADA As First USD-Backed Stablecoin On Cardano Goes Live" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Major-Bullish-Milestone-For-ADA-As-First-USD-Backed-Stablecoin-On-Cardano-Goes-Live.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Major-Bullish-Milestone-For-ADA-As-First-USD-Backed-Stablecoin-On-Cardano-Goes-Live-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Major-Bullish-Milestone-For-ADA-As-First-USD-Backed-Stablecoin-On-Cardano-Goes-Live-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Major-Bullish-Milestone-For-ADA-As-First-USD-Backed-Stablecoin-On-Cardano-Goes-Live-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>The Cardano blockchain gears up to see the launch of one of its most anticipated stablecoin projects, Djed. Shahaf Bar-Geffen, the head of COTI Network, reiterated during an interview that the <a href="https://zycrypto.com/cardano-unveils-djed-an-innovative-stablecoin-for-the-fast-growing-ecosystem-issued-by-coti/">algorithm stablecoin</a> would launch on the mainnet in January.</p>



<p>Speaking with popular Cardano-focused podcaster, &#8216;bigpey,&#8217; Shahaf stated:</p>



<p><em>&#8220;Next month is our goal to launch the mainnet of Djed and Shen. Right now, you can play with the testnet on Djed.xyz.&#8221;</em></p>



<p>Bar-Geffen notes that the launch took this long because developers wanted to ensure that the stablecoin integrates with Cardano&#8217;s Vasil hardfork. Conducting audits also added to the delay of the launch. According to the COTI CEO, developers conducted two rigorous audits to test the security of the stablecoin&#8217;s smart contract.</p>



<p><em>&#8220;One thing we cannot fail on is security. If people are not interested in the product…, I can live with that. I can&#8217;t live with leaving security vulnerabilities in the code without doing everything that we could to make sure that we block all hedges,&#8221; he said.</em></p>



<p>Meanwhile, he also revealed that COTI and IOG would open-source the highly complicated smart contract that powers the stablecoin shortly after launch. COTI first announced the January launch timeline of Djed during the Cardano Summit back in November.</p>



<h2 id="h-djed-is-already-poised-to-gain-adoption-in-the-cardano-ecosystem"><strong>Djed is already poised to gain adoption in the Cardano ecosystem</strong></h2>



<p>The Djed algorithmic stablecoin launch comes with many perks to the Cardano blockchain. Djed boasts of being backed by only cryptocurrencies — including SHEN, its reserve currency, and ADA, the native token of Cardano.</p>



<p>The stablecoin could likely see very rapid adoption due to the fact that it is overcollateralized and has an on-chain proof-of-reserve. COTI already partnered with several Cardano decentralized finance protocols to integrate the stablecoin at launch.</p>



<p>However, this expectation may not play out for several reasons. For one, trust in algorithmic stablecoins has been notably low in the crypto space <a href="https://zycrypto.com/i-bet-big-and-i-think-i-lost-do-kwon-speaks-on-terras-crash/">since the crash</a> of Terra&#8217;s UST and its sister token, LUNA.</p>



<p>Similarly, other stablecoin projects that will compete with Djed are also under development in the Cardano ecosystem. Notably, some of these projects have also run into their own problems.</p>



<p>Last month, Ardana, a company developing a fiat-backed fully reserved stablecoin for the Cardano ecosystem, shut down due to funding problems. Charles Hodkinson, the IOG CEO, commented that it was unfortunate how the project went down. He, however, remains optimistic that more projects will spring up as Cardano grows to become an ecosystem of blockchains.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/cardano-centered-stablecoin-djed-set-to-debut-in-january-ada-poised-for-rapid-adoption/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Companies Seek Partnership And Acquisition Strategies For Business Development</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/crypto-companies-seek-partnership-and-acquisition-strategies-for-business-development/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/crypto-companies-seek-partnership-and-acquisition-strategies-for-business-development/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Isa Nsereko]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 21:35:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=76622</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Crypto-Companies-Seek-Partnership-And-Acquisiton-Strategies-For-Business-Development.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Crypto Companies Seek Partnership And Acquisiton Strategies For Business Development" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Crypto-Companies-Seek-Partnership-And-Acquisiton-Strategies-For-Business-Development.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Crypto-Companies-Seek-Partnership-And-Acquisiton-Strategies-For-Business-Development-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Crypto-Companies-Seek-Partnership-And-Acquisiton-Strategies-For-Business-Development-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Crypto-Companies-Seek-Partnership-And-Acquisiton-Strategies-For-Business-Development-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>According to a November 30, 2022 news announcement on its website, Poloniex has entered into a strategic partnership with Huobi that involves working together on ecosystem expansion, project cooperation, liquidity support, and global compliance. Poloniex is a cryptocurrency exchange and service provider, founded in 2014. Huobi is a Seychelles-based cryptocurrency exchange founded in 2013 in [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Crypto-Companies-Seek-Partnership-And-Acquisiton-Strategies-For-Business-Development.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Crypto Companies Seek Partnership And Acquisiton Strategies For Business Development" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Crypto-Companies-Seek-Partnership-And-Acquisiton-Strategies-For-Business-Development.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Crypto-Companies-Seek-Partnership-And-Acquisiton-Strategies-For-Business-Development-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Crypto-Companies-Seek-Partnership-And-Acquisiton-Strategies-For-Business-Development-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Crypto-Companies-Seek-Partnership-And-Acquisiton-Strategies-For-Business-Development-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>According to a November 30, 2022 news announcement on its website, Poloniex has entered into a strategic partnership with Huobi that involves working together on ecosystem expansion, project cooperation, liquidity support, and global compliance.</p>



<p>Poloniex is a cryptocurrency exchange and service provider, founded in 2014. Huobi is a Seychelles-based cryptocurrency exchange founded in 2013 in China and was publicly listed in Hong Kong in 2018.</p>



<p>According to the announcement on Huobi, with effect from December 2022, Huobi will evaluate all projects on Poloniex on a monthly basis with top performing projects standing a chance to be listed directly on Huobi, enjoy full support from Huobi, and get access to users from Huobi. Both parties have stated that going forwards, they will progressively pursue strategic partnerships with other players in the industry.</p>



<p>In a November 30, 2022 blog, Binance, the world’s largest crypto exchange by trading volumes, announced that it had acquired 100% of&nbsp; the Japanese-registered crypto exchange service provider, Sakura Exchange BitCoin (SEBC). This acquisition allows the entry of Binance into the Japanese market as a Japan Financial Services Agency (JFSA) regulated entity. SEBC offers consultation and brokerage services to its customers.</p>



<p><em>“We are honored and delighted to make this announcement with Binance, one of the world’s leading crypto asset exchange service providers. On top of our effort to prioritize user protection, Binance’s strong compliance system will contribute to building a more compliant atmosphere for users in Japan and help them access key crypto services needed for mass adoption in the future”, said Hitomi Yamamoto, the CEO of SEBC.</em></p>



<p>Crypto.com is an official sponsor of the 2022 FIFA World Cup in Qatar. Through the partnership with FIFA, Crypto.com aims to drive awareness of its trading platform to an estimated global audience of over 5 billion watching the world cup event. Crypto.com, in partnership with Coca-Cola, is also launching a series of non-fungible tokens (NFTs) to celebrate the 2022 FIFA World Cup in Qatar. Crypto.com has other sports partnerships in motorsport, basketball, and ice hockey.</p>



<p>Strategic partnerships and acquisitions offer companies the opportunity to attract new customers, to drive innovation&nbsp; and to outperform competitors. Other reasons for strategic partnerships and acquisitions include the ability to expand into new or niche markets, for conducting research aimed at improving existing technologies or for exploring new technologies.</p>



<p>Though the terms of Binance&#8217;s acquisition of SEBC are yet to be fully disclosed, crypto exchanges and companies are seeking strategic partnerships and acquisitions to attract new customers, increase exchange liquidity, expand product offering, to facilitate token listings, and to deal with regulatory barriers.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/crypto-companies-seek-partnership-and-acquisition-strategies-for-business-development/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Are Fears of Bitcoin Miners’ Selling Pressure Overblown? This Expert Thinks So</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/are-fears-of-bitcoin-miners-selling-pressure-overblown-this-expert-thinks-so/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/are-fears-of-bitcoin-miners-selling-pressure-overblown-this-expert-thinks-so/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Newton Gitonga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 20:08:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XBTUSD]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=76619</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/Bitcoin-Miners-Are-Changing-The-Energy-Industry-Here-Is-How-They-Are-Doing-It.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Bitcoin Miners Are Changing The Energy Industry: Here Is How They Are Doing It" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/Bitcoin-Miners-Are-Changing-The-Energy-Industry-Here-Is-How-They-Are-Doing-It.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/Bitcoin-Miners-Are-Changing-The-Energy-Industry-Here-Is-How-They-Are-Doing-It-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/Bitcoin-Miners-Are-Changing-The-Energy-Industry-Here-Is-How-They-Are-Doing-It-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/Bitcoin-Miners-Are-Changing-The-Energy-Industry-Here-Is-How-They-Are-Doing-It-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>Crypto’s stretched-out bear market cycle has been attributed to many factors, key among them unfavourable monetary policies by the US Fed, the Russo-Ukrainian war, global pandemics and the FTX debacle.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/Bitcoin-Miners-Are-Changing-The-Energy-Industry-Here-Is-How-They-Are-Doing-It.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Bitcoin Miners Are Changing The Energy Industry: Here Is How They Are Doing It" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/Bitcoin-Miners-Are-Changing-The-Energy-Industry-Here-Is-How-They-Are-Doing-It.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/Bitcoin-Miners-Are-Changing-The-Energy-Industry-Here-Is-How-They-Are-Doing-It-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/Bitcoin-Miners-Are-Changing-The-Energy-Industry-Here-Is-How-They-Are-Doing-It-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/Bitcoin-Miners-Are-Changing-The-Energy-Industry-Here-Is-How-They-Are-Doing-It-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>Crypto’s stretched-out bear market cycle has been attributed to many factors, key among them unfavourable monetary policies by the US Fed, the Russo-Ukrainian war, global pandemics and the FTX debacle.</p>



<p>Notably, fears of a further sell-off being occasioned by BTC miners dumping to avoid losing their hard-earned rewards and support their operations have been rising. However, according to Jaran Mellerud, a Bitcoin mining analyst and consultant, claims about miners dumping and sparking a major BTC sell-off are puffed up.</p>



<p>Today, the pundit explained why BTC miners are unlikely to cause any significant sell-off in the market, noting that such-like claims were “extremely overblown”. While the public image of miners as enormous bitcoin holders and influential market participants might have been accurate in the early years when the block reward was 50BTC, and miners held a higher portion of Bitcoins circulating supply, he noted that “times have changed, and miners no longer hold a meaningful share of the bitcoin supply.”</p>



<p>It is important to note that for miners to <a href="https://zycrypto.com/former-bitmex-ceo-arthur-hayes-on-why-bitcoin-price-has-likely-reached-bottom/">influence price</a> significantly, they must collectively own a substantial portion of Bitcoin’s circulating supply. As per data from CoinMarketCap, Bitcoin’s circulating supply is 19.2 million BTC. Bitcoin miners are estimated to hold only 1% to 4% of that supply (Roughly 120,000 BTC to 820,000 BTC).</p>



<p>According to Mellerud, <em>“Even if miners sold 300% of their production (2700 BTC daily), it would not amount to more than 0.6% of bitcoin&#8217;s spot volume.”</em></p>



<p>He emphasised that the only worst-case scenario of Miners impacting the spot market was if they dumped their entire holdings once-which again, was “implausible”. Considering miners held 120,000 BTC, if they liquidated all their holdings over 30 days, it would amount to only 1% of the spot volume in an exchange like Binance, which handles an average of 430,000 BTC in daily trading, meaning it would not move markets on a whim.</p>



<p>On the other hand, considering they held 820,000 BTC and sold it all over 30 days, it would be almost 7% of Bitcoin&#8217;s spot volume. The spot market would lack sufficient liquidity to accommodate such large sales, plummeting Bitcoin&#8217;s prices. As ZyCrypto reported, miners sold a maximum of 350% of their <a href="https://zycrypto.com/bitcoins-mining-reserves-plunge-to-12-year-low-heres-what-it-means/">daily production</a> this year, which didn’t even come close to 1% of Bitcoin&#8217;s total spot volume.</p>



<p>The analyst concluded that “<em>Bitcoin&#8217;s spot market has strong liquidity and should be able to accommodate the selling pressure from miners.” </em>Based on his assessment, the selling pressure from miners was thus “<em>overrated and will gradually weaken as the block reward gets smaller”.</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/are-fears-of-bitcoin-miners-selling-pressure-overblown-this-expert-thinks-so/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>FTX&#8217;s Sam Bankman-Fried Accepts Extradition To The US After Deadlock</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/ftxs-sam-bankman-fried-accepts-extradition-to-the-us-after-deadlock/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/ftxs-sam-bankman-fried-accepts-extradition-to-the-us-after-deadlock/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Newton Gitonga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 20:03:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=76616</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/FTXs-Sam-Bankman-Fried-Accepts-Extradition-To-The-US-After-Deadlock.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="FTX&#039;s Sam Bankman-Fried Accepts Extradition To The US After Deadlock" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/FTXs-Sam-Bankman-Fried-Accepts-Extradition-To-The-US-After-Deadlock.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/FTXs-Sam-Bankman-Fried-Accepts-Extradition-To-The-US-After-Deadlock-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/FTXs-Sam-Bankman-Fried-Accepts-Extradition-To-The-US-After-Deadlock-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/FTXs-Sam-Bankman-Fried-Accepts-Extradition-To-The-US-After-Deadlock-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>Beleaguered FTX ex-CEO Sam Bankman Fried (SBF) could be extradited to the United States as early as this week.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/FTXs-Sam-Bankman-Fried-Accepts-Extradition-To-The-US-After-Deadlock.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="FTX&#039;s Sam Bankman-Fried Accepts Extradition To The US After Deadlock" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/FTXs-Sam-Bankman-Fried-Accepts-Extradition-To-The-US-After-Deadlock.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/FTXs-Sam-Bankman-Fried-Accepts-Extradition-To-The-US-After-Deadlock-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/FTXs-Sam-Bankman-Fried-Accepts-Extradition-To-The-US-After-Deadlock-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/FTXs-Sam-Bankman-Fried-Accepts-Extradition-To-The-US-After-Deadlock-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>Beleaguered FTX ex-CEO Sam Bankman Fried (SBF) could be extradited to the United States as early as this week.</p>



<p>According to a New York Times (NYT) report, SBF reportedly told the court in the Bahamas on Monday that he was ready to waive his right to fight extradition to the US, where he faces an array of charges following the collapse of his crypto exchange last month.</p>



<p>The hearing, which took less than an hour, was unexpected, with SBF’s local defence lawyer Jerone Roberts saying that he had not been informed of the hearing. The court reportedly accorded a 15 minutes recess to allow Roberts to confer with SBF over his extradition remarks. The lawyer later told the court that his client wanted to see the indictment against him before agreeing to extradition. However, due to the mix-up, the judge decided to send SBF back to prison pending a proper hearing.</p>



<p>Monday’s session is the latest scene in the high-stakes drama that has been playing out since <a href="https://zycrypto.com/ftxs-founder-sam-bankman-fried-arrested-in-the-bahamas/">SBF was arrested last week</a> following a request by the United States authorities. SBF, 30, is facing over eight charges in the US, including conspiracy to commit wire fraud on customers; conspiracy to commit wire fraud on lenders; conspiracy to commit securities fraud; conspiracy to commit money laundering; and conspiracy to violate the campaign finance.</p>



<p>SBF’s legal team asked the judge to release him on $250,000 cash bail in his first arraignment last week. The team also declared that their client would fight extradition to the United States should it be requested. The court, however, denied their request to have SBF released on bail, with the prosecution labelling him as a flight risk. </p>



<p>Whereas it is unclear what led to SBF’s change of attitude, a source who asked not to be identified noted that it was likely because he would be able to get bail in the US. Some believe that SBF would rather be held in the relatively luxurious US correction facilities than in his current Bahamian corrections department, which is said to be overcrowded and dirty.</p>



<p>Reports circulating in the past week described Fox Hill jail in Nassau-SBF’s current prison-as overcrowded and that he was sharing a small cell with five other individuals. According to a Dec 17 report by the NY Times, a former inmate freed from jail last year described the prison as saying, “It’s no living situation for no type of living being.”&nbsp;</p>



<p>The disgraced CEO will also likely receive vegan meals and proper medical care with his apparent deficit disorder (ADD) diagnosis in US facilities, unlike his current facility.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/ftxs-sam-bankman-fried-accepts-extradition-to-the-us-after-deadlock/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum’s Co-founder Vitalik Buterin Discloses Three Landmark Opportunities For Crypto In 2023</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/ethereums-co-founder-vitalik-buterin-discloses-three-landmark-opportunities-for-crypto-in-2023/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/ethereums-co-founder-vitalik-buterin-discloses-three-landmark-opportunities-for-crypto-in-2023/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aliyu Pokima]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 19:37:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=76614</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Ethereums-Vitalik-Buterin-Claps-Back-At-PoS-Skeptics-Ahead-Of-The-Merge.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Ethereum’s Vitalik Buterin Claps Back At PoS Skeptics Ahead Of The Merge" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Ethereums-Vitalik-Buterin-Claps-Back-At-PoS-Skeptics-Ahead-Of-The-Merge.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Ethereums-Vitalik-Buterin-Claps-Back-At-PoS-Skeptics-Ahead-Of-The-Merge-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Ethereums-Vitalik-Buterin-Claps-Back-At-PoS-Skeptics-Ahead-Of-The-Merge-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Ethereums-Vitalik-Buterin-Claps-Back-At-PoS-Skeptics-Ahead-Of-The-Merge-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>It is that time of the year when crypto executives and industry players map out clear-cut plans for the new year, and Vitalik Buterin has hinted at three favourable areas.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Ethereums-Vitalik-Buterin-Claps-Back-At-PoS-Skeptics-Ahead-Of-The-Merge.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Ethereum’s Vitalik Buterin Claps Back At PoS Skeptics Ahead Of The Merge" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Ethereums-Vitalik-Buterin-Claps-Back-At-PoS-Skeptics-Ahead-Of-The-Merge.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Ethereums-Vitalik-Buterin-Claps-Back-At-PoS-Skeptics-Ahead-Of-The-Merge-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Ethereums-Vitalik-Buterin-Claps-Back-At-PoS-Skeptics-Ahead-Of-The-Merge-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Ethereums-Vitalik-Buterin-Claps-Back-At-PoS-Skeptics-Ahead-Of-The-Merge-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<ul>
<li>Vitalik Buterin shares “huge opportunities” for developers in digital asset spaces in 2023.</li>



<li>The Ethereum co-founder pointed to crypto wallets, revolutionary stablecoins, and using crypto to take down big tech.</li>



<li>Is the mass adoption wave over? Vitalik Buterin and David Hofman share opposing views.&nbsp;</li>
</ul>



<p>It is that time of the year when crypto executives and industry players map out clear-cut plans for the new year, and Vitalik Buterin has hinted at three favourable areas.</p>



<p>During an interview with Bankless&#8217;s David Hoffman, he shared what he believes are the three biggest opportunities. Responding to an issue raised by Hoffman on his concerns that the digital asset mass adoption wave is over, Buterin answered in the negative and went on the list of three areas of growth in 2023.</p>



<p>First is digital asset wallets highlighting the need for special attention to wallet infrastructure to enable billions of users seamlessly. </p>



<p><em>“If you can make a wallet that a billion people will use, that&#8217;s a huge opportunity,” </em>said Buterin.</p>



<p>Next is stablecoins, which has been a touchy subject this year following the collapse of Terra in May. For Buterin, there are still “more opportunities for developers to build in web3.”</p>



<p>The aim for developers in 2023 is to build a hyper-inflation-resistant stable that will be revolutionary in the industry.</p>



<p><em>“If you can make a stablecoin that can actually survive anything up to, and including, a U.S. dollar hyperinflation, that’s a huge opportunity as well if you can create something that will feel like a lifeline for everyone going through that situation,” </em>Buterin said.</p>



<p>Finally, he suggested technical developments in blockchains to compete with big tech using Ethereum as a reference point. If developers can use blockchains to “fight” centralized entities like Google and Facebook, they will lead to more market dominance for developers in the industry.</p>



<p><em>“If you can get signed in with Ethereum to work and if you can unseat Facebook and Google and Twitter as the login overlords of the internet, that itself is a huge opportunity, right?”&nbsp;</em></p>



<h2 id="h-2023-can-be-a-turning-point"><strong>2023 can be a turning point</strong></h2>



<p>After a bad year for digital assets, industry participants have their eyes glued to a better year ahead. The events that gave this year a negative outlook ranged from scams to the <a href="https://zycrypto.com/crypto-exchange-binance-temporarily-halts-withdrawal-of-luna-and-ust-on-the-terra-network/">collapse</a> of popular entities like Terra and FTX.</p>



<p>In the wake of all these, users are still keen on a bull run with some floating popular statements across social media like “all the bad eggs have left crypto in 2022.” Suppose 2023 is going to take a new look. In that case, things need to be in place from early January, including clear-cut regulations and more use cases like Buterin suggested driving increased adoption. </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/ethereums-co-founder-vitalik-buterin-discloses-three-landmark-opportunities-for-crypto-in-2023/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dogecoin Takes Biggest Hit, Falls 18% Following Elon Musk’s Twitter Poll</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/dogecoin-takes-biggest-hit-falls-18-following-elon-musks-twitter-poll/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/dogecoin-takes-biggest-hit-falls-18-following-elon-musks-twitter-poll/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aliyu Pokima]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 19:31:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Doge]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DOGEUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elon Musk]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Twitter]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=76612</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Dogecoins-Future-Could-Follow-This-Bullish-Trajectory-To-1-DOGE-Price-Thanks-To-Elon-Musk.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Dogecoin&#039;s Future Could Follow This Bullish Trajectory To $1 DOGE Price Thanks To Elon Musk" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Dogecoins-Future-Could-Follow-This-Bullish-Trajectory-To-1-DOGE-Price-Thanks-To-Elon-Musk.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Dogecoins-Future-Could-Follow-This-Bullish-Trajectory-To-1-DOGE-Price-Thanks-To-Elon-Musk-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Dogecoins-Future-Could-Follow-This-Bullish-Trajectory-To-1-DOGE-Price-Thanks-To-Elon-Musk-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Dogecoins-Future-Could-Follow-This-Bullish-Trajectory-To-1-DOGE-Price-Thanks-To-Elon-Musk-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>After the digital asset market took a bearish look as a result of the recent hike in interest rates, Dogecoin (DOGE), has taken further steps back following a controversial Twitter poll. ]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Dogecoins-Future-Could-Follow-This-Bullish-Trajectory-To-1-DOGE-Price-Thanks-To-Elon-Musk.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Dogecoin&#039;s Future Could Follow This Bullish Trajectory To $1 DOGE Price Thanks To Elon Musk" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Dogecoins-Future-Could-Follow-This-Bullish-Trajectory-To-1-DOGE-Price-Thanks-To-Elon-Musk.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Dogecoins-Future-Could-Follow-This-Bullish-Trajectory-To-1-DOGE-Price-Thanks-To-Elon-Musk-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Dogecoins-Future-Could-Follow-This-Bullish-Trajectory-To-1-DOGE-Price-Thanks-To-Elon-Musk-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Dogecoins-Future-Could-Follow-This-Bullish-Trajectory-To-1-DOGE-Price-Thanks-To-Elon-Musk-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<ul>
<li>Dogecoin takes a nosedive after Twitter users vote for Elon Musk to leave the CEO role.</li>



<li>The meme coin has fallen over 18% a few hours after the poll, signalling the strong ties Musk has with the coin. </li>



<li>Experts&#8217; analysis points to the high possibility of Twitter still incorporating Dogecoin with Musk’s imminent departure.</li>
</ul>



<p>After the digital asset market took a bearish look as a result of the recent hike in interest rates, Dogecoin (DOGE) took further steps back following a controversial Twitter poll.</p>



<p>Elon Musk took over the management of Twitter in October after a $44 billion buyout, but things have looked shaky since he took over the helm of affairs. In his bid to make the platform more decentralized, Musk deployed Twitter polls to encourage user participation in high-profile decision-making.</p>



<p>In his recent poll on Monday, he asked if he should step down as the head of Twitter, and 57.5% voted in favour. The result of the poll has affected Musk’s backed Dogecoin leading to double figure losses.</p>



<p>DOGE dipped 11% in a few hours to trade at $0.07, coupled with panic from users that with Musk gone, the Dogecoin partnership with the social media gains <a href="https://zycrypto.com/elon-musk-mulls-resigning-as-ceo-of-twitter-whats-next-for-dogecoin/">may become strained</a>. The recent slide of the biggest meme coin has been the sequence of events as the asset has risen and fallen in the past due to Musk’s involvement.</p>



<p>Dogecoin has shown little signs of recovery since it fell by 11% and now trades at $0.074, with bulls trying to push their favourite asset back to its highs in early November.</p>



<p>Altcoins, including Ethereum (ETH) and Solana (SOL), alongside the S&amp;P 500, NASDAQ, and Dow Jones Industrial Average lost points in the past 48 hours as the market still flashed red.</p>



<h2 id="h-twitter-is-still-with-dogecoin"><strong>Twitter is still with Dogecoin</strong></h2>



<p>DOGE has recorded successes since its creation as a meme coin, but most of its triumphs have been linked with Musk. From his Saturday Night Live (SNL) appearance, which pushed the asset to its all-time high of $0.73, to his recent Twitter <a href="https://zycrypto.com/dogecoin-sprints-north-as-musk-pledges-to-close-twitter-acquisition-deal-by-friday-1-doge-coming/">acquisition</a>, which saw the coin trade at a year high of $0.14.</p>



<p>Despite the decision of the new Twitter chief executive, Musk still remains in the management of the company, and so far, there have been no signs of the company cutting ties with cryptocurrencies. Last month Musk revealed plans to integrate new payment systems into Twitter, sparking DOGE to a 19.4% uphill run.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/dogecoin-takes-biggest-hit-falls-18-following-elon-musks-twitter-poll/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Nigeria Set To Consider Bitcoin As A Legal Tender: Here’s All You Need To Know</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/nigeria-set-to-consider-bitcoin-as-a-legal-tender-heres-all-you-need-to-know/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/nigeria-set-to-consider-bitcoin-as-a-legal-tender-heres-all-you-need-to-know/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aliyu Pokima]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 21:13:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Nigeria]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=76555</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/Central-African-Republic-Looks-To-Strengthen-Economic-Trajectory-With-Bitcoin-As-Legal-Tender.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Central African Republic Looks To Strengthen Economic Trajectory With Bitcoin As Legal Tender" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/Central-African-Republic-Looks-To-Strengthen-Economic-Trajectory-With-Bitcoin-As-Legal-Tender.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/Central-African-Republic-Looks-To-Strengthen-Economic-Trajectory-With-Bitcoin-As-Legal-Tender-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/Central-African-Republic-Looks-To-Strengthen-Economic-Trajectory-With-Bitcoin-As-Legal-Tender-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/Central-African-Republic-Looks-To-Strengthen-Economic-Trajectory-With-Bitcoin-As-Legal-Tender-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>Africa’s most populous country, Nigeria, may be next in line to consider bitcoin and other cryptocurrencies as legal tender in 2023 as it prepares a law to recognize digital assets.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/Central-African-Republic-Looks-To-Strengthen-Economic-Trajectory-With-Bitcoin-As-Legal-Tender.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Central African Republic Looks To Strengthen Economic Trajectory With Bitcoin As Legal Tender" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/Central-African-Republic-Looks-To-Strengthen-Economic-Trajectory-With-Bitcoin-As-Legal-Tender.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/Central-African-Republic-Looks-To-Strengthen-Economic-Trajectory-With-Bitcoin-As-Legal-Tender-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/Central-African-Republic-Looks-To-Strengthen-Economic-Trajectory-With-Bitcoin-As-Legal-Tender-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/Central-African-Republic-Looks-To-Strengthen-Economic-Trajectory-With-Bitcoin-As-Legal-Tender-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<ul>
<li>Reports have made rounds concerning Nigeria’s decision to allow Bitcoin as a payment solution.&nbsp;</li>



<li>Hopes for the change in government policy hinged on the proposed amendment to the Investment and Securities Act 2007.&nbsp;</li>



<li>Nigerian crypto enthusiasts say they need their government to back digital assets for good as it will, in turn, push up the eNaira. </li>
</ul>



<p>Africa’s most populous country, Nigeria, may be next in line to consider bitcoin and other cryptocurrencies as legal tender in 2023 as it prepares a law to recognize digital assets.</p>



<p>Babangida Ibrahim, the House of Representatives Committee Chairman on Capital Markets, said in an interview that the law which will recognize digital assets is being pushed to keep up with “<em>recent global practices.”</em></p>



<p><em>“Like I said earlier during the second reading, we need an efficient and vibrant capital market in Nigeria. For us to do that, we have to be up to date with global practices.”</em></p>



<p>The hopes of recognizing Bitcoin rests on the proposed Investment and Securities Act which will empower the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) to “<em>recognize digital assets and funds as capital for investments.” </em>The landmark legislation would also set clear-cut roles of administrative bodies in the country regarding digital assets.</p>



<p>The roles of the Central Bank and the SEC have clashed in several jurisdictions regarding the control of virtual currencies. In Nigeria, users called out the Central Bank after it placed a ban on cryptocurrencies and exchanges last year, saying it has encroached into the territory of the SEC.</p>



<p>The proposed law comes as the new <a href="https://zycrypto.com/nigerias-cbdc-launch-all-the-sides-of-the-coin/">e-naira&#8217;s</a> poor adoption makes rounds. The country’s Central Bank digital currency (CBDC) has only recorded a meagre 0.5% a year after its launch, with many blaming the government’s indecisive policies regarding the state of blockchain and virtual currencies.</p>



<h2 id="h-nigeria-s-policy-holding-a-potential-mass-adoption"><strong>Nigeria’s policy holding a potential mass adoption</strong></h2>



<p>With a population of over 200 million people, Nigeria has an edge in terms of potential blockchain and web3 projects as investors can leverage the growing population. Despite this advantage, most projects cited in Africa have gone to neighbouring countries due to the government’s mixed blockchain policies. </p>



<p>In 2021, the Central Bank of Nigeria issued a statement prohibiting the activities of digital asset exchanges in the country as well as other cryptocurrency activities. The <a href="https://zycrypto.com/nigerias-minister-urges-the-government-to-embrace-cryptocurrencies-after-stringent-bans/">ban</a> was far-reaching as it compelled banks to close accounts related to cryptocurrencies. Despite all this, Nigeria’s potential for digital asset adoption remains intact as the 11th-highest crypto market in 2022.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/nigeria-set-to-consider-bitcoin-as-a-legal-tender-heres-all-you-need-to-know/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>XRP Army Eager To Receive Verdict On Ripple vs. SEC Lawsuit As Attorney Sets Tentative Settlement Date</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/xrp-army-eager-to-receive-verdict-on-ripple-vs-sec-lawsuit-as-attorney-sets-tentative-settlement-date/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/xrp-army-eager-to-receive-verdict-on-ripple-vs-sec-lawsuit-as-attorney-sets-tentative-settlement-date/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jared Kirui]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 20:38:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=76550</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Ripple-Lawsuit-SECs-Win-Against-This-Blockchain-Firm-in-A-High-Profile-Securities-Case-Unnerves-XRP-Army.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Ripple Lawsuit: SEC&#039;s Win Against This Blockchain Firm in A High-Profile Securities Case Unnerves XRP Army" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Ripple-Lawsuit-SECs-Win-Against-This-Blockchain-Firm-in-A-High-Profile-Securities-Case-Unnerves-XRP-Army.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Ripple-Lawsuit-SECs-Win-Against-This-Blockchain-Firm-in-A-High-Profile-Securities-Case-Unnerves-XRP-Army-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Ripple-Lawsuit-SECs-Win-Against-This-Blockchain-Firm-in-A-High-Profile-Securities-Case-Unnerves-XRP-Army-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Ripple-Lawsuit-SECs-Win-Against-This-Blockchain-Firm-in-A-High-Profile-Securities-Case-Unnerves-XRP-Army-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>Ripple's XRP price has been consolidating as investors await a court decision in the case with the SEC.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Ripple-Lawsuit-SECs-Win-Against-This-Blockchain-Firm-in-A-High-Profile-Securities-Case-Unnerves-XRP-Army.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Ripple Lawsuit: SEC&#039;s Win Against This Blockchain Firm in A High-Profile Securities Case Unnerves XRP Army" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Ripple-Lawsuit-SECs-Win-Against-This-Blockchain-Firm-in-A-High-Profile-Securities-Case-Unnerves-XRP-Army.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Ripple-Lawsuit-SECs-Win-Against-This-Blockchain-Firm-in-A-High-Profile-Securities-Case-Unnerves-XRP-Army-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Ripple-Lawsuit-SECs-Win-Against-This-Blockchain-Firm-in-A-High-Profile-Securities-Case-Unnerves-XRP-Army-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Ripple-Lawsuit-SECs-Win-Against-This-Blockchain-Firm-in-A-High-Profile-Securities-Case-Unnerves-XRP-Army-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<ul>
<li>Ripple&#8217;s XRP price has been consolidating as investors await a court decision in the case with the SEC.</li>



<li>Lawyer John Deaton expects the lawsuit&#8217;s outcome to delay until April or May.</li>
</ul>



<p>Ripple&#8217;s XRP traded at $0.33 Monday, below a crucial resistance of $0.4, according to data provided by CoinMarketCap. Bears have been rejecting a break above $0.4, but bulls are struggling to avoid a possible drop. As Ripple&#8217;s case with the US Securities and Exchange Commission drags, the tug of war is because of an uncertain landscape.</p>



<p>Investors were increasingly growing, hoping December could become a monumental moment for Ripple. The filing of the summary judgment briefs on November 30 <a href="https://zycrypto.com/crypto-whales-are-super-bullish-on-xrp-as-the-ripple-vs-sec-case-nears-long-awaited-end/">heightened the expectations</a>. On December 2, the parties in the lawsuit met to discuss redactions of the court filings. Subsequently, the summary judgments became public on December 5, raising speculations that the case was ending. Since Ripple had previously made milestone wins, investors expected the case could end &#8220;anytime&#8221; from December 5.</p>



<p>Most recently, Cardano&#8217;s co-founder Charles Hoskinson <a href="https://zycrypto.com/xrp-army-gleeful-as-rumors-of-secs-lawsuit-against-ripple-wrapping-up-next-week-swirl/">hinted</a> at December 15 as the day the decision could arrive. In an AMA session, the blockchain entrepreneur said, &#8220;<em>(he had) heard rumors that the Ripple case will be settled December 15<sup>th</sup>. Let’s just see. That could have catastrophic implications for the industry, one way or the other.</em>&#8220;</p>



<h2 id="h-ripple-s-case-with-sec-to-be-settled-in-april-or-may-pro-xrp-lawyer-says"><strong>Ripple’s case with SEC to be settled in April or May, pro-XRP lawyer says</strong></h2>



<p>As it stands, Ripple enthusiasts remain in the dark as the date for settlement is contested. XRP supporter and lawyer John Deaton says the outcome could wait until April or early May. Deaton was responding to a question at the RealVision Crypto briefing about whether a March 31<sup>st</sup> settlement date was possible.</p>



<p>According to Deaton, March 31 would be the earliest date based on the fact that there are numerous pages of documents for the court to scrutinize before the final judgment. The lawyer said that there are 17 amicus briefs filed, making a too-early settlement difficult.</p>



<h2 id="h-what-s-the-case-outcome-mean-for-xrp"><strong>What&#8217;s the case outcome mean for XRP</strong></h2>



<p>XRP&#8217;s recent price actions show investors are eager to receive the verdict. The recent consolidation implies that traders are cautious, as any negative outcome could cause a price decline.</p>



<p>Nonetheless, XRP bulls remain on standby should the case go in their favour. If Ripple wins, that would mean that XRP would not be classified as a security as SEC has for a long time alleged. In the meantime, a breakout at $0.4 remains doubtful unless some positives involving the case come up.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/xrp-army-eager-to-receive-verdict-on-ripple-vs-sec-lawsuit-as-attorney-sets-tentative-settlement-date/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Elon Musk Mulls Resigning As CEO Of Twitter — What&#8217;s Next For Dogecoin?</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/elon-musk-mulls-resigning-as-ceo-of-twitter-whats-next-for-dogecoin/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/elon-musk-mulls-resigning-as-ceo-of-twitter-whats-next-for-dogecoin/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Brenda Ngari]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 17:58:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Doge]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DOGEUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elon Musk]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=76542</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Dogecoins-Future-Could-Follow-This-Bullish-Trajectory-To-1-DOGE-Price-Thanks-To-Elon-Musk.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Dogecoin&#039;s Future Could Follow This Bullish Trajectory To $1 DOGE Price Thanks To Elon Musk" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Dogecoins-Future-Could-Follow-This-Bullish-Trajectory-To-1-DOGE-Price-Thanks-To-Elon-Musk.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Dogecoins-Future-Could-Follow-This-Bullish-Trajectory-To-1-DOGE-Price-Thanks-To-Elon-Musk-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Dogecoins-Future-Could-Follow-This-Bullish-Trajectory-To-1-DOGE-Price-Thanks-To-Elon-Musk-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Dogecoins-Future-Could-Follow-This-Bullish-Trajectory-To-1-DOGE-Price-Thanks-To-Elon-Musk-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>With Musk now seriously considering stepping down as Twitter CEO, is the price of his favourite meme coin headed south?]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Dogecoins-Future-Could-Follow-This-Bullish-Trajectory-To-1-DOGE-Price-Thanks-To-Elon-Musk.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Dogecoin&#039;s Future Could Follow This Bullish Trajectory To $1 DOGE Price Thanks To Elon Musk" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Dogecoins-Future-Could-Follow-This-Bullish-Trajectory-To-1-DOGE-Price-Thanks-To-Elon-Musk.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Dogecoins-Future-Could-Follow-This-Bullish-Trajectory-To-1-DOGE-Price-Thanks-To-Elon-Musk-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Dogecoins-Future-Could-Follow-This-Bullish-Trajectory-To-1-DOGE-Price-Thanks-To-Elon-Musk-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Dogecoins-Future-Could-Follow-This-Bullish-Trajectory-To-1-DOGE-Price-Thanks-To-Elon-Musk-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>Dogecoin has enjoyed several mini rallies in recent months amid speculation that it could play a part in Elon Musk’s Twitter plans. In fact, DOGE became one of the best performers in the crypto markets as the capricious billionaire, who has long had a penchant for the doggy-themed crypto, took the helm at Twitter.</p>



<p>With Musk now seriously considering stepping down as Twitter CEO, is the price of his favourite meme coin headed south?</p>



<h2 id="h-twitter-s-elon-musk-might-soon-relinquish-ceo-role"><strong>Twitter’s Elon Musk Might Soon Relinquish CEO Role</strong></h2>



<p>A new drama is emerging around Twitter as Elon Musk released a poll asking his followers whether or not he should step down from the microblogging site. At press time, the verdict was split, with 57.5% of the roughly 17.5 million responses supporting his resignation.</p>



<p>Musk indicated that he would accept the results of the Twitter survey, meaning he is ready to give that important role to another person.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Should I step down as head of Twitter? I will abide by the results of this poll.</p>&mdash; Elon Musk (@elonmusk) <a href="https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1604617643973124097?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">December 18, 2022</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>Notably, Musk will not be looking for just anybody but for a CEO who can actually “keep Twitter alive”. Interestingly, former NSA contractor turned whistleblower Edward Snowden declared he’s ready to be head of the social media company, and he would prefer bitcoin as payment for his new potential job.</p>



<h2><strong>Why It Matters For DOGE</strong></h2>



<p>Musk has been a major supporter of Dogecoin. His plan has always been to send DOGE skywards. The Tesla CEO’s statements about the currency have also consistently impacted its price. In October, for instance, DOGE rocketed to 12 cents on news of Musk’s completion of his <a href="https://zycrypto.com/dogecoin-bulls-go-all-in-as-billionaire-dogefather-elon-musk-finally-closes-on-44b-twitter-deal/">$44 billion takeover</a> of Twitter and the leak of documents that hinted that the electric car mogul was working on a wallet prototype that would support deposits and withdrawals of crypto.</p>



<p>There was unconfirmed speculation that the aspiring Martian may use Dogecoin in his plans for Twitter 2.0 until he suggested that his time as the “Chief Twit” could be coming to a close.</p>



<p>Notably, the crypto industry is still reeling after a brutal month: investor confidence has been ruined following news that <a href="https://zycrypto.com/ftx-comes-clean-and-admits-that-it-owes-over-3-billion-to-its-50-biggest-creditors/">FTX</a>, once one of the largest and most prominent cryptocurrency exchanges, went bankrupt.</p>



<p>Who knows what’s coming? But if Musk is really resigning as CEO of the bird app, plans of <a href="https://zycrypto.com/doge-rallies-30-on-twitter-payments-anticipation-as-elon-musk-props-up-dogecoin/">integrating Dogecoin payments</a> — and subsequently adding utility to the Shiba Inu-themed meme coin — might be put on hold. This means investors pining for a DOGE moonshot in the near term could be in for a rude awakening.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/elon-musk-mulls-resigning-as-ceo-of-twitter-whats-next-for-dogecoin/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance.US To Pay $1.02 Billion To Get Insolvent Voyager Digital’s Assets</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/binance-us-to-pay-1-02-billion-to-get-insolvent-voyager-digitals-assets/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/binance-us-to-pay-1-02-billion-to-get-insolvent-voyager-digitals-assets/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Brenda Ngari]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 17:18:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=76539</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Binance.US-To-Pay-1.02-Billion-To-Get-Insolvent-Voyager-Digitals-Assets.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Binance.US To Pay $1.02 Billion To Get Insolvent Voyager Digital’s Assets" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Binance.US-To-Pay-1.02-Billion-To-Get-Insolvent-Voyager-Digitals-Assets.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Binance.US-To-Pay-1.02-Billion-To-Get-Insolvent-Voyager-Digitals-Assets-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Binance.US-To-Pay-1.02-Billion-To-Get-Insolvent-Voyager-Digitals-Assets-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Binance.US-To-Pay-1.02-Billion-To-Get-Insolvent-Voyager-Digitals-Assets-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>Binance.US, the American entity of the eponymous global exchange, has agreed to buy the assets of the now-bankrupt crypto brokerage firm Voyager Digital for a whopping $1.022 billion.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Binance.US-To-Pay-1.02-Billion-To-Get-Insolvent-Voyager-Digitals-Assets.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Binance.US To Pay $1.02 Billion To Get Insolvent Voyager Digital’s Assets" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Binance.US-To-Pay-1.02-Billion-To-Get-Insolvent-Voyager-Digitals-Assets.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Binance.US-To-Pay-1.02-Billion-To-Get-Insolvent-Voyager-Digitals-Assets-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Binance.US-To-Pay-1.02-Billion-To-Get-Insolvent-Voyager-Digitals-Assets-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Binance.US-To-Pay-1.02-Billion-To-Get-Insolvent-Voyager-Digitals-Assets-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>Binance.US, the American entity of the eponymous global exchange, has agreed to buy the assets of the now-bankrupt crypto brokerage firm Voyager Digital for a whopping $1.022 billion.</p>



<p>A Monday announcement notes that Binance.US emerged as the “highest and best bid” for its assets.</p>



<h2 id="h-binance-us-wins-bid-to-acquire-voyager"><strong>Binance.US Wins Bid To Acquire Voyager&nbsp;</strong></h2>



<p>Voyager seems to have finally found a buyer for its assets.</p>



<p>The U.S. unit of Binance will pay Voyager $1.022 billion, representing the lender’s crypto portfolio (valued at around $1.002 billion), and an additional consideration equal to $20 million of incremental value.</p>



<p>The deal is expected to be closed by April 2023. However, it won’t go through until the bankruptcy court approves the purchase agreement on January 5. Meanwhile, Binance has agreed to make a $10 million deposit in good faith and will refund Voyager for some expenses up to a maximum of $15 million.</p>



<p>After crypto prices plunged, Voyager on 1st July blocked customers from withdrawing their money. Its clients thereon became company creditors in bankruptcy court, forced to get in line with restructuring lawyers and financiers as rookie participants in a potentially gruelling process to get their crypto back.</p>



<h2><strong>Finally, A Way Out For Users?</strong></h2>



<p>Binance.US is effectively bailing out Voyager Digital users as it “aims to return crypto to customers in kind, in accordance with court-approved disbursements and platform capabilities.&#8221;</p>



<p>&#8220;We hope our selection brings to an end a painful bankruptcy process which saw customers unfairly dragged into it at no fault of their own,&#8221; Binance.US president and CEO Brian Schroder <a href="https://twitter.com/BrianShroder/status/1604825059813920770">tweeted</a>.</p>



<p>He added that once the deal is completed, Voyager users will finally be able to access their crypto funds via new accounts at Binance.US by as early as March 2023.</p>



<p>Prior to its downfall, Sam Bankman-Fried’s FTX had <a href="https://zycrypto.com/ftx-bags-voyager-digital-assets-after-highly-competitive-bidding-process/">won</a> a $1.4 billion auction to acquire Voyager’s assets, beating out competitors Binance and Wave Financial. But with the exchange itself filing for bankruptcy in November, those plans changed.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/binance-us-to-pay-1-02-billion-to-get-insolvent-voyager-digitals-assets/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cardano&#8217;s Hoskinson Lambasts XRP Army for Being Unreasonably Vicious</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/cardanos-hoskinson-says-hell-never-comment-on-xrp-lambasts-community-for-being-unreasonably-vicious/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/cardanos-hoskinson-says-hell-never-comment-on-xrp-lambasts-community-for-being-unreasonably-vicious/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Newton Gitonga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2022 22:47:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADAUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=76535</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Ethereums-Buterin-Throws-Jab-At-XRP-As-He-Propels-Fight-Against-Canadas-New-Crypto-Regulation.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Ethereum&#039;s Buterin Throws Jab At XRP As He Propels Fight Against Canada’s New Crypto Regulation" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Ethereums-Buterin-Throws-Jab-At-XRP-As-He-Propels-Fight-Against-Canadas-New-Crypto-Regulation.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Ethereums-Buterin-Throws-Jab-At-XRP-As-He-Propels-Fight-Against-Canadas-New-Crypto-Regulation-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Ethereums-Buterin-Throws-Jab-At-XRP-As-He-Propels-Fight-Against-Canadas-New-Crypto-Regulation-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Ethereums-Buterin-Throws-Jab-At-XRP-As-He-Propels-Fight-Against-Canadas-New-Crypto-Regulation-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>Charles Hoskinson, the co-founder of Cardano, has hit back at XRP supporters over claims that he was trying to damage Ripple’s reputation and create FUD against the embattled network.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Ethereums-Buterin-Throws-Jab-At-XRP-As-He-Propels-Fight-Against-Canadas-New-Crypto-Regulation.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Ethereum&#039;s Buterin Throws Jab At XRP As He Propels Fight Against Canada’s New Crypto Regulation" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Ethereums-Buterin-Throws-Jab-At-XRP-As-He-Propels-Fight-Against-Canadas-New-Crypto-Regulation.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Ethereums-Buterin-Throws-Jab-At-XRP-As-He-Propels-Fight-Against-Canadas-New-Crypto-Regulation-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Ethereums-Buterin-Throws-Jab-At-XRP-As-He-Propels-Fight-Against-Canadas-New-Crypto-Regulation-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Ethereums-Buterin-Throws-Jab-At-XRP-As-He-Propels-Fight-Against-Canadas-New-Crypto-Regulation-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p><a href="https://zycrypto.com/charles-hoskinson-says-indias-anti-crypto-regulatory-environment-is-preventing-cardanos-entry/">Charles Hoskinson</a>, the co-founder of Cardano, has hit back at XRP supporters over claims that he was trying to damage Ripple’s reputation and create FUD against the embattled network.</p>



<p>In a six-minute video Friday, Hoskinson expressed frustrations over how some <a href="https://zycrypto.com/xrp-whales-are-moving-millions-from-binance-as-looming-litigation-causes-record-outflows/">XRP community</a> members had responded to comments he made concerning the projected time the SEC vs Ripple case would likely end.</p>



<p>“<em>I talked a bit about a rumour that I had heard from a pretty reliable source who was close to the case about a potential resolution of the case by December 15<sup>th</sup>. So, I just threw it out there and said, well, that’s something I’ve heard,</em>” he said referring to comments he made in a surprise Ask Me Anything (AMA) session on Monday, Dec 12.</p>



<p>According to Hoskinson, it was perfectly normal to reference the XRP case when asked whether Cardano was a security because the Ripple case is one of the corollaries to any cryptocurrencies being securities.</p>



<p>However, despite clarifying that he had made the comments out of a “rumour”, many people in both the XRP community and the media started spreading the word that Charles Hoskinson believed the case was going to get settled on December 15<sup>th</sup>.</p>



<p><em>“After it didn’t get resolved, I was accused of lying and I was accused of yet again creating a FUD and trolling,”</em> he said.&nbsp;</p>



<h2 id="h-xrp-adherents"><strong>XRP Adherents</strong></h2>



<p>Hoskinson, who claimed to have been supportive of Ripple’s initiatives and efforts to popularize cryptocurrency, blamed a section of Ripple supporters for allegedly being close-minded.</p>



<p>Apart from not believing that XRP <a href="https://zycrypto.com/microstrategys-saylor-says-xrp-is-a-security-touts-bitcoin-as-the-only-crypto-commodity/">is a security</a>, he noted that he did not think that the SEC was bribed to go after Ripple, saying that those claims were “a conspiracy”. Further, he noted that although Ethereum did get gentler treatment for some reason than others, that did not necessarily mean that there was bribery and corruption.</p>



<p><em>“For saying that,</em> I was mocked, harassed and brutalized by the XRP community, and yet again,<em> now I’m being brutalized.”</em></p>



<p><em>“So, it has left me asking, ‘is there any value at all in mentioning, engaging with or discussing anything about XRP?’ and at this juncture, given what’s happened,</em> I don’t think there is…If asked in the future about XRP,<em> I’m just going to say “NO COMMENT”,</em> he concluded, noting that never in his career in the crypto space had he encountered a community so willing to attack a person who frankly has not attacked them viciously.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/cardanos-hoskinson-says-hell-never-comment-on-xrp-lambasts-community-for-being-unreasonably-vicious/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Inside Kevin O&#8217;Leary and Binance&#8217;s CZ Hot Exchange Over FTX’s Collapse</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/inside-kevin-oleary-and-binances-cz-hot-exchange-over-ftxs-collapse/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/inside-kevin-oleary-and-binances-cz-hot-exchange-over-ftxs-collapse/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Newton Gitonga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2022 22:40:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=76533</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Bahamas-Attorney-General-Defends-The-Countrys-Action-After-FTXs-Collapse.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Bahamas’ Attorney General Defends The Country&#039;s Action After FTX&#039;s Collapse" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Bahamas-Attorney-General-Defends-The-Countrys-Action-After-FTXs-Collapse.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Bahamas-Attorney-General-Defends-The-Countrys-Action-After-FTXs-Collapse-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Bahamas-Attorney-General-Defends-The-Countrys-Action-After-FTXs-Collapse-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Bahamas-Attorney-General-Defends-The-Countrys-Action-After-FTXs-Collapse-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>Following the collapse of FTX, questions about what could have happened have been raging.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Bahamas-Attorney-General-Defends-The-Countrys-Action-After-FTXs-Collapse.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Bahamas’ Attorney General Defends The Country&#039;s Action After FTX&#039;s Collapse" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Bahamas-Attorney-General-Defends-The-Countrys-Action-After-FTXs-Collapse.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Bahamas-Attorney-General-Defends-The-Countrys-Action-After-FTXs-Collapse-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Bahamas-Attorney-General-Defends-The-Countrys-Action-After-FTXs-Collapse-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Bahamas-Attorney-General-Defends-The-Countrys-Action-After-FTXs-Collapse-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>Following the collapse of FTX, questions about what could have happened have been raging. In the past week, Binance CEO Changpeng Zhao” CZ” and Canadian investor Kevin O’Leary have also been engaging in a fiery battle of words for their alleged involvement with FTX.</p>



<p>Despite the <a href="https://zycrypto.com/ftxs-founder-sam-bankman-fried-arrested-in-the-bahamas/">arrest of Sam Bankman-fried</a> “SBF”, the ex-CEO of FTX in the Bahamas on Dec 12, Congressional hearings on the FTX debacle kicked off as planned mid-week. Kevin O’Leary, accused of receiving $15 million to promote FTX despite allegedly knowing the exchange’s fraudulent activities testified on Dec 14. When asked by Senator Pat Toomey why he thought FTX failed, he noted that FTX and Binance were at war with each other, putting the other out of business intentionally. “<em>Binance is a massive unregulated global monopoly now. They put FTX out of business,” </em>he said.</p>



<p>In an interview with CNBC’s Squawk Box afterwards, O’Leary stated that he had contacted SBF before his arrest, seeking answers on the circumstances leading to the collapse. According to him, SBF allegedly stated that they had spent $2 to $3 billion in “off-balance sheet funds” buying back FTX stock from Binance to try and prevent FTX’s collapse.</p>



<p>As it may be recalled, before the collapse of FTX in early November, CZ tweeted that they would <a href="https://zycrypto.com/binance-to-liquidate-ftxs-ftt-holdings-due-to-recent-revelations/">liquidate the entirety</a> of its position in FTX Token (totalling $2.1 billion) after a leaked balance sheet disclosed most FTX holdings were tied up in FTT. Less than three days after the tweet, FTT plunged roughly 94%, rendering the exchange bankrupt.</p>



<p>According to O’Leary, <a href="https://zycrypto.com/binance-ceo-cz-blasts-kevin-oleary-for-supposedly-defending-ftx/">CZ orchestrated FTX’s collapse</a> due to irresponsible communication. “<em>Why in the world would a block trade, like the one by CZ, be tweeted out saying- I have $550 million worth of FTT tokens. I&#8217;m going to put to the market?- You don’t trade like that. You go find buyers, you form a syndicate and you clear market with a trade,”</em> O’Leary charged.</p>



<p>On Thursday, CZ fired back, calling O’Leary a liar and accusing him of making a “bunch of nonsense claims.” According to the Binance CEO, it was suspicious that O’Leary had chosen only to take up what SBF had told him as the truth without digging deeper. He further accused the 68-year-old investor of ignoring all the “small spendings” by FTX and instead focusing on Binance’s sale of FTT.</p>



<p><em>“He (O’Leary) says he did not know that Binance was a shareholder of FTX, so he invested in FTX without looking at the cap table, but he was very specific in the way he accounts for a transaction two years ago, so that’s kind of contradictory,” </em>said CZ<em>. “So, I think Kevin is a liar, I think he is lying about a bunch of stuff”</em>. On Friday, O’Leary <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2feTmaguqhU&amp;ab_channel=CNBCTelevision">responded,</a> arguing that CZ’s accusations against him were a lie.</p>



<p>That said, as the war between the two businessmen rages on, the possibility of arrests or a Madoff Clawback for funds received from FTX being imposed on the two businessmen has become a concern for the crypto community.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/inside-kevin-oleary-and-binances-cz-hot-exchange-over-ftxs-collapse/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>What to Expect from Bitcoin in 2023 — the Bullish and the Bearish</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/what-to-expect-from-bitcoin-in-2023-the-bullish-and-the-bearish/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/what-to-expect-from-bitcoin-in-2023-the-bullish-and-the-bearish/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Olivia Brooke]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2022 22:32:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Featured]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XBTUSD]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=76529</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/What-to-Expect-from-Bitcoin-in-2023-—-the-Bullish-and-the-Bearish.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="What to Expect from Bitcoin in 2023 — the Bullish and the Bearish" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/What-to-Expect-from-Bitcoin-in-2023-—-the-Bullish-and-the-Bearish.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/What-to-Expect-from-Bitcoin-in-2023-—-the-Bullish-and-the-Bearish-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/What-to-Expect-from-Bitcoin-in-2023-—-the-Bullish-and-the-Bearish-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/What-to-Expect-from-Bitcoin-in-2023-—-the-Bullish-and-the-Bearish-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>Just a year ago, the cryptocurrency market recorded one of the best yearly runs Bitcoin has ever had. While bearish calls were made early into 2021, Bitcoin bulls...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/What-to-Expect-from-Bitcoin-in-2023-—-the-Bullish-and-the-Bearish.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="What to Expect from Bitcoin in 2023 — the Bullish and the Bearish" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/What-to-Expect-from-Bitcoin-in-2023-—-the-Bullish-and-the-Bearish.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/What-to-Expect-from-Bitcoin-in-2023-—-the-Bullish-and-the-Bearish-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/What-to-Expect-from-Bitcoin-in-2023-—-the-Bullish-and-the-Bearish-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/What-to-Expect-from-Bitcoin-in-2023-—-the-Bullish-and-the-Bearish-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>Just a year ago, the cryptocurrency market recorded one of the best yearly runs <a href="https://zycrypto.com/bitcoin-whales-double-down-on-gigantic-btc-buys-despite-macro-headwinds/">Bitcoin</a> has ever had. While bearish calls were made early into 2021, Bitcoin bulls pushed prices to a staggering $68,000 in November of the same year.</p>



<h2 id="h-where-is-bitcoin-headed-in-2023-the-bearish"><strong>Where is Bitcoin headed in 2023?; The bearish</strong></h2>



<p>Positive sentiments began to flood the Bitcoin community, and major price predictions were made ahead of 2022. But Bitcoin would underperform, starting the new year with a massive price decline. </p>



<p>January saw Bitcoin at $35,000; Prices fluctuated between $30,000 &#8211; $45,000 between January and June.</p>



<p>The months leading up to December would see Bitcoin slowly lose momentum and go downhill. Although key players were still bullish, the recent events plaguing the market have swayed prominent voices.</p>



<p>From VanEck, a leading global investment manager offering U.S. investors exposure to gold and ETF investment, Bitcoin is expected to decline by 29.4% from its press time price of $16,789. This, however, is only going to persist from January till March.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="647" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/image-4-1024x647.png" alt="" class="wp-image-76530" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/image-4-1024x647.png 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/image-4-300x190.png 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/image-4-768x485.png 768w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/image-4-1536x971.png 1536w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/image-4-2048x1294.png 2048w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /><figcaption class="wp-element-caption">BTCUSD Chart by <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BTCUSD/">TradingView</a></figcaption></figure>



<p>“<em>Bitcoin will test $10-12K in Q1 amid a wave of miner bankruptcies, which will mark the low point of the crypto winter.” </em>&#8211; VanEck.</p>



<p>From April till June, Bitcoin is expected to take a leap upward, as inflation and other surrounding activities are cited as factors that could spur the next bull run for the leading cryptocurrency.</p>



<p>VanEck explains in a recent tweet below, saying; </p>



<p><em>“In the second half of 2023, Bitcoin will rise to $30K. Lower inflation, easing energy concerns, a possible truce in Ukraine, and a turnaround in M2 supply will power the start of a new bull market.”  </em></p>



<h2><strong>Bitcoin 2023; The bullish </strong></h2>



<p>Taking a more bullish approach is Arthur Hayes, the former CEO of BitMEX.</p>



<p>He recently expressed certainty that Bitcoin miners and centralized exchanges that swayed market movement by selling Bitcoin in large quantities will no longer drive lower prices.</p>



<p>Maintaining that <a href="https://zycrypto.com/former-bitmex-ceo-arthur-hayes-on-why-bitcoin-price-has-likely-reached-bottom/">Bitcoin has bottomed</a>, he reckons that liquidations will be halted as sellers are already done selling. More importantly, he looks to the federal reserve to revive risk assets like Bitcoin by implementing new monetary policies. An even more bullish Tim Draper forecasted $250,000 for Bitcoin by late 2022 or early 2023.</p>



<p>While Bitcoin is attempting to clutch $20,000 before the year&#8217;s close, it isn&#8217;t very likely, considering existing market conditions, that $250,000 will be attained this year.</p>



<p>Most analysts and investors remain fixed on the possible outcome for Bitcoin next year. Key figures have also expressed bullish sentiments for altcoins like Dogecoin (DOGE) and Cardano (ADA).</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/what-to-expect-from-bitcoin-in-2023-the-bullish-and-the-bearish/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Full Ether Meltdown Might Be Looming On The Horizon Due To These Alarming Factors — Analysis</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/a-full-ether-meltdown-might-be-looming-on-the-horizon-due-to-these-alarming-factors-analysis/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/a-full-ether-meltdown-might-be-looming-on-the-horizon-due-to-these-alarming-factors-analysis/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Brenda Ngari]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Dec 2022 20:14:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=76511</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Ethereums-Next-Big-Upgrade-Slated-For-2023-—-Heres-why-Its-Super-Bullish-For-ETH.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Ethereum’s Next Big Upgrade Slated For 2023 — Here’s why It’s Super Bullish For ETH" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Ethereums-Next-Big-Upgrade-Slated-For-2023-—-Heres-why-Its-Super-Bullish-For-ETH.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Ethereums-Next-Big-Upgrade-Slated-For-2023-—-Heres-why-Its-Super-Bullish-For-ETH-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Ethereums-Next-Big-Upgrade-Slated-For-2023-—-Heres-why-Its-Super-Bullish-For-ETH-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Ethereums-Next-Big-Upgrade-Slated-For-2023-—-Heres-why-Its-Super-Bullish-For-ETH-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>Blockchain analytics provider CryptoQuant sees an Ethereum (ETH) price blackout on the horizon.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Ethereums-Next-Big-Upgrade-Slated-For-2023-—-Heres-why-Its-Super-Bullish-For-ETH.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Ethereum’s Next Big Upgrade Slated For 2023 — Here’s why It’s Super Bullish For ETH" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Ethereums-Next-Big-Upgrade-Slated-For-2023-—-Heres-why-Its-Super-Bullish-For-ETH.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Ethereums-Next-Big-Upgrade-Slated-For-2023-—-Heres-why-Its-Super-Bullish-For-ETH-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Ethereums-Next-Big-Upgrade-Slated-For-2023-—-Heres-why-Its-Super-Bullish-For-ETH-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Ethereums-Next-Big-Upgrade-Slated-For-2023-—-Heres-why-Its-Super-Bullish-For-ETH-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>Blockchain analytics provider CryptoQuant sees an Ethereum (ETH) price blackout on the horizon. According to CryptoQuant, potential negative fundamental factors could precipitate a mass sell-off event for the second-largest cryptocurrency by market cap.</p>



<h2><strong>Why A Vicious ETH Sell-Off Is Likely</strong></h2>



<p>CryptoQuant has pinpointed issues that could trigger a full-blown ETH correction.</p>



<p>The first potential catalyst is the dramatic increase of inflows into the ETH 2.0 deposit contract, where staked ether is trapped until the implementation of the next big upgrade, <a href="https://zycrypto.com/gargantuan-feat-staked-ether-withdrawals-are-coming-in-march-2023-core-developers-concur/">Shanghai</a>. The amount locked in the contract now represents 12% of the total ETH supply. A chart shared by CryptoQuant shows that the amount of new depositors has been dropping.</p>



<p>With a target release time frame of March 2023, the Shanghai hard fork will make it possible to withdraw staked ETH, tying up loose ends from the monumental September Merge update.</p>



<p>The second factor is that ether balances on centralized exchanges continue declining. Analysts at the on-chain analytics platform harbour the opinion that the forthcoming Shanghai upgrade will likely initiate a major ether sell-off due to the staked ETH withdrawals. There&#8217;s some $18.9 billion worth of ether currently staked with the network at press time, according to data aggregated on Dune Analytics.</p>



<h2 id="h-the-future-outlook-for-the-eth-ecosystem"><strong>The Future Outlook For The ETH Ecosystem</strong></h2>



<p>It’s now over one year since the crypto market peaked in November 2021, and there are no signs of a new bull rally commencing in the near term. Cryptocurrencies were <a href="https://zycrypto.com/bitcoin-and-ethereum-take-a-nosedive-as-fed-signal-more-interest-rates-hike/">shaken </a>yesterday following a hawkish speech from the U.S. Central bank. The Fed on Wednesday raised interest rates by 50 basis points as it continues to slow the economy.</p>



<p>While it&#8217;s difficult to predict which way the market will move, some believe the positive change in ether&#8217;s tokenomics brought about by the Merge technological upgrade could ultimately help the cryptocurrency outperform bitcoin and the broader market once the FTX contagion ebbs and the macroeconomic conditions improve.</p>



<p>Ether is changing hands at $1,177 as of press time, a 4.55% drop over the last 24 hours. Perhaps time will tell whether the No. 2 crypto is due for an epic dump or a bullish trend reversal.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/a-full-ether-meltdown-might-be-looming-on-the-horizon-due-to-these-alarming-factors-analysis/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
