<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>News Archives &#8902; ZyCrypto</title>
	<atom:link href="https://zycrypto.com/category/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://zycrypto.com/category/news/</link>
	<description>ZyCrypto Is A Cryptocurrency News Media, Focusing On Daily News, Expert Opinions, Analysis, Reviews, And So Much More.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 21:18:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/cropped-ZyCrypto-Site-Logo-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News Archives &#8902; ZyCrypto</title>
	<link>https://zycrypto.com/category/news/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Biden Throws Crypto Traders Under the Bus in Debt Deal</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/biden-throws-crypto-traders-under-the-bus-in-debt-deal/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/biden-throws-crypto-traders-under-the-bus-in-debt-deal/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Newton Gitonga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 21:18:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=81199</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Biden-Throws-Crypto-Traders-Under-the-Bus-in-Debt-Deal.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Biden Throws Crypto Traders Under the Bus in Debt Deal" decoding="async" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Biden-Throws-Crypto-Traders-Under-the-Bus-in-Debt-Deal.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Biden-Throws-Crypto-Traders-Under-the-Bus-in-Debt-Deal-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Biden-Throws-Crypto-Traders-Under-the-Bus-in-Debt-Deal-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Biden-Throws-Crypto-Traders-Under-the-Bus-in-Debt-Deal-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>As budget negotiations in the US progress, President Joe Biden has made it clear that crypto can wait.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Biden-Throws-Crypto-Traders-Under-the-Bus-in-Debt-Deal.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Biden Throws Crypto Traders Under the Bus in Debt Deal" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Biden-Throws-Crypto-Traders-Under-the-Bus-in-Debt-Deal.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Biden-Throws-Crypto-Traders-Under-the-Bus-in-Debt-Deal-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Biden-Throws-Crypto-Traders-Under-the-Bus-in-Debt-Deal-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Biden-Throws-Crypto-Traders-Under-the-Bus-in-Debt-Deal-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>As budget negotiations in the US progress, President Joe Biden has made it clear that crypto can wait.</p>



<p>On Sunday, the POTUS did not mince words when addressing budget negotiations during his speech at the G7 summit stating he will not protect wealthy tax cheats and crypto traders. According to the president, he had already met with all four congressional leaders and stressed the need for bipartisan cooperation to move forward prior to departing for the summit.</p>



<p>President Biden had put forth a proposal that exceeds 2 trillion dollars in spending cuts and new revenues in early March before proposing to cut a further $1 trillion in his pursuit of fiscal responsibility. However, he expressed dissatisfaction with various other proposals, such as excess payments to pharmaceutical companies as well as hefty tax breaks for the oil industry and crypto traders, deeming them unacceptable.</p>



<p><em>“Now its time for the other side to move from their extreme positions because much of what they’ve already proposed is simply, quite frankly unacceptable…. I’m not going to agree to a deal that protects wealthy tax cheats and crypto traders while putting food assistants at risk for nearly 1 million Americans,”</em> Biden <a href="https://twitter.com/SkyNews/status/1660225824262434816">said</a> on Sunday.</p>



<p>This statement comes at a time when US regulators are intensifying their scrutiny of the cryptocurrency realm and clearly indicates that the forthcoming debt deal will not safeguard crypto investors within the country. Notably, Biden’s assertions also have the ability to undermine his administration’s efforts to pursue crypto regulations, as he directed in his March 2022 <a href="https://zycrypto.com/heres-the-whole-bushel-of-bidens-groundbreaking-executive-order-for-cryptocurrencies/">executive order</a>.</p>



<p>Meanwhile, while Biden’s proposal underscores his commitment to prioritizing the well-being of ordinary Americans, the crypto community have perceived it as a way of gaining political mileage, given he is seeking re-election next year.</p>



<p>Elsewhere, various US presidential candidates seem to be taking his administration’s outright hostility towards crypto to their advantage, vowing to champion pro-crypto reforms when elected. Earlier this week, Robert F. Kennedy Jr, a Democratic presidential candidate, noted that he is committed to upholding people’s right to hold Bitcoin.</p>



<p><em>&#8220;Everybody is so passionate about Bitcoin, not just because it’s a currency but because it’s an exercise in democracy,&#8221;</em> Kennedy said at the Bitcoin 2023 conference in Miami Saturday. <em>“As president, I will make sure that you got your own wallet that the government can’t interfere with. Nobody is going to be taxing your electricity 30% and that we can nature this product in America where it’s going to create wealth for Americans.”</em>&nbsp;</p>



<p>Vivek Ramaswamy, another presidential candidate, announced at the same event that they had officially started accepting Bitcoin donations for his campaign, saying <em>“Let’s make the 2024 election a referendum on fiat currency.”</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/biden-throws-crypto-traders-under-the-bus-in-debt-deal/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cardano’s Explosive Network Developments Fuel Speculation for $1 ADA Price Milestone</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/cardanos-explosive-network-developments-fuel-speculation-for-1-ada-price-milestone/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/cardanos-explosive-network-developments-fuel-speculation-for-1-ada-price-milestone/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Newton Gitonga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 20:26:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADAUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=81186</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Cardanos-Transaction-Volume-Sees-Huge-Upsurge-Amid-Price-Fluctuations-ADA-Network-In-Bullish-Outlook.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Cardano’s Transaction Volume Sees Huge Upsurge Amid Price Fluctuations: ADA Network In Bullish Outlook" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Cardanos-Transaction-Volume-Sees-Huge-Upsurge-Amid-Price-Fluctuations-ADA-Network-In-Bullish-Outlook.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Cardanos-Transaction-Volume-Sees-Huge-Upsurge-Amid-Price-Fluctuations-ADA-Network-In-Bullish-Outlook-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Cardanos-Transaction-Volume-Sees-Huge-Upsurge-Amid-Price-Fluctuations-ADA-Network-In-Bullish-Outlook-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Cardanos-Transaction-Volume-Sees-Huge-Upsurge-Amid-Price-Fluctuations-ADA-Network-In-Bullish-Outlook-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>Cardano is set to experience significant growth following notable developments within its network.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Cardanos-Transaction-Volume-Sees-Huge-Upsurge-Amid-Price-Fluctuations-ADA-Network-In-Bullish-Outlook.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Cardano’s Transaction Volume Sees Huge Upsurge Amid Price Fluctuations: ADA Network In Bullish Outlook" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Cardanos-Transaction-Volume-Sees-Huge-Upsurge-Amid-Price-Fluctuations-ADA-Network-In-Bullish-Outlook.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Cardanos-Transaction-Volume-Sees-Huge-Upsurge-Amid-Price-Fluctuations-ADA-Network-In-Bullish-Outlook-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Cardanos-Transaction-Volume-Sees-Huge-Upsurge-Amid-Price-Fluctuations-ADA-Network-In-Bullish-Outlook-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Cardanos-Transaction-Volume-Sees-Huge-Upsurge-Amid-Price-Fluctuations-ADA-Network-In-Bullish-Outlook-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>Cardano is set to experience significant growth following notable developments within its network. Several key advancements were highlighted in the latest weekly development report released Friday, May 19.</p>



<p>According to the report, in scaling efforts, the Hydra team achieved significant milestones with the release of the first mainnet-compatible <a href="https://zycrypto.com/cardano-releases-first-mainnet-compatible-version-of-hydra-node-ada-looks-to-ride-the-wave-to-major-gains/">Hydra</a> node version. These advancements address critical issues that need resolution before integrating Hydra Head with real ADA, ensuring users&#8217; smooth and secure experience.</p>



<p>Voltaire workshops also commenced, providing opportunities for collaboration and networking among local Cardano communities. Voltaire is a big upgrade for Cardano in the future. As per the Cardano website, the Voltaire era&nbsp;of Cardano “will provide the final pieces required for the Cardano network to become a self-sustaining system.”</p>



<p>Elsewhere, the team responsible for making decisions worked with the research and networking teams to improve the Ouroboros Genesis design. They improved how they select the starting point, how they choose candidates, and how they use important connections. These changes were made to make the whole system work better and be more stable.</p>



<p>Notably, the Daedalus team completed work on the proxy server, guaranteeing ADA conversion rates from the CoinGecko API are dependable. As per the report, this team is preparing to release an updated version of Daedalus that will smoothly switch to this new endpoint.</p>



<p>Meanwhile, amid the developments, Cardano continued to witness significant progress, with various teams actively working on <a href="https://zycrypto.com/cardanos-impressive-fundamentals-fuel-speculation-for-ada-reaching-1-price-milestone/">numerous projects</a>, all contributing to the platform&#8217;s overall advancement.</p>



<p>The latest report reveals some impressive numbers for Cardano. So far, 127 projects have been launched on the platform, creating over 8.28 million native tokens. Additionally, there have been 8,277 Plutus scripts executed, showcasing the versatility and functionality of Cardano.</p>



<p>Notably, Cardano is now home to a whopping 1,242 active projects in various development stages. These projects collectively process a remarkable 66.7 million transactions, highlighting the platform&#8217;s growing popularity and widespread use.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="572" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-22-1024x572.png" alt="" class="wp-image-81179" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-22-1024x572.png 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-22-300x168.png 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-22-768x429.png 768w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-22.png 1431w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>This substantial increase in activity demonstrates the growing interest and adoption of Cardano as a preferred blockchain platform. The Cardano team has also been championing more decentralization, as evidenced by an upcoming Stake Pool Operators (SPO) vote, enabling SPOs to vote on important decisions about the network&#8217;s future.</p>



<p>With these notable developments and ongoing initiatives, Cardano is set to offer a robust infrastructure and foster innovation in the decentralized ecosystem, which is bullish for the entire ecosystem amid price watchtower to $1.</p>



<p>Proponents of the network’s native token ADA could also enjoy massive returns on their assets soon as the network continues to attract more users. The cryptocurrency was trading at $0.36 at press time, down 1.31% in the past 24 hours.&nbsp;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/cardanos-explosive-network-developments-fuel-speculation-for-1-ada-price-milestone/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Coindeal Executive Charged With $45 Million Crypto Fraud Involving 10,000 Victims</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/coindeal-executive-charged-with-45-million-crypto-fraud-involving-10000-victims/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/coindeal-executive-charged-with-45-million-crypto-fraud-involving-10000-victims/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Newton Gitonga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 19:50:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=81182</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/Malaysia-Duo-Charged-Over-Bitcoin-Investment-Fraud.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Malaysia Duo Charged Over Bitcoin Investment Fraud" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/Malaysia-Duo-Charged-Over-Bitcoin-Investment-Fraud.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/Malaysia-Duo-Charged-Over-Bitcoin-Investment-Fraud-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/Malaysia-Duo-Charged-Over-Bitcoin-Investment-Fraud-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/Malaysia-Duo-Charged-Over-Bitcoin-Investment-Fraud-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>Bryan Lee, an executive associated with crypto exchange CoinDeal, has been charged in connection with a cryptocurrency investment fraud scheme that defrauded more than 10,000 victims and resulted in losses exceeding $45 million.&#160; According to a Friday statement by the US Department of Justice (DOJ), Lee is accused of collaborating with Neil Chandran and others [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/Malaysia-Duo-Charged-Over-Bitcoin-Investment-Fraud.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Malaysia Duo Charged Over Bitcoin Investment Fraud" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/Malaysia-Duo-Charged-Over-Bitcoin-Investment-Fraud.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/Malaysia-Duo-Charged-Over-Bitcoin-Investment-Fraud-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/Malaysia-Duo-Charged-Over-Bitcoin-Investment-Fraud-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/Malaysia-Duo-Charged-Over-Bitcoin-Investment-Fraud-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>Bryan Lee, an executive associated with crypto exchange CoinDeal, has been charged in connection with a cryptocurrency investment fraud scheme that defrauded more than 10,000 victims and resulted in losses exceeding $45 million.&nbsp;</p>



<p>According to a Friday statement by the US Department of Justice (DOJ), Lee is accused of collaborating with Neil Chandran and others to <a href="https://www.justice.gov/opa/press-release/file/1584496/download">deceive</a> investors in companies controlled by Chandran, collectively known as &#8220;ViRSE.&#8221;</p>



<p>These companies allegedly claimed to be developing virtual-world technologies and their cryptocurrency for use in a metaverse. To entice potential investors, the fraudulent operation promised substantial returns upon the acquisition of these companies by wealthy individuals. </p>



<p>The firms even propagated false assertions that two billionaires, one affiliated with a well-known online retail company and the other with an electric car company, were supporting the ventures in a bid to substantiate their claims. However, the DOJ alleged that these claims were entirely fabricated, designed solely to deceive unsuspecting individuals.</p>



<p>Lee,57, as the nominee owner and director of ViMarket, allegedly followed Chandran&#8217;s instructions in handling investor funds deposited into ViMarket&#8217;s bank accounts. CoinDeal was the primary vehicle through which the fraudulent investment opportunity was marketed to potential victims. Lee and Chandran then proceeded to <a href="https://zycrypto.com/ohio-man-who-stole-713-bitcoins-from-us-authorities-is-set-to-plead-guilty-of-theft/">misappropriate</a> millions of dollars by purchasing luxury cars and real estate.</p>



<p>According to the DOJ, Lee faces multiple charges, including conspiracy, mail fraud, wire fraud, and engaging in monetary transactions involving unlawfully obtained assets. If convicted, he could face over 60 years in prison.</p>



<p>Notably, Chandran was arrested in June 2022 and charged accordingly. Michael Glaspie, another individual involved with the scheme, pleaded guilty to wire fraud for his role in marketing the investment under the name &#8220;CoinDeal&#8221; and is scheduled to be sentenced on June 16.</p>



<p>Meanwhile, while Lee made his initial appearance in federal court on Friday, May 19, Chandran is scheduled for a status conference on June 14.&nbsp;</p>



<p>That said, as the legal process unfolds, it is anticipated that further revelations regarding the extent of the alleged fraudulent activities will come to light, with the DOJ calling on victims to present themselves.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/coindeal-executive-charged-with-45-million-crypto-fraud-involving-10000-victims/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Over 53% Of Minted Bitcoin Is Now ‘Dormant’ &#8211; Here’s What It Means As Asset Continues To Soar</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/over-53-of-minted-bitcoin-is-now-dormant-heres-what-it-means-as-asset-continues-to-soar/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/over-53-of-minted-bitcoin-is-now-dormant-heres-what-it-means-as-asset-continues-to-soar/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aliyu Pokima]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 19:31:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=81178</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoins-Price-Outlook-Uncertain-as-Key-Support-Level-Faces-Crucial-Test.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoins-Price-Outlook-Uncertain-as-Key-Support-Level-Faces-Crucial-Test.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoins-Price-Outlook-Uncertain-as-Key-Support-Level-Faces-Crucial-Test-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoins-Price-Outlook-Uncertain-as-Key-Support-Level-Faces-Crucial-Test-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoins-Price-Outlook-Uncertain-as-Key-Support-Level-Faces-Crucial-Test-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>The hodling culture is deeply rooted in digital assets and current indicators show growth across multiple cryptocurrencies amid recent bear markets. Recent data released by blockchain analytics firm Glassnode shows that holders have not moved more than half the number of Bitcoin (BTC) in circulation in two years. The figure, which stands at 53.14% is [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoins-Price-Outlook-Uncertain-as-Key-Support-Level-Faces-Crucial-Test.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoins-Price-Outlook-Uncertain-as-Key-Support-Level-Faces-Crucial-Test.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoins-Price-Outlook-Uncertain-as-Key-Support-Level-Faces-Crucial-Test-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoins-Price-Outlook-Uncertain-as-Key-Support-Level-Faces-Crucial-Test-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoins-Price-Outlook-Uncertain-as-Key-Support-Level-Faces-Crucial-Test-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<ul>
<li>New data shows that over 53% of Bitcoin has not moved in the last two years despite price swings in recent months.&nbsp;</li>



<li>The activities of sophisticated investors and whales, coupled with increased lost assets, are significant for the figure.</li>
</ul>



<p>The hodling culture is deeply rooted in digital assets and current indicators show growth across multiple cryptocurrencies amid recent bear markets.</p>



<p>Recent data released by blockchain analytics firm Glassnode shows that holders have not moved more than half the number of Bitcoin (BTC) in circulation in two years. The figure, which stands at 53.14% is at an all-time high which points to the growing desire by investors to hold assets on a long-term basis.</p>



<p>While 19.3 million BTC has been mined since 2009, the report shows that 10.2 million BTC are still sitting in wallets. The factors responsible for over $300 billion worth of BTC going dormant are the trading patterns of whales and, unfortunately, lost assets.</p>



<p>The CEO of Arkham Intelligence, commenting on the report, stated that dormant coins will eventually come back in circulation over time.&nbsp;</p>



<p>“<em>Coins have organically transferred from those with high-time and liquidity preference to those with low-time and liquidity preference. Through all the shake-ups, for every seller, there’s a buyer.&#8221;</em></p>



<p>This data comes up as the price of the market leader <a href="https://zycrypto.com/bitcoin-pierces-30000-for-first-time-since-june-as-bernstein-calls-btc-faster-horse-compared-to-gold/">moves</a> past the $30,000 mark for the first time in eight months after a positive start in Q1 2023. An increase in the price of BTC can lead dormant assets to come back into the scene as long-term holders will look to trade for profits.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-will-hodling-continue">Will hodling continue?</h2>



<p>In the last decade, several whales resurfaced huge crypto holdings making shocking returns by moving assets to new wallets. Glassnode indicated investors are less likely to spend coins after 155 days and will hold those assets for a long time.</p>



<p>Records also show long-term ‘sophisticated investors’ make more money than retail investors. Morel also stated that some assets will never return to circulation because they have simply been lost. This is a major problem attributed to amateur investors who forget their wallet’s private keys.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/over-53-of-minted-bitcoin-is-now-dormant-heres-what-it-means-as-asset-continues-to-soar/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>XRP Lawsuit: Ripple And SEC Request Additional Time to Disclose Hinman Files — Is A Settlement Looming?</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/xrp-lawsuit-ripple-and-sec-request-additional-time-to-disclose-hinman-files-is-a-settlement-looming/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/xrp-lawsuit-ripple-and-sec-request-additional-time-to-disclose-hinman-files-is-a-settlement-looming/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Newton Gitonga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 16:48:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=81165</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRP-Lawsuit-Ripple-And-SEC-Request-Additional-Time-to-Disclose-Hinman-Files-—-Is-A-Settlement-Looming.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="XRP Lawsuit: Ripple And SEC Request Additional Time to Disclose Hinman Files — Is A Settlement Looming?" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRP-Lawsuit-Ripple-And-SEC-Request-Additional-Time-to-Disclose-Hinman-Files-—-Is-A-Settlement-Looming.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRP-Lawsuit-Ripple-And-SEC-Request-Additional-Time-to-Disclose-Hinman-Files-—-Is-A-Settlement-Looming-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRP-Lawsuit-Ripple-And-SEC-Request-Additional-Time-to-Disclose-Hinman-Files-—-Is-A-Settlement-Looming-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRP-Lawsuit-Ripple-And-SEC-Request-Additional-Time-to-Disclose-Hinman-Files-—-Is-A-Settlement-Looming-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>Ripple and the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) have jointly requested additional time to disclose the Hinman documents, raising speculation about a potential settlement in their ongoing legal battle.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRP-Lawsuit-Ripple-And-SEC-Request-Additional-Time-to-Disclose-Hinman-Files-—-Is-A-Settlement-Looming.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="XRP Lawsuit: Ripple And SEC Request Additional Time to Disclose Hinman Files — Is A Settlement Looming?" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRP-Lawsuit-Ripple-And-SEC-Request-Additional-Time-to-Disclose-Hinman-Files-—-Is-A-Settlement-Looming.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRP-Lawsuit-Ripple-And-SEC-Request-Additional-Time-to-Disclose-Hinman-Files-—-Is-A-Settlement-Looming-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRP-Lawsuit-Ripple-And-SEC-Request-Additional-Time-to-Disclose-Hinman-Files-—-Is-A-Settlement-Looming-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRP-Lawsuit-Ripple-And-SEC-Request-Additional-Time-to-Disclose-Hinman-Files-—-Is-A-Settlement-Looming-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>Ripple and the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) have jointly requested additional time to disclose the Hinman documents, raising speculation about a potential settlement in their ongoing legal battle.</p>



<p>In a Friday, May 19 letter to District Judge Analisa Torres, both parties argued that the voluminous nature of the materials and the necessary redactions necessitate more time. Notably, while the original deadline had been set for June 6 2023, by the court, the parties sought a one-week extension to June 13.</p>



<p>This development follows a <a href="https://zycrypto.com/groundbreaking-ripple-win-in-xrp-case-looking-likely-as-court-rejects-secs-request-to-keep-hinman-docs-hidden/">recent decision</a> by Judge Torres to deny the SEC&#8217;s motion to seal the Hinman documents earlier this week. On May 16, Judge Torres ruled that the documents were judicial and subject to a strong presumption of public access. The decision was welcomed by Ripple CEO Brad Garlinghouse, who called it “another win for transparency.”</p>



<p>The documents in question are tied to a controversial 2018 speech by Bill Hinman, a former SEC director, where he stated that he did not consider Bitcoin or Ethereum as securities. Ripple has sought access to these documents, believing they support their argument that XRP should not be classified as a security.</p>



<p>The SEC had previously claimed that Hinman&#8217;s speech represented his personal views rather than the Commission&#8217;s policy, and thus the documents should be withheld from public scrutiny. However, the recent ruling by Judge Torres has brought them into the public domain. This decision marks another setback for the SEC&#8217;s attempt to seal these documents, as a judge had previously ruled against their efforts last year.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-a-settlement-in-the-horizon"><strong>A Settlement in the Horizon?</strong></h2>



<p>Meanwhile, following this week’s events, the possibility of public access to these documents has added fuel to the speculation about a potential settlement between Ripple and the SEC.</p>



<p><em>“Whiff of settlement talks &#8211; since this is a joint filing. The SEC does not want the Kraken released here… Still feels most like a mutually beneficial delay to work on settlement,”</em> tweeted long-term Ripple supporter Hugh Breslin.</p>



<p><em>“</em><em>My thoughts exactly</em>!” another Ripple proponent wrote, replying to Breslin.&nbsp;</p>



<p>That said, it is important to note that the outcome of this <a href="https://zycrypto.com/xrp-eyes-monster-move-as-new-lawsuit-outcomes-set-ripple-on-path-to-gigantic-win-against-the-sec/">high-profile lawsuit</a> holds significant implications for the regulation of digital assets, not only in the United States but also globally. This is because it has the potential to provide clarity on the classification of cryptocurrencies and shape future regulatory frameworks.</p>



<p>That said, as the Parties await a decision from Judge Torres regarding the requested extension, the Ripple adherents await eagerly as the decision may provide crucial insights into the SEC&#8217;s stance on digital assets and the future of Ripple&#8217;s XRP.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/xrp-lawsuit-ripple-and-sec-request-additional-time-to-disclose-hinman-files-is-a-settlement-looming/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>United States Senators Lash Out At Signature’s Executives For Blaming Bank’s Collapse On Crypto After “Reckless” Management</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/united-states-senators-lash-out-at-signatures-executives-for-blaming-banks-collapse-on-crypto-after-reckless-management/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/united-states-senators-lash-out-at-signatures-executives-for-blaming-banks-collapse-on-crypto-after-reckless-management/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aliyu Pokima]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 16:32:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=81160</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/FTX-Blew-40-Million-On-Meals-Private-Jets-And-Luxury-Hotels-In-Less-Than-Nine-Months-Before-Its-Collapse.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="FTX Blew $40 Million On Meals, Private Jets, And Luxury Hotels In Less Than Nine Months Before Its Collapse" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/FTX-Blew-40-Million-On-Meals-Private-Jets-And-Luxury-Hotels-In-Less-Than-Nine-Months-Before-Its-Collapse.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/FTX-Blew-40-Million-On-Meals-Private-Jets-And-Luxury-Hotels-In-Less-Than-Nine-Months-Before-Its-Collapse-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/FTX-Blew-40-Million-On-Meals-Private-Jets-And-Luxury-Hotels-In-Less-Than-Nine-Months-Before-Its-Collapse-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/FTX-Blew-40-Million-On-Meals-Private-Jets-And-Luxury-Hotels-In-Less-Than-Nine-Months-Before-Its-Collapse-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>As investigations into Silvergate Banks ramp up, discoveries alongside the blame game from different sources come to light. At a Senate Banking Committee hearing on May 16, Scott Shay, a former executive of Silvergate Bank, gave his statement on the facts leading to the bank&#8217;s collapse. From his testimony, he leaned towards putting most of [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/FTX-Blew-40-Million-On-Meals-Private-Jets-And-Luxury-Hotels-In-Less-Than-Nine-Months-Before-Its-Collapse.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="FTX Blew $40 Million On Meals, Private Jets, And Luxury Hotels In Less Than Nine Months Before Its Collapse" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/FTX-Blew-40-Million-On-Meals-Private-Jets-And-Luxury-Hotels-In-Less-Than-Nine-Months-Before-Its-Collapse.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/FTX-Blew-40-Million-On-Meals-Private-Jets-And-Luxury-Hotels-In-Less-Than-Nine-Months-Before-Its-Collapse-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/FTX-Blew-40-Million-On-Meals-Private-Jets-And-Luxury-Hotels-In-Less-Than-Nine-Months-Before-Its-Collapse-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/FTX-Blew-40-Million-On-Meals-Private-Jets-And-Luxury-Hotels-In-Less-Than-Nine-Months-Before-Its-Collapse-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<ul>
<li>A former executive of Signature Bank has made several attempts to heap blame for the bank’s failure on digital assets.&nbsp;</li>



<li>After implementing reckless management policies, Senator Cynthia Lummis criticized the position as a deflationary approach.</li>



<li>The NYDFS continues to reveal events resulting in the collapse of the bank months after taking over to “<em>protect the US economy.”&nbsp;</em></li>
</ul>



<p>As investigations into Silvergate Banks ramp up, discoveries alongside the blame game from different sources come to light.</p>



<p>At a Senate Banking Committee <a href="https://www.banking.senate.gov/newsroom/majority/brown-holds-failed-bank-executives-accountable-mismanagement">hearing</a> on May 16, Scott Shay, a former executive of Silvergate Bank, gave his statement on the facts leading to the bank&#8217;s collapse. From his testimony, he leaned towards putting most of the blame on the bank’s readiness to deal with web3 start-ups rather than on the management team.</p>



<p>He stated that the bank started accepting deposits from digital asset firms in 2018, although the number dropped over the years due to the industry’s high volatility, especially in mid-2022. He further noted that the bank was affected by the fall of “<em>a bank with strong ties to the digital asset sector.”</em></p>



<p>The authorities asked clients to withdraw their funds leading to a massive $16 billion withdrawal from Signature Bank. After his testimony, Senators evaluated his testimony, with many lashing out at him for the complete failure of the bank.</p>



<p>Senator Cynthia Lummis knocked Shay out for trying to shift responsibility away from his team.</p>



<p>“<em>It looks like there has been a lot of deflection of blame onto those particular depositors that deal in digital assets and onto regulators, but you haven’t accepted any blame yourself,” </em>she said.</p>



<p>Despite referring to digital assets ten times during his testimony, he denied pointing fingers at web3 firms for the bank&#8217;s collapse. </p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-accused-of-keeping-millions">Accused of keeping millions</h2>



<p>At the hearing, Senator Elizabeth Warren further <a href="https://www.warren.senate.gov/newsroom/press-releases/at-hearing-warren-blasts-former-svb-and-signature-bank-ceos-for-keeping-millions-after-recklessly-crashing-banks">criticized</a> Shay and Silicon Valley’s CEO Gregory Pecker who are accused of “<em>keeping millions after recklessly crashing banks.”</em></p>



<p><em>“Right now, the law says that people like Mr. Becker and Mr. Shay can pay themselves tens of millions of dollars in bonuses and stock options, and when the banks blow up, Mr. Becker and Mr. Shay get to keep all the money. And that is just plain wrong. If we don&#8217;t fix it, every CEO for these multibillion-dollar banks will keep right on loading up on risks and blowing up banks, and everybody else is going to have to pay for it.”</em></p>



<p>Senator Warren also noted that she will work on a bill to curtail the powers of bank executives to receive these “<em>crazy paychecks.”&nbsp;</em></p>



<p>Recall that in April, the New York Department of Financial Services (NYDFS) said it would be wrong to blame virtual assets for the bank’s collapse but rather on “a <em>new-fashioned bank run.”</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/united-states-senators-lash-out-at-signatures-executives-for-blaming-banks-collapse-on-crypto-after-reckless-management/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Network Remains Congested, But Is It Due to Possible Malicious Attack?</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/bitcoin-network-remains-congested-but-is-it-due-to-possible-malicious-attack/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/bitcoin-network-remains-congested-but-is-it-due-to-possible-malicious-attack/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Marco Tulio]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 16:19:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=81157</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/10/Bitcoin-Whitepaper-Marks-Eleventh-Anniversary-With-A-1-Billion-BTC-Network-Transaction-Fee-Milestone-1.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Bitcoin Whitepaper Marks Eleventh Anniversary With A $1 Billion BTC Network Transaction Fee Milestone" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/10/Bitcoin-Whitepaper-Marks-Eleventh-Anniversary-With-A-1-Billion-BTC-Network-Transaction-Fee-Milestone-1.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/10/Bitcoin-Whitepaper-Marks-Eleventh-Anniversary-With-A-1-Billion-BTC-Network-Transaction-Fee-Milestone-1-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/10/Bitcoin-Whitepaper-Marks-Eleventh-Anniversary-With-A-1-Billion-BTC-Network-Transaction-Fee-Milestone-1-768x448.jpg 768w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/10/Bitcoin-Whitepaper-Marks-Eleventh-Anniversary-With-A-1-Billion-BTC-Network-Transaction-Fee-Milestone-1-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/10/Bitcoin-Whitepaper-Marks-Eleventh-Anniversary-With-A-1-Billion-BTC-Network-Transaction-Fee-Milestone-1-610x356.jpg 610w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>Since last week, the Bitcoin network has remained congested with more than 420,000 unconfirmed transactions, raising suspicions of a possible malicious attack. According to several developers and cryptocurrency community enthusiasts, the Bitcoin network is being attacked by persons who are willing to lose millions of dollars to render the network unusable. Bitcoin community expresses concern [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/10/Bitcoin-Whitepaper-Marks-Eleventh-Anniversary-With-A-1-Billion-BTC-Network-Transaction-Fee-Milestone-1.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Bitcoin Whitepaper Marks Eleventh Anniversary With A $1 Billion BTC Network Transaction Fee Milestone" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/10/Bitcoin-Whitepaper-Marks-Eleventh-Anniversary-With-A-1-Billion-BTC-Network-Transaction-Fee-Milestone-1.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/10/Bitcoin-Whitepaper-Marks-Eleventh-Anniversary-With-A-1-Billion-BTC-Network-Transaction-Fee-Milestone-1-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/10/Bitcoin-Whitepaper-Marks-Eleventh-Anniversary-With-A-1-Billion-BTC-Network-Transaction-Fee-Milestone-1-768x448.jpg 768w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/10/Bitcoin-Whitepaper-Marks-Eleventh-Anniversary-With-A-1-Billion-BTC-Network-Transaction-Fee-Milestone-1-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/10/Bitcoin-Whitepaper-Marks-Eleventh-Anniversary-With-A-1-Billion-BTC-Network-Transaction-Fee-Milestone-1-610x356.jpg 610w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>Since last week, the Bitcoin network has remained congested with more than 420,000 unconfirmed transactions, raising suspicions of a possible malicious attack.</p>



<p>According to several developers and cryptocurrency community enthusiasts, the Bitcoin network is<a href="https://zycrypto.com/bitcoins-surging-transaction-fees-viewed-as-direct-attack-by-a-cross-section-of-the-community/"> being attacked</a> by persons who are willing to lose millions of dollars to render the network unusable.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-bitcoin-community-expresses-concern"><strong>Bitcoin community expresses concern</strong></h2>



<p>Developer iris.to/jogi (@proofofjogi) stated over the weekend that Bitcoin is under a DoS attack, one of the many tools hackers use to overwhelm a website by flooding the network with access requests.</p>



<p><em>&#8220;Bitcoin is under DoS attack. High transaction fees are the chosen pain point by the attacker, probably to make Bitcoin unusable for smaller players.&#8221;</em></p>



<p>In addition, he explained that this could have been planned for several months, as network congestion has been increasing since the implementation of the Ordinals protocol, which allows the issuance of NFT tokens on the Bitcoin network.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">From ordinals to DoS attack didn&#39;t take that much time. 3ish months, give or take couple days.<br><br>We&#39;re in the then-they-fight-you-stage</p>&mdash; iris.to/jogi (@proofofjogi) <a href="https://twitter.com/proofofjogi/status/1655157040753385472?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">May 7, 2023</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>Furthermore, user Chad Pleb pointed out that the Bitcoin network&#8217;s congestion is maliciously caused by hackers or groups willing to spend up to $9 million in losses from the minting of Ordinals tokens.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">If these stats are correct, that&#39;s ~300 BTC(~$9M in USD) for &quot;transacting&quot; json and links to jpegs? JFC <a href="https://t.co/JToc9zErzw">pic.twitter.com/JToc9zErzw</a></p>&mdash; Chad Pleb (@chad_pleb) <a href="https://twitter.com/chad_pleb/status/1654948345364766725?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">May 6, 2023</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>This argument was supported by Francis Pouliot, CEO and co-founder of Bull Bitcoin, who showed an image of a conversation in which a person indicated that anyone with a large amount of money could make the Bitcoin network unusable by increasing transaction costs through excessive minting of Ordinals.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Average Bitcoin transaction costs rise to 2021 levels</strong></h2>



<p>Despite the fact that <a href="https://zycrypto.com/bitcoins-price-outlook-uncertain-as-key-support-level-faces-crucial-test/">BTC price</a> is far from the bullish rally it experienced during 2021, where transaction costs reached an all-time high of $70, the actual cost for verifying transactions has remained relatively high, ranging between $8 and $20.</p>



<p>Although some analysts indicate that this is a momentary issue as average fees have been decreasing, network congestion is not improving, according to Bitcoin&#8217;s blockchain explorer and mempool, Mempool Space.</p>



<p>At the time of writing this note, there are more than 300,000 pending transactions, with an average cost of medium priority of approximately $7. This proves that the latest Bitcoin update sacrificed network stability for unnecessary innovation.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/bitcoin-network-remains-congested-but-is-it-due-to-possible-malicious-attack/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin&#8217;s Price Faces Bleak Outlook as Selling Pressure from Miners Surge</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/bitcoins-price-faces-bleak-outlook-as-selling-pressure-from-miners-surge/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/bitcoins-price-faces-bleak-outlook-as-selling-pressure-from-miners-surge/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Newton Gitonga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 19:09:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XBTUSD]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=81142</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/Senator-Ted-Cruz-Believes-Excess-Renewable-Energy-In-Texas-Presents-A-Great-Opportunity-For-Bitcoin-Miners.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Senator Ted Cruz Believes Excess Renewable Energy In Texas Presents A Great Opportunity For Bitcoin Miners" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/Senator-Ted-Cruz-Believes-Excess-Renewable-Energy-In-Texas-Presents-A-Great-Opportunity-For-Bitcoin-Miners.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/Senator-Ted-Cruz-Believes-Excess-Renewable-Energy-In-Texas-Presents-A-Great-Opportunity-For-Bitcoin-Miners-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/Senator-Ted-Cruz-Believes-Excess-Renewable-Energy-In-Texas-Presents-A-Great-Opportunity-For-Bitcoin-Miners-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/Senator-Ted-Cruz-Believes-Excess-Renewable-Energy-In-Texas-Presents-A-Great-Opportunity-For-Bitcoin-Miners-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>Bitcoin, the world's largest cryptocurrency, is facing a challenging outlook as selling pressure from miners increases.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/Senator-Ted-Cruz-Believes-Excess-Renewable-Energy-In-Texas-Presents-A-Great-Opportunity-For-Bitcoin-Miners.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Senator Ted Cruz Believes Excess Renewable Energy In Texas Presents A Great Opportunity For Bitcoin Miners" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/Senator-Ted-Cruz-Believes-Excess-Renewable-Energy-In-Texas-Presents-A-Great-Opportunity-For-Bitcoin-Miners.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/Senator-Ted-Cruz-Believes-Excess-Renewable-Energy-In-Texas-Presents-A-Great-Opportunity-For-Bitcoin-Miners-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/Senator-Ted-Cruz-Believes-Excess-Renewable-Energy-In-Texas-Presents-A-Great-Opportunity-For-Bitcoin-Miners-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/Senator-Ted-Cruz-Believes-Excess-Renewable-Energy-In-Texas-Presents-A-Great-Opportunity-For-Bitcoin-Miners-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>Bitcoin, the world&#8217;s largest cryptocurrency, is facing a challenging outlook as selling pressure from miners increases.</p>



<p>The cryptocurrency’s price has been consolidating in a tight, sideways pattern in the past week after facing a significant pullback in early May. On several occasions this week, the price attempted to push and stay above $27,000 but failed towards the weekend, with various fundamentals suggesting the cryptocurrency could face a further drop.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="647" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-20-1024x647.png" alt="" class="wp-image-81144" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-20-1024x647.png 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-20-300x190.png 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-20-768x485.png 768w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-20-1536x971.png 1536w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-20-2048x1294.png 2048w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /><figcaption class="wp-element-caption">BTCUSD Chart by <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BTCUSD/">TradingView</a></figcaption></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-miners-sell-their-coins"><strong>Miners Sell their coins</strong></h2>



<p>Apart from dwindling trading volumes, potentially reflecting investors&#8217; lack of interest in a low-volatility market, there are indications that <a href="https://zycrypto.com/crypto-miners-are-feeling-the-pinch-of-high-energy-prices-and-slump-in-crypto-prices/">Bitcoin miners</a> may have played a role in the recent decline in price.</p>



<p>Earlier today, onchain analytics firm CryptoQuant took to Twitter to share these observations, stating that there is a high probability that 1,750 BTC has ultimately made its way to Binance, one of the leading cryptocurrency exchanges. CryptoQuant&#8217;s assertions came after a thorough examination of various wallets linked to Bitcoin miners by “IT Tech”, an author and analyst at the firm, who tracked the movement of the coins to the exchange.</p>



<p><em>“There is a high probability that 1750 BTC ultimately went to Binance. Miners&#8217; reserves are decreasing, indicating a selling pressure from the miners&#8217; side,</em>” wrote IT Tech.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="645" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-19-1024x645.png" alt="" class="wp-image-81143" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-19-1024x645.png 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-19-300x189.png 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-19-768x484.png 768w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-19.png 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>Notably, amid declining prices, Bitcoin&#8217;s hashrate has also experienced a minor decline in recent days. This decrease indicates a migration of miners away from the Bitcoin ecosystem. As of the current writing, Bitcoin Network Hash Rate was 344.77M, down from 440M on May 2.</p>



<p>These developments raise concerns among market participants, which explains the stagnation of Bitcoin&#8217;s price. Bitcoin&#8217;s price has been experiencing volatility in recent weeks, with several factors, including regulatory inflation concerns impacting its trajectory. The increasing selling pressure from miners, combined with whale transactions, thus adds another layer of complexity to the market.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Miners’ Sales to Subside Soon</strong></h2>



<p>Nevertheless, despite these developments, CryptoQuant’s analyst “BaroVirtual” notes that the unloading of bags may <a href="https://zycrypto.com/are-fears-of-bitcoin-miners-selling-pressure-overblown-this-expert-thinks-so/">slow down</a> soon. </p>



<p><em>“From May 5, 2023, Bitcoin miners began to reduce their Bitcoin holdings drastically, and on May 9, 2023, the miner&#8217;s net position moved into negative territory, indicating intense pressure from miners. Currently, the miner net position values are in the zone where Bitcoin bounced off in previous times, and the local uptrend continued,”</em> the pundit recently wrote.&nbsp;</p>



<p>According to him, miners could significantly slow down sales when Bitcoin hits the $24,000 target.</p>



<p>Bitcoin traded at $26,853 at press time, down 1.14% in the past 24 hours. In the past week, the price has only managed to gain by 1.73%, as per data from CoinMarketCap.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/bitcoins-price-faces-bleak-outlook-as-selling-pressure-from-miners-surge/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Max Keiser Says XRP And All Cryptocurrencies Are Securities, Except For Bitcoin — Here&#8217;s Why</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/max-keiser-says-xrp-and-all-cryptocurrencies-are-securities-except-for-bitcoin-heres-why/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/max-keiser-says-xrp-and-all-cryptocurrencies-are-securities-except-for-bitcoin-heres-why/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Newton Gitonga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 18:59:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=81139</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Max-Keiser-Says-XRP-And-All-Cryptocurrencies-Are-Securities-Except-For-Bitcoin-—-Heres-Why.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Max Keiser Says XRP And All Cryptocurrencies Are Securities, Except For Bitcoin — Here&#039;s Why" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Max-Keiser-Says-XRP-And-All-Cryptocurrencies-Are-Securities-Except-For-Bitcoin-—-Heres-Why.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Max-Keiser-Says-XRP-And-All-Cryptocurrencies-Are-Securities-Except-For-Bitcoin-—-Heres-Why-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Max-Keiser-Says-XRP-And-All-Cryptocurrencies-Are-Securities-Except-For-Bitcoin-—-Heres-Why-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Max-Keiser-Says-XRP-And-All-Cryptocurrencies-Are-Securities-Except-For-Bitcoin-—-Heres-Why-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>Renowned Bitcoin advocate Max Keiser insists that all cryptocurrencies, except for Bitcoin, should be classified as securities. ]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Max-Keiser-Says-XRP-And-All-Cryptocurrencies-Are-Securities-Except-For-Bitcoin-—-Heres-Why.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Max Keiser Says XRP And All Cryptocurrencies Are Securities, Except For Bitcoin — Here&#039;s Why" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Max-Keiser-Says-XRP-And-All-Cryptocurrencies-Are-Securities-Except-For-Bitcoin-—-Heres-Why.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Max-Keiser-Says-XRP-And-All-Cryptocurrencies-Are-Securities-Except-For-Bitcoin-—-Heres-Why-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Max-Keiser-Says-XRP-And-All-Cryptocurrencies-Are-Securities-Except-For-Bitcoin-—-Heres-Why-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Max-Keiser-Says-XRP-And-All-Cryptocurrencies-Are-Securities-Except-For-Bitcoin-—-Heres-Why-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>Renowned Bitcoin advocate Max Keiser insists that all cryptocurrencies, except for Bitcoin, should be classified as securities.</p>



<p>In a recent tweet, Max Keiser, an advisor to the El Salvadorian government on Bitcoin, boldly proclaimed that <a href="https://zycrypto.com/xrp-eyes-monster-move-as-new-lawsuit-outcomes-set-ripple-on-path-to-gigantic-win-against-the-sec/">XRP</a> and all other cryptocurrencies should be classified as securities except for Bitcoin.</p>



<p>Keiser&#8217;s tweet was in response to recent statements by Gary Gensler, the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) chairman, regarding the regulatory classification of digital assets. During a question-and-answer session at the 27th annual Financial Markets Conference hosted by the Federal Reserve Bank of Atlanta on May 15, Gensler referred to crypto markets as “generally non-compliant”, adding that they were based on the “false narrative of decentralization”.</p>



<p>In response to Gensler’s statement, Keiser tweeted on May 16; &#8211;</p>



<p><em>&#8220;Gary&#8217;s right. Everything not Bitcoin, is a security (including ETH &amp; XRP). We already put this into law in El Salvador. We&#8217;re Bitcoin Country and we&#8217;re thriving. I invite Gary Gensler to El Salvador to come and see how we became the leading BTC country in the world.&#8221;</em></p>



<p>But Keiser&#8217;s criticism of XRP did not end there. On Wednesday, May 17, the self-proclaimed Bitcoin maximalist continued his tirade, labelling Ripple as &#8220;crooks&#8221; and supporting the SEC&#8217;s decision to shut them down.</p>



<p><em>&#8220;Ripple are crooks. Their business model is selling unregistered securities. The SEC is right to shut them down,&#8221;</em> Keiser stated, commenting on an article highlighting Ripple’s $250 million acquisition of Swiss custody firm Metaco.</p>



<p>Keiser&#8217;s recent rants have triggered intense discussions within the cryptocurrency community, with some members of the XRP community engaging the Bitcoiner in heated conversations. One notable XRP enthusiast, Mr Huber, referred to Judge Analisa Torres&#8217; recent ruling. Recently, the judge ordered the sealing of documents related to Ripple&#8217;s XRP sales to On-Demand Liquidity clients, citing the need to protect sensitive information concerning Ripple&#8217;s primary business line.</p>



<p><em>“A judge calling to protect Ripple&#8217;s sales of XRP because it&#8217;s their main line of business also doesn&#8217;t sound the slightest like a judge who is going to shut it down,” </em>Huber wrote in a Thursday, May 18 tweet tagging Keiser.</p>



<p>That said, the assertions by Keiser, who has long been an ardent supporter of Bitcoin, highlight a growing debate on the regulatory status of various cryptocurrencies. Keiser implies that these digital assets should be subjected to stricter regulations to safeguard investors&#8217; interests by categorising cryptocurrencies as securities. On various occasions, chair Gensler reiterated that all cryptocurrencies apart from Bitcoin are securities and should be regulated under existing laws.</p>



<p>That said, amidst the ongoing debate surrounding cryptocurrency regulation, industry participants, investors, and regulators eagerly anticipate <a href="https://zycrypto.com/ripples-brad-garlinghouse-blames-confusing-u-s-crypto-rules-for-flow-of-investment-to-europe-and-asia/">clearer guidelines</a> from the SEC or lawmakers. It will also be interesting to see what the court finally decides in the ongoing SEC vs Ripple Lawsuit with judgement day drawing near.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/max-keiser-says-xrp-and-all-cryptocurrencies-are-securities-except-for-bitcoin-heres-why/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>$0.001 Shiba Inu Price Beckons As Shibarium Launch Proves To Be A Game-Changer For SHIB</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/0-001-shiba-inu-price-beckons-as-shibarium-launch-proves-to-be-a-game-changer-for-shib/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/0-001-shiba-inu-price-beckons-as-shibarium-launch-proves-to-be-a-game-changer-for-shib/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aaron Feuerstein]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 16:36:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIB]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIBA INU]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIBUSD]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=81130</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Shiba-Inus-Shibarium-Renews-Bullish-Momentum-For-0.001-SHIB-As-Massive-Token-Burn-Expected.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Shiba Inu&#039;s Shibarium Renews Bullish Momentum For &#039;$0.001 SHIB&#039; As Massive Token Burn Expected" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Shiba-Inus-Shibarium-Renews-Bullish-Momentum-For-0.001-SHIB-As-Massive-Token-Burn-Expected.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Shiba-Inus-Shibarium-Renews-Bullish-Momentum-For-0.001-SHIB-As-Massive-Token-Burn-Expected-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Shiba-Inus-Shibarium-Renews-Bullish-Momentum-For-0.001-SHIB-As-Massive-Token-Burn-Expected-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Shiba-Inus-Shibarium-Renews-Bullish-Momentum-For-0.001-SHIB-As-Massive-Token-Burn-Expected-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>Despite a recent lacklustre performance, Shiba Inu, the cryptocurrency that gained popularity in late 2021, still has a dedicated community of supporters who remain optimistic about its future trajectory and price breakout to the highly-coveted $0.001 price.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Shiba-Inus-Shibarium-Renews-Bullish-Momentum-For-0.001-SHIB-As-Massive-Token-Burn-Expected.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Shiba Inu&#039;s Shibarium Renews Bullish Momentum For &#039;$0.001 SHIB&#039; As Massive Token Burn Expected" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Shiba-Inus-Shibarium-Renews-Bullish-Momentum-For-0.001-SHIB-As-Massive-Token-Burn-Expected.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Shiba-Inus-Shibarium-Renews-Bullish-Momentum-For-0.001-SHIB-As-Massive-Token-Burn-Expected-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Shiba-Inus-Shibarium-Renews-Bullish-Momentum-For-0.001-SHIB-As-Massive-Token-Burn-Expected-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Shiba-Inus-Shibarium-Renews-Bullish-Momentum-For-0.001-SHIB-As-Massive-Token-Burn-Expected-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>Despite a recent lacklustre performance, <a href="https://zycrypto.com/3-catalysts-renewing-bullish-drive-for-0-001-shib-price-as-meme-coins-see-sudden-resurgence/">Shiba Inu</a>, the cryptocurrency that gained popularity in late 2021, still has a dedicated community of supporters who remain optimistic about its future trajectory and price breakout to the highly-coveted $0.001 price. While there are concerns about its high supply and lack of utility, the Shiba Inu team is actively working on initiatives to address these issues, such as developing Shibarium, an upcoming layer-2 (L2) blockchain network.</p>



<p>2022 saw favourable conditions for the 2nd most popular meme coin as growing adoption and integration continued. More exchanges and merchants began to accept Shiba Inu as a form of payment. In addition, burn events and supply reduction permanently reduced some of Shiba Inu&#8217;s supply from circulation. If this continues, it could help reduce the supply and increase the value of the cryptocurrency.</p>



<p>Shiba Inu has one of the most loyal communities in Crypto, and the launch of Shiboshis, Shiba Inu&#8217;s own NFT project, and other NFT projects built on the Shiba Inu network could add utility and value to the Shiba Inu ecosystem. However, according to a recent interview in the international business times, the Shibarium Layer 2 blockchain project is still in development, according to Project Leader Shytoshi Kusama.</p>



<p><a href="https://zycrypto.com/shibarium-the-project-set-to-propel-shiba-inu-beyond-predictions-of-a-0-001-shib-price/">Shibarium</a> is currently in beta test mode, and as Kusama had previously stated numerous times, all tokens on the testnet Puppynet are not real and are merely for testing. However, he once more cautioned the Shiba Inu community about this, noting that thus far, no actual tokens have been singed.</p>



<p>On the other hand, some general factors may influence the price of SHIB. First, the state of the market as a whole is probably going to have an impact on Shiba Inu&#8217;s price. For example, Shiba Inu&#8217;s price is more likely to increase if the cryptocurrency market, in general, is bullish. On the other hand, Shiba Inu&#8217;s price is more likely to diminish if the market is bearish.</p>



<p>Shiba Inu prices can also be impacted by news and events. For instance, the price will likely increase if there is good news regarding Shiba Inu, such as a new alliance or a significant advancement. In contrast, the price will probably decrease if there is bad news, like a security breach or scandal.</p>



<p>As with all meme coins, there is, of course, speculation. Shiba Inu buyers engage in speculation when they purchase SHIB in anticipation of a price increase. Speculation can cause prices to rise quickly, but it can also cause prices to fall quickly.</p>



<p>As with all meme coins, investors should proceed cautiously and only invest what they can afford to lose.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/0-001-shiba-inu-price-beckons-as-shibarium-launch-proves-to-be-a-game-changer-for-shib/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Canada And Australia Continue Consultation And Research Into CBDCs</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/canada-and-australia-continue-consultation-and-research-into-cbdcs/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/canada-and-australia-continue-consultation-and-research-into-cbdcs/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Isa Nsereko]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 16:30:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=81128</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/Bitcoiners-Uneased-As-Nigerias-CBN-Rolls-Out-CBDC-Guidelines.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Bitcoiners Uneased As Nigeria&#039;s CBN Rolls Out CBDC Guidelines" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/Bitcoiners-Uneased-As-Nigerias-CBN-Rolls-Out-CBDC-Guidelines.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/Bitcoiners-Uneased-As-Nigerias-CBN-Rolls-Out-CBDC-Guidelines-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/Bitcoiners-Uneased-As-Nigerias-CBN-Rolls-Out-CBDC-Guidelines-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/Bitcoiners-Uneased-As-Nigerias-CBN-Rolls-Out-CBDC-Guidelines-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>According to a May 8, 2023 press release, the Bank of Canada has launched online public consultations to understand the features that could be included in a digital Canadian dollar. The consultation seeks to understand how Canadians would likely use a Canadian digital dollar, what security features are important, and accessibility and privacy concerns. The [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/Bitcoiners-Uneased-As-Nigerias-CBN-Rolls-Out-CBDC-Guidelines.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Bitcoiners Uneased As Nigeria&#039;s CBN Rolls Out CBDC Guidelines" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/Bitcoiners-Uneased-As-Nigerias-CBN-Rolls-Out-CBDC-Guidelines.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/Bitcoiners-Uneased-As-Nigerias-CBN-Rolls-Out-CBDC-Guidelines-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/Bitcoiners-Uneased-As-Nigerias-CBN-Rolls-Out-CBDC-Guidelines-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/Bitcoiners-Uneased-As-Nigerias-CBN-Rolls-Out-CBDC-Guidelines-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>According to a May 8, 2023 press release, the Bank of Canada has launched online public consultations to understand the features that could be included in a digital Canadian dollar.</p>



<p>The consultation seeks to understand how Canadians would likely use a Canadian digital dollar, what security features are important, and accessibility and privacy concerns. The public consultation runs until June 19, 2023.</p>



<p>The Bank of Canada has stated that a digital Canadian dollar is not needed at this time, and any decision to issue one rests with Parliament and the Government of Canada.</p>



<p>In November 2022, the Canadian government launched a consultation on digital currencies, including stablecoins and central bank digital currency (CBDC). The Bank of Canada continues to actively research, prepare and consult on the case of a potential CBDC. The Bank of Canada will publish a report summarizing this consultation later this year.</p>



<p>Meanwhile, the Governor of the Reserve Bank of Australia (RBA), Philip Lowe, said that the RBA had issued a small amount of digital currency to explore possible use cases of new forms of digital money, including a CBDC, as part of a research project with the Digital Finance Cooperative Research Centre (DFCRC).&nbsp;</p>



<p>Lowe made these remarks at the Reserve Bank Board Dinner in Perth on May 2, 2023. Lowe further said that the RBA was very interested in this project&#8217;s results.</p>



<p>In an August 2022 joint media release, the RBA and the DFCRC announced a collaboration on a research project to explore use cases for a CBDC in Australia. The report on the project’s findings is expected in mid-2023.</p>



<p>According to the PwC Global Crypto Regulation Report 2023, Australia does not have a bespoke regulatory framework for digital assets unless the assets are caught through existing rules which apply to financial products and general consumer law.</p>



<p>In December 2021, the Australian Government agreed to establish regulatory regimes for digital assets, including a licensing and custody regime, decentralized autonomous organizations structures, reviewing the policy framework for digital assets taxation, token mapping and research on potential CBDC viability.</p>



<p>In May 2022, the Australian Government undertook to consult on custody obligations for third-party custodians of crypto assets and provide additional consumer safeguards. In September 2022, a draft bill, the Digital Assets (Market Regulation) Bill, was published for parliamentary debate and public consultation on digital assets, including stablecoins.</p>



<p>The Australian Securities and Investments Commission (ASIC) continues to support the development of a regulatory framework with a focus on consumer protection and market integrity.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/canada-and-australia-continue-consultation-and-research-into-cbdcs/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ripple&#8217;s Brad Garlinghouse Blames Confusing U.S. Crypto Rules for Flow of Investment to Europe and Asia</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/ripples-brad-garlinghouse-blames-confusing-u-s-crypto-rules-for-flow-of-investment-to-europe-and-asia/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/ripples-brad-garlinghouse-blames-confusing-u-s-crypto-rules-for-flow-of-investment-to-europe-and-asia/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aaron Feuerstein]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 14:06:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Brad Garlinghouse]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=81123</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ripples-Brad-Garlinghouse-Blames-Confusing-U.S.-Crypto-Rules-for-Flow-of-Investment-to-Europe-and-Asia.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Ripple&#039;s Brad Garlinghouse Blames Confusing U.S. Crypto Rules for Flow of Investment to Europe and Asia" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ripples-Brad-Garlinghouse-Blames-Confusing-U.S.-Crypto-Rules-for-Flow-of-Investment-to-Europe-and-Asia.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ripples-Brad-Garlinghouse-Blames-Confusing-U.S.-Crypto-Rules-for-Flow-of-Investment-to-Europe-and-Asia-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ripples-Brad-Garlinghouse-Blames-Confusing-U.S.-Crypto-Rules-for-Flow-of-Investment-to-Europe-and-Asia-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ripples-Brad-Garlinghouse-Blames-Confusing-U.S.-Crypto-Rules-for-Flow-of-Investment-to-Europe-and-Asia-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>In a recent CNBC interview, Ripple CEO Brad Garlinghouse underlined the regulatory uncertainty that U.S. cryptocurrency companies must deal with.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ripples-Brad-Garlinghouse-Blames-Confusing-U.S.-Crypto-Rules-for-Flow-of-Investment-to-Europe-and-Asia.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Ripple&#039;s Brad Garlinghouse Blames Confusing U.S. Crypto Rules for Flow of Investment to Europe and Asia" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ripples-Brad-Garlinghouse-Blames-Confusing-U.S.-Crypto-Rules-for-Flow-of-Investment-to-Europe-and-Asia.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ripples-Brad-Garlinghouse-Blames-Confusing-U.S.-Crypto-Rules-for-Flow-of-Investment-to-Europe-and-Asia-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ripples-Brad-Garlinghouse-Blames-Confusing-U.S.-Crypto-Rules-for-Flow-of-Investment-to-Europe-and-Asia-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ripples-Brad-Garlinghouse-Blames-Confusing-U.S.-Crypto-Rules-for-Flow-of-Investment-to-Europe-and-Asia-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>Regulations play a critical role in reshaping the global cryptocurrency business, which is undergoing considerable changes. In a recent CNBC interview, Ripple CEO <a href="https://zycrypto.com/ripples-brad-garlinghouse-tells-where-crypto-market-is-headed-as-xrp-lawsuit-heads-for-conclusion/">Brad Garlinghouse</a> underlined the regulatory uncertainty that U.S. cryptocurrency companies must deal with.</p>



<p>He voiced concerns that this unpredictability is suppressing innovation and driving businesses to look for more benevolent countries.</p>



<p>In the interview, he said, <em>&#8220;Frankly, it&#8217;s why you&#8217;re seeing entrepreneurship and investment flowing into other jurisdictions — and certainly, Europe has been a significant beneficiary of the confusion that has existed in the U.S.&#8221;</em></p>



<p>Garlinghouse&#8217;s worries are shared by several industry players who contend that regulatory clarity is crucial for promoting innovation, luring investment, and guaranteeing consumer protection. Yet, while other nations have proactively worked to provide a supportive regulatory environment for cryptocurrencies, the United States has come under fire for moving too slowly in this direction.</p>



<p>Garlinghouse indicated that more cryptocurrency businesses might think about moving or expanding their operations abroad due to the regulatory uncertainties in the United States. This pattern may slow the development of the U.S. cryptocurrency market and result in a talent and capital outflow.</p>



<p>In a tweet, the CEO said: <em>&#8220;I think it&#8217;s fair to say the U.S. has made it as confusing as possible as to what the rules of the road are for the crypto industry. The SEC has really been at the forefront of that confusion.&#8221;</em></p>



<p>Due to their transparent and thorough regulatory frameworks, nations like Switzerland, Singapore, and Malta have become popular destinations for cryptocurrency businesses. These governments have taken proactive steps to create regulations that strike a balance between consumer protection and innovation, creating a more stable environment for the growth of crypto firms.</p>



<p>According to Garlinghouse, the regulatory uncertainty experienced by U.S. cryptocurrency companies creates serious obstacles to the growth and competitiveness of the sector. The United States runs the risk of losing its status as a major center for the cryptocurrency industry as more businesses look for chances abroad.</p>



<p>Garlinghouse emphasized that Ripple is investing more money elsewhere because of the regulatory uncertainties present in the United States. He stressed that the vast majority of Ripple&#8217;s clientele—roughly 95%—is situated outside of the United States. Additionally, he stated that overseas locations would be the primary focus of Ripple&#8217;s employment efforts in the upcoming year.</p>



<p>The CEO of Ripple also spoke on the business&#8217;s financial situation, noting that it is now in a good place. This comes after Ripple&#8217;s most recent <a href="https://zycrypto.com/ripple-acquires-crypto-custody-provider-metaco-for-250m-as-xrp-lawsuit-nears-end-game/">acquisition of Metaco</a>, a Swiss company specializing in cryptocurrency custody services. Garlinghouse disclosed that $250 million in cash from Ripple&#8217;s balance sheet was used to pay for Metaco.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/ripples-brad-garlinghouse-blames-confusing-u-s-crypto-rules-for-flow-of-investment-to-europe-and-asia/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Turkey Takes the Lead: Crypto Ownership Surges by 27%, Making it the Fastest-Growing Crypto Market</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/turkey-takes-the-lead-crypto-ownership-surges-by-27-making-it-the-fastest-growing-crypto-market/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/turkey-takes-the-lead-crypto-ownership-surges-by-27-making-it-the-fastest-growing-crypto-market/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aaron Feuerstein]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 22:20:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Turkey]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=81120</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/The-Death-Of-The-Lira-Is-Fueling-A-Massive-Spike-In-Bitcoin-USDT-Activity-In-Turkey.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="The &quot;Death Of The Lira&quot; Is Fueling A Massive Spike In Bitcoin, USDT Activity In Turkey" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/The-Death-Of-The-Lira-Is-Fueling-A-Massive-Spike-In-Bitcoin-USDT-Activity-In-Turkey.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/The-Death-Of-The-Lira-Is-Fueling-A-Massive-Spike-In-Bitcoin-USDT-Activity-In-Turkey-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/The-Death-Of-The-Lira-Is-Fueling-A-Massive-Spike-In-Bitcoin-USDT-Activity-In-Turkey-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/The-Death-Of-The-Lira-Is-Fueling-A-Massive-Spike-In-Bitcoin-USDT-Activity-In-Turkey-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>Turkey has seen a huge increase in cryptocurrency ownership as the country&#8217;s inflation rates skyrocket, according to GWI Research. With a 27.1% increase in ownership from July-September 2021 to July-September 2022, Turkey had the biggest growth in cryptocurrency ownership, according to the survey, which looked at people between the ages of 16 and 64. Argentina [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/The-Death-Of-The-Lira-Is-Fueling-A-Massive-Spike-In-Bitcoin-USDT-Activity-In-Turkey.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="The &quot;Death Of The Lira&quot; Is Fueling A Massive Spike In Bitcoin, USDT Activity In Turkey" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/The-Death-Of-The-Lira-Is-Fueling-A-Massive-Spike-In-Bitcoin-USDT-Activity-In-Turkey.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/The-Death-Of-The-Lira-Is-Fueling-A-Massive-Spike-In-Bitcoin-USDT-Activity-In-Turkey-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/The-Death-Of-The-Lira-Is-Fueling-A-Massive-Spike-In-Bitcoin-USDT-Activity-In-Turkey-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/The-Death-Of-The-Lira-Is-Fueling-A-Massive-Spike-In-Bitcoin-USDT-Activity-In-Turkey-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>Turkey has seen a huge increase in cryptocurrency ownership as the country&#8217;s inflation rates skyrocket, according to GWI Research. With a 27.1% increase in ownership from July-September 2021 to July-September 2022, <a href="https://zycrypto.com/ripple-to-donate-1-million-in-xrp-to-earthquake-victims-in-turkey-and-syria/">Turkey</a> had the biggest growth in cryptocurrency ownership, according to the survey, which looked at people between the ages of 16 and 64. Argentina and the Philippines were close behind, with increases of 23.5% and 23.4% in crypto ownership rates.</p>



<p>The soaring inflation rates in these nations can be blamed for the rise in crypto possession. The Turkish Lira had a sharp collapse in late 2021, losing 44% of its value in relation to the US dollar. Early in 2022, the country&#8217;s inflation rate exceeded 30%; by the end of the year, it was a startling 72.31%. The daily trading volume of cryptocurrencies in Turkey reached an average of $1.8 billion due to these economic considerations.</p>



<p>The use of cryptocurrencies in these nations has broad ramifications. Over 2.4 million Turks, or about 2.94% of the population, are now considered Bitcoin owners. The devaluation of the Turkish Lira, which impacted many Turkish families&#8217; savings and investments, has improved the environment for the adoption of cryptocurrencies. Additionally, the Turkish populace has come to favour cryptocurrencies due to their simplicity of use and perception of them as a hedge against inflation.</p>



<p>Trading is the only available alternative for people interested in the field due to Turkey&#8217;s lack of a regulatory framework, which has allowed cryptocurrency trading to grow. However, as the government prepares to introduce its central bank&#8217;s digital currency, the digital lira, in 2023, regulatory adjustments are anticipated in the upcoming years. Higher taxes and more precise regulations for cryptocurrency-related activity are predicted, yet a total ban on cryptocurrencies seems unlikely.</p>



<p>A loss of faith in fiat money and demand for alternative stores of value in Argentina and the Philippines has also sparked the popularity of cryptocurrencies. The public&#8217;s increased interest in cryptocurrencies is a sign that digital assets are becoming more widely accepted and that decentralised financial systems are becoming more prevalent.</p>



<p>Significant trading volumes are seen on major Turkish cryptocurrency exchanges like BtcTurk and Paribu, indicating that the rise in cryptocurrency ownership in these nations is not going unnoticed. Another sign of cryptocurrencies&#8217; expanding societal influence is their growth into other industries, like sports sponsorship and university courses.</p>



<p>Cryptocurrencies have become popular for people looking to secure their wealth as the global economy struggles with the pandemic&#8217;s aftermath and inflationary pressures. The rise in cryptocurrency ownership in Turkey, Argentina, and the Philippines demonstrates the growing acceptance and acknowledgement of cryptocurrencies as an alternative financial tool in times of economic upheaval, even though difficulties and concerns still exist.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/turkey-takes-the-lead-crypto-ownership-surges-by-27-making-it-the-fastest-growing-crypto-market/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ripple Launches A Novel Platform For Governments, Central Banks Developing CBDCs</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/ripple-launches-a-novel-platform-for-governments-central-banks-developing-cbdcs/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/ripple-launches-a-novel-platform-for-governments-central-banks-developing-cbdcs/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Brenda Ngari]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 20:23:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=81109</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Montenegro-Joins-Hands-With-Ripple-To-Pilot-First-National-Digital-Currency-—-Mammoth-Boost-to-XRP.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Montenegro Joins Hands With Ripple To Pilot First National Digital Currency — Mammoth Boost to XRP?" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Montenegro-Joins-Hands-With-Ripple-To-Pilot-First-National-Digital-Currency-—-Mammoth-Boost-to-XRP.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Montenegro-Joins-Hands-With-Ripple-To-Pilot-First-National-Digital-Currency-—-Mammoth-Boost-to-XRP-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Montenegro-Joins-Hands-With-Ripple-To-Pilot-First-National-Digital-Currency-—-Mammoth-Boost-to-XRP-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Montenegro-Joins-Hands-With-Ripple-To-Pilot-First-National-Digital-Currency-—-Mammoth-Boost-to-XRP-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>Described as “a frictionless end-to-end solution”, the new platform is based on Ripple's XRP Ledger and is an improved version of Ripple's Private Ledger.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Montenegro-Joins-Hands-With-Ripple-To-Pilot-First-National-Digital-Currency-—-Mammoth-Boost-to-XRP.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Montenegro Joins Hands With Ripple To Pilot First National Digital Currency — Mammoth Boost to XRP?" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Montenegro-Joins-Hands-With-Ripple-To-Pilot-First-National-Digital-Currency-—-Mammoth-Boost-to-XRP.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Montenegro-Joins-Hands-With-Ripple-To-Pilot-First-National-Digital-Currency-—-Mammoth-Boost-to-XRP-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Montenegro-Joins-Hands-With-Ripple-To-Pilot-First-National-Digital-Currency-—-Mammoth-Boost-to-XRP-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Montenegro-Joins-Hands-With-Ripple-To-Pilot-First-National-Digital-Currency-—-Mammoth-Boost-to-XRP-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>San Francisco-based blockchain payments firm <a href="https://zycrypto.com/ripple-acquires-crypto-custody-provider-metaco-for-250m-as-xrp-lawsuit-nears-end-game/">Ripple</a> has introduced a platform for governments, central banks, and financial institutions to create their own digital currency. Described as “a frictionless end-to-end solution”, the new platform is based on Ripple&#8217;s XRP Ledger and is an improved version of Ripple&#8217;s Private Ledger.</p>



<p>Ripple has also joined forces with the Hong Kong Monetary Authority, which acts as the defacto central bank, for the launch of the digital Hong Kong dollar (e-HKD) pilot program.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-what-is-the-point-of-ripple-s-new-cbdc-platform"><strong>What Is The Point Of Ripple’s New CBDC Platform?</strong></h2>



<p>CBDCs are a hot topic right now. Unlike crypto assets like Bitcoin or Ethereum, CBDCs are controlled and managed by a centralized entity. Per the Atlantic Council’s tracker, only 11 nations have rolled out a central bank digital currency so far, but many other countries are researching and testing the technology.</p>



<p>Ripple has waded further into the CBDC game via the launch of a new platform for creating blockchain-based digital currencies. The Ripple platform allows for the oversight and customization of the entire life cycle of the CBDC, including minting, distribution, redemption, and removal from circulation. The CBDC platform will also let institutions operate and conduct inter-institutional settlement and distribution functions.</p>



<p>Ripple will leverage the power of blockchain technology used for the <a href="https://zycrypto.com/automated-market-makers-finally-coming-to-xrpl-why-this-feature-could-be-super-bullish-for-1-xrp-price/">XRP Ledger</a> and provide a way for government institutions to increase financial inclusion and reduce the risk involved in domestic and cross-border payments.</p>



<p>President of the Republic of Palau, Surangel Whipps Jr, hailed Ripple’s new CBDC platform while describing how it’s enabling them to create their own solutions.</p>



<p>“<em>Partnering with Ripple to help create our national digital currency is part of our commitment to lead in financial innovation and technologies, which will provide the citizens of Palau with greater financial access”.</em></p>



<p>It will be possible for financial institutions to use the platform to oversee the distribution processes involving their digital currency, while end users — both corporate and retail — will be able to hold their CBDC securely and use them to pay and receive payment for goods and services, similar to how banking apps function today. This entails the convenience of offline transactions and as well as accommodating non-smartphone cases.</p>



<p>Ripple is also collaborating with Taiwan’s Fubon Bank to develop a real estate asset tokenization and equity release product using a retail version of the e-HKD CBDC.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/ripple-launches-a-novel-platform-for-governments-central-banks-developing-cbdcs/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
