<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>News Archives &#8902; ZyCrypto</title>
	<atom:link href="https://zycrypto.com/category/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://zycrypto.com/category/news/</link>
	<description>ZyCrypto Is A Cryptocurrency News Media, Focusing On Daily News, Expert Opinions, Analysis, Reviews, And So Much More.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 22:07:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/cropped-ZyCrypto-Site-Logo-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News Archives &#8902; ZyCrypto</title>
	<link>https://zycrypto.com/category/news/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Why Joining 75,000 XRP Holders Against the SEC Does Not Affect Potential Recovery for XRP Holders</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/why-joining-75000-xrp-holders-against-the-sec-does-not-affect-potential-recovery-for-xrp-holders/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/why-joining-75000-xrp-holders-against-the-sec-does-not-affect-potential-recovery-for-xrp-holders/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aaron Feuerstein]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 22:07:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=82732</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Why-Pro-Ripple-Lawyer-Says-XRP-Cant-Be-Classed-As-A-Security-Even-If-It-Was-Sold-As-One.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Why Pro-Ripple Lawyer Says XRP Can’t Be Classed As A Security Even If It Was Sold As One" decoding="async" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Why-Pro-Ripple-Lawyer-Says-XRP-Cant-Be-Classed-As-A-Security-Even-If-It-Was-Sold-As-One.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Why-Pro-Ripple-Lawyer-Says-XRP-Cant-Be-Classed-As-A-Security-Even-If-It-Was-Sold-As-One-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Why-Pro-Ripple-Lawyer-Says-XRP-Cant-Be-Classed-As-A-Security-Even-If-It-Was-Sold-As-One-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Why-Pro-Ripple-Lawyer-Says-XRP-Cant-Be-Classed-As-A-Security-Even-If-It-Was-Sold-As-One-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>Prominent crypto lawyer John E. Deaton was recently asked about the possibility of more XRP holders joining the civil case against Ripple in Oakland, California, if the verdict in SEC vs Ripple goes against Ripple and the judge declares XRP a security.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Why-Pro-Ripple-Lawyer-Says-XRP-Cant-Be-Classed-As-A-Security-Even-If-It-Was-Sold-As-One.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Why Pro-Ripple Lawyer Says XRP Can’t Be Classed As A Security Even If It Was Sold As One" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Why-Pro-Ripple-Lawyer-Says-XRP-Cant-Be-Classed-As-A-Security-Even-If-It-Was-Sold-As-One.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Why-Pro-Ripple-Lawyer-Says-XRP-Cant-Be-Classed-As-A-Security-Even-If-It-Was-Sold-As-One-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Why-Pro-Ripple-Lawyer-Says-XRP-Cant-Be-Classed-As-A-Security-Even-If-It-Was-Sold-As-One-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Why-Pro-Ripple-Lawyer-Says-XRP-Cant-Be-Classed-As-A-Security-Even-If-It-Was-Sold-As-One-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>Prominent crypto lawyer John E. Deaton was recently asked about the possibility of more XRP holders joining the civil case against Ripple in Oakland, California, if the verdict in <a href="https://zycrypto.com/sec-vs-ripple-hinman-documents-release-is-a-boost-to-ethereum-jpmorgan-analysts-share-opinion/">SEC vs Ripple</a> goes against Ripple and the judge declares XRP a security. Just last week, a California Judge certified a class of American purchasers of XRP in a complaint accusing Ripple Labs of selling unregistered securities. This second legal concern Ripple is facing is the subject of the tweet that prompted the question.</p>



<p>Concerning the ongoing legal conflict between Ripple Labs and the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), Deaton discussed the possible options and their potential impact on Ripple, XRP investors, and the SEC.</p>



<p>Regarding any money flowing from Ripple to the SEC, the lawyer is sure it won&#8217;t happen for years and only if Ripple were to lose on appeal.</p>



<p>Deaton said: <em>“If the Supreme Court takes it on appeal (which I believe they will if Congress hasn’t acted by then), I believe Ripple hands down wins with this Supreme Court. If the SEC wins Ripple will appeal and the status quo that exists today will continue over the next 2-5 years.”</em></p>



<p>He claims that if the SEC prevails and the civil case attorneys triumph because the Californian judge upholds Judge Torres&#8217; decision, Ripple will also appeal that case and no money will change hands, possibly never. If Ripple loses all of its challenges in five years, the SEC, not the civil claimants, would be responsible for collecting the $1.3 billion.</p>



<p>It&#8217;s important to note that the SEC would receive this money rather than the civil claimants. In response, the SEC would create a repayment fund akin to the Veritaseum case, enabling holders of XRP to sell their tokens.</p>



<p>Deaton emphasizes an intriguing aspect of the situation that some may have missed. He argues that if the SEC were to lose, the damages that could be recovered in civil litigation would rise. Conversely, an SEC victory could make obtaining any financial losses more challenging for the civil lawsuit&#8217;s plaintiffs.</p>



<p>Deaton stresses that signing up for the 75K list, a list of XRP owners he represents in SEC vs Ripple, does not constitute a waiver of any rights or claims. Being on the list instead aids in identifying a sizable potential class of XRP holders. Holders of XRP on the list would probably be informed if there was ever a financial recovery in either the civil or SEC lawsuit.</p>



<p>He said: <em>“Also if Ripple loses and Congress fixes this regulatory mess during the 5 years of appeals, it all goes away anyway. Bottom line, being on the list didn’t waive anything and, if anything, it identified your claims (if you have any) long ago.”</em></p>



<p>Critics who claim that joining the 75K list and claiming that XRP is not a security would be damaging if XRP holders received financial compensation are dismissed by the attorney. He clarifies that even if a judge and an appeals court found differently, being mistaken about XRP&#8217;s security status would not result in punishment.</p>



<p>Given the possible outcomes, Deaton expresses doubt about the civil lawsuit&#8217;s impact. He contends that, paradoxically, XRP investors would gain if the SEC finally wins since it would receive the largest settlement and the best resolution.</p>



<p>These observations from John E. Deaton offer helpful perspectives on the probable outcomes and repercussions for all parties involved as the Ripple-SEC legal dispute continues.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/why-joining-75000-xrp-holders-against-the-sec-does-not-affect-potential-recovery-for-xrp-holders/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ex-SEC Chair Joins Chorus Pushing For Spot Bitcoin ETF Approval</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/ex-sec-chair-joins-chorus-pushing-for-spot-bitcoin-etf-approval/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/ex-sec-chair-joins-chorus-pushing-for-spot-bitcoin-etf-approval/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Brenda Ngari]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 20:53:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XBTUSD]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=82729</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ex-SEC-Chair-Joins-Chorus-Pushing-For-Spot-Bitcoin-ETF-Approval.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Ex-SEC Chair Joins Chorus Pushing For Spot Bitcoin ETF Approval" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ex-SEC-Chair-Joins-Chorus-Pushing-For-Spot-Bitcoin-ETF-Approval.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ex-SEC-Chair-Joins-Chorus-Pushing-For-Spot-Bitcoin-ETF-Approval-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ex-SEC-Chair-Joins-Chorus-Pushing-For-Spot-Bitcoin-ETF-Approval-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ex-SEC-Chair-Joins-Chorus-Pushing-For-Spot-Bitcoin-ETF-Approval-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>In July 2013, Cameron and Tyler Winklevoss filed paperwork to introduce the first-ever Bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF). A decade later, the industry is still waiting for a spot Bitcoin product.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ex-SEC-Chair-Joins-Chorus-Pushing-For-Spot-Bitcoin-ETF-Approval.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Ex-SEC Chair Joins Chorus Pushing For Spot Bitcoin ETF Approval" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ex-SEC-Chair-Joins-Chorus-Pushing-For-Spot-Bitcoin-ETF-Approval.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ex-SEC-Chair-Joins-Chorus-Pushing-For-Spot-Bitcoin-ETF-Approval-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ex-SEC-Chair-Joins-Chorus-Pushing-For-Spot-Bitcoin-ETF-Approval-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ex-SEC-Chair-Joins-Chorus-Pushing-For-Spot-Bitcoin-ETF-Approval-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>During his latest interview, Jay Clayton voiced his openness to a spot bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF). The former Securities and Exchange Commission chairman noted that he was doubtful about trading in the BTC market during his time in office. However, he admitted that the emergence of reputable institutions in the crypto industry is an impressive development not seen before. </p>



<p>As such, he believes it would be &#8216;hard to resist&#8217; okaying a physically-backed bitcoin ETF as long as the requisite regulatory protections are in place, similar to those in the futures market.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-clayton-bullish-on-spot-bitcoin-etf-approval"><strong>Clayton Bullish On Spot Bitcoin ETF Approval</strong></h2>



<p>In July 2013, Cameron and Tyler Winklevoss filed paperwork to introduce the first-ever Bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF). A decade later, the industry is still waiting for a spot Bitcoin product.</p>



<p>Speaking during a Monday <a href="https://twitter.com/SquawkCNBC/status/1678381857367289856">interview </a>with <em>CNBC</em>, the former chair of the SEC, Jay Clayton, pinpointed the noteworthy changes he has witnessed in market sentiment toward crypto since his tenure. &#8220;This is an offshore, retail, nothing close to what I would say are the core of our financial markets,&#8221; Clayton posited of Bitcoin&#8217;s earlier days.</p>



<p>While Clayton was previously wary of the Bitcoin market due to concerns of wash trading and market manipulation, the former securities regulator recognized the remarkable steps the industry has made, particularly in terms of institutional investment.</p>



<p>Prominent reputable companies are now foraying into Bitcoin, showing increasing confidence in the industry’s regulatory safeguards and trading credentials. “The fact that we have these institutions that know markets better than anybody and saying we&#8217;re going to put our reputation behind it, I find that pretty remarkable,&#8221; Clayton observed.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Time For Bitcoin ETF Approval</strong></h2>



<p>Speaking of spot bitcoin ETFs, Clayton said he thought applicants have a strong chance at approval if they can ascertain that it’s a more efficient way for investors to invest in the crypto asset.</p>



<p>“If they’re right that the spot market has similar efficacy to the futures market, it would be hard to resist approving a bitcoin ETF.”</p>



<p>The former Wall Street regulator is popularly known for launching an unprecedented suit against Ripple and two of its top executives in late 2020 while he was still chair of the SEC. He is also responsible for the rejection of numerous physically backed bitcoin ETFs during his stint as the 32nd chairman of the commission.</p>



<p>As of right now, there&#8217;s still no spot Bitcoin ETF trading in the United States, but BlackRock’s application a couple of weeks ago signalled to the industry that the time may be coming when that changes. In recent weeks, we’ve seen around half a dozen new filings for a spot bitcoin ETF. Has the market matured enough to support an ETF as Clayton suggests, and can applicants give the SEC adequate guarantees that an ETF would be safe for investors?</p>



<p>While Clayton is bullish on the approval of a spot crypto ETF if certain conditions are met, he did not say when he expects such a long-awaited product to happen in the U.S finally.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/ex-sec-chair-joins-chorus-pushing-for-spot-bitcoin-etf-approval/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The First Court Hearing For Terra Co-Founder Held In South Korea</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/the-first-court-hearing-for-terra-co-founder-held-in-south-korea/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/the-first-court-hearing-for-terra-co-founder-held-in-south-korea/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Brenda Ngari]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 20:43:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[South Korea]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Terra]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=82727</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/LUNA-Nosedives-A-Staggering-60-As-Binance-Disables-Terra-Withdrawals-—-Whats-Next-For-UST.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="LUNA Nosedives A Staggering 60% As Binance Disables Terra Withdrawals — What&#039;s Next For UST?" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/LUNA-Nosedives-A-Staggering-60-As-Binance-Disables-Terra-Withdrawals-—-Whats-Next-For-UST.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/LUNA-Nosedives-A-Staggering-60-As-Binance-Disables-Terra-Withdrawals-—-Whats-Next-For-UST-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/LUNA-Nosedives-A-Staggering-60-As-Binance-Disables-Terra-Withdrawals-—-Whats-Next-For-UST-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/LUNA-Nosedives-A-Staggering-60-As-Binance-Disables-Terra-Withdrawals-—-Whats-Next-For-UST-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>Terraform Labs' trouble continues as the Seoul Southern District Court on Monday conducted the first hearing for Daniel Shin and seven other employees of the company.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/LUNA-Nosedives-A-Staggering-60-As-Binance-Disables-Terra-Withdrawals-—-Whats-Next-For-UST.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="LUNA Nosedives A Staggering 60% As Binance Disables Terra Withdrawals — What&#039;s Next For UST?" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/LUNA-Nosedives-A-Staggering-60-As-Binance-Disables-Terra-Withdrawals-—-Whats-Next-For-UST.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/LUNA-Nosedives-A-Staggering-60-As-Binance-Disables-Terra-Withdrawals-—-Whats-Next-For-UST-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/LUNA-Nosedives-A-Staggering-60-As-Binance-Disables-Terra-Withdrawals-—-Whats-Next-For-UST-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/LUNA-Nosedives-A-Staggering-60-As-Binance-Disables-Terra-Withdrawals-—-Whats-Next-For-UST-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>Terraform Labs&#8217; trouble continues as the Seoul Southern District Court on Monday conducted the first hearing for Daniel Shin and seven other employees of the company. Shin, who was indicted in April by South Korea on violations of capital-markets law, among other charges, skipped the hearing. His legal team requested additional trial preparation time.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-legal-proceedings-for-daniel-shin-begin-in-seoul"><strong>Legal Proceedings For Daniel Shin Begin In Seoul</strong></h2>



<p>A trial preparation hearing for Terraform co-founder Daniel Shin kicked off in a Seoul Southern District Court.</p>



<p>According to a report from local news outlet <em>News1 Korea</em> on July 10, the Seoul court held the preliminary hearing for Shin and seven of his alleged accomplices. However, the former Terra exec reportedly did not personally show up for the hearing. His attorneys argued that this case is more technical and asked for extra time. Judge Jang Seong-hoon approved the request and set August 28 as the second trial date.</p>



<p>Shin and the seven others were indicted without detention on April 25 by the Seoul Southern District Prosecutor’s Office for myriad charges, including illegal trading. At the time, prosecutors said the entire Terra project was “fictitious” and bound to fail.</p>



<p>Prosecutors have alleged that Shin and his accomplices misled investors and manipulated the price of some tokens via media coverage and transactions beginning in 2018. They reportedly accrued “unfair profits” of around 462.9 billion won (over $350 million). Shin’s attorneys denied all the allegations in April. Nonetheless, the authorities said at the time that they had already frozen 246.8 billion won ($184.7 million) in assets from the people indicted.&nbsp;</p>



<p>Shin co-founded Terraform Labs with Do Kwon back in 2018. His legal team has previously asserted that he left the company in 2020, prior to the spectacular May 2022 implosion of the Terra ecosystem. Per his LinkedIn profile, Shin then went on to launch payments firm PortOne Global. </p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Global Legal Fallout</strong></h2>



<p>The catastrophic meltdown of Terra caused by its algorithmic stablecoin terraUSD (UST) dropping from its peg with the U.S. dollar sent shockwaves throughout the crypto markets, triggering a series of high-profile bankruptcy cases.</p>



<p>Legal fallout from the multi-billion-dollar Terra cataclysm now spans multiple countries following the <a href="https://zycrypto.com/terras-luna-sees-selloff-following-founder-do-kwons-arrest-in-montenegro/">detention </a>of Do Kwon and chief financial officer Han Chang Joon in Montenegro in March.</p>



<p>Both the United States and his native South Korea are pushing for Kwon’s extradition, but he and Joon must first face charges of using forged travel documents in Montenegro. As <em>ZyCrypto </em><a href="https://zycrypto.com/terras-do-kwon-found-guilty-of-passport-forgery-in-montenegro-sentenced-to-four-months-in-prison/">reported</a> last month, Kwon was sentenced to four months in prison in the Balkan nation.</p>



<p>Meanwhile, the cornered crypto founder has moved to dismiss charges brought against him by the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), on the basis that Terra-linked tokens don’t qualify as securities.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/the-first-court-hearing-for-terra-co-founder-held-in-south-korea/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Standard Chartered Bank Says Bitcoin Price Likely To Hit $50,000 This Year, $120,000 By 2024</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/standard-chartered-bank-says-bitcoin-price-likely-to-hit-50000-this-year-120000-by-2024/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/standard-chartered-bank-says-bitcoin-price-likely-to-hit-50000-this-year-120000-by-2024/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Brenda Ngari]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 17:39:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XBTUSD]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=82724</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoins-Price-Outlook-Uncertain-as-Key-Support-Level-Faces-Crucial-Test.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoins-Price-Outlook-Uncertain-as-Key-Support-Level-Faces-Crucial-Test.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoins-Price-Outlook-Uncertain-as-Key-Support-Level-Faces-Crucial-Test-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoins-Price-Outlook-Uncertain-as-Key-Support-Level-Faces-Crucial-Test-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoins-Price-Outlook-Uncertain-as-Key-Support-Level-Faces-Crucial-Test-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>Multinational bank Standard Chartered, which in December 2022 predicted that the bitcoin price was on track to plummet as low as $5,000 in 2023, now believes that the world's first and largest cryptocurrency will cost ten times more by year-end and an astounding $120,000 in 2024.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoins-Price-Outlook-Uncertain-as-Key-Support-Level-Faces-Crucial-Test.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoins-Price-Outlook-Uncertain-as-Key-Support-Level-Faces-Crucial-Test.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoins-Price-Outlook-Uncertain-as-Key-Support-Level-Faces-Crucial-Test-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoins-Price-Outlook-Uncertain-as-Key-Support-Level-Faces-Crucial-Test-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoins-Price-Outlook-Uncertain-as-Key-Support-Level-Faces-Crucial-Test-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>Multinational bank Standard Chartered, which in December 2022 <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2022-12-05/bitcoin-sinks-further-70-in-standard-chartered-list-of-possible-2023-upsets?utm_source=google&amp;utm_medium=bd&amp;cmpId=google&amp;sref=323RPL5z">predicted </a>that the <a href="https://zycrypto.com/analyst-reveals-what-market-conditions-could-supercharge-bitcoin-price-to-310000/">bitcoin price</a> was on track to plummet as low as $5,000 in 2023, now believes that the world&#8217;s first and largest cryptocurrency will cost ten times more by year-end and an astounding $120,000 in 2024.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-120-000-bitcoin-supply-shock-will-slingshot-btc-skyward"><strong>$120,000: Bitcoin Supply Shock Will Slingshot BTC Skyward</strong></h2>



<p>Standard Chartered has shared a rosy outlook for Bitcoin.</p>



<p>According to a <a href="https://www.reuters.com/technology/standard-chartered-bumps-up-bitcoin-forecast-120000-2023-07-10/">report </a>by Standard Chartered Bank’s Global Head of Research &amp; Chief Strategist, Geoff Kendrick, Bitcoin has the potential to reach $50,000 this year. Thereafter, the top crypto will climb to $120,000 by the end of next year.</p>



<p>In the banking group’s opinion, the price boom would be driven by one key factor: bitcoin supply dynamics. As network miners use more resources to secure the network, they dump less of their BTC coins, causing a demand-supply disparity that favors the bulls.</p>



<p>“Increased profitability for miners to mine Bitcoin means they can reduce sales while maintaining cash inflow, reducing the net supply of Bitcoin and driving up Bitcoin’s price,” Kendrick opined.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Exciting Times Ahead For Bitcoin</strong></h2>



<p>Standard Chartered giving a bullish forecast on Bitcoin’s future price makes it the latest firm to conclude that digital assets are here to stay especially after BlackRock&#8217;s recent entry into the spot Bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF) arena. BlackRock’s ETF application could make it much easier for fellow Wall Street firms to embrace cryptocurrencies and subsequently transform the BTC market.</p>



<p>Assuming the financial giant succeeds in its ETF quest and other institutional investors follow suit, it would stabilize the Bitcoin price at a considerably higher level than the current $30,000.</p>



<p>Since <a href="https://zycrypto.com/btc-surges-past-31k-now-up-80-this-year-as-wall-street-eyes-digital-gold/">popping above $31k</a> in June, bitcoin has changed hands between $29,500 and $31,500 levels. The crypto was little changed on Monday, dropping by 0.1% over the past 24 hours to trade at $30,252.43 at press time, according to CoinGecko.</p>



<p>That being said, the involvement of huge financial institutions, whether it be for ETF filings or the new EDX crypto exchange marks a substantial shift and a pivotal moment for the crypto industry in the United States and globally.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/standard-chartered-bank-says-bitcoin-price-likely-to-hit-50000-this-year-120000-by-2024/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Supply Held by U.S. Entities Spike Following BlackRock’s Spot Bitcoin ETF Application</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/bitcoin-supply-held-by-u-s-entities-spike-following-blackrocks-spot-bitcoin-etf-application/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/bitcoin-supply-held-by-u-s-entities-spike-following-blackrocks-spot-bitcoin-etf-application/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Olivia Brooke]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 19:52:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XBTUSD]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=82716</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Theres-A-50-Chance-BlackRocks-Spot-Bitcoin-ETF-Gets-Greenlight-From-SEC-Top-Bloomberg-Analyst-Predicts.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="There’s A 50% Chance BlackRock’s Spot Bitcoin ETF Gets Greenlight From SEC, Top Bloomberg Analyst Predicts" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Theres-A-50-Chance-BlackRocks-Spot-Bitcoin-ETF-Gets-Greenlight-From-SEC-Top-Bloomberg-Analyst-Predicts.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Theres-A-50-Chance-BlackRocks-Spot-Bitcoin-ETF-Gets-Greenlight-From-SEC-Top-Bloomberg-Analyst-Predicts-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Theres-A-50-Chance-BlackRocks-Spot-Bitcoin-ETF-Gets-Greenlight-From-SEC-Top-Bloomberg-Analyst-Predicts-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Theres-A-50-Chance-BlackRocks-Spot-Bitcoin-ETF-Gets-Greenlight-From-SEC-Top-Bloomberg-Analyst-Predicts-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>According to data from Glassnode, the Bitcoin network has seen an upsurge in the amount of Bitcoin held by market players.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Theres-A-50-Chance-BlackRocks-Spot-Bitcoin-ETF-Gets-Greenlight-From-SEC-Top-Bloomberg-Analyst-Predicts.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="There’s A 50% Chance BlackRock’s Spot Bitcoin ETF Gets Greenlight From SEC, Top Bloomberg Analyst Predicts" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Theres-A-50-Chance-BlackRocks-Spot-Bitcoin-ETF-Gets-Greenlight-From-SEC-Top-Bloomberg-Analyst-Predicts.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Theres-A-50-Chance-BlackRocks-Spot-Bitcoin-ETF-Gets-Greenlight-From-SEC-Top-Bloomberg-Analyst-Predicts-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Theres-A-50-Chance-BlackRocks-Spot-Bitcoin-ETF-Gets-Greenlight-From-SEC-Top-Bloomberg-Analyst-Predicts-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Theres-A-50-Chance-BlackRocks-Spot-Bitcoin-ETF-Gets-Greenlight-From-SEC-Top-Bloomberg-Analyst-Predicts-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>According to data from Glassnode, the Bitcoin network has seen an upsurge in the amount of Bitcoin held by market players. Notably, this uptrend was spotted amongst Bitcoin holders in the United States.</p>



<p>Glassnode asserted that the new development was triggered by BlackRock’s recent announcement concerning its spot Bitcoin ETF application. The new development signals a potential inflection point in the asset’s supply dominance if the trend continues.</p>



<p><em>“Following the Blackrock Bitcoin ETF request announcement on June 15th, the share of Bitcoin supply held/traded by US entities has experienced a notable uptick, marking a potential inflection point in supply dominance if the trend is sustained.”</em></p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Following the Blackrock <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Bitcoin?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Bitcoin</a> ETF request announcement on June 15th, the share of Bitcoin supply held/traded by US entities has experienced a notable uptick, marking a potential inflection point in supply dominance if the trend is sustained. <a href="https://t.co/DvRCYB4BUF">pic.twitter.com/DvRCYB4BUF</a></p>&mdash; glassnode (@glassnode) <a href="https://twitter.com/glassnode/status/1677637186559135745?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">July 8, 2023</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>The price of Bitcoin could also benefit from the success of the Bitcoin ETF request, as it will become the first spot Bitcoin ETF in the country. </p>



<p>In a recent interview with Fox News, Larry Fink, the CEO of BlackRock, made some <a href="https://zycrypto.com/btc-holds-above-31k-as-blackrock-ceo-larry-fink-lauds-bitcoin-for-digitizing-gold/">bullish remarks about Bitcoin</a>, as he explained that the asset is pioneering the digitalization of gold differently.</p>



<p><em>“I do believe the role of crypto is [that] it’s digitizing gold in many ways. Instead of investing in gold as a hedge against inflation, as hedge against the onerous problems of any country, or the devaluation of your currency.. let’s be clear: Bitcoin is an international asset, it’s not based on any one currency, and so it can represent an asset that people can play as an alternative.” Fink asserted.</em></p>



<p>Sentiments around BlackRock&#8217;s spot Bitcoin ETF filing are mixed at this time. While some market participants are positive that the ETF proposal by the $10 trillion asset manager could usher in more institutional investors, others insist that the ETF poses a more significant risk to the Bitcoin market.</p>



<p>Notably, Cathie Wood, the CEO of Ark Invest, stated that the SEC would likely reject BlackRock’s ETF proposal. Speaking to Fortune Crypto in a recent interview, Wood is <a href="https://fortune.com/crypto/2023/07/06/we-dont-think-thats-true-cathie-wood-says-blackrock-doesnt-have-an-edge-when-it-comes-to-sec-approval-for-a-spot-bitcoin-etf/amp/">quoted</a> saying; </p>



<p><em>“We [Ark Invest] know that there was a surveillance clause in their prospectus that ours didn’t include, but what I’m told is it won’t take much time for us to amend our prospectus, and that all of the exchanges are moving in this direction.”</em></p>



<p>At report time, <a href="https://zycrypto.com/bitcoins-correlation-with-traditional-markets-and-gold-diminishes-heres-why/">Bitcoin</a> is trading for $30,274. After clearing hourly losses, Bitcoin seems to be positioning itself for a comeback. The apex cryptocurrency could retest its recent high of $30,403 in the near term.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/bitcoin-supply-held-by-u-s-entities-spike-following-blackrocks-spot-bitcoin-etf-application/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Global Super Computer: Vision for Polkadot Revealed by Co-Founder Gavin Wood</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/global-super-computer-vision-for-polkadot-revealed-by-co-founder-gavin-wood/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/global-super-computer-vision-for-polkadot-revealed-by-co-founder-gavin-wood/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aaron Feuerstein]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 19:22:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DOT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DOTUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Polkadot]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=82714</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Polkadot-Tops-Rivals-in-Developer-Activity-Following-Influx-From-Solana.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Polkadot Tops Rivals in Developer Activity Following Influx From Solana" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Polkadot-Tops-Rivals-in-Developer-Activity-Following-Influx-From-Solana.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Polkadot-Tops-Rivals-in-Developer-Activity-Following-Influx-From-Solana-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Polkadot-Tops-Rivals-in-Developer-Activity-Following-Influx-From-Solana-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Polkadot-Tops-Rivals-in-Developer-Activity-Following-Influx-From-Solana-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>Dr Gavin Wood, the creator of Polkadot, made a ground-breaking revelation about his ambitious aspirations to build a global supercomputer on the Polkadot network.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Polkadot-Tops-Rivals-in-Developer-Activity-Following-Influx-From-Solana.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Polkadot Tops Rivals in Developer Activity Following Influx From Solana" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Polkadot-Tops-Rivals-in-Developer-Activity-Following-Influx-From-Solana.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Polkadot-Tops-Rivals-in-Developer-Activity-Following-Influx-From-Solana-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Polkadot-Tops-Rivals-in-Developer-Activity-Following-Influx-From-Solana-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Polkadot-Tops-Rivals-in-Developer-Activity-Following-Influx-From-Solana-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>Dr Gavin Wood, the creator of <a href="https://zycrypto.com/uniswaps-groundbreaking-decision-expanding-business-to-polkadot-via-moonbeam-parachain/">Polkadot</a>, made a ground-breaking revelation about his ambitious aspirations to build a global supercomputer on the Polkadot network. The announcement was made during the recent Polkadot Decoded conference when Wood highlighted the vast potential of Polkadot and outlined its key features.</p>



<p>Because of the scattered and incompatible nature of the current internet infrastructure, Wood sees Polkadot as a worldwide supercomputer. He asserts that a decentralized network with seamless data sharing and connectivity between various blockchains and networks is what the future holds.</p>



<p>Wood emphasized the need for a platform to unite specialized blockchains into one cohesive network. He stated, <em>&#8220;Polkadot aims to create a scalable and interoperable platform where different blockchains can communicate and share information, essentially creating a global supercomputer.&#8221;</em></p>



<p>Several crucial aspects could help Polkadot take over the market. To begin with, its distinctive architecture enables the effortless movement of any data or asset across several blockchains.</p>



<p>Polkadot emphasizes the underlying resources needed to communicate and interact between chains rather than concentrating simply on chains. Polkadot is a platform for developers to create applications for people, not simply a platform for hosting chains, according to Wood.</p>



<p>And then, of course, the resilience of Polkadot is a key feature. Even though the word &#8220;unstoppable&#8221; has been used to characterize blockchain networks, Wood thinks the word &#8220;resilience&#8221; is more accurate and better describes Polkadot&#8217;s capacity to withstand attempts to interfere with how it is supposed to work. Polkadot ensures the network&#8217;s integrity by offering resilience against the corruption of purpose.</p>



<p>In a broader sense, Polkadot functions as a provider of highly resilient general-purpose computation. Wood compares it to a modern multicore computer, where each core runs separately and simultaneously. These cores, referred to as parachains, operate on Polkadot constantly. He revealed plans to go from a roughly 50-core CPU to 500 or even 1000 cores, giving the network more computational power.  </p>



<p>Polkadot&#8217;s cores have characteristics in common with central processing units (CPUs), including bandwidth, compute power and latency. The quantity of data processed per second, or bandwidth, is now believed to be around 1 MB. The Geekbench 5 benchmark rates a core&#8217;s processing power at about 380. Additionally, there is a 6-second lag between each subsequent chunk of work.</p>



<p>Polkadot&#8217;s promise, meanwhile, goes beyond holding parachains in place. Wood considers the feasibility of directly executing smart contracts on Polkadot cores. Although this implementation is not immediately available, it highlights how flexible and all-encompassing Polkadot&#8217;s computational capabilities are. Developers may run complex logic and keep a lot of state by utilizing Polkadot&#8217;s cores&#8217; power and bandwidth, outperforming the limitations of conventional smart contract platforms.</p>



<p>Furthermore, Polkadot uses a relay chain and parachains structure to guarantee excellent scalability and security. Parallel processing and higher transaction throughput are made possible via parachains, which are separate chains that link to the primary relay chain. Thanks to this design, Polkadot can manage many transactions at once, making it appropriate for enterprise-level applications.</p>



<p>Additionally, the governance structure of Polkadot is intended to be open and democratic. It makes the platform fair and inclusive by enabling token holders to participate in decision-making. This decentralized governance strategy complies with blockchain technology&#8217;s guiding principles and offers a robust and secure framework for developing the Internet.</p>



<p>Dr Gavin Wood has further cemented Polkadot&#8217;s reputation as a pioneer in the blockchain sector by revealing the platform&#8217;s concept for a global supercomputer. The blockchain ecosystem is a strong candidate for the future of decentralized apps and services due to its distinctive architecture, scalability, and democratic governance approach. Polkadot&#8217;s concept has the potential to transform the internet as we know it and bring in a new era of frictionless communication and cooperation across blockchains and networks as the world progresses toward a more connected future.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/global-super-computer-vision-for-polkadot-revealed-by-co-founder-gavin-wood/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Shrimps and Crabs Accumulate BTC Aggressively Amid Heightened Institutional Interest</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/bitcoin-shrimps-and-crabs-accumulate-btc-aggressively-amid-heightened-institutional-interest/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/bitcoin-shrimps-and-crabs-accumulate-btc-aggressively-amid-heightened-institutional-interest/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Newton Gitonga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 19:12:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XBTUSD]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=82711</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-Shrimps-and-Crabs-Accumulate-BTC-Aggressively-Amid-Heightened-Institutional-Interest.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Bitcoin Shrimps and Crabs Accumulate BTC Aggressively Amid Heightened Institutional Interest" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-Shrimps-and-Crabs-Accumulate-BTC-Aggressively-Amid-Heightened-Institutional-Interest.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-Shrimps-and-Crabs-Accumulate-BTC-Aggressively-Amid-Heightened-Institutional-Interest-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-Shrimps-and-Crabs-Accumulate-BTC-Aggressively-Amid-Heightened-Institutional-Interest-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-Shrimps-and-Crabs-Accumulate-BTC-Aggressively-Amid-Heightened-Institutional-Interest-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>Bitcoin has continued to show impressive strength, recovering roughly 100% year to date. In the past week alone, the...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-Shrimps-and-Crabs-Accumulate-BTC-Aggressively-Amid-Heightened-Institutional-Interest.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Bitcoin Shrimps and Crabs Accumulate BTC Aggressively Amid Heightened Institutional Interest" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-Shrimps-and-Crabs-Accumulate-BTC-Aggressively-Amid-Heightened-Institutional-Interest.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-Shrimps-and-Crabs-Accumulate-BTC-Aggressively-Amid-Heightened-Institutional-Interest-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-Shrimps-and-Crabs-Accumulate-BTC-Aggressively-Amid-Heightened-Institutional-Interest-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-Shrimps-and-Crabs-Accumulate-BTC-Aggressively-Amid-Heightened-Institutional-Interest-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>Bitcoin has continued to show impressive strength, recovering roughly 100% year to date. In the past week alone, the leading cryptocurrency by market capitalization has grown by over 17%, perching above $30,000.</p>



<p>This growth comes from improving metrics, particularly from small-scale investors who have been demonstrating remarkable conviction and commitment by steadily growing their holdings, even in the face of the cryptocurrency market&#8217;s volatility and regulatory challenges.</p>



<p>On Wednesday, Glassnode&#8217;s lead analyst, &#8220;Checkmate&#8221;, sheds light on the significant impact these smaller investors are making in the market. In a tweet, the pundit highlighted <a href="https://zycrypto.com/bitcoin-shrimps-and-crabs-increase-holdings-by-almost-1-million-btc-amid-price-drop/">Bitcoin shrimps</a>, or addresses holding less than 1BTC, noting that they have been stacking sats at an impressive rate of 33.8k BTC monthly. According to the pundit&#8217;s analysis, for every new coin entering the market, shrimps are acquiring 1.25 BTC, effectively reducing the available supply.</p>



<p><em>&#8220;The last time the little guy stacked this hard was 2017 ATH, buying the top. Five years later, they are stacking harder, faster, and in a more sustained manner, despite all the bullshit. Bullish,&#8221;</em> the pundit wrote, attributing the purchases to the <em>&#8220;success of Bitcoin education visualized via on-chain data.&#8221;</em></p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img decoding="async" src="https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/19zmIYhFMmTJCDF35qpMvVXxns1ZujOvsI-EdJPxe6u5oafBLjLxx_dFhX0gClFQEsllWUvVZEFpApOFvufz8P_M9O3fCo0a8VZ1hd3m8y9c-08S24QQ7XYDJed52WgbiNVD-YRuUOTdbEx6YBmYMg" alt=""/></figure>



<p>On the other hand, Checkmate highlighted the so-called &#8220;Bitcoin crabs&#8221;, or investors who hold between 1 and 10 BTC. According to the pundit, this cohort has also aggressively accumulated coins, with a monthly rate of 22,400 BTC.</p>



<p>Remarkably, this accumulation represents an additional 83% of the mined supply, further emphasizing their growing influence in the market. The commitment these entities show, considering their higher investment range, highlights their belief in the long-term value of Bitcoin.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img decoding="async" src="https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/G0GFfcuiXhlz5XbsBwWFdb6E5Jx7P2RfjdvnHWrgwDZpSMbJudf86d8IOVqKFeFKfV_RI5WZV9nkvD7KskBwWtFNIwPheJhXwLfMs_KRDKYnvZIB7zoDNKSSxLg3zNIpieDJBAb4cx3jKUdbgRneDg" alt=""/></figure>



<p>Notably, while Bitcoin shrimps and crabs persist in accumulating coins, a striking contrast can be observed with the behaviour of Bitcoin whales (entities holding 1000-5000 BTC) and humpbacks (entities holding over 5000 BTC), who have been distributing their coins over the past eight years or so.</p>



<p>That said, the increased <a href="https://zycrypto.com/blackrock-highly-optimistic-on-spot-bitcoin-etf-approval-as-ceo-larry-fink-terms-bitcoin-an-international-asset/">institutional interest</a> in Bitcoin has significantly motivated shrimps and crabs to accumulate coins aggressively. The recognition and adoption of Bitcoin by mainstream institutions such as Fidelity and Blackrock, as well as major banks, have sparked confidence among smaller investors, who see the potential for substantial returns and a hedge against traditional financial risks.</p>



<p>At press time, Bitcoin was trading at $30,276 after surging just over 2% in the past 24 hours. </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/bitcoin-shrimps-and-crabs-accumulate-btc-aggressively-amid-heightened-institutional-interest/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Shiba Inu &#8216;Monster Move&#8217; Draws Near Amid Imminent Launch Of Shibarium In August</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/shiba-inu-monster-move-draws-near-amid-imminent-launch-of-shibarium-in-august/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/shiba-inu-monster-move-draws-near-amid-imminent-launch-of-shibarium-in-august/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Newton Gitonga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 13:58:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIBA INU]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIBUSD]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=82708</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Massive-Shiba-Inu-Whale-Moves-182-Billion-Coins-to-Gemini-—-What-Could-Go-Wrong-for-SHIB.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Massive Shiba Inu Whale Moves 182 Billion Coins to Exchanges — What Could Go Wrong for SHIB?" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Massive-Shiba-Inu-Whale-Moves-182-Billion-Coins-to-Gemini-—-What-Could-Go-Wrong-for-SHIB.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Massive-Shiba-Inu-Whale-Moves-182-Billion-Coins-to-Gemini-—-What-Could-Go-Wrong-for-SHIB-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Massive-Shiba-Inu-Whale-Moves-182-Billion-Coins-to-Gemini-—-What-Could-Go-Wrong-for-SHIB-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Massive-Shiba-Inu-Whale-Moves-182-Billion-Coins-to-Gemini-—-What-Could-Go-Wrong-for-SHIB-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>Lead dev reveals an ambitious vision to create a more decentralized and long-lasting community for SHIB.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Massive-Shiba-Inu-Whale-Moves-182-Billion-Coins-to-Gemini-—-What-Could-Go-Wrong-for-SHIB.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Massive Shiba Inu Whale Moves 182 Billion Coins to Exchanges — What Could Go Wrong for SHIB?" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Massive-Shiba-Inu-Whale-Moves-182-Billion-Coins-to-Gemini-—-What-Could-Go-Wrong-for-SHIB.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Massive-Shiba-Inu-Whale-Moves-182-Billion-Coins-to-Gemini-—-What-Could-Go-Wrong-for-SHIB-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Massive-Shiba-Inu-Whale-Moves-182-Billion-Coins-to-Gemini-—-What-Could-Go-Wrong-for-SHIB-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Massive-Shiba-Inu-Whale-Moves-182-Billion-Coins-to-Gemini-—-What-Could-Go-Wrong-for-SHIB-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>Shytoshi Kusama, the anonymous lead developer for Shiba Inu, has revealed an ambitious vision to create a more decentralized and long-lasting community for SHIB.</p>



<p>In a Thursday blog titled &#8220;Long Live Shivainu!,&#8221; Kusama shared insights into the project&#8217;s progress and outlined the path ahead. Kusama started by acknowledging the initial question that sparked this endeavour, <em>&#8220;Is it possible to build a leaderless, 100% decentralized, autonomous, persistent community?&#8221;</em></p>



<p>While many projects have attempted similar goals, Kusama emphasized that <a href="https://zycrypto.com/shiba-inu-unlocks-remarkable-price-trajectory-amid-exciting-ecosystem-updates-for-shibarium/">Shiba Inu</a> has surpassed expectations and become one of the most successful projects. However, the pundit stressed the importance of achieving true permanence, going beyond mere decentralization, and ensuring a robust foundation for the community. To fulfil the original vision of Shib&#8217;s founder, Ryoshi, Kusama proposed an update that adds intent and expands on the concept of a decentralized and enduring community.</p>



<p>In his view, establishing a Decentralized Autonomous Organization (DAO) is fundamental to realising this vision. A DAO is a blockchain-based organization that operates without a central authority. Kusama proposed wrapping the existing &#8220;Shiba Doggy DAO&#8221; with the Cayman Foundation in the blog.</p>



<p>With the emergence of DAOs in the past three or so years, the need for a legal framework that protects members, safeguards funds, and enables governance has led to the establishment of the so-called DAO legal wrapper. As a result, some jurisdictions, like the Cayman Islands, Singapore, Switzerland and Panama, have emerged as some of the most popular for DAO incorporation due to their progressive pro-crypto laws.</p>



<p>According to Kusama, this move aims to ensure that the DAO&#8217;s decisions are executed by the foundation, guaranteeing the proper management of DAO assets.</p>



<p>Furthermore, Kusama introduced the Doggy DAO(s) concept, which will govern different aspects of the Shiba Inu ecosystem. He revealed that the governance would be divided into four segments, with each core token in the system having its respective governance responsibility. This division ensures equal representation and supports the long-term sustainability of the community.</p>



<p>In other exciting news, the pundit announced Shib&#8217;s sponsorship of the Blockchain Futurist Conference, Eth Toronto, and Eth Women, scheduled to take place in Toronto in August. The event will serve as a platform to showcase completed projects, including the highly anticipated <a href="https://zycrypto.com/0-001-shib-price-looks-nigh-as-shiba-inus-testnet-sees-rising-activity-ahead-of-shibarium-mainnet/">Shibarium network</a>.</p>



<p><em>&#8220;At this location, the completed World paper will be exhibited, all Shib branded projects will be published, and Treat will be published in detail for the first time.&nbsp;In addition, it is very likely that we will also discuss and release the L2 Shibarium that we have been waiting for</em>,&#8221; wrote Kusama.</p>



<p>That said, following Kusama&#8217;s reveal, it will be interesting to see how SHIB&#8217;s vision for a decentralized community proceeds to fruition even as the ecosystem enters an exciting implementation phase, showcasing its unwavering commitment to revolutionize the cryptocurrency landscape.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/shiba-inu-monster-move-draws-near-amid-imminent-launch-of-shibarium-in-august/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Brighter Times Lie Ahead For XRP As Bank Of America Heaps Praises On Ripple’s Cross-Border Payments</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/brighter-times-lie-ahead-for-xrp-as-bank-of-america-heaps-praises-on-ripples-cross-border-payments/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/brighter-times-lie-ahead-for-xrp-as-bank-of-america-heaps-praises-on-ripples-cross-border-payments/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Brenda Ngari]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 21:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=82695</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ripple-Buys-Shares-In-European-Crypto-Exchange-Bitstamp-Massive-XRP-Growth-Ahead.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Ripple Buys Shares In European Crypto Exchange Bitstamp: Massive XRP Growth Ahead?" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ripple-Buys-Shares-In-European-Crypto-Exchange-Bitstamp-Massive-XRP-Growth-Ahead.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ripple-Buys-Shares-In-European-Crypto-Exchange-Bitstamp-Massive-XRP-Growth-Ahead-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ripple-Buys-Shares-In-European-Crypto-Exchange-Bitstamp-Massive-XRP-Growth-Ahead-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ripple-Buys-Shares-In-European-Crypto-Exchange-Bitstamp-Massive-XRP-Growth-Ahead-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>In a recent report by Bank of America, the role of Ripple in the payments industry, especially in the Asia-Pacific (APAC) region, has been hailed by the second-largest bank in the United States.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ripple-Buys-Shares-In-European-Crypto-Exchange-Bitstamp-Massive-XRP-Growth-Ahead.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Ripple Buys Shares In European Crypto Exchange Bitstamp: Massive XRP Growth Ahead?" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ripple-Buys-Shares-In-European-Crypto-Exchange-Bitstamp-Massive-XRP-Growth-Ahead.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ripple-Buys-Shares-In-European-Crypto-Exchange-Bitstamp-Massive-XRP-Growth-Ahead-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ripple-Buys-Shares-In-European-Crypto-Exchange-Bitstamp-Massive-XRP-Growth-Ahead-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ripple-Buys-Shares-In-European-Crypto-Exchange-Bitstamp-Massive-XRP-Growth-Ahead-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>In a recent report by Bank of America, the role of Ripple in the payments industry, especially in the Asia-Pacific (APAC) region, has been hailed by the second-largest bank in the United States. A team of analysts from the bank is unabashedly bullish on the company’s tech.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-bank-of-america-endorses-ripple-as-a-possible-exception"><strong>Bank Of America Endorses Ripple As A “Possible Exception”</strong></h2>



<p>In a recent <a href="https://business.bofa.com/content/dam/flagship/global-transaction-services/treasury-innovations-outlook/payments-innovation-in-apac.pdf">report </a>by Bank of America entitled “Breaking New Ground: Harnessing Payments Innovation in APAC”, the bank highlighted the role of blockchain in digitizing trade documents and the potential of Ripple’s frictionless remittance solutions to transform cross-border payments.</p>



<p>Bank of America acknowledges the evolutionary power of technology in enabling real-time payments. According to the bank’s report, APIs are the primary catalysts for the adoption of real-time payments, and they have revolutionized both customer connectivity and transaction processing. </p>



<p>“Banks can save money by utilizing Ripple’s technology, which is one of the reasons cross-border payments through Ripple have become so well-known. By eliminating middlemen and utilizing blockchain technology, Ripple lowers the transaction costs associated with international payments,” said Bank of America.</p>



<p>The bank dubbed Ripple’s work in the cross-border payments space as a “possible exception”, adding that banking institutions can boost the value and competitiveness of their products by passing down the cost-saving benefits to their customers. Moreover, in a highly competitive market, the decrease in operational costs also improves banks&#8217; overall financial health and profitability.</p>



<p>The Head of Treasury Products APAC at Bank of America, Es Venkat, posited: “We’re already seeing Open Banking become a reality in EMEA, with the API mechanism being used to develop many new use cases.”</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Did XRP’s Future Just Get A Lot Brighter?</strong></h2>



<p>Ripple Labs has, in the past <a href="https://zycrypto.com/xrp-sees-ultra-bullish-use-cases-after-colombias-central-bank-taps-ripple-to-pilot-cbdc/">inked deals </a>with a myriad of financial services providers across the globe. While the recognition by the Bank of America is a big deal, it’s important to note that the majority of financial giants are still not using Ripple’s tech as they are deterred by the company’s legal troubles in the United States. </p>



<p>The San Francisco-based blockchain payments firm has been <a href="https://zycrypto.com/xrp-holders-are-completely-fcked-messari-founder-predicts-drop-to-0-10-as-the-sec-sues-ripple/">locked in a courtroom war </a>with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission since 2020 over the allegation it broke federal securities laws by selling the XRP cryptocurrency to retail consumers.&nbsp;</p>



<p>If Ripple’s tech achieves widespread adoption after it&#8217;s incorporated into the existing traditional financial infrastructure, it will result in tremendous changes to the global payments ecosystem.  </p>



<p>As for the XRP price, the bears have held off any attempts by the bulls to drive the price of crypto higher despite <a href="https://zycrypto.com/ripple-lawsuit-sec-has-a-3-chance-of-winning-says-lawyer-predicts-xrp-victory-surge-to-10-price/">increasing hopes of a favorable outcome for Ripple</a> in its ongoing SEC lawsuit. The sixth-largest cryptocurrency by market cap was trading around $0.4674 at publication time, plummeting 0.9% over the last day, per CoinGecko. Whether XRP will embark on a new journey north soon remains anyone&#8217;s guess.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/brighter-times-lie-ahead-for-xrp-as-bank-of-america-heaps-praises-on-ripples-cross-border-payments/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How AI Can Propel Bitcoin’s Price To $760,000, Former BitMEX CEO Arthur Hayes Explains</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/how-ai-can-propel-bitcoins-price-to-760000-former-bitmex-ceo-arthur-hayes-explains/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/how-ai-can-propel-bitcoins-price-to-760000-former-bitmex-ceo-arthur-hayes-explains/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Brenda Ngari]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 20:36:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XBTUSD]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=82690</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/07/Bitcoin-Price-Shrugs-Off-Escalating-Regulatory-Attention-To-Revisit-40000-For-Second-Time-In-Two-Days.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Bitcoin Price Shrugs Off Escalating Regulatory Attention To Revisit $40,000 For Second Time In Two Days" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/07/Bitcoin-Price-Shrugs-Off-Escalating-Regulatory-Attention-To-Revisit-40000-For-Second-Time-In-Two-Days.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/07/Bitcoin-Price-Shrugs-Off-Escalating-Regulatory-Attention-To-Revisit-40000-For-Second-Time-In-Two-Days-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/07/Bitcoin-Price-Shrugs-Off-Escalating-Regulatory-Attention-To-Revisit-40000-For-Second-Time-In-Two-Days-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/07/Bitcoin-Price-Shrugs-Off-Escalating-Regulatory-Attention-To-Revisit-40000-For-Second-Time-In-Two-Days-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>Former BitMEX CEO Arthur Hayes thinks that Bitcoin will become the native currency of AI-powered economies and hit over $750,000 in the process.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/07/Bitcoin-Price-Shrugs-Off-Escalating-Regulatory-Attention-To-Revisit-40000-For-Second-Time-In-Two-Days.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Bitcoin Price Shrugs Off Escalating Regulatory Attention To Revisit $40,000 For Second Time In Two Days" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/07/Bitcoin-Price-Shrugs-Off-Escalating-Regulatory-Attention-To-Revisit-40000-For-Second-Time-In-Two-Days.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/07/Bitcoin-Price-Shrugs-Off-Escalating-Regulatory-Attention-To-Revisit-40000-For-Second-Time-In-Two-Days-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/07/Bitcoin-Price-Shrugs-Off-Escalating-Regulatory-Attention-To-Revisit-40000-For-Second-Time-In-Two-Days-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/07/Bitcoin-Price-Shrugs-Off-Escalating-Regulatory-Attention-To-Revisit-40000-For-Second-Time-In-Two-Days-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>Former BitMEX CEO Arthur Hayes thinks that <a href="https://zycrypto.com/blackrocks-renewed-bitcoin-etf-application-featuring-coinbase-raises-questions-on-secs-scrutiny/">Bitcoin</a> will become the native currency of AI-powered economies and hit over $750,000 in the process. Hayes’s rationale is hinged on the benchmark cryptocurrency’s inherent attributes that could make it interoperable with the fast-growing realm of artificial intelligence.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-hayes-calls-btc-the-logical-currency-choice-for-ai"><strong>Hayes Calls BTC The “Logical Currency Choice For AI”</strong></h2>



<p>In his latest intriguing piece titled “Massa”, Arthur Hayes has delved into the potential integration of Bitcoin and artificial intelligence (AI).</p>



<p>According to the Thursday <a href="https://cryptohayes.substack.com/p/massa">blog post</a>, the well-known crypto trader suggested that Bitcoin will ascend as the dominant currency for AI. He argued that the premier crypto’s attributes as a purely digital, censorship-resistant, and digitally scarce currency make it the most fitting choice for AIs.</p>



<p>“Bitcoin is thus the logical currency choice for any AI. It is purely digital, censorship-resistant, provably scarce, and its intrinsic value is completely electricity-cost-dependent. There is nothing in existence today that comes close to challenging Bitcoin on these aspects.”</p>



<p>Hayes added that compared to fiat currencies and gold, which don’t have irrefutable value or quantifiability, Bitcoin&#8217;s immutable supply is programmatically capped at 21 million coins, making it a logical choice for any AI looking for a currency that’s reliable and enshrined with “clear and transparent” rules from the outset.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Bitcoin’s Road To A $760,000 Price Tag</strong></h2>



<p>Where would a possible convergence between Bitcoin and AI leave the top cryptocurrency?</p>



<p>Hayes predicted that Bitcoin could reach a staggering $760,000 per coin on the back of an AI boost.</p>



<p>“If Bitcoin is seen as likely to be — or even starts to be — used by AIs, then we could see two separate manias combine into one mega mania: the mania of wanting to escape inflation within the fiat financial system and the mania of wanting to own a piece of the next phase of human and computer evolution,” Hayes stated. “The overlap of these two manias would likely drive investors to grossly overpay for growth, causing the value of the Bitcoin network to rise to silly levels.”</p>



<p>Arthur Hayes is no stranger to sky-high price forecasts. In April 2022, the industry stalwart explained how Western financial policy&#8217;s “doom loop” would spark <a href="https://zycrypto.com/cathie-wood-sticks-with-1-million-bitcoin-prediction-amid-maelstrom-of-regulatory-crackdowns-heres-why/">Bitcoin’s run to $1 million</a> by 2030.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/how-ai-can-propel-bitcoins-price-to-760000-former-bitmex-ceo-arthur-hayes-explains/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin’s Correlation with Traditional Markets and Gold Diminishes: Here’s Why</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/bitcoins-correlation-with-traditional-markets-and-gold-diminishes-heres-why/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/bitcoins-correlation-with-traditional-markets-and-gold-diminishes-heres-why/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Erie Maxwell]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 20:02:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=82683</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/04/Bitcoin-On-Track-To-Outpace-Golds-Market-Value-Mike-Novogratz-Says.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Bitcoin On Track To Outpace Gold’s Market Value, Mike Novogratz Says" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/04/Bitcoin-On-Track-To-Outpace-Golds-Market-Value-Mike-Novogratz-Says.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/04/Bitcoin-On-Track-To-Outpace-Golds-Market-Value-Mike-Novogratz-Says-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/04/Bitcoin-On-Track-To-Outpace-Golds-Market-Value-Mike-Novogratz-Says-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/04/Bitcoin-On-Track-To-Outpace-Golds-Market-Value-Mike-Novogratz-Says-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>The correlation between Bitcoin (BTC) and gold, as well as the traditional market continues to be a burning issue. According to IntoTheBlock, a shift is being witnessed because the connection between BTC and the traditional market continues to decline.&#160; The market insight provider stated, “Bitcoin Correlation Shift: A month ago, BTC demonstrated an inverse correlation [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/04/Bitcoin-On-Track-To-Outpace-Golds-Market-Value-Mike-Novogratz-Says.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Bitcoin On Track To Outpace Gold’s Market Value, Mike Novogratz Says" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/04/Bitcoin-On-Track-To-Outpace-Golds-Market-Value-Mike-Novogratz-Says.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/04/Bitcoin-On-Track-To-Outpace-Golds-Market-Value-Mike-Novogratz-Says-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/04/Bitcoin-On-Track-To-Outpace-Golds-Market-Value-Mike-Novogratz-Says-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/04/Bitcoin-On-Track-To-Outpace-Golds-Market-Value-Mike-Novogratz-Says-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>The correlation between Bitcoin (BTC) and gold, as well as the traditional market continues to be a burning issue.</p>



<p>According to IntoTheBlock, a shift is being witnessed because the connection between BTC and the traditional market continues to decline.&nbsp;</p>



<p>The market insight provider <a href="https://twitter.com/intotheblock/status/1673595342695301122">stated</a>, <em>“Bitcoin Correlation Shift: A month ago, BTC demonstrated an inverse correlation with the stock market and a minor positive link with Gold. Fast forward to today, it’s intriguing to see BTC showing no connection with traditional markets &amp; a negative correlation with gold.”</em></p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img decoding="async" src="https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/hsmF61qZWMMStBjhqfAj-8AKb0-4FQMM9OOGlZqZcOAmw7wSeH_HGXdZBmNSVbLatVaipt70hhrNkGo2sT4bt5hxw0q6dvku7o12BdOvkKsSWJNz83m0YWn5x_gOTE9SMC6kMRmmyZw4qaE5uoJfyQ8" alt=""/><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"><em>Source:IntoTheBlock</em></figcaption></figure>



<p>Glassnode, a leading on-chain metrics provider, shared similar sentiments and acknowledged that Bitcoin’s price action was decoupling from both gold and silver. This was because its 30-day correlation with gold stood at lows of -0.78, whereas that of silver hit -0.9.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img decoding="async" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/373Q-adF5AiT9sqeTaF2CTgTIBK1PbrDC1c26yUbd12e6GwxMcx6L6HlpncLefw6GbtZieYgtI5IiV6H8KLFVeen12TckCGJxndcdLJ9uPfaNxWMabAuOfKT3TCaPnJfoSFR2KstVeJ2LBzr38Z6vi8" alt=""/><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"><em>Source: Glassnode</em></figcaption></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-what-does-the-declining-correlation-mean"><strong>What Does the Declining Correlation Mean?</strong></h2>



<p>The decoupling of BTC from the stock and traditional market, as well as its negative connection with gold is a welcome move because the leading cryptocurrency is showcasing itself as a different asset class. This might be the case as more big players continue penetrating the Bitcoin market.</p>



<p>Notably, correlation illustrates the tendency of two items to move in a similar or opposite direction after a given period of time.</p>



<p>The comparison between gold and BTC has gained steam over the years, especially when it comes to the issue of being a hedge against inflation or store of value. Bitcoin’s status as an alternative to gold continues to be tested based on its decentralized nature and finite supply.</p>



<p>Previously, Bitcoin showed a strong correlation with the stock market. This was because whenever the stock market experienced a sharp sell-off, BTC followed suit, especially during periods of economic uncertainty, as showcased during the peak of the pandemic in 2020.&nbsp;</p>



<p>Meanwhile, a research report by Bernstein <a href="https://zycrypto.com/bitcoin-pierces-30000-for-first-time-since-june-as-bernstein-calls-btc-faster-horse-compared-to-gold/">acknowledged</a> that BTC was a ‘faster horse’ than gold. This was after the top cryptocurrency breached the psychological price of $30K for the first time in April since June 2022.&nbsp;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/bitcoins-correlation-with-traditional-markets-and-gold-diminishes-heres-why/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>88% Of Institutional Investors Bullish on Crypto&#8217;s Next Decade, Binance Survey</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/88-of-institutional-investors-bullish-on-cryptos-next-decade-binance-survey/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/88-of-institutional-investors-bullish-on-cryptos-next-decade-binance-survey/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Newton Gitonga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 19:44:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=82681</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/BTC-Primed-For-Trillion-Dollar-Boost-As-BlackRock-Offers-Direct-Bitcoin-Exposure-To-Institutional-Investors.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="BTC Primed For Trillion-Dollar Boost As BlackRock Offers Direct Bitcoin Exposure To Institutional Investors" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/BTC-Primed-For-Trillion-Dollar-Boost-As-BlackRock-Offers-Direct-Bitcoin-Exposure-To-Institutional-Investors.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/BTC-Primed-For-Trillion-Dollar-Boost-As-BlackRock-Offers-Direct-Bitcoin-Exposure-To-Institutional-Investors-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/BTC-Primed-For-Trillion-Dollar-Boost-As-BlackRock-Offers-Direct-Bitcoin-Exposure-To-Institutional-Investors-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/BTC-Primed-For-Trillion-Dollar-Boost-As-BlackRock-Offers-Direct-Bitcoin-Exposure-To-Institutional-Investors-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>According to a recent survey conducted by Binance, a staggering 88% of institutional investors have expressed a bullish outlook for the next decade in the world of cryptocurrency. The &#8220;Institutional Crypto Outlook Survey&#8221; survey collected responses from 208 Binance institutional clients and VIP users from March 31 to May 15, 2023, providing valuable insights into [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/BTC-Primed-For-Trillion-Dollar-Boost-As-BlackRock-Offers-Direct-Bitcoin-Exposure-To-Institutional-Investors.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="BTC Primed For Trillion-Dollar Boost As BlackRock Offers Direct Bitcoin Exposure To Institutional Investors" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/BTC-Primed-For-Trillion-Dollar-Boost-As-BlackRock-Offers-Direct-Bitcoin-Exposure-To-Institutional-Investors.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/BTC-Primed-For-Trillion-Dollar-Boost-As-BlackRock-Offers-Direct-Bitcoin-Exposure-To-Institutional-Investors-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/BTC-Primed-For-Trillion-Dollar-Boost-As-BlackRock-Offers-Direct-Bitcoin-Exposure-To-Institutional-Investors-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/BTC-Primed-For-Trillion-Dollar-Boost-As-BlackRock-Offers-Direct-Bitcoin-Exposure-To-Institutional-Investors-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>According to a recent survey conducted by Binance, a staggering 88% of institutional investors have expressed a bullish outlook for the next decade in the world of cryptocurrency.</p>



<p>The &#8220;Institutional Crypto Outlook Survey&#8221; survey collected responses from 208 Binance institutional clients and VIP users from March 31 to May 15, 2023, providing valuable insights into their attitudes, preferences, adoption, and motivations regarding cryptocurrency investments.</p>



<p>One of the most notable findings is that 63.5% of the respondents expressed a positive outlook for crypto in the next 12 months. However, when looking ahead to the next decade, an overwhelming majority of 88% indicated their positive sentiment, indicating a strong belief in the long-term potential of cryptocurrency.</p>



<p>The survey highlights that 47.1% of institutional investors maintained their crypto allocation over the past year, while 35.6% increased their allocation during the same period. The report noted that 50% of respondents expect to increase their allocation to crypto further, demonstrating a growing confidence in the asset class. Interestingly, only 4.3% of respondents anticipate reducing their crypto allocation in the next 12 months.</p>



<p>Regarding areas of interest, the survey also revealed that institutional investors are particularly focused on infrastructure, with 53.9% of respondents considering it the most important sector for them or their funds.</p>



<p><em>&#8220;Infrastructure, L1 and L2 are areas of focus among institutional investors. 53.9% of investors found infrastructure to be the sector of most importance to them or their funds. This was closely followed by L1 and L2 sectors at 48.1% and 43.8%, respectively. In terms of usage, DeFi dApps were the most widely used in recent months,&#8221;</em> the survey <a href="https://research.binance.com/static/pdf/institutional-crypto-outlook-survey-2023.pdf">report</a> noted.</p>



<p>Notably, regulatory risk emerged as the primary concern for institutional investors, followed by counterparty and custody risks for institutional investors. Interestingly, price volatility did not deter the group, with most expressing high comfort levels with cryptocurrency volatility.</p>



<p>However, the survey highlighted that institutional investors believe increased real-world use cases and regulatory clarity will drive cryptocurrency adoption. As the industry matures, these investors foresee a growing acceptance of cryptocurrencies in mainstream applications and a more supportive regulatory environment.</p>



<p>The survey comes on the heels of heightened scrutiny over the crypto market, with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) recently filing <a href="https://zycrypto.com/this-is-an-opportunity-to-get-rule-clarity-in-court-coinbase-stresses-on-the-positive-amid-sec-lawsuit/">lawsuits</a> against Binance and Coinbase in its crypto enforcement barrage. However, institutions have remained undeterred, as demonstrated by the numerous Spot Bitcoin ETF filings by prominent firms such as WisdomTree, BlackRock, VanEck, and Fidelity.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/88-of-institutional-investors-bullish-on-cryptos-next-decade-binance-survey/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Glassnode Co-Founder Optimistic as Ethereum Reclaims Key Support, Setting Stage for Bullish Momentum</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/glassnode-co-founder-optimistic-as-ethereum-reclaims-key-support-setting-stage-for-bullish-momentum/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/glassnode-co-founder-optimistic-as-ethereum-reclaims-key-support-setting-stage-for-bullish-momentum/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Newton Gitonga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 19:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=82679</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Ethereums-Vitalik-Buterin-Claps-Back-At-PoS-Skeptics-Ahead-Of-The-Merge.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Ethereum’s Vitalik Buterin Claps Back At PoS Skeptics Ahead Of The Merge" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Ethereums-Vitalik-Buterin-Claps-Back-At-PoS-Skeptics-Ahead-Of-The-Merge.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Ethereums-Vitalik-Buterin-Claps-Back-At-PoS-Skeptics-Ahead-Of-The-Merge-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Ethereums-Vitalik-Buterin-Claps-Back-At-PoS-Skeptics-Ahead-Of-The-Merge-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Ethereums-Vitalik-Buterin-Claps-Back-At-PoS-Skeptics-Ahead-Of-The-Merge-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>Yann Allemann, co-founder of popular crypto on-chain analytics firm Glassnode has expressed optimism about Ethereum's future even as the cryptocurrency continues to display resilience in the face of regulatory challenges within the crypto market.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Ethereums-Vitalik-Buterin-Claps-Back-At-PoS-Skeptics-Ahead-Of-The-Merge.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Ethereum’s Vitalik Buterin Claps Back At PoS Skeptics Ahead Of The Merge" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Ethereums-Vitalik-Buterin-Claps-Back-At-PoS-Skeptics-Ahead-Of-The-Merge.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Ethereums-Vitalik-Buterin-Claps-Back-At-PoS-Skeptics-Ahead-Of-The-Merge-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Ethereums-Vitalik-Buterin-Claps-Back-At-PoS-Skeptics-Ahead-Of-The-Merge-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Ethereums-Vitalik-Buterin-Claps-Back-At-PoS-Skeptics-Ahead-Of-The-Merge-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>Yann Allemann, co-founder of popular crypto on-chain analytics firm Glassnode has expressed optimism about Ethereum&#8217;s future even as the cryptocurrency continues to display resilience in the face of regulatory challenges within the crypto market.</p>



<p>In a tweet on July 5, the pundit highlighted <a href="https://zycrypto.com/ethereums-buterin-voices-sympathy-for-solana-and-other-tokens-targeted-by-sec/">Ethereum&#8217;s</a> recent price action, noting by price reclaiming the key support level of $1,900 and surging to $1,950, the popular cryptocurrency is showing solid signs of bullish momentum.</p>



<p>Despite its impressive rebound in the first quarter, surging to over $2,150 in April, the second-largest cryptocurrency by market capitalization has encountered a period of consolidation, facing resistance as it strives to surpass previous price levels. Recently, the price briefly breached the $1,900 mark before retracing after a brief surge to $1,950.</p>



<p>Allemann also emphasized the notable revival of Ether&#8217;s Relative Strength Index (RSI) during its recent upward momentum, stating, <em>&#8220;Backed by an ascending trendline, ETH is positioned for continued expansion. Any potential pullbacks may encounter robust support at $1.8k and $1.65k. Exciting times lie ahead!&#8221;</em></p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img decoding="async" src="https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/AAAxvPk5KeBeyUmIhpEwu_lhTWKp0HQviv4fAtdOVZdGH_G9jI2H_YFflh7mqBBjQDGPqVjI3QrCmX_Zm8oFCGuIJjUL1uiUcDKgP4Tcm8rwqMM2flBkEn-sGc7DT5yig7SJEl-FIKicvp4X3A8aAQ" alt=""/></figure>



<p>While market volatility is always possible, Yann Allemann&#8217;s noted that potential retracements in Ethereum&#8217;s price could find more substantial support at $1.8k and $1.65k. However, he described this as an opportunity that provides investors with a potential buying opportunity.</p>



<p>In a <a href="https://twitter.com/NothinButGains/status/1676714555639218176">tweet</a>, cryptocurrency analyst and trader &#8220;Trader Karl&#8221; highlighted Ethereum&#8217;s price movement, highlighting the $1,910 level. According to the pundit, this resistance level holds significant importance for Ethereum in the short term. If the price manages to break through this level convincingly, it could pave the way for further upward movement, with the following notable resistance point being the April high of $2,100.</p>



<p>Twenty-five-year market veteran Jordan Lindsey shared his analysis on Ether on Wednesday, calling on investors to be cautious even as price trades inside a &#8220;massive contraction&#8221;.</p>



<p><em>&#8220;We are getting close to where we are going to have a resolution of that,</em>&#8221; he <a href="https://twitter.com/TradersMastery/status/1676643227540291584">said</a>, warning that price could break out of either side. He, however, shared his targets, stating that a break above $2,100 could push ETH to around $3,300. Conversely, a breach of the red trendline could trigger a downward move towards $1,140.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img decoding="async" src="https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/9nn-v2v5jPv5sG-1Z9Ri9rQvIYZJTGLZxl8kbMx5kIBPOq_tJt3FXJqRAhSJxvG6DSZOryUMXYeAsOhzIwo8fWsR2N65jqQT-1QnZS7CtoPZPrvacQXm0jWNwU-V1zl6yHvgoLapBDeYpkXX6tebcw" alt=""/></figure>



<p>That said, Ethereum&#8217;s performance is significant for its ecosystem and the broader cryptocurrency market. As one of the leading cryptocurrencies, Ethereum often sets the tone for other digital assets. Thus, a strong rally in Ethereum could potentially boost the overall market sentiment and encourage further investment in the cryptocurrency space.</p>



<p>At press time, ETH was trading at $1,858, down 0.17% in the past 24 hours, as per data from CoinMarketCap.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/glassnode-co-founder-optimistic-as-ethereum-reclaims-key-support-setting-stage-for-bullish-momentum/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>XRP Is Not A Security? Pro-Crypto Lawyer Hints At Huge Unraveling In Ripple vs SEC Case</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/xrp-is-not-a-security-pro-crypto-lawyer-hints-at-huge-unraveling-in-ripple-vs-sec-case/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/xrp-is-not-a-security-pro-crypto-lawyer-hints-at-huge-unraveling-in-ripple-vs-sec-case/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Newton Gitonga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 19:54:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=82668</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ripple-SEC-Suit-Did-XRP-Sales-Violate-Securities-Laws-Judge-Could-Declare-Verdict-As-Soon-As-June.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Ripple-SEC Suit: Did XRP Sales Violate Securities Laws? Judge Could Declare Verdict As Soon As June" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ripple-SEC-Suit-Did-XRP-Sales-Violate-Securities-Laws-Judge-Could-Declare-Verdict-As-Soon-As-June.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ripple-SEC-Suit-Did-XRP-Sales-Violate-Securities-Laws-Judge-Could-Declare-Verdict-As-Soon-As-June-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ripple-SEC-Suit-Did-XRP-Sales-Violate-Securities-Laws-Judge-Could-Declare-Verdict-As-Soon-As-June-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ripple-SEC-Suit-Did-XRP-Sales-Violate-Securities-Laws-Judge-Could-Declare-Verdict-As-Soon-As-June-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>Outspoken pro-Ripple lawyer John Deaton has expressed optimism regarding the SEC vs Ripple lawsuit predicting that Judge Torres will thoroughly address the core question of whether XRP is a security in her upcoming summary judgment.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ripple-SEC-Suit-Did-XRP-Sales-Violate-Securities-Laws-Judge-Could-Declare-Verdict-As-Soon-As-June.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Ripple-SEC Suit: Did XRP Sales Violate Securities Laws? Judge Could Declare Verdict As Soon As June" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ripple-SEC-Suit-Did-XRP-Sales-Violate-Securities-Laws-Judge-Could-Declare-Verdict-As-Soon-As-June.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ripple-SEC-Suit-Did-XRP-Sales-Violate-Securities-Laws-Judge-Could-Declare-Verdict-As-Soon-As-June-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ripple-SEC-Suit-Did-XRP-Sales-Violate-Securities-Laws-Judge-Could-Declare-Verdict-As-Soon-As-June-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ripple-SEC-Suit-Did-XRP-Sales-Violate-Securities-Laws-Judge-Could-Declare-Verdict-As-Soon-As-June-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>Outspoken pro-Ripple lawyer <a href="https://zycrypto.com/xrp-lawsuit-john-deaton-highlights-4-likely-outcomes-in-ripple-vs-sec-suit-as-case-takes-surprising-turn/">John Deaton</a> has expressed optimism regarding the SEC vs Ripple lawsuit, predicting that Judge Torres will thoroughly address the core question of whether XRP is a security in her upcoming summary judgment.</p>



<p>In a Twitter thread on Monday, Deaton firmly asserted that &#8220;XRP IS NOT A SECURITY.&#8221; He then established parallels between XRP and diverse assets like orange groves, whiskey, condos, and even Bitcoin (BTC). Deaton&#8217;s argument centred on the notion that despite these assets being marketed and sold as investment contracts, their inherent characteristics remained unaltered.</p>



<p><em>&#8220;BTC was once sold as an investment contract (SEC v. Shavers), but that particular sale didn&#8217;t transform BTC into anything other than what it is: a digital commodity,&#8221; </em>he stated.</p>



<p>Further, contrary to the belief of many experienced lawyers, Deaton asserted that Judge Torres would not shy away from addressing the issue of secondary sales concerning <a href="https://zycrypto.com/ripple-lawsuit-crypto-lawyer-sheds-light-on-imminent-judgment-in-sec-case-as-xrp-army-awaits-verdict/">XRP</a>.</p>



<p><em>&#8220;I believe Judge Torres has to address the underlying asset and secondary market sales. Could she avoid the issues and issue a ruling? Of course she could. But it would be a greater act of judicial activism to ignore the SEC&#8217;s theory and NOT address these issues,&#8221; </em>he said.</p>



<p>To support his argument, Deaton referred to a similar case handled by Judge Castel in 2020 involving the Telegram messaging app. This legal dispute began when the SEC intervened and halted Telegram&#8217;s intended distribution of GRAM tokens. However, Judge Castel ruled in favour of the SEC, stating that Telegram had to repay investors $1.2 billion from their unsuccessful initial coin offering (ICO) for the Telegram Open Network.&nbsp;</p>



<p>It is important to remember that the theory posited by the SEC was that Ripple engaged in continuous activity resembling an ICO, considering each sale of XRP as part of a broader plan involving securities. However, Deaton clarified that the situation with XRP differed from the Telegram case because the latter involved an ICO with written contracts.</p>



<p>Deaton further contended that XRP, powered by the XRP Ledger (XRPL) technology, had been operating effectively and openly traded for over seven years. Notably, <a href="https://zycrypto.com/john-deaton-debates-ripple-security-claims-as-holders-admit-lack-of-research-before-buying-xrp/">even SEC staff</a> members were permitted to own XRP until 2019, which was not the case with the Gram token.</p>



<p>The issue of secondary market transactions of XRP has been a crucial aspect in the SEC and Ripple legal battle. While the SEC accused Ripple of offering XRP as an unregistered security, it did not clearly distinguish between Ripple&#8217;s direct sales and the subsequent trading on the secondary market, leading to confusion. Recently, Deaton opined that Judge Torres might address this issue based on a previous examination in the SEC vs LBRY lawsuit, as it sheds more light on the issue.</p>



<p>That said, while there&#8217;s no guarantee, Judge Torres&#8217; summary judgment decision could shed light on XRP&#8217;s security classification, potentially impacting the crypto industry significantly.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/xrp-is-not-a-security-pro-crypto-lawyer-hints-at-huge-unraveling-in-ripple-vs-sec-case/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
