<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>News Archives &#8902; ZyCrypto</title>
	<atom:link href="https://zycrypto.com/category/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://zycrypto.com/category/news/</link>
	<description>ZyCrypto Is A Cryptocurrency News Media, Focusing On Daily News, Expert Opinions, Analysis, Reviews, And So Much More.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 21:38:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/cropped-ZyCrypto-Site-Logo-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News Archives &#8902; ZyCrypto</title>
	<link>https://zycrypto.com/category/news/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>XRP Is Not A Security? Pro-Crypto Lawyer Hints At Huge Unraveling In Ripple vs SEC Case</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/xrp-is-not-a-security-pro-crypto-lawyer-hints-at-huge-unraveling-in-ripple-vs-sec-case/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/xrp-is-not-a-security-pro-crypto-lawyer-hints-at-huge-unraveling-in-ripple-vs-sec-case/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Newton Gitonga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 19:54:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=82668</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ripple-SEC-Suit-Did-XRP-Sales-Violate-Securities-Laws-Judge-Could-Declare-Verdict-As-Soon-As-June.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Ripple-SEC Suit: Did XRP Sales Violate Securities Laws? Judge Could Declare Verdict As Soon As June" decoding="async" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ripple-SEC-Suit-Did-XRP-Sales-Violate-Securities-Laws-Judge-Could-Declare-Verdict-As-Soon-As-June.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ripple-SEC-Suit-Did-XRP-Sales-Violate-Securities-Laws-Judge-Could-Declare-Verdict-As-Soon-As-June-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ripple-SEC-Suit-Did-XRP-Sales-Violate-Securities-Laws-Judge-Could-Declare-Verdict-As-Soon-As-June-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ripple-SEC-Suit-Did-XRP-Sales-Violate-Securities-Laws-Judge-Could-Declare-Verdict-As-Soon-As-June-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>Outspoken pro-Ripple lawyer John Deaton has expressed optimism regarding the SEC vs Ripple lawsuit predicting that Judge Torres will thoroughly address the core question of whether XRP is a security in her upcoming summary judgment.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ripple-SEC-Suit-Did-XRP-Sales-Violate-Securities-Laws-Judge-Could-Declare-Verdict-As-Soon-As-June.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Ripple-SEC Suit: Did XRP Sales Violate Securities Laws? Judge Could Declare Verdict As Soon As June" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ripple-SEC-Suit-Did-XRP-Sales-Violate-Securities-Laws-Judge-Could-Declare-Verdict-As-Soon-As-June.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ripple-SEC-Suit-Did-XRP-Sales-Violate-Securities-Laws-Judge-Could-Declare-Verdict-As-Soon-As-June-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ripple-SEC-Suit-Did-XRP-Sales-Violate-Securities-Laws-Judge-Could-Declare-Verdict-As-Soon-As-June-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ripple-SEC-Suit-Did-XRP-Sales-Violate-Securities-Laws-Judge-Could-Declare-Verdict-As-Soon-As-June-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>Outspoken pro-Ripple lawyer <a href="https://zycrypto.com/xrp-lawsuit-john-deaton-highlights-4-likely-outcomes-in-ripple-vs-sec-suit-as-case-takes-surprising-turn/">John Deaton</a> has expressed optimism regarding the SEC vs Ripple lawsuit, predicting that Judge Torres will thoroughly address the core question of whether XRP is a security in her upcoming summary judgment.</p>



<p>In a Twitter thread on Monday, Deaton firmly asserted that &#8220;XRP IS NOT A SECURITY.&#8221; He then established parallels between XRP and diverse assets like orange groves, whiskey, condos, and even Bitcoin (BTC). Deaton&#8217;s argument centred on the notion that despite these assets being marketed and sold as investment contracts, their inherent characteristics remained unaltered.</p>



<p><em>&#8220;BTC was once sold as an investment contract (SEC v. Shavers), but that particular sale didn&#8217;t transform BTC into anything other than what it is: a digital commodity,&#8221; </em>he stated.</p>



<p>Further, contrary to the belief of many experienced lawyers, Deaton asserted that Judge Torres would not shy away from addressing the issue of secondary sales concerning <a href="https://zycrypto.com/ripple-lawsuit-crypto-lawyer-sheds-light-on-imminent-judgment-in-sec-case-as-xrp-army-awaits-verdict/">XRP</a>.</p>



<p><em>&#8220;I believe Judge Torres has to address the underlying asset and secondary market sales. Could she avoid the issues and issue a ruling? Of course she could. But it would be a greater act of judicial activism to ignore the SEC&#8217;s theory and NOT address these issues,&#8221; </em>he said.</p>



<p>To support his argument, Deaton referred to a similar case handled by Judge Castel in 2020 involving the Telegram messaging app. This legal dispute began when the SEC intervened and halted Telegram&#8217;s intended distribution of GRAM tokens. However, Judge Castel ruled in favour of the SEC, stating that Telegram had to repay investors $1.2 billion from their unsuccessful initial coin offering (ICO) for the Telegram Open Network.&nbsp;</p>



<p>It is important to remember that the theory posited by the SEC was that Ripple engaged in continuous activity resembling an ICO, considering each sale of XRP as part of a broader plan involving securities. However, Deaton clarified that the situation with XRP differed from the Telegram case because the latter involved an ICO with written contracts.</p>



<p>Deaton further contended that XRP, powered by the XRP Ledger (XRPL) technology, had been operating effectively and openly traded for over seven years. Notably, <a href="https://zycrypto.com/john-deaton-debates-ripple-security-claims-as-holders-admit-lack-of-research-before-buying-xrp/">even SEC staff</a> members were permitted to own XRP until 2019, which was not the case with the Gram token.</p>



<p>The issue of secondary market transactions of XRP has been a crucial aspect in the SEC and Ripple legal battle. While the SEC accused Ripple of offering XRP as an unregistered security, it did not clearly distinguish between Ripple&#8217;s direct sales and the subsequent trading on the secondary market, leading to confusion. Recently, Deaton opined that Judge Torres might address this issue based on a previous examination in the SEC vs LBRY lawsuit, as it sheds more light on the issue.</p>



<p>That said, while there&#8217;s no guarantee, Judge Torres&#8217; summary judgment decision could shed light on XRP&#8217;s security classification, potentially impacting the crypto industry significantly.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/xrp-is-not-a-security-pro-crypto-lawyer-hints-at-huge-unraveling-in-ripple-vs-sec-case/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>BlackRock&#8217;s Renewed Bitcoin ETF Application Featuring Coinbase Raises Questions on SEC&#8217;s Scrutiny</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/blackrocks-renewed-bitcoin-etf-application-featuring-coinbase-raises-questions-on-secs-scrutiny/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/blackrocks-renewed-bitcoin-etf-application-featuring-coinbase-raises-questions-on-secs-scrutiny/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Newton Gitonga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 19:33:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=82662</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/Mark-Cuban-Says-He-Wont-Invest-In-Bitcoin-Futures-ETFs.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Mark Cuban Says He Won&#039;t Invest In Bitcoin Futures ETFs" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/Mark-Cuban-Says-He-Wont-Invest-In-Bitcoin-Futures-ETFs.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/Mark-Cuban-Says-He-Wont-Invest-In-Bitcoin-Futures-ETFs-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/Mark-Cuban-Says-He-Wont-Invest-In-Bitcoin-Futures-ETFs-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/Mark-Cuban-Says-He-Wont-Invest-In-Bitcoin-Futures-ETFs-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>BlackRock, the World&#8217;s largest asset manager, has submitted a revised application for a Bitcoin-focused exchange-traded fund (ETF) to U.S. regulators through Nasdaq. The filing, which was done on June 29, named Coinbase Global Inc. as a partner, tasked with providing the so-called surveillance support for the proposed ETF due to its huge dollar-to-bitcoin trading volume [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/Mark-Cuban-Says-He-Wont-Invest-In-Bitcoin-Futures-ETFs.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Mark Cuban Says He Won&#039;t Invest In Bitcoin Futures ETFs" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/Mark-Cuban-Says-He-Wont-Invest-In-Bitcoin-Futures-ETFs.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/Mark-Cuban-Says-He-Wont-Invest-In-Bitcoin-Futures-ETFs-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/Mark-Cuban-Says-He-Wont-Invest-In-Bitcoin-Futures-ETFs-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/Mark-Cuban-Says-He-Wont-Invest-In-Bitcoin-Futures-ETFs-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>BlackRock, the World&#8217;s largest asset manager, has submitted a revised application for a Bitcoin-focused exchange-traded fund (ETF) to U.S. regulators through Nasdaq.</p>



<p>The filing, which was done on June 29, named Coinbase Global Inc. as a partner, tasked with providing the so-called surveillance support for the proposed ETF due to its huge dollar-to-bitcoin trading volume in the U.S. Notably, according to the document reviewed by ZyCrypto, BlackRock&#8217;s resubmission depict a valid agreement with Coinbase that took effect on June 16.</p>



<p>The decision to amend the application follows recent feedback from the SEC, which deemed initial filings by various issuers such as BlackRock and Fidelity insufficient and lacking the necessary information on the spot bitcoin exchange and surveillance-sharing agreement.</p>



<p>BlackRock&#8217;s initial filing on June 15 mentioned the need for a surveillance-sharing agreement without specifying the exchange that would partner with them. However, other companies, including Fidelity Investments, Invesco, VanEck, 21Shares, and WisdomTree, updated their applications and named Coinbase their surveillance partner.</p>



<p>Meanwhile, as BlackRock&#8217;s latest filing comes to light, concerns arise regarding potential conflicts of interest involving the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). These concerns stem from the fact that the SEC has recently taken <a href="https://zycrypto.com/coinbase-suffers-double-whammy-as-sec-and-state-regulators-act-against-exchange-for-unregistered-securities/">legal action against Coinbase</a>, accusing the exchange of engaging in the sale of unregistered securities.</p>



<p>In a Monday tweet, pro-ripple lawyer John Deaton hit out at the SEC, claiming that BlackRock&#8217;s filing exposed the agency’s shortcomings.</p>



<p><em>&#8220;The SEC/Gary Gensler are essentially claiming Coinbase is running an illegal business, yet the largest Asset Manager in the World and others are disclosing their intent to do business with this illegal business. It tells you all you need to know about what&#8217;s really going on,&#8221; </em>said Deaton<em>&nbsp;</em></p>



<p>Ryan Selkins, the founder and CEO of the crypto data research firm Messari, also expressed his views on the matter. In a July 4 tweet, the pundit stated that the recent news of BlackRock, WisdomTree, and Fidelity choosing Coinbase as their exchange partners simply confirmed what was already known; <em>&#8220;Coinbase is a legitimate U.S. financial institution, and Gary Gensler is a corrupt crony capitalist.&#8221;</em></p>



<p>In a critical tone, Selkins further remarked that Gary Gensler, the current SEC chairman, is a &#8220;corrupt crony capitalist&#8221;, adding that he expects significant developments once Gensler steps down from his position, a resignation he believes will be requested by the White House before the year concludes.</p>



<p>Meanwhile, as the debate surrounding the implementation of a U.S. spot Bitcoin ETF unfolds, the World&#8217;s largest cryptocurrency has continued to hold strong after an 88% increase year-to-date and a 14% surge in the last month alone. As the SEC continues its scrutiny of Bitcoin spot ETF applications, the industry eagerly awaits further developments, with the expectation that an early approval could propel the price of BTC towards its all-time highs.</p>



<p>At the time of reporting, BTC was trading at $30,209, up just over 1% in the past 24 hours.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/blackrocks-renewed-bitcoin-etf-application-featuring-coinbase-raises-questions-on-secs-scrutiny/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Polygon Shows Volatility Following Launch Of &#8216;The Value Prop&#8217;</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/polygon-shows-volatility-following-launch-of-the-value-prop/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/polygon-shows-volatility-following-launch-of-the-value-prop/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aaron Feuerstein]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 18:50:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Polygon]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=82657</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Report-Shows-Growth-In-Multiple-Ethereum-Layer-2-Networks-Polygon-Leads-The-Pack.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Report Shows Growth In Multiple Ethereum Layer 2 Networks; Polygon Leads The Pack" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Report-Shows-Growth-In-Multiple-Ethereum-Layer-2-Networks-Polygon-Leads-The-Pack.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Report-Shows-Growth-In-Multiple-Ethereum-Layer-2-Networks-Polygon-Leads-The-Pack-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Report-Shows-Growth-In-Multiple-Ethereum-Layer-2-Networks-Polygon-Leads-The-Pack-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Report-Shows-Growth-In-Multiple-Ethereum-Layer-2-Networks-Polygon-Leads-The-Pack-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>For investors and holders of MATIC, tensions remain high. According to data, whale buying activity has increased significantly, demonstrating high support and confidence in the project. Large-scale investors appear to know Polygon&#8217;s technology&#8217;s potential and advancements. Polygon also unveiled &#8220;The Value Prop,&#8221; an open library of blockchain use cases along with the price recovery. This [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Report-Shows-Growth-In-Multiple-Ethereum-Layer-2-Networks-Polygon-Leads-The-Pack.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Report Shows Growth In Multiple Ethereum Layer 2 Networks; Polygon Leads The Pack" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Report-Shows-Growth-In-Multiple-Ethereum-Layer-2-Networks-Polygon-Leads-The-Pack.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Report-Shows-Growth-In-Multiple-Ethereum-Layer-2-Networks-Polygon-Leads-The-Pack-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Report-Shows-Growth-In-Multiple-Ethereum-Layer-2-Networks-Polygon-Leads-The-Pack-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Report-Shows-Growth-In-Multiple-Ethereum-Layer-2-Networks-Polygon-Leads-The-Pack-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>For investors and holders of MATIC, tensions remain high. According to data, whale buying activity has increased significantly, demonstrating high support and confidence in the project. Large-scale investors appear to know Polygon&#8217;s technology&#8217;s potential and advancements.</p>



<p>Polygon also unveiled &#8220;The Value Prop,&#8221; an open library of blockchain use cases along with the price recovery. This is a significant development as this extensive catalogue features more than 300 applications and several use examples from a range of industry verticals, blockchain networks, and geographic regions. The effort attempts to emphasize blockchain technology&#8217;s beneficial uses outside of asset trading by portraying it as a flexible tool with practical utility.</p>



<p>The crypto community has noticed and backed Polygon&#8217;s dedication to pushing blockchain application cases. The action is a key step toward boosting blockchain technology usage and recognition. The industry has expressed curiosity and excitement in Polygon&#8217;s presentation of upgradeable smart contracts. With the help of these upgradeable smart contracts, developers can modify and update their contracts to increase flexibility and adaptability.</p>



<p>Meanwhile, Polygon is also working on “System Smart Contracts Governance”, as Mateusz Rzeszowski, governance facilitator of Polygon Labs, said: <em>“Following the first pillar, we present an approach to upgradeable contracts in Polygon protocols, including a potential governance model which allows for both security and decentralization.”</em></p>



<p>The suggested Ecosystem Council model proposes a decentralized, community-controlled council of credible and tech-savvy persons who can change system smart contracts in a timelock-restricted manner. The community would vote for the council using the $MATIC token, which would be up for election and removal. Polygon Labs notes that any Polygon protocol would require a unique check on the council&#8217;s operations. The governance approach seeks to reconcile effective council governance with community control, requiring less active governance and mitigating potential attack vectors.</p>



<p>Rzeszowski added, “This type of governance can minimize requirements for active governance, voter fatigue, and apathy, as well as potential attack vectors connected to, for example, regularly held elections.<em>”</em></p>



<p>Despite recent turbulence, these promising developments within the Polygon ecosystem have helped rebuild trust in the project. The price recovery and the introduction of &#8220;The Value Prop&#8221; have shown how committed Polygon is to promoting blockchain technology and giving its consumers real value.</p>



<p>As the cryptocurrency industry expands, initiatives like Polygon seek to show blockchain technology&#8217;s potential beyond cryptocurrencies. The range of use cases in &#8220;The Value Prop&#8221; database may inspire entrepreneurs, companies, and developers to research the possibilities presented by blockchain in solving modern issues.</p>



<p>The resilience of Polygon in the face of turbulence and its proactive strategy to push blockchain use cases strengthen its status as a top Web3 network. Investors and business leaders continue to show interest in and support for the initiative.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/polygon-shows-volatility-following-launch-of-the-value-prop/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance Defies FUD With $2B Inflows In 24 Hours Amid Senior Execs Departure Controversy</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/binance-defies-fud-with-2b-inflows-in-24-hours-amid-senior-execs-departure-controversy/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/binance-defies-fud-with-2b-inflows-in-24-hours-amid-senior-execs-departure-controversy/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Newton Gitonga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 18:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=82654</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/A-Deliberate-Move-—-Shark-Tank-Star-Kevin-OLeary-Blames-Binance-For-FTX-Collapse.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="“A Deliberate Move” — Shark Tank Star Kevin O’Leary Blames Binance For FTX Collapse" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/A-Deliberate-Move-—-Shark-Tank-Star-Kevin-OLeary-Blames-Binance-For-FTX-Collapse.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/A-Deliberate-Move-—-Shark-Tank-Star-Kevin-OLeary-Blames-Binance-For-FTX-Collapse-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/A-Deliberate-Move-—-Shark-Tank-Star-Kevin-OLeary-Blames-Binance-For-FTX-Collapse-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/A-Deliberate-Move-—-Shark-Tank-Star-Kevin-OLeary-Blames-Binance-For-FTX-Collapse-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>Binance has managed to defy fear, uncertainty, and doubt (FUD) over the past 24 hours amidst growing regulatory scrutiny and the recent departure of several top executives. This follows a Thursday report by Fortune that the exchange&#8217;s General Counsel Han Ng, Chief Strategy Officer Patrick Hillmann, and Senior Vice President for Compliance Steven Christie had [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/A-Deliberate-Move-—-Shark-Tank-Star-Kevin-OLeary-Blames-Binance-For-FTX-Collapse.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="“A Deliberate Move” — Shark Tank Star Kevin O’Leary Blames Binance For FTX Collapse" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/A-Deliberate-Move-—-Shark-Tank-Star-Kevin-OLeary-Blames-Binance-For-FTX-Collapse.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/A-Deliberate-Move-—-Shark-Tank-Star-Kevin-OLeary-Blames-Binance-For-FTX-Collapse-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/A-Deliberate-Move-—-Shark-Tank-Star-Kevin-OLeary-Blames-Binance-For-FTX-Collapse-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/A-Deliberate-Move-—-Shark-Tank-Star-Kevin-OLeary-Blames-Binance-For-FTX-Collapse-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>Binance has managed to defy fear, uncertainty, and doubt (FUD) over the past 24 hours amidst growing regulatory scrutiny and the recent departure of several top executives.</p>



<p>This follows a Thursday <a href="https://fortune.com/crypto/2023/07/06/binance-crisis-executives-quit-changpeng-zhao-justice-department/">report</a> by Fortune that the exchange&#8217;s General Counsel Han Ng, Chief Strategy Officer Patrick Hillmann, and Senior Vice President for Compliance Steven Christie had all tendered their resignations in the past week.</p>



<p>As per Fortune&#8217;s report, the resignations were allegedly influenced by investigations initiated by the U.S. Department of Justice (DOJ) against the exchange. The investigations focused on allegations of money laundering, violations of sanctions, and purported efforts to mislead regulators in the United States. Reportedly some insiders also claimed that the recent departures of executives were significantly influenced by <a href="https://zycrypto.com/binance-boss-zhao-tips-when-the-next-unstoppable-bitcoin-bull-run-will-begin/">Binance CEO</a> Changpeng Zhao&#8217;s &#8220;CZ&#8221; response to the Department of Justice (DOJ) investigation.</p>



<p>However, Hillmann took to Twitter to clarify that his departure was due to personal reasons and not due to any conflict with CZ or the exchange.&nbsp;</p>



<p><em>&#8220;It&#8217;s true that I am leaving Binance, but I&#8217;m doing so on good terms. I continue to respect and support CZ and am grateful for having had the incredible opportunity to work under his leadership,&#8221;</em> said Hillman.</p>



<p>On the other hand, while confirming that he is indeed leaving the company, Christie emphasized on Friday that the reasons for his departure are different from what was reported. Having been involved in crypto compliance since 2015, he expressed feeling tired and acknowledged the need to lose some weight, as well as spend more time with his family.</p>



<p>Meanwhile, responding to media inquiries regarding his departure from Binance, Noah Perlman, the Chief Compliance Officer, clarified that he was not leaving the organization, tweeting, &#8220;<em>I&#8217;m proud to be part of this incredible organization as we navigate the growing pains of the crypto industry.&#8221;</em></p>



<p>CZ himself addressed the departures on Twitter, attributing them to regular turnover rather than the speculative reasons suggested by the media.</p>



<p><em>&#8220;More FUD about some departures. Yes, there is turnover (at every company). But the reasons dreamed up by the &#8220;news&#8221; are completely wrong,&#8221;</em> <a href="https://twitter.com/cz_binance/status/1677092535871602691">said</a> CZ.</p>



<p>He emphasized that as the crypto market and global landscape evolve, personnel changes are common in any organization. CZ further thanked the former team members for their contributions to Binance&#8217;s growth and wished them the best in their future endeavours.</p>



<p>That said, despite the ongoing controversies and legal challenges, Binance has exhibited remarkable resilience, attracting a significant influx of deposits that reflect the continued confidence traders have in the exchange. According to data from DefiLama, within the past 24 hours, approximately $1.99 billion in deposits have been made to the platform, underscoring the enduring trust and support Binance enjoys within the crypto community.</p>



<p>The crypto market has also been displaying a notable level of stability, as Bitcoin reclaimed its position above $30,000 shortly after experiencing a minor dip following the Fortune report.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/binance-defies-fud-with-2b-inflows-in-24-hours-amid-senior-execs-departure-controversy/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>SEC’s Approval Of Spot Bitcoin ETFs Won’t Be A Game-Changer For Crypto Industry, JPMorgan Strategists Opine</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/secs-approval-of-spot-bitcoin-etfs-wont-be-a-game-changer-for-crypto-industry-jpmorgan-strategists-opine/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/secs-approval-of-spot-bitcoin-etfs-wont-be-a-game-changer-for-crypto-industry-jpmorgan-strategists-opine/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Brenda Ngari]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 17:09:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Featured]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[JPMorgan]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XBTUSD]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=82651</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/SECs-Approval-Of-Spot-Bitcoin-ETFs-Wont-Be-A-Game-Changer-For-Crypto-Industry-JPMorgan-Strategists-Opine.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="SEC’s Approval Of Spot Bitcoin ETFs Won’t Be A Game-Changer For Crypto Industry, JPMorgan Strategists Opine" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/SECs-Approval-Of-Spot-Bitcoin-ETFs-Wont-Be-A-Game-Changer-For-Crypto-Industry-JPMorgan-Strategists-Opine.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/SECs-Approval-Of-Spot-Bitcoin-ETFs-Wont-Be-A-Game-Changer-For-Crypto-Industry-JPMorgan-Strategists-Opine-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/SECs-Approval-Of-Spot-Bitcoin-ETFs-Wont-Be-A-Game-Changer-For-Crypto-Industry-JPMorgan-Strategists-Opine-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/SECs-Approval-Of-Spot-Bitcoin-ETFs-Wont-Be-A-Game-Changer-For-Crypto-Industry-JPMorgan-Strategists-Opine-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>While most crypto fans believe the hoped-for successful approval of a spot bitcoin exchange-traded fund in the U.S. would be a seminal moment in the history of crypto, JPMorgan analysts claim such a move by the SEC would not have a significant impact on the market for a couple of reasons.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/SECs-Approval-Of-Spot-Bitcoin-ETFs-Wont-Be-A-Game-Changer-For-Crypto-Industry-JPMorgan-Strategists-Opine.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="SEC’s Approval Of Spot Bitcoin ETFs Won’t Be A Game-Changer For Crypto Industry, JPMorgan Strategists Opine" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/SECs-Approval-Of-Spot-Bitcoin-ETFs-Wont-Be-A-Game-Changer-For-Crypto-Industry-JPMorgan-Strategists-Opine.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/SECs-Approval-Of-Spot-Bitcoin-ETFs-Wont-Be-A-Game-Changer-For-Crypto-Industry-JPMorgan-Strategists-Opine-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/SECs-Approval-Of-Spot-Bitcoin-ETFs-Wont-Be-A-Game-Changer-For-Crypto-Industry-JPMorgan-Strategists-Opine-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/SECs-Approval-Of-Spot-Bitcoin-ETFs-Wont-Be-A-Game-Changer-For-Crypto-Industry-JPMorgan-Strategists-Opine-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>BlackRock, the world’s largest asset manager and currently the de-facto leader of the ETF movement, applied with the SEC last month, driving optimism and higher bitcoin prices.</p>



<p>While most crypto fans believe the hoped-for successful approval of a spot bitcoin exchange-traded fund in the U.S. would be a seminal moment in the history of crypto, JPMorgan analysts claim such a move by the SEC would not have a significant impact on the market for a couple of reasons.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-spot-bitcoin-etfs-have-rather-marginal-benefits"><strong>Spot Bitcoin ETFs Have “Rather Marginal” Benefits</strong></h2>



<p>The news surrounding a flurry of applications from the likes of <a href="https://zycrypto.com/btc-primed-for-trillion-dollar-boost-as-blackrock-expects-landmark-bitcoin-etf-approval/">BlackRock</a>, <a href="https://zycrypto.com/11-1-trillion-giant-fidelity-renews-push-for-spot-bitcoin-etf/">Fidelity</a>, <a href="https://zycrypto.com/spot-bitcoin-etf-craze-valkyrie-becomes-the-latest-firm-to-apply-for-sec-approval/">Valkyrie</a>, <a href="https://zycrypto.com/bitcoin-etfs-in-motion-an-analysis-of-open-spot-btc-etf-applications-in-the-market/">WisdomTree</a>,<a href="https://zycrypto.com/ark-invest-gains-edge-in-spot-bitcoin-etf-race-with-epic-surveillance-sharing-maneuver/"> ARK Invest</a>, and others, for a spot bitcoin ETF sent the price of the bellwether crypto to multi-month highs. For most enthusiasts, this was a sign that institutional investment into the cryptoverse was once again upon us.</p>



<p>However, JPMorgan analysts led by Nikolaos Panigirtzoglou point out in a Thursday report that spot BTC ETFs have long existed in Canada and Europe without garnering much investor interest, hence “the potential approval of physically backed bitcoin ETFs by the SEC [Securities and Exchange Commission] is unlikely to be a game changer for crypto markets.&#8221;</p>



<p>The analysts also acknowledged that spot BTC ETFs provide certain advantages over futures bitcoin ETFs, but these benefits are “rather marginal”. Physically-backed Bitcoin ETFs would allow a large swath of retail American investors to have skin in the game without having to store the cryptocurrency themselves. Unlike the futures-based ETFs, these spot ETFs also have the potential to reflect real-time supply and demand more accurately, causing improved liquidity and enhanced price transparency, as per JPMorgan analysts.</p>



<p>Yet, the launch of spot bitcoin ETFs could transfer trading activity from bitcoin futures markets in the U.S. &#8220;to the extent spot bitcoin ETFs replace futures-based bitcoin ETFs,&#8221; they added.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Will 2023 Be The Year Of The Spot Bitcoin ETF?</strong></h2>



<p>While several high-profile funds and companies have filed paperwork for spot Bitcoin ETFs with the SEC in the past, all have either backed out or faced outright denials from the U.S. regulator since 2017. In Canada, however, key funds, including Purpose Bitcoin, 3iQ CoinShares, and CI Galaxy Bitcoin — all directly invested in spot BTC — are already available for customers.</p>



<p>JPMorgan strategists believe the SEC might actually OK one of the recent new applications for the long-awaited spot product because some of the regulator’s previous concerns are assumed to be addressed as the would-be ETF issuers have indicated their intention to enter into surveillance-sharing agreements with Coinbase, the largest crypto exchange in the US. Under a surveillance-sharing agreement, information about market trading and clearing activities is shared between entities to deter any potential market manipulation.</p>



<p>Last month, the SEC approved the first leveraged bitcoin futures ETF, Volatility Shares 2x Bitcoin Strategy ETF (BITX). The open question now is whether the commission will also approve the first-ever spot Bitcoin ETF in the U.S. this year. </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/secs-approval-of-spot-bitcoin-etfs-wont-be-a-game-changer-for-crypto-industry-jpmorgan-strategists-opine/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance’s CZ Shrugs Off News Of Senior Executive Personnel Resigning As Attempts To Spread FUD</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/binances-cz-shrugs-off-news-of-senior-executive-personnel-resigning-as-attempts-to-spread-fud/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/binances-cz-shrugs-off-news-of-senior-executive-personnel-resigning-as-attempts-to-spread-fud/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Brenda Ngari]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 16:57:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Changpeng Zhao]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=82649</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Binance-Prepares-To-Pay-Fines-To-Settle-Outstanding-U.S.-Regulatory-Probes.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Binance Prepares To Pay Fines To Settle Outstanding U.S. Regulatory Probes" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Binance-Prepares-To-Pay-Fines-To-Settle-Outstanding-U.S.-Regulatory-Probes.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Binance-Prepares-To-Pay-Fines-To-Settle-Outstanding-U.S.-Regulatory-Probes-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Binance-Prepares-To-Pay-Fines-To-Settle-Outstanding-U.S.-Regulatory-Probes-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Binance-Prepares-To-Pay-Fines-To-Settle-Outstanding-U.S.-Regulatory-Probes-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>Binance founder Changpeng “CZ” Zhao has shrugged off news of top executives leaving the exchange, reportedly over his...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Binance-Prepares-To-Pay-Fines-To-Settle-Outstanding-U.S.-Regulatory-Probes.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Binance Prepares To Pay Fines To Settle Outstanding U.S. Regulatory Probes" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Binance-Prepares-To-Pay-Fines-To-Settle-Outstanding-U.S.-Regulatory-Probes.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Binance-Prepares-To-Pay-Fines-To-Settle-Outstanding-U.S.-Regulatory-Probes-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Binance-Prepares-To-Pay-Fines-To-Settle-Outstanding-U.S.-Regulatory-Probes-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Binance-Prepares-To-Pay-Fines-To-Settle-Outstanding-U.S.-Regulatory-Probes-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>Binance founder Changpeng “CZ” Zhao has shrugged off news of top executives leaving the exchange, reportedly over his handling of regulatory investigations. Zhao said it was “FUD,” claiming the reasons for the execs&#8217; departures are “dreamed up” and “completely wrong.”</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-top-binance-executives-bow-out"><strong>Top Binance Executives Bow Out</strong></h2>



<p>A surprising number of key executive personnel at Binance have resigned from their posts.</p>



<p>According to a June 6 <a href="https://fortune.com/crypto/2023/07/06/binance-crisis-executives-quit-changpeng-zhao-justice-department/">report </a>from <em>Fortune </em>citing an internal source, executives in senior leadership positions, including chief strategy officer Patrick Hillmann, general counsel Han Ng, senior director of investigations Matthew Price, and senior vice president for compliance Steven Christie exited the exchange over CEO Changpeng Zhao’s response to the U.S. Justice Department’s investigation. The DoJ is purportedly <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-05-05/binance-faces-us-probe-of-possible-russian-sanctions-violations">probing </a>Binance for allowing Russians to use the crypto exchange in violation of U.S. sanctions.&nbsp;</p>



<p>The news publication also labelled the top personnel’s decision to resign from the exchange “a management and strategic crisis for Binance”. </p>



<p>Hillmann, however, said in a <a href="https://twitter.com/PRHillmann/status/1677070523740884992">tweet </a>that he was leaving Binance on good terms after a two-year tenure and it’s “simply time for me to move on to the next challenge”, adding that his wife was about to give birth to their second child, “so the time is right for me to step aside.”</p>



<p>“More FUD about some departures. Yes, there is turnover (at every company). But the reasons dreamed up by the “news” are completely wrong,” CZ tweeted in response to the high-profile departures. “As markets and the global environment for crypto changes, as our organization evolves, and as personal situations change, there is turnover at every company.”</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">4. More FUD about some departures. Yes, there is turnover (at every company). But the reasons dreamed up by the “news” are completely wrong.<br><br>As an organization that has grown from 30 to 8000 people in 6 years, from 0 to the world’s largest crypto exchange in less than 5 months…</p>&mdash; CZ <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f536.png" alt="🔶" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> Binance (@cz_binance) <a href="https://twitter.com/cz_binance/status/1677092535871602691?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">July 6, 2023</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>Notably, there have also been replacements following these resignations. A different <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-07-06/binance-executive-patrick-hillmann-us-employees-leave-as-crisis-deepens#xj4y7vzkg">report </a>from <em>Bloomberg</em>, also citing a source, noted that Eleanor Hughes, previously Binance’s Head of Legal for APAC and MENA regions, is set to become the new general counsel, stepping into Ng’s shoes. Noah Perlamn, who joined Binance as the chief compliance officer in February, will stay at the company.</p>



<p>The management reshuffles at Binance come as the exchange is the subject of enforcement action from multiple regulators. The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) <a href="https://zycrypto.com/us-sec-files-fresh-charges-against-binance-and-ceo-changpeng-zhao/">sued </a>Binance on allegations of violating federal securities laws and misusing customer funds. The world’s largest exchange was also <a href="https://zycrypto.com/bitcoin-ether-slump-as-cftc-sues-binance-and-cz-over-willful-violation-of-u-s-laws/">accused </a>by the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) of failing to register properly before offering commodities trading services.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/binances-cz-shrugs-off-news-of-senior-executive-personnel-resigning-as-attempts-to-spread-fud/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance Boss Zhao Tips When The Next Unstoppable Bitcoin Bull Run Will Begin</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/binance-boss-zhao-tips-when-the-next-unstoppable-bitcoin-bull-run-will-begin/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/binance-boss-zhao-tips-when-the-next-unstoppable-bitcoin-bull-run-will-begin/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Brenda Ngari]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 17:48:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XBTUSD]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=82644</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Binance-Boss-Zhao-Tips-When-The-Next-Unstoppable-Bitcoin-Bull-Run-Will-Begin.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Binance Boss Zhao Tips When The Next Unstoppable Bitcoin Bull Run Will Begin" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Binance-Boss-Zhao-Tips-When-The-Next-Unstoppable-Bitcoin-Bull-Run-Will-Begin.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Binance-Boss-Zhao-Tips-When-The-Next-Unstoppable-Bitcoin-Bull-Run-Will-Begin-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Binance-Boss-Zhao-Tips-When-The-Next-Unstoppable-Bitcoin-Bull-Run-Will-Begin-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Binance-Boss-Zhao-Tips-When-The-Next-Unstoppable-Bitcoin-Bull-Run-Will-Begin-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>Binance CEO Changpeng “CZ” Zhao has shared his prediction for the next parabolic Bitcoin bull run while giving his thoughts on BlackRock’s giant entry into the crypto market.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Binance-Boss-Zhao-Tips-When-The-Next-Unstoppable-Bitcoin-Bull-Run-Will-Begin.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Binance Boss Zhao Tips When The Next Unstoppable Bitcoin Bull Run Will Begin" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Binance-Boss-Zhao-Tips-When-The-Next-Unstoppable-Bitcoin-Bull-Run-Will-Begin.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Binance-Boss-Zhao-Tips-When-The-Next-Unstoppable-Bitcoin-Bull-Run-Will-Begin-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Binance-Boss-Zhao-Tips-When-The-Next-Unstoppable-Bitcoin-Bull-Run-Will-Begin-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Binance-Boss-Zhao-Tips-When-The-Next-Unstoppable-Bitcoin-Bull-Run-Will-Begin-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>Bitcoin is changing hands for over $30,000 per coin as institutional capital floods into the market following a number of high-profile exchange-traded fund filings.</p>



<p>But when will the bellwether cryptocurrency enter a new super-bullish cycle?</p>



<p>Binance CEO Changpeng “CZ” Zhao recently shared his prediction for the next parabolic Bitcoin bull run while giving his thoughts on BlackRock’s giant entry into the crypto market.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-relentless-btc-bull-run-likely-after-halving-zhao"><strong>Relentless </strong><strong>BTC Bull Run Likely After Halving: Zhao</strong></h2>



<p>Binance chief executive officer Changpeng Zhao has revealed when he expects the onset of the next major bull run.</p>



<p>Speaking during a Twitter AMA session on July 5, Zhao noted that the price of bitcoin has typically moved in four-year-long cycles, and he believed this trend would likely continue. Although the Binance chief acknowledged that he could not predict the future accurately, Zhao maintained that 2025 would be the most likely year for the next majestic bull market as it will be the year after the next Bitcoin halving event. “The year after Bitcoin halving is usually the bull year,” CZ said.</p>



<p>True to form, BTC tends to chalk out massive gains in the months after halving the mining rewards. The fourth halving is due in early 2024.</p>



<p>During the “ask me anything” session, Zhao also said that BlackRock’s recent foray into the spot bitcoin exchange-traded fund territory is “hugely beneficial” for the nascent cryptocurrency industry.</p>



<p>BlackRock, the world’s largest asset manager with $9.5 trillion under management, <a href="https://zycrypto.com/btc-primed-for-trillion-dollar-boost-as-blackrock-expects-landmark-bitcoin-etf-approval/">applied </a>to the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) for a spot Bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF) a few weeks ago.</p>



<p>Pundits think the odds are in favour of the financial giant, which is almost unbeaten when going up against the SEC, at 575-1, as nearly every single one of its ETF filings has received a green light.</p>



<p>Bitcoin may be far below the all-time high of $69,044 it registered in November 2021, but this much is undeniable: It had transcended expectations in 2023 by jumping over 85% since the beginning of the year when it was trading at around $17,000. BTC has spiked by circa 20% since BlackRock’s spot ETF filing, wildly as more companies <a href="https://zycrypto.com/bitcoin-etfs-in-motion-an-analysis-of-open-spot-btc-etf-applications-in-the-market/">rushed to submit their applications</a>.</p>



<p>Zhao further dismissed some worries that BlackRock could take up Binance’s market share in the course of time, noting that the overlap between their respective customer bases was “minimal.”</p>



<p>“Anyone who’s coming into crypto that’s not in crypto today will bring additional people into crypto. Will they compete for any of the existing users with us? Yes, probably a little bit. But to be honest, look at our user base. The overlap is minimal.”</p>



<p>For Zhao, the heightened institutional demand and Bitcoin’s forthcoming halving are the two key factors why Binance aims to be “prepared for higher [trading] volumes” in the coming eighteen months.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/binance-boss-zhao-tips-when-the-next-unstoppable-bitcoin-bull-run-will-begin/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Gemini&#8217;s Winklevoss Demands $1.46B Settlement from DCG In EARN Product Tussle</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/geminis-winklevoss-demands-1-46b-settlement-from-dcg-in-earn-product-tussle/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/geminis-winklevoss-demands-1-46b-settlement-from-dcg-in-earn-product-tussle/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Newton Gitonga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 17:31:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=82640</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/05/Bitcoin-Has-Much-More-Meaningful-Value-Compared-to-the-US-Dollar-Tyler-Winklevoss-Asserts.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Bitcoin Has Much More Meaningful Value Compared to the US Dollar, Tyler Winklevoss Asserts" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/05/Bitcoin-Has-Much-More-Meaningful-Value-Compared-to-the-US-Dollar-Tyler-Winklevoss-Asserts.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/05/Bitcoin-Has-Much-More-Meaningful-Value-Compared-to-the-US-Dollar-Tyler-Winklevoss-Asserts-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/05/Bitcoin-Has-Much-More-Meaningful-Value-Compared-to-the-US-Dollar-Tyler-Winklevoss-Asserts-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/05/Bitcoin-Has-Much-More-Meaningful-Value-Compared-to-the-US-Dollar-Tyler-Winklevoss-Asserts-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>Gemini has escalated its conflict with Digital Currency Group (DCG) after approximately seven months since Genesis Global Trading, DCG&#8217;s lending arm, suspended withdrawals. On Tuesday, Gemini co-founder Cameron Winklevoss presented Barry Silbert, the founder of DCG, with a &#8220;best and final offer&#8221; letter to settle the $1.465 billion debt owed to Gemini. Winklevoss&#8217;s letter carried [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/05/Bitcoin-Has-Much-More-Meaningful-Value-Compared-to-the-US-Dollar-Tyler-Winklevoss-Asserts.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Bitcoin Has Much More Meaningful Value Compared to the US Dollar, Tyler Winklevoss Asserts" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/05/Bitcoin-Has-Much-More-Meaningful-Value-Compared-to-the-US-Dollar-Tyler-Winklevoss-Asserts.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/05/Bitcoin-Has-Much-More-Meaningful-Value-Compared-to-the-US-Dollar-Tyler-Winklevoss-Asserts-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/05/Bitcoin-Has-Much-More-Meaningful-Value-Compared-to-the-US-Dollar-Tyler-Winklevoss-Asserts-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/05/Bitcoin-Has-Much-More-Meaningful-Value-Compared-to-the-US-Dollar-Tyler-Winklevoss-Asserts-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>Gemini has escalated its conflict with Digital Currency Group (DCG) after approximately seven months since Genesis Global Trading, DCG&#8217;s lending arm, suspended withdrawals.</p>



<p>On Tuesday, Gemini co-founder Cameron Winklevoss presented Barry Silbert, the founder of DCG, with a &#8220;best and final offer&#8221; <a href="https://twitter.com/cameron/status/1676024844641550337">letter</a> to settle the $1.465 billion debt owed to Gemini. Winklevoss&#8217;s letter carried a clear request, threatening legal action against Silbert and DCG if an agreement is not reached by July 6.</p>



<p>The proposed settlement further outlined payments in intervals and specified that they would be denominated in BTC, ETH, and U.S. dollars. Notably, the settlement also included a significant forbearance payment of $275 million, which Winklevoss expects to be fulfilled on July 21.</p>



<p>In the latest letter, <a href="https://zycrypto.com/secs-refusal-to-approve-a-spot-bitcoin-etf-makes-it-a-failed-regulator-says-geminis-cameron-winklevoss/">Winklevoss</a> accused Silbert of fraud, alleging that he knowingly lied to creditors, including Gemini, in 2022 regarding DCG&#8217;s absorption of the $1.2 billion losses incurred from Three Arrows Capital&#8217;s collapse. Winklevoss further claimed that DCG employed a &#8220;bogus long-dated promissory note&#8221; to address the financial shortfall while deliberately prolonging the mediation process to raise funds for repaying a $630 million loan.</p>



<p>Winklevoss also expressed frustration with Silbert&#8217;s actions, accusing him of playing the victim during the whole process.&nbsp;</p>



<p>&#8220;<em>It takes a special kind of person to owe $3.3 billion dollars to hundreds of thousands of people and believe, or at least pretend to believe, that they are some kind of victim. Not even Sam Bankman-Friend was capable of such delusion,&#8221; </em>said<em> </em>Winklevoss.<em>&nbsp;</em></p>



<p>Notably, the long-drawn conflict arose from a partnership gone soar between the two sides regarding Gemini&#8217;s Earn product. Launched in early 2021, Gemini Earn was a high-yield program that allowed customers to lend their crypto assets to Genesis. Genesis then invested the funds in institutions and paid investors an 8% interest. However, following FTX&#8217;s collapse last November, Genesis halted customer withdrawals, leaving Gemini unable to repay its Earn customers.</p>



<p>In January, Winklevoss made a public statement <a href="https://zycrypto.com/gemini-vows-legal-action-against-genesis-parent-company-amidst-bankruptcy-filing/">alleging</a> that approximately 340,000 participants in the yield-bearing product were owed around $900 million by Genesis. The exchange further shut down the Earn program and dissolved the master loan agreement between its customers and Genesis.</p>



<p>In response, Barry Silbert defended his integrity and good intentions in a letter to DCG shareholders, blaming the failures on the 2022 crypto winter. The two entities then turned to mediation without success, with Winkelvoss blaming Silbert for completely undermining the process.</p>



<p>That said, as the deadline looms, it will be interesting to see the outcome of the settlement negotiations, with a positive outcome potentially benefiting thousands of Earn users.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/geminis-winklevoss-demands-1-46b-settlement-from-dcg-in-earn-product-tussle/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Coinbase Stocks Make Move as CBOE Lists Exchange in Refiled ETF Application</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/coinbase-stocks-make-move-as-cboe-lists-exchange-in-refiled-etf-application/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/coinbase-stocks-make-move-as-cboe-lists-exchange-in-refiled-etf-application/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ponvang Bulus]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 16:52:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=82637</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Coinbase-Lays-Off-1100-People-In-Preparation-For-Prolonged-Bear-Market.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Coinbase Lays Off 1,100 People In Preparation For Prolonged Bear Market" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Coinbase-Lays-Off-1100-People-In-Preparation-For-Prolonged-Bear-Market.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Coinbase-Lays-Off-1100-People-In-Preparation-For-Prolonged-Bear-Market-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Coinbase-Lays-Off-1100-People-In-Preparation-For-Prolonged-Bear-Market-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Coinbase-Lays-Off-1100-People-In-Preparation-For-Prolonged-Bear-Market-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>Coinbase stocks soared over 11% earlier this week following the mention of the exchange as a surveillance partner in Chicago Board Options Exchange (CBOE) refiled Bitcoin spot Exchange-Traded Fund (ETF) application. The CBOE refiled a spot Bitcoin ETF application on Friday last week on behalf of  Fidelity, WisdomTree, VanEck and Invesco products. The US Securities [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Coinbase-Lays-Off-1100-People-In-Preparation-For-Prolonged-Bear-Market.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Coinbase Lays Off 1,100 People In Preparation For Prolonged Bear Market" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Coinbase-Lays-Off-1100-People-In-Preparation-For-Prolonged-Bear-Market.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Coinbase-Lays-Off-1100-People-In-Preparation-For-Prolonged-Bear-Market-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Coinbase-Lays-Off-1100-People-In-Preparation-For-Prolonged-Bear-Market-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Coinbase-Lays-Off-1100-People-In-Preparation-For-Prolonged-Bear-Market-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>Coinbase stocks soared over 11% earlier this week following the mention of the exchange as a surveillance partner in Chicago Board Options Exchange (CBOE) refiled Bitcoin spot Exchange-Traded Fund (ETF) application. The CBOE refiled a spot Bitcoin ETF application on Friday last week on behalf of  Fidelity, WisdomTree, VanEck and Invesco products.</p>



<p>The US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) had last week dismissed the latest Bitcoin ETF applications, saying they were inadequate because they lacked surveillance partners. Shortly after, CBOE refiled the applications, naming Coinbase as a surveillance partner.</p>



<p>Following the refiling, Coinbase stocks shot up on Monday’s session as investors seem optimistic about the outcome of the ETF application. According to the filing, the CBOE said that Coinbase will “supplement its ability to obtain information that would be helpful in detecting, investigating, and deterring fraud and market manipulation.”</p>



<p>There have been several applications for a Bitcoin ETF in the past, but only futures Bitcoin ETFs have been approved so far. However, investment managers are seeking a spot ETF, which is expected to boost investor confidence in the mainstream adoption of Bitcoin.</p>



<p>The SEC has refused to approve any of the ETF applications, citing fears of market manipulation. After meeting the condition of adding a surveillance partner, there may be hope for approval this time around.</p>



<p>Similarly, NASDAQ on Monday, 3 July refiled Bitcoin ETF applications on behalf of iShares Bitcoin Trust and BlackRock since BlackRock is seeking to launch its ETF through NASDAQ.</p>



<p><em>&#8220;The Spot BTC SSA is expected to be a bilateral surveillance-sharing agreement between Nasdaq and Coinbase that is intended to supplement the Exchange’s market surveillance program,&#8221; the filing reads.</em></p>



<p>This is coming at a time when Coinbase is in court, facing allegations of securities laws violation levelled against it by the SEC. It remains to be seen if the court case will disqualify Coinbase as a surveillance partner for the two refiled ETF applications.</p>



<p>However, with the two filings listing Coinbase as a surveillance partner, investors’ confidence may continue to soar with a resultant rise in the prices of Coinbase stocks in the coming days. The effect may also spill to Bitcoin, further fueling the ongoing rally.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/coinbase-stocks-make-move-as-cboe-lists-exchange-in-refiled-etf-application/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Shiba Inu Core Dev Teases Shibarium Launch Timeline Amid Super Bullish Strategy For SHIB</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/shiba-inu-core-dev-teases-shibarium-launch-timeline-amid-super-bullish-strategy-for-shib/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/shiba-inu-core-dev-teases-shibarium-launch-timeline-amid-super-bullish-strategy-for-shib/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Newton Gitonga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 12:26:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIB]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIBA INU]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIBUSD]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=82605</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Shiba-Inu-Community-Anticipates-Major-Updates-Rocket-Pond-Launch-SHIB-Metaverse-and-Shibarium-Mainnet.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Shiba Inu Community Anticipates Major Updates: Rocket Pond Launch, SHIB Metaverse, and Shibarium Mainnet" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Shiba-Inu-Community-Anticipates-Major-Updates-Rocket-Pond-Launch-SHIB-Metaverse-and-Shibarium-Mainnet.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Shiba-Inu-Community-Anticipates-Major-Updates-Rocket-Pond-Launch-SHIB-Metaverse-and-Shibarium-Mainnet-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Shiba-Inu-Community-Anticipates-Major-Updates-Rocket-Pond-Launch-SHIB-Metaverse-and-Shibarium-Mainnet-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Shiba-Inu-Community-Anticipates-Major-Updates-Rocket-Pond-Launch-SHIB-Metaverse-and-Shibarium-Mainnet-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>Shytoshi Kusama, the lead developer behind Shiba Inu, has provided a glimpse into the highly anticipated launch of Shibarium, a layer-2 protocol within the Shiba Inu ecosystem, sparking excitement and speculation among the community.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Shiba-Inu-Community-Anticipates-Major-Updates-Rocket-Pond-Launch-SHIB-Metaverse-and-Shibarium-Mainnet.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Shiba Inu Community Anticipates Major Updates: Rocket Pond Launch, SHIB Metaverse, and Shibarium Mainnet" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Shiba-Inu-Community-Anticipates-Major-Updates-Rocket-Pond-Launch-SHIB-Metaverse-and-Shibarium-Mainnet.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Shiba-Inu-Community-Anticipates-Major-Updates-Rocket-Pond-Launch-SHIB-Metaverse-and-Shibarium-Mainnet-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Shiba-Inu-Community-Anticipates-Major-Updates-Rocket-Pond-Launch-SHIB-Metaverse-and-Shibarium-Mainnet-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Shiba-Inu-Community-Anticipates-Major-Updates-Rocket-Pond-Launch-SHIB-Metaverse-and-Shibarium-Mainnet-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>Shytoshi Kusama, the lead developer behind <a href="https://zycrypto.com/shiba-inu-unlocks-remarkable-price-trajectory-amid-exciting-ecosystem-updates-for-shibarium/">Shiba Inu</a>, has provided a glimpse into the highly anticipated launch of Shibarium, a layer-2 protocol within the Shiba Inu ecosystem, sparking excitement and speculation among the community.</p>



<p>Over the weekend, Lucie, the content marketer for Shiba Inu, took to Twitter to share a discussion in a Telegram group chat, where Kusama was asked about any potential changes to the launch date or plan of <a href="https://zycrypto.com/0-001-shib-price-looks-nigh-as-shiba-inus-testnet-sees-rising-activity-ahead-of-shibarium-mainnet/">Shibarium</a>. Confidently, Kusama responded, <em>&#8220;It doesn&#8217;t matter; everything is already set. I can&#8217;t change the date or plan. It&#8217;s called a launch strategy.&#8221;</em> </p>



<p>This tweet quickly gained traction within the community, generating further anticipation and interest with various individuals praising the project&#8217;s developers.</p>



<p>&#8220;<em>Wow. Strong Words!! I love how the team is handling the launch. Very strategic!! And I believe the timing will be perfect,&#8221;</em> American Businessman Old Horse replied to Lucie&#8217;s tweet.</p>



<p>However, critics of Kusama have accused him of toying with people&#8217;s emotions by consistently raising false expectations.</p>



<p><em>&#8220;Honestly ShytoshiKusama, I would believe that statement had you not been insinuating the launch of Shibarium and giving false hope, especially as much as you have in the recent six months. At this point, you&#8217;re just toying with people&#8217;s emotions,&#8221;</em> one individual commented.</p>



<p>In April, Kusama indicated a launch timeframe of two to four months. Last month, the developer disclosed that the launch of Shibarium is imminent. Lucie also hinted in May that the Shibarium launch is closer than expected. Interestingly, July 11 would mark the four-month milestone since the beta release, prompting discussions around the possibility of the launch happening on that date.</p>



<p>Austin Hilton, CEO of Redhill Group and a member of the Shiba Inu community predicted on July 3 that Shibarium would likely launch in mid-August. Hilton expressed his intention to purchase and hold over 20,000 BONE tokens leading up to August, hoping that the Shibarium launch will bring exponential growth potential to BONE.</p>



<p>That said, these conflicting projections have left the community in anticipation, eagerly awaiting an official announcement from the Shiba Inu team regarding the launch date. Despite this obscurity, excitement is expected to keep building around SHIB, preparing it for a massive surge.</p>



<p>Following a significant decline to its lowest point of the year, SHIB faces difficulties breaking the $0.000008 monthly resistance. Should Bulls demonstrate sufficient strength to overcome the level, there is a possibility of witnessing SHIB subtracting another zero and surging to $0.00002 soon.</p>



<p>At press time, SHIB was trading at $$0.000007478 after dropping 2.73% in the past 24 hours, as per CoinMarketCap data.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/shiba-inu-core-dev-teases-shibarium-launch-timeline-amid-super-bullish-strategy-for-shib/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>BTC Holds Above $31K As BlackRock CEO Larry Fink Lauds Bitcoin For ‘Digitizing Gold’</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/btc-holds-above-31k-as-blackrock-ceo-larry-fink-lauds-bitcoin-for-digitizing-gold/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/btc-holds-above-31k-as-blackrock-ceo-larry-fink-lauds-bitcoin-for-digitizing-gold/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Brenda Ngari]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 12:18:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XBTUSD]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=82624</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTC-Holds-Above-31K-As-BlackRock-CEO-Larry-Fink-Lauds-Bitcoin-For-‘Digitizing-Gold.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="BTC Holds Above $31K As BlackRock CEO Larry Fink Lauds Bitcoin For ‘Digitizing Gold’" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTC-Holds-Above-31K-As-BlackRock-CEO-Larry-Fink-Lauds-Bitcoin-For-‘Digitizing-Gold.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTC-Holds-Above-31K-As-BlackRock-CEO-Larry-Fink-Lauds-Bitcoin-For-‘Digitizing-Gold-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTC-Holds-Above-31K-As-BlackRock-CEO-Larry-Fink-Lauds-Bitcoin-For-‘Digitizing-Gold-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTC-Holds-Above-31K-As-BlackRock-CEO-Larry-Fink-Lauds-Bitcoin-For-‘Digitizing-Gold-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>BlackRock chief executive officer Larry Fink, who once said Bitcoin was being largely utilized for “illicit activities”, said on July 5 that the original cryptocurrency was “digitizing gold.”]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTC-Holds-Above-31K-As-BlackRock-CEO-Larry-Fink-Lauds-Bitcoin-For-‘Digitizing-Gold.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="BTC Holds Above $31K As BlackRock CEO Larry Fink Lauds Bitcoin For ‘Digitizing Gold’" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTC-Holds-Above-31K-As-BlackRock-CEO-Larry-Fink-Lauds-Bitcoin-For-‘Digitizing-Gold.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTC-Holds-Above-31K-As-BlackRock-CEO-Larry-Fink-Lauds-Bitcoin-For-‘Digitizing-Gold-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTC-Holds-Above-31K-As-BlackRock-CEO-Larry-Fink-Lauds-Bitcoin-For-‘Digitizing-Gold-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTC-Holds-Above-31K-As-BlackRock-CEO-Larry-Fink-Lauds-Bitcoin-For-‘Digitizing-Gold-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>BlackRock chief executive officer Larry Fink, who once said Bitcoin was being largely utilized for “illicit activities”, said on July 5 that the original cryptocurrency was “digitizing gold.”</p>



<p>Fink’s remarks come weeks after the world’s biggest asset manager <a href="https://zycrypto.com/btc-primed-for-trillion-dollar-boost-as-blackrock-expects-landmark-bitcoin-etf-approval/">filed paperwork</a> to list a spot Bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF) in the United States, with digital asset exchange Coinbase acting as its surveillance partner.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-bitcoin-as-an-international-asset"><strong>Bitcoin As An “International Asset”</strong></h2>



<p>BlackRock boss Larry Fink delivered pro-bitcoin comments during his latest interview.</p>



<p>Speaking on<em> Fox Business</em> Wednesday, Fink said he believes the role of crypto was mostly “digitizing gold”.&nbsp;</p>



<p>“Instead of investing in gold as a hedge against inflation, a hedge against the onerous problems of any one country, or the devaluation of your currency whatever country you’re in — let’s be clear, bitcoin is an international asset, it’s not based on any one currency and so it can represent an asset that people can play as an alternative,” the billionaire added.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr"><a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Bitcoin?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Bitcoin</a> is an International Asset. &#8211; Larry Fink, BlackRock CEO <a href="https://t.co/WIVKITXYPj">pic.twitter.com/WIVKITXYPj</a></p>&mdash; Michael Saylor<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/26a1.png" alt="⚡" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> (@saylor) <a href="https://twitter.com/saylor/status/1676687611379826688?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">July 5, 2023</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>BlackRock, which manages over $9.5 trillion in assets worldwide, helped Bitcoin <a href="https://zycrypto.com/btc-surges-past-31k-now-up-80-this-year-as-wall-street-eyes-digital-gold/">bounce out of the doldrums</a> with its ETF filing with the SEC, causing big institutional players to pour capital into the space and driving the top crypto to levels not seen in 12 months.</p>



<p>Crypto enthusiasts are excited by the prospect of a spot bitcoin ETF in the U.S. that would offer investors exposure to the flagship digital asset on a regulated crypto exchange without the hassle of custody.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>BlackRock Seeks To Democratize Crypto: Larry Fink</strong></h2>



<p>Fink further said his company would work with regulators and hear any concerns they might have regarding their spot bitcoin ETF application.</p>



<p>&#8220;What we&#8217;re trying to do with crypto is make it more democratized and make it much cheaper for investors,&#8221; Fink explained. &#8220;Right now, the bid-ask spread for crypto is very expensive. It does erode a lot of the returns&#8230;We hope our regulators look at these filings as a way to democratize crypto,&#8221; he continued.</p>



<p>Although BlackRock has a stunning record of getting ETFs greenlit by the SEC, the CEO admitted he has no idea when a decision for its spot bitcoin ETF could be made amid the regulator’s brutal crackdown on the crypto industry.</p>



<p>Fink’s bullishness now is a noticeable <a href="https://zycrypto.com/bitcoin-could-evolve-into-a-global-market-says-head-of-the-worlds-largest-asset-firm/">change of tune</a> from back in 2017 when he <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2017/10/13/blackrock-ceo-larry-fink-calls-bitcoin-an-index-of-money-laundering.html">posited </a>that “Bitcoin just shows you how much demand for money laundering there is in the world.” However, he later conceded that BTC was a “great asset class” and that New York-based BlackRock had even accrued some profits after investing in the cryptocurrency.&nbsp;</p>



<p>Satoshi Nakamoto&#8217;s rebel child is presently changing hands at $31,200.39 at the time of publication, up 2.4% over the past 24 hours as per CoinGecko. The cryptocurrency was valued at less than $17,000 at the beginning of 2023.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/btc-holds-above-31k-as-blackrock-ceo-larry-fink-lauds-bitcoin-for-digitizing-gold/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>BlackRock Highly Optimistic On Spot Bitcoin ETF Approval As CEO Larry Fink Terms Bitcoin An &#8216;International Asset&#8217;</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/blackrock-highly-optimistic-on-spot-bitcoin-etf-approval-as-ceo-larry-fink-terms-bitcoin-an-international-asset/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/blackrock-highly-optimistic-on-spot-bitcoin-etf-approval-as-ceo-larry-fink-terms-bitcoin-an-international-asset/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aaron Feuerstein]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 11:48:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XBTUSD]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=82622</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/ProShares-Bitcoin-ETF-To-Go-Live-Tomorrow-Marking-Major-Milestone-For-Crypto-World.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="ProShares Bitcoin ETF To Go Live Tomorrow, Marking Major Milestone For Crypto World" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/ProShares-Bitcoin-ETF-To-Go-Live-Tomorrow-Marking-Major-Milestone-For-Crypto-World.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/ProShares-Bitcoin-ETF-To-Go-Live-Tomorrow-Marking-Major-Milestone-For-Crypto-World-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/ProShares-Bitcoin-ETF-To-Go-Live-Tomorrow-Marking-Major-Milestone-For-Crypto-World-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/ProShares-Bitcoin-ETF-To-Go-Live-Tomorrow-Marking-Major-Milestone-For-Crypto-World-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>BlackRock's reputation and track record have instilled hope within the crypto world, as the company has had an overwhelmingly successful history with its ETF applications.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/ProShares-Bitcoin-ETF-To-Go-Live-Tomorrow-Marking-Major-Milestone-For-Crypto-World.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="ProShares Bitcoin ETF To Go Live Tomorrow, Marking Major Milestone For Crypto World" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/ProShares-Bitcoin-ETF-To-Go-Live-Tomorrow-Marking-Major-Milestone-For-Crypto-World.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/ProShares-Bitcoin-ETF-To-Go-Live-Tomorrow-Marking-Major-Milestone-For-Crypto-World-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/ProShares-Bitcoin-ETF-To-Go-Live-Tomorrow-Marking-Major-Milestone-For-Crypto-World-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/ProShares-Bitcoin-ETF-To-Go-Live-Tomorrow-Marking-Major-Milestone-For-Crypto-World-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p><a href="https://zycrypto.com/bitcoins-resilience-shines-amid-largest-decline-of-btc-inflows-and-supply-in-history/">Bitcoin</a> has had a remarkable price performance this year, outperforming the S&amp;P 500&#8217;s 15% year-to-date gain. The price of Bitcoin has climbed by 83% since the start of 2023, with a sizable chunk of that growth taking place after June 15th. When BlackRock, the biggest asset manager in the world, applied for a <a href="https://zycrypto.com/legal-expert-reveals-the-odds-of-a-spot-bitcoin-etf-approval-in-2023/">Spot Bitcoin ETF</a>, prices surged alongside.</p>



<p>BlackRock joined a group of fund managers, including ARC, Invesco, VanEck, and Grayscale, who were all eager to enter the market. However, the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), so far, has turned down any applications for a spot Bitcoin ETF, primarily due to concerns about fraud and manipulation.</p>



<p>BlackRock&#8217;s reputation and track record have instilled hope within the crypto world, as the company has had an overwhelmingly successful history with its ETF applications. Out of BlackRock&#8217;s 576 ETF applications, only one was rejected in 2014. Therefore, the crypto sector eagerly awaits the outcome of BlackRock&#8217;s latest filing.</p>



<p>BlackRock and NASDAQ recently resubmitted their application and named Coinbase as the custodial surveillance partner for the Spot Bitcoin Trust in response to the SEC&#8217;s requirement that BlackRock designate a surveillance partner to solve these issues.</p>



<p>Larry Fink, Chairman and CEO of BlackRock, emphasized the firm&#8217;s dedication to long-term investors and their history of close cooperation with authorities in an exclusive interview with Liz Claman and Charlie Gasparino on Fox Business’ “The Claman Countdown”. Fink expressed hope about working with authorities and addressing their concerns to eventually get permission, even if he couldn&#8217;t specify the present submission.</p>



<p>Fink emphasized BlackRock&#8217;s commitment to product digitization, noting that ETFs have already transformed the mutual fund sector. His firm believes that tokenizing the assets and securities that Bitcoin symbolizes will further democratize investment. BlackRock wants to make investing more accessible and affordable by offering investors fractional shares.</p>



<p>Fink said: <em>“You know ETF was a big revolution for the mutual fund industry and it&#8217;s really taking over the mutual fund industry and we do believe that if we can create. More tokenization of assets and securities, and that&#8217;s what Bitcoin is. It could revolutionize again, finance.”</em>&nbsp;</p>



<p>The huge bid-ask spread for cryptocurrencies, which reduces returns and raises transaction costs, is one issue that Fink noted. BlackRock wants to democratize the cryptocurrency industry and lower costs for investors, and to do this; it needs regulatory clearance for Bitcoin ETFs. Fink&#8217;s optimistic view of Bitcoin contrasts with his earlier scepticism, brought on by early contact with illegal activity. Fink views Bitcoin as a digital asset that can act as an alternative investment, much like gold, offering a buffer against inflation and currency devaluation as it becomes more widely available.</p>



<p>He added: “<em>Let&#8217;s be clear Bitcoin is an international asset it&#8217;s not based on anyone currency and so it can represent an asset that people can play as an alternative.”</em></p>



<p>Regarding the underlying technology, Fink thinks blockchain has a lot of promise to simplify transactions and do away with some financial intermediaries. Fink acknowledges the technology&#8217;s growth and potential to improve transaction processes by ensuring transparency and doing away with the need for custodians, even though it has not yet reached its full maturity.</p>



<p>The comments by Fink, founder of the largest asset manager in the world, come as a surprise to many. As recent as a few years ago, his viewpoint on crypto was arguably different and recent comments come as a 180-degree turn. In a CNCB Interview in 2021, he said, &#8220;I&#8217;m probably more on the Jamie Dimon camp,&#8221; referring to the former JPMorgan Chase CEO and Chairman who <a href="https://zycrypto.com/jpmorgan-ceo-jamie-dimon-calls-bitcoin-worthless-asserts-regulation-will-kill-it/">stated that bitcoin is &#8220;worthless.&#8221;</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/blackrock-highly-optimistic-on-spot-bitcoin-etf-approval-as-ceo-larry-fink-terms-bitcoin-an-international-asset/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>SEC Chair Gary Gensler&#8217;s Fake Resignation Rumors Jolts Crypto Markets, AI To Blame For The Rumors</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/sec-chair-gary-genslers-fake-resignation-rumors-jolts-crypto-markets-ai-to-blame-for-the-rumors/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/sec-chair-gary-genslers-fake-resignation-rumors-jolts-crypto-markets-ai-to-blame-for-the-rumors/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aliyu Pokima]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 20:37:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=82620</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/SEC-Chief-Gary-Gensler-Hints-Ethereums-Move-To-Proof-of-Stake-Might-Transform-ETH-Into-A-Security.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="SEC Chief Gary Gensler Hints Ethereum’s Move To Proof-of-Stake Might Transform ETH Into A Security" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/SEC-Chief-Gary-Gensler-Hints-Ethereums-Move-To-Proof-of-Stake-Might-Transform-ETH-Into-A-Security.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/SEC-Chief-Gary-Gensler-Hints-Ethereums-Move-To-Proof-of-Stake-Might-Transform-ETH-Into-A-Security-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/SEC-Chief-Gary-Gensler-Hints-Ethereums-Move-To-Proof-of-Stake-Might-Transform-ETH-Into-A-Security-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/SEC-Chief-Gary-Gensler-Hints-Ethereums-Move-To-Proof-of-Stake-Might-Transform-ETH-Into-A-Security-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>Gary Gensler’s time at the helm of affairs at the SEC will not be ending anytime soon following the squashing of AI-generated resignation rumors.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/SEC-Chief-Gary-Gensler-Hints-Ethereums-Move-To-Proof-of-Stake-Might-Transform-ETH-Into-A-Security.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="SEC Chief Gary Gensler Hints Ethereum’s Move To Proof-of-Stake Might Transform ETH Into A Security" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/SEC-Chief-Gary-Gensler-Hints-Ethereums-Move-To-Proof-of-Stake-Might-Transform-ETH-Into-A-Security.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/SEC-Chief-Gary-Gensler-Hints-Ethereums-Move-To-Proof-of-Stake-Might-Transform-ETH-Into-A-Security-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/SEC-Chief-Gary-Gensler-Hints-Ethereums-Move-To-Proof-of-Stake-Might-Transform-ETH-Into-A-Security-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/SEC-Chief-Gary-Gensler-Hints-Ethereums-Move-To-Proof-of-Stake-Might-Transform-ETH-Into-A-Security-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<ul>
<li>Swirling rumours of Gary Gensler’s resignation have been confirmed by the SEC to be fake.</li>



<li>Forensics indicate that the source of the rumour stems from an AI-generated text.</li>



<li>The markets took a steep dive but recalibrated itself after an official disclosure by the SEC debunking the rumour</li>
</ul>



<p>Gary Gensler’s time at the helm of affairs at the SEC will not be ending anytime soon following the squashing of AI-generated resignation rumours.</p>



<p>Crypto Twitter whipped itself into a frenzy after a news story made the rounds that SEC Chair Gary Gensler had submitted his resignation following an internal investigation. According to the report, Gensler was investigated for “alleged misconduct, and the decision to step down underscores the seriousness of the findings.” </p>



<p>Several Web 3 influencers on Twitter shared the story, with one post from Whale Chart reaching over 1.4 million views. Still reeling from the SEC designation of some virtual currencies as securities and repeated <a href="https://zycrypto.com/secs-refusal-to-approve-a-spot-bitcoin-etf-makes-it-a-failed-regulator-says-geminis-cameron-winklevoss/">denials</a> of a Bitcoin spot ETF, a large majority of the virtual assets industry welcomed the news of Gensler’s resignation with glee.</p>



<p>However, the SEC’s public relations team has denied the rumors of Gensler’s resignation, with FOX Business reporters Eleanor Terrett and Charles Gasparino poking holes in the story.</p>



<p>Digital analysis of the fake story revealed that a large chunk of the text was generated by artificial intelligence (AI). According to the AI-text detector ZeroGPT, the article in question was 96.8% generated, while other posts on the website indicated heavy AI usage.</p>



<p>In the hours following the rumors, virtual asset prices took a hit as Bitcoin (BTC) and Ethereum (ETH) lost as much as 2% of their values. However, the start of the week saw a rebound in the markets as the largest virtual currency assets recouped some of their losses heading into the holidays.</p>



<p>At the moment, the global crypto market capitalization stands at $1.19 trillion, a 1.26% plunge over the last 24 hours. The biggest winners from the SEC’s clarification appeared to be transaction volumes, as 48-hour volume inched toward $40 billion.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-not-the-first-fiasco-with-gensler"><strong>Not the first fiasco with Gensler</strong></h2>



<p>This is not the first time rumors of Gensler’s resignation are circulating in the ecosystem. In April, a similar publication made the rounds claiming the SEC Chair was about to be sacked.</p>



<p>Gary Gensler has received scathing criticisms over the SEC’s handling of the FTX fiasco and increased enforcement action over the digital asset industry, underscored by its <a href="https://zycrypto.com/binance-mounts-offensive-against-sec-crypto-lawyer-explains-why-this-is-a-huge-move/">lawsuits</a> against Ripple Labs, Coinbase, and Binance.</p>



<p>A bill titled “The SEC Stabilization Act” by U.S. lawmakers in early June sought to fire Gensler from his role as head of the SEC on grounds of tyranny.</p>



<p><em>“U.S. capital markets must be protected from a tyrannical Chairman, including the current one,”</em> said U.S. Rep. Warren Davidson. <em>“That is why I’m introducing legislation to fix the ongoing abuse of power and ensure protection that is in the best interest of the market for years to come.”</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/sec-chair-gary-genslers-fake-resignation-rumors-jolts-crypto-markets-ai-to-blame-for-the-rumors/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Is Crypto Spring Finally Here? Bitcoin Reaches One Year High As Altcoins Eye Comeback</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/is-crypto-spring-finally-here-bitcoin-reaches-one-year-high-as-altcoins-eye-comeback/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/is-crypto-spring-finally-here-bitcoin-reaches-one-year-high-as-altcoins-eye-comeback/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aaron Feuerstein]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 20:24:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XBTUSD]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=82618</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/05/Bitcoin-Bull-Markets-Show-Increasing-Traction-Among-Altcoins.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Bitcoin Bull Markets Show Increasing Traction Among Altcoins" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/05/Bitcoin-Bull-Markets-Show-Increasing-Traction-Among-Altcoins.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/05/Bitcoin-Bull-Markets-Show-Increasing-Traction-Among-Altcoins-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/05/Bitcoin-Bull-Markets-Show-Increasing-Traction-Among-Altcoins-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/05/Bitcoin-Bull-Markets-Show-Increasing-Traction-Among-Altcoins-768x448.jpg 768w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/05/Bitcoin-Bull-Markets-Show-Increasing-Traction-Among-Altcoins-610x356.jpg 610w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>On CNBC's Crypto World, Chris Ferraro, President and Chief Investment Officer at Galaxy Digital, discussed what investors should anticipate for the second half of the year. In his view, two main catalysts will determine the market in the third quarter.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/05/Bitcoin-Bull-Markets-Show-Increasing-Traction-Among-Altcoins.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Bitcoin Bull Markets Show Increasing Traction Among Altcoins" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/05/Bitcoin-Bull-Markets-Show-Increasing-Traction-Among-Altcoins.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/05/Bitcoin-Bull-Markets-Show-Increasing-Traction-Among-Altcoins-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/05/Bitcoin-Bull-Markets-Show-Increasing-Traction-Among-Altcoins-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/05/Bitcoin-Bull-Markets-Show-Increasing-Traction-Among-Altcoins-768x448.jpg 768w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/05/Bitcoin-Bull-Markets-Show-Increasing-Traction-Among-Altcoins-610x356.jpg 610w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>The price of cryptocurrencies has significantly increased in recent weeks, with <a href="https://zycrypto.com/legal-expert-reveals-the-odds-of-a-spot-bitcoin-etf-approval-in-2023/">Bitcoin</a> reaching a one-year high of $31,344, according to data from CoinMarketCap. The leading digital currency recently rose to a level last seen in June 2022, and many investors and enthusiasts believe this could herald the beginning of the long-awaited Crypto Spring.</p>



<p>On CNBC&#8217;s Crypto World, Chris Ferraro, President and Chief Investment Officer at Galaxy Digital, discussed what investors should anticipate for the year&#8217;s second half. In his view, two main catalysts will determine the market in the third quarter.</p>



<p>The prospective release of regulated access products, notably ETFs, by critical international financial institutions in the United States and the results of ongoing regulatory proceedings are two essential elements that Ferraro identifies as influencing the cryptocurrency market. He thinks the primary market driver will be accepting these easily accessed financial products.</p>



<p>Ferraro highlights the underlying success of Bitcoin, which has witnessed considerable growth and has outperformed many other assets globally and cites the excellent atmosphere around ETF applications.</p>



<p>Ferraro admits that the lack of regulatory clarity has been a troublesome theme this year when it comes to this topic. He is upbeat about the asset class and its prospects globally, though. He provides examples of other nations actively developing a legislative framework and encouraging cryptocurrency enterprises, including the UK, Europe, and Hong Kong.</p>



<p>He said: <em>“I&#8217;m less optimistic in the US and I&#8217;m less optimistic only because we really risk losing our competitive advantage. The United States has been the largest capital market and the place where capital formation happens globally for decades and the path that we have taken is in the opposite direction of that for crypto. And so capital both physical capital, intellectual capital is moving to other jurisdictions.”</em></p>



<p>Ferraro raises concerns about the possibility of the US losing its competitive edge in the cryptocurrency industry if legislative reforms proceed more slowly, causing the exodus of capital and expertise to other jurisdictions.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-the-case-for-altcoins"><strong>The Case for Altcoins</strong></h2>



<p>The rise of Bitcoin frequently sets the pace for the broader cryptocurrency market. The question is whether the Altcoin market will follow Bitcoin&#8217;s impressive year-to-date rally.</p>



<p>It is usual for other cryptocurrencies, the so-called Altcoins, to see similar upward fluctuations as Bitcoin develops momentum and garners attention. In the past, cryptocurrencies have imitated Bitcoin&#8217;s success by riding the crest of investor interest and favourable mood.</p>



<p>However, altcoin performance may not always perfectly reflect that of Bitcoin, mainly because they are not all created equal. Every cryptocurrency has a set of distinctive qualities, and market dynamics can differ greatly. While some alternative cryptocurrencies might closely follow Bitcoin&#8217;s price development, others might show independent price changes depending on their fundamentals and market demand.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/is-crypto-spring-finally-here-bitcoin-reaches-one-year-high-as-altcoins-eye-comeback/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
