<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>News Archives &#8902; ZyCrypto</title>
	<atom:link href="https://zycrypto.com/category/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://zycrypto.com/category/news/</link>
	<description>ZyCrypto Is A Cryptocurrency News Media, Focusing On Daily News, Expert Opinions, Analysis, Reviews, And So Much More.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 14:31:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/cropped-ZyCrypto-Site-Logo-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News Archives &#8902; ZyCrypto</title>
	<link>https://zycrypto.com/category/news/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Ripple Contemplates IPO As SEC Lawsuit Finally Nears End — Will It Propel XRP To $10?</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/ripple-contemplates-ipo-as-sec-lawsuit-finally-nears-end-will-it-propel-xrp-to-10/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/ripple-contemplates-ipo-as-sec-lawsuit-finally-nears-end-will-it-propel-xrp-to-10/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Newton Gitonga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 14:31:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=81761</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Legal-Expert-Has-‘No-Doubt-Ripple-Will-Win-Legal-War-Against-SEC-—-Can-It-Supercharge-XRP-To-1.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Legal Expert Has ‘No Doubt’ Ripple Will Win Legal War Against SEC — Can It Supercharge XRP To $1?" decoding="async" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Legal-Expert-Has-‘No-Doubt-Ripple-Will-Win-Legal-War-Against-SEC-—-Can-It-Supercharge-XRP-To-1.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Legal-Expert-Has-‘No-Doubt-Ripple-Will-Win-Legal-War-Against-SEC-—-Can-It-Supercharge-XRP-To-1-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Legal-Expert-Has-‘No-Doubt-Ripple-Will-Win-Legal-War-Against-SEC-—-Can-It-Supercharge-XRP-To-1-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Legal-Expert-Has-‘No-Doubt-Ripple-Will-Win-Legal-War-Against-SEC-—-Can-It-Supercharge-XRP-To-1-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>Ripple is reportedly considering an initial public offering (IPO) as its legal battle with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) approaches its conclusion.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Legal-Expert-Has-‘No-Doubt-Ripple-Will-Win-Legal-War-Against-SEC-—-Can-It-Supercharge-XRP-To-1.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Legal Expert Has ‘No Doubt’ Ripple Will Win Legal War Against SEC — Can It Supercharge XRP To $1?" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Legal-Expert-Has-‘No-Doubt-Ripple-Will-Win-Legal-War-Against-SEC-—-Can-It-Supercharge-XRP-To-1.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Legal-Expert-Has-‘No-Doubt-Ripple-Will-Win-Legal-War-Against-SEC-—-Can-It-Supercharge-XRP-To-1-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Legal-Expert-Has-‘No-Doubt-Ripple-Will-Win-Legal-War-Against-SEC-—-Can-It-Supercharge-XRP-To-1-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Legal-Expert-Has-‘No-Doubt-Ripple-Will-Win-Legal-War-Against-SEC-—-Can-It-Supercharge-XRP-To-1-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>Ripple is reportedly considering an initial public offering (IPO) as its legal battle with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) approaches its conclusion.</p>



<p>During a May 31 interview with Digital Perspectives, Linda P. Jones, a seasoned Wall Street veteran with 25 years of experience, alluded to this possibility by providing her expert analysis on the potential implications of a Ripple Initial Public Offering (IPO).</p>



<p>Jones performed an initial assessment to approximate the potential stock value of Ripple. Using the latest data from private investments firm Linqto, she determined Ripple&#8217;s current share price to be $35, which corresponds to a valuation of $5.7 billion. Linqto offers interested investors the opportunity to purchase stocks before the company goes public in an IPO. However, Jones highlighted a disparity in Linqto&#8217;s valuation, suggesting that it seems disproportionately low when considering Ripple&#8217;s historical performance and its significant holdings of <a href="https://zycrypto.com/a-new-boom-for-xrp-record-breaking-address-activity-indicates-upturn-ahead-to-1-xrp-price/">XRP</a>.</p>



<p>Drawing attention to Ripple&#8217;s extensive XRP reserves, Jones emphasized that the 42 billion XRP tokens held in escrow are currently valued at $21 billion, assuming a market rate of $0.50 per token. In her view, this valuation alone exceeds Ripple&#8217;s current market value by four times, indicating a significant undervaluation and suggesting that Ripple&#8217;s true worth could be considerably higher.</p>



<p>The pundit further drew a comparison to Coinbase&#8217;s successful IPO, speculating that Ripple&#8217;s valuation could reach $107 billion, 20 times its current value, meaning $600 per share.</p>



<p>According to her, if the XRP lawsuit concludes favourably and the token regains its previous high of $3.59, the XRP escrow value could surge to $150 billion, potentially driving Ripple&#8217;s stock price even higher. She further expressed her belief in Ripple’s potential to achieve a half-trillion-dollar valuation, considering the successes of companies like Nvidia and Apple.</p>



<p>Ripple has previously expressed its desire to go public. In May 2022, CEO Brad Garlinghouse stated during a conference in Davos that Ripple would explore the possibility of an initial public offering (IPO) once the ongoing lawsuit with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) reached its conclusion. Recently, he expressed his belief in the case <a href="https://zycrypto.com/xrp-lawsuit-ripple-boss-confident-groundbreaking-verdict-is-coming-in-weeks-after-hinman-speech-docs-win/">concluding in weeks</a>.</p>



<p>Meanwhile, according to Eleanor Terrett, a Fox Business reporter, the blockchain firm reportedly conducted a successful private &#8220;roadshow&#8221; in April to meet with potential investors ahead of its IPO. Terrett tweeted on Thursday that the event was attended by numerous respected institutional investment firms on Wall Street, indicating strong interest in Ripple&#8217;s offering.</p>



<p>That said, as the lawsuit nears its end, a win for Ripple could have far-reaching implications for the firm and the broader cryptocurrency market. It could also enable the company to go public, increasing its popularity and potentially pushing the value of XRP to the long-awaited milestone of $10.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/ripple-contemplates-ipo-as-sec-lawsuit-finally-nears-end-will-it-propel-xrp-to-10/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cryptojacking Volumes On The Rise — Report</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/cryptojacking-volumes-on-the-rise-report/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/cryptojacking-volumes-on-the-rise-report/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Isa Nsereko]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 14:14:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=81757</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/Nvidia-Hack-How-Lapsus-Demands-May-Strangely-Benefit-Crypto-Miners.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Nvidia Hack: How Lapsus$ Demands May Strangely Benefit Crypto Miners" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/Nvidia-Hack-How-Lapsus-Demands-May-Strangely-Benefit-Crypto-Miners.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/Nvidia-Hack-How-Lapsus-Demands-May-Strangely-Benefit-Crypto-Miners-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/Nvidia-Hack-How-Lapsus-Demands-May-Strangely-Benefit-Crypto-Miners-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/Nvidia-Hack-How-Lapsus-Demands-May-Strangely-Benefit-Crypto-Miners-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>According to the “2023 SonicWall Cyber Threat Report”, 139.3 million cryptojacking attempts were recorded in 2022 compared to 97.1 million in 2021, a 43% year-over-year increase. The observed attack volumes exceeded the 100-million mark for the first time. The report stated that cryptojacking volume increased in North America, Asia, and Europe. However, the Latin America [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/Nvidia-Hack-How-Lapsus-Demands-May-Strangely-Benefit-Crypto-Miners.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Nvidia Hack: How Lapsus$ Demands May Strangely Benefit Crypto Miners" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/Nvidia-Hack-How-Lapsus-Demands-May-Strangely-Benefit-Crypto-Miners.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/Nvidia-Hack-How-Lapsus-Demands-May-Strangely-Benefit-Crypto-Miners-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/Nvidia-Hack-How-Lapsus-Demands-May-Strangely-Benefit-Crypto-Miners-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/Nvidia-Hack-How-Lapsus-Demands-May-Strangely-Benefit-Crypto-Miners-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>According to the “2023 SonicWall Cyber Threat Report”, 139.3 million cryptojacking attempts were recorded in 2022 compared to 97.1 million in 2021, a 43% year-over-year increase. The observed attack volumes exceeded the 100-million mark for the first time. The report stated that cryptojacking volume increased in North America, Asia, and Europe. However, the Latin America region recorded a 66% drop year-over-year.</p>



<p>Despite skyrocketing attack volumes in Europe, the United States (U.S.) remained the country with the highest volume with cryptojacking attempts rising 41% year over year. Retail had the highest total cryptojacking attack volumes by industry, followed by Education, Finance, Healthcare, and Government.</p>



<p>In cryptojacking, attackers gain access to the victim’s computer or mobile device’s computing power and use them for cryptocurrency mining without the knowledge and authorization of the victim.</p>



<p>Cryptojacking attacks have occurred across various industries. Launched in 2017, Coinhive allowed website owners to embed JavaScript code onto their websites, thereby using the website visitor&#8217;s computer to mine the cryptocurrency, Monero.</p>



<p>In another cryptojacking incident, researchers at the cloud monitoring and defence firm RedLock reported that Tesla’s cloud system had been cryptojacked in February 2018 after hackers exploited a password vulnerability to mine cryptocurrency. Tesla said that the data exposure was minimal and quickly addressed the vulnerability.</p>



<p>In 2018, a cryptojacking code was discovered on the Los Angeles Times Homicide Report page. The code used minimal computing power such that users could not easily detect when their devices were used to mine the Monero cryptocurrency.</p>



<p>In 2018, a European water utility control system was cryptojacked and used to generate the Monero cryptocurrency.</p>



<p>As per the 2022 SonicWall’s Threat Mindset survey, 66% of organizations were more concerned about cyberattacks in 2022 than in previous years. 29% of organizations reported that they have roughly the same amount of concern about attacks as they did in 2021, with only 5% reporting as being less concerned.</p>



<p>Respondents ranked Ransomware (91%) as the top cyber attack concern. Other concerns by the respondents were; Phishing and spear-phishing (76%), Encrypted malware (66%), File-less attacks (39%), Memory-based malware (24%), Cryptojacking (23%), IoT malware (22%), and Side-channel attacks (18%).</p>



<p>Sonicwall recommends the following to detect and prevent cryptojacking in your organization: Keeping computers and web browsers up to date, using reputable anti-malware software, regularly updating antivirus and security software on all devices, and educating users to be cautious when opening emails and attachments.</p>



<p>Further recommendations from SonicWall to detect cryptojacking include preventing unauthorized downloads, using ad blockers, using zero-day protection, Implementing strong authentication, protecting cloud resources, and using anti-bot protection to help prevent malware from spreading to a computer or network.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/cryptojacking-volumes-on-the-rise-report/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Scammers Hack OpenAI CTO’s Twitter Account to Promote Crypto Scam</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/scammers-hack-openai-ctos-twitter-account-to-promote-crypto-scam/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/scammers-hack-openai-ctos-twitter-account-to-promote-crypto-scam/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Newton Gitonga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 13:55:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Twitter]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=81753</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/Scammers-Impersonating-Elon-Musk-Make-Away-With-Millions-Worth-Of-Dogecoin.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Scammers Impersonating Elon Musk Make Away With Millions&#039; Worth Of Dogecoin" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/Scammers-Impersonating-Elon-Musk-Make-Away-With-Millions-Worth-Of-Dogecoin.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/Scammers-Impersonating-Elon-Musk-Make-Away-With-Millions-Worth-Of-Dogecoin-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/Scammers-Impersonating-Elon-Musk-Make-Away-With-Millions-Worth-Of-Dogecoin-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/Scammers-Impersonating-Elon-Musk-Make-Away-With-Millions-Worth-Of-Dogecoin-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>Scammers hijacked the Twitter account of OpenAI CTO Mira Murati to promote a crypto scam. The account was found promoting a fake cryptocurrency airdrop claimed to be conducted by OpenAI, the company behind the popular AI tool, ChatGPT. A phishing link to a scam airdrop of the purported OPENAI token was live on the account [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/Scammers-Impersonating-Elon-Musk-Make-Away-With-Millions-Worth-Of-Dogecoin.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Scammers Impersonating Elon Musk Make Away With Millions&#039; Worth Of Dogecoin" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/Scammers-Impersonating-Elon-Musk-Make-Away-With-Millions-Worth-Of-Dogecoin.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/Scammers-Impersonating-Elon-Musk-Make-Away-With-Millions-Worth-Of-Dogecoin-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/Scammers-Impersonating-Elon-Musk-Make-Away-With-Millions-Worth-Of-Dogecoin-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/Scammers-Impersonating-Elon-Musk-Make-Away-With-Millions-Worth-Of-Dogecoin-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>Scammers hijacked the Twitter account of OpenAI CTO Mira Murati to promote a crypto scam. The account was found promoting a fake cryptocurrency airdrop claimed to be conducted by OpenAI, the company behind the popular AI tool, ChatGPT.</p>



<p>A phishing link to a scam airdrop of the purported OPENAI token was live on the account for about an hour before it was taken down. The verified Twitter account asked its over 126,000 followers to send ETH to a designated address in exchange for the non-existent OPENAI token.</p>



<p>Indeed, there is a crypto token known as OpenAI ERC, but it is a token linked to a free-to-use telegram bot that provides users access to ChatGTP and DALL-E via chat commands. It is not linked to OpenAI, the company that created ChatGPT.</p>



<p>As expected, the tweet got significant traction, with almost 80,000 views and 83 retweets, while no one was allowed to comment. Blockchain security firm, Beosin told Cointelegraph that the hackers used a crypto wallet-draining kit that could drain non-fungible tokens (NFTs) and ERC-20 tokens from any wallet that authorizes it.</p>



<p>Fortunately, there was no evidence that any of her followers fell for the scam at the point of recovering the account, but it is hard to tell since no comments were allowed for any victim to warn others.</p>



<p>This is just one of many Twitter hack incidents this year in which hackers used the accounts of prominent people with large followings to promote their crypto scams. The governor of Madhya Pradesh, an Indian state, suffered a similar attack on his official Twitter account earlier this year, alongside other top public figures, including Ripple CEO Brad Garlinghouse.</p>



<p>It appears such attacks usually target communities of projects that are either popular or bullish. Most attacks initially targeted the Ripple community at the beginning of the year when XRP rallied to new levels, and now OpenAI since ChatGPT has become a household name.</p>



<p>To avoid being a victim, take your time to verify from reliable sources before engaging in any such offers, ideally published on official websites. Also, try to report suspicious offers like this one, as some accounts did on Twitter, which helped to get the attention of the account owner, who could have been the victim of a sim swap attack.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/scammers-hack-openai-ctos-twitter-account-to-promote-crypto-scam/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto.com Secures “Major” Operational License in Singapore</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/crypto-com-secures-major-operational-license-in-singapore/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/crypto-com-secures-major-operational-license-in-singapore/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ponvang Bulus]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 13:28:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto.com]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Singapore]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=81751</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/Crypto.coms-CRO-Becomes-The-New-SHIB-—-Gains-x4-Of-Its-Value-In-Record-Time.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Crypto.com’s CRO Becomes The New SHIB — Gains x4 Of Its Value In Record Time" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/Crypto.coms-CRO-Becomes-The-New-SHIB-—-Gains-x4-Of-Its-Value-In-Record-Time.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/Crypto.coms-CRO-Becomes-The-New-SHIB-—-Gains-x4-Of-Its-Value-In-Record-Time-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/Crypto.coms-CRO-Becomes-The-New-SHIB-—-Gains-x4-Of-Its-Value-In-Record-Time-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/Crypto.coms-CRO-Becomes-The-New-SHIB-—-Gains-x4-Of-Its-Value-In-Record-Time-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>Top crypto trading platform Crypto.com has received what it describes as a major Payment Institution (MPI) License from the Monetary Authority of Singapore. In a blog post on 1 June, the exchange said the license is for Digital Payment Token (DPT) services. The platform will now continue to extend its Digital Payment Token (DPT) services [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/Crypto.coms-CRO-Becomes-The-New-SHIB-—-Gains-x4-Of-Its-Value-In-Record-Time.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Crypto.com’s CRO Becomes The New SHIB — Gains x4 Of Its Value In Record Time" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/Crypto.coms-CRO-Becomes-The-New-SHIB-—-Gains-x4-Of-Its-Value-In-Record-Time.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/Crypto.coms-CRO-Becomes-The-New-SHIB-—-Gains-x4-Of-Its-Value-In-Record-Time-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/Crypto.coms-CRO-Becomes-The-New-SHIB-—-Gains-x4-Of-Its-Value-In-Record-Time-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/Crypto.coms-CRO-Becomes-The-New-SHIB-—-Gains-x4-Of-Its-Value-In-Record-Time-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>Top crypto trading platform Crypto.com has received what it describes as a major Payment Institution (MPI) License from the Monetary Authority of Singapore. In a blog post on 1 June, the exchange said the license is for Digital Payment Token (DPT) services.</p>



<p>The platform will now continue to extend its Digital Payment Token (DPT) services to customers in Singapore, where it has its global headquarters.</p>



<p><em>“The Monetary Authority of Singapore is recognized globally as a regulator that ensures responsible innovation of the digital assets sector,” said Kris Marszalek, CEO of Crypto.com.</em></p>



<p><em>“We are proud to receive the license from a regulator prioritising consumer protection, safety, and security. We look forward to continuing to collaborate with MAS and leading at the forefront of crypto in our home market of Singapore,” he added.</em></p>



<p>Crypto.com is a crypto exchange known for its strict compliance with the regulatory standards of the countries where it operates. It has over 80 million users worldwide, who enjoy the high security and privacy that the platform provides.</p>



<p>The company’s primary aim is to make financial services available to all by facilitating crypto adoption, and this license is a big step towards achieving this. MAS issued an in-principle or preliminary license in June last year but is giving a full license to the crypto giant this time.</p>



<p>Indeed, Singapore has been a crypto hub over the years, and this license further demonstrates its commitment to the industry.</p>



<p><em>“Singapore continues to be a hub for blockchain and fintech innovation. The Major Payment Institution license underscores our ongoing commitment to build with the Web3 community in Singapore,” said Chin Tah Ang, General Manager of Singapore of Crypto.com.</em></p>



<p>Crypto.com has a number of other licenses it secured before now. It had in November 2022 obtained a Major Payment Institution license for e-money issuance, account issuance, cross border and domestic money transfer services from the Monetary Authority of Singapore.</p>



<p>Similarly, the Autorité des marchés financiers (AMF) in France licensed the company as a Digital Asset Service Provider (DASP) in September 2022. It also has business licenses from the UK Financial Conduct Authority (FCA) and the Dubai Virtual Assets Regulatory Authority (VARA), to name a few.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/crypto-com-secures-major-operational-license-in-singapore/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Russia Drops State-Backed Crypto Exchange Plans, Rolls Out New Regulatory Model For Industry</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/russia-drops-state-backed-crypto-exchange-plans-rolls-out-new-regulatory-model-for-industry/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/russia-drops-state-backed-crypto-exchange-plans-rolls-out-new-regulatory-model-for-industry/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aliyu Pokima]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 19:09:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Russia]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=81748</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/Putin-Not-Going-To-Ban-Bitcoin-In-Russia-As-He-Supports-Proposal-To-Regulate-Crypto-Mining.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Putin &#039;Not Going To Ban Bitcoin In Russia&#039; As He Supports Proposal To Regulate Crypto Mining" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/Putin-Not-Going-To-Ban-Bitcoin-In-Russia-As-He-Supports-Proposal-To-Regulate-Crypto-Mining.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/Putin-Not-Going-To-Ban-Bitcoin-In-Russia-As-He-Supports-Proposal-To-Regulate-Crypto-Mining-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/Putin-Not-Going-To-Ban-Bitcoin-In-Russia-As-He-Supports-Proposal-To-Regulate-Crypto-Mining-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/Putin-Not-Going-To-Ban-Bitcoin-In-Russia-As-He-Supports-Proposal-To-Regulate-Crypto-Mining-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>Russia has long been criticized for its mixed signals towards digital assets. However, this could change soon as the news of backing private exchanges marks a new dawn for the country’s relationship with cryptocurrencies.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/Putin-Not-Going-To-Ban-Bitcoin-In-Russia-As-He-Supports-Proposal-To-Regulate-Crypto-Mining.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Putin &#039;Not Going To Ban Bitcoin In Russia&#039; As He Supports Proposal To Regulate Crypto Mining" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/Putin-Not-Going-To-Ban-Bitcoin-In-Russia-As-He-Supports-Proposal-To-Regulate-Crypto-Mining.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/Putin-Not-Going-To-Ban-Bitcoin-In-Russia-As-He-Supports-Proposal-To-Regulate-Crypto-Mining-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/Putin-Not-Going-To-Ban-Bitcoin-In-Russia-As-He-Supports-Proposal-To-Regulate-Crypto-Mining-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/Putin-Not-Going-To-Ban-Bitcoin-In-Russia-As-He-Supports-Proposal-To-Regulate-Crypto-Mining-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<ul>
<li>Russia terminates plans to launch a state-owned digital asset exchange with plans to back private investors.</li>



<li>According to authorities, the rules will be a model for the entire industry to facilitate cross-border payments amongst others.</li>



<li>Experts weigh in on the Kremlin’s stance on digital assets amid financial restrictions by the EU and other international organizations.&nbsp;</li>
</ul>



<p>Russia has long been criticized for its mixed signals towards digital assets. However, this could change soon as the news of backing private exchanges marks a new dawn for the country’s relationship with cryptocurrencies.</p>



<p>Russian lawmakers plan to cease the formation of government-owned cryptocurrency exchanges with talks of introducing a new regulation template for private firms. According to <a href="https://twitter.com/wublockchain/status/1663188043178844162?s=46&amp;t=sCvh3f3rMDfXyJcf1y1Eyg">reports</a>, the country will move forward with a broad regulatory framework to be monitored by the Central Bank.</p>



<p>Anatoly Aksakov, the head of the lower House Committee on Financial Markets, stated that private firms would be encouraged to facilitate cross-border payments subject to certain restrictions that the government will impose.</p>



<p>“<em>Instead of creating one national crypto exchange, it is planned to establish rules for the establishment and operation of such infrastructures,” </em>he added.&nbsp;</p>



<p>Throwing more light on the government’s position, Ivan Chebeskov, the Director of Financial Policy in the Ministry of Finance, stated that “<em>The Ministry did not support the establishment of one national crypto-exchange. The idea, instead, is to legally regulate the possibility of creating such sites by business.”</em></p>



<p>Industry experts have hailed the move describing it as a step in the right direction. Olieg Ogienko, the founder of BitRiver, said that the move will help cushion the risk of sanctions and cyber attacks on crypto infrastructure and eliminate monopolies. Similarly, GIS Mining boss Ivan Gostev added,</p>



<p>“<em>It would allow for more competitive and innovative companies to develop</em>.”</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-russia-s-move-to-digital-assets"><strong>Russia&#8217;s move to digital assets</strong></h2>



<p>Mixed signals have plagued Russia’s relationship with cryptocurrencies for years, beginning with the government’s desire for total fiscal control. Last year, the Bank of Russia announced plans for an outright ban of Bitcoin payments before the Ministry of Finance proposed a deal for crypto regulation.</p>



<p>Months later, President Vladimir Putin signed a law prohibiting digital asset payments citing risk and economic sabotage. Sanctions imposed on Russia due to the Ukraine invasion led to the country <a href="https://zycrypto.com/russia-turns-to-stablecoins-in-droves-as-sanctions-bite-even-harder/">exploring</a> stablecoins to bypass financial restrictions. </p>



<p>This new move will strengthen the country’s position as a virtual currency-friendly country. In 2020, Russia was ranked #2 in terms of digital asset adoption, with 12% of the country&#8217;s population owning crypto.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/russia-drops-state-backed-crypto-exchange-plans-rolls-out-new-regulatory-model-for-industry/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>“A One Way Trip”- Ethereum NFTs Can Be Moved To Bitcoin, Developers Reveal</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/a-one-way-trip-ethereum-nfts-can-be-moved-to-bitcoin-developers-reveal/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/a-one-way-trip-ethereum-nfts-can-be-moved-to-bitcoin-developers-reveal/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aliyu Pokima]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 18:55:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XBTUSD]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=81740</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ordinals-Attract-Ethereum-Devs-To-Bitcoin-As-Projects-Mass-Adoption-Skyrockets.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Ordinals Attract Ethereum Devs To Bitcoin As Project’s Mass Adoption Skyrockets" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ordinals-Attract-Ethereum-Devs-To-Bitcoin-As-Projects-Mass-Adoption-Skyrockets.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ordinals-Attract-Ethereum-Devs-To-Bitcoin-As-Projects-Mass-Adoption-Skyrockets-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ordinals-Attract-Ethereum-Devs-To-Bitcoin-As-Projects-Mass-Adoption-Skyrockets-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ordinals-Attract-Ethereum-Devs-To-Bitcoin-As-Projects-Mass-Adoption-Skyrockets-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>Six months after its launch and with over 10 million inscriptions, Ordinals is paving the way for top developers looking to integrate the Bitcoin (BTC) ecosystem with the cryptoverse.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ordinals-Attract-Ethereum-Devs-To-Bitcoin-As-Projects-Mass-Adoption-Skyrockets.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Ordinals Attract Ethereum Devs To Bitcoin As Project’s Mass Adoption Skyrockets" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ordinals-Attract-Ethereum-Devs-To-Bitcoin-As-Projects-Mass-Adoption-Skyrockets.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ordinals-Attract-Ethereum-Devs-To-Bitcoin-As-Projects-Mass-Adoption-Skyrockets-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ordinals-Attract-Ethereum-Devs-To-Bitcoin-As-Projects-Mass-Adoption-Skyrockets-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ordinals-Attract-Ethereum-Devs-To-Bitcoin-As-Projects-Mass-Adoption-Skyrockets-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<ul>
<li>Bitcoin Miladys rolls out a “bridge” that lets Ethereum NFT users migrate to the Bitcoin Network through Ordinals.&nbsp;</li>



<li>The process automatically destroys the original NFT on Ethereum when transferred, earning the tag “<em>a one-way trip”&nbsp;</em></li>



<li>The move puts BTC enthusiasts in a frenzy as they count on the benefits of having sought-after Ethereum NFTs on their network.&nbsp;</li>
</ul>



<p>Six months after its launch and with over 10 million inscriptions, Ordinals is paving the way for top developers looking to integrate the Bitcoin (BTC) ecosystem with the cryptoverse.</p>



<p>The developers behind Bitcoin Miladys have announced the possibility of Ethereum non-fungible token (NFT) holders transferring their assets to the Bitcoin Network. Still, there is a little caveat, the Ethereum copy gets permanently destroyed.</p>



<p>The project was launched in partnership with Xverse Bitcoin Wallet, and Ordinals Market leverages a burn and mint process to move assets between both networks. The BRC- 721E token standard bridge, as it is fondly called, sends the Ethereum NFTs to a burn address, making it completely inaccessible to the holder after it is destroyed. The token is then re-created on Bitcoin through Ordinals. </p>



<p>Several cross-chain bridges act as escrow platforms that hold user tokens even after minting secondary tokens on another network. If the user wants to reclaim the primary asset in the future, the secondary asset is burned.</p>



<p>Although more beneficial to users, this escrow process is not compatible with the BRC-721E process as it is only a one-way trip. This process can lead to issues for NFT holders, including loss of assets if not implemented properly. A similar issue occurred earlier this year when a Bored Ape Yacht Club (BAYC) holder burned his NFT on Ethereum and tried to mint it on Bitcoin. </p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-community-laud-btc-ordinals-development"><strong>Community laud BTC Ordinals&#8217; development</strong></h2>



<p>Earlier this year, there were endless debates on the utilities of Ordinals to the Bitcoin Network. While many saw it as an opportunity to bolster an upward momentum, others felt the network should be left as it was without “<em>worthless tokens.”</em></p>



<p>Recent events may have proved doubters wrong as users now BTC Ordinals have <a href="https://zycrypto.com/ordinals-attract-ethereum-devs-to-bitcoin-as-projects-mass-adoption-skyrockets/">ignited</a> forces even outside the network to create tools for its expansion. The BRC-721E projects can swing millions into the Bitcoin ecosystem and place it in direct competition with Ethereum and Solana.</p>



<p>The project which enables immutable and verified Ethereum NFTs to Bitcoin has been described as “<em>the turning point.” </em>The project works with all Ethereum NFTs and is not limited to Miladys, according to the Ordinal Market page.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/a-one-way-trip-ethereum-nfts-can-be-moved-to-bitcoin-developers-reveal/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Apple Set To Launch Mixed Reality Headset: Here’s What We Know So Far And The Battle With Meta</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/apple-set-to-launch-mixed-reality-headset-heres-what-we-know-so-far-and-the-battle-with-meta/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/apple-set-to-launch-mixed-reality-headset-heres-what-we-know-so-far-and-the-battle-with-meta/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aliyu Pokima]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 18:51:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Apple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[META]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=81737</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Apple-Set-To-Launch-Mixed-Reality-Headset-Heres-What-We-Know-So-Far-And-The-Battle-With-Meta.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Apple Set To Launch Mixed Reality Headset: Here’s What We Know So Far And The Battle With Meta" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Apple-Set-To-Launch-Mixed-Reality-Headset-Heres-What-We-Know-So-Far-And-The-Battle-With-Meta.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Apple-Set-To-Launch-Mixed-Reality-Headset-Heres-What-We-Know-So-Far-And-The-Battle-With-Meta-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Apple-Set-To-Launch-Mixed-Reality-Headset-Heres-What-We-Know-So-Far-And-The-Battle-With-Meta-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Apple-Set-To-Launch-Mixed-Reality-Headset-Heres-What-We-Know-So-Far-And-The-Battle-With-Meta-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>The battle for the ideal metaverse platform enters top gear, with Meta and Apple leading the quest to create the perfect augmented reality experience despite a few roadblocks.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Apple-Set-To-Launch-Mixed-Reality-Headset-Heres-What-We-Know-So-Far-And-The-Battle-With-Meta.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Apple Set To Launch Mixed Reality Headset: Here’s What We Know So Far And The Battle With Meta" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Apple-Set-To-Launch-Mixed-Reality-Headset-Heres-What-We-Know-So-Far-And-The-Battle-With-Meta.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Apple-Set-To-Launch-Mixed-Reality-Headset-Heres-What-We-Know-So-Far-And-The-Battle-With-Meta-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Apple-Set-To-Launch-Mixed-Reality-Headset-Heres-What-We-Know-So-Far-And-The-Battle-With-Meta-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Apple-Set-To-Launch-Mixed-Reality-Headset-Heres-What-We-Know-So-Far-And-The-Battle-With-Meta-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<ul>
<li>Apple will kick off its metaverse push with a mixed-reality headset. </li>



<li>The technology giant is developing RealityOs software to complement its high-end hardware in creating the perfect metaverse solution.&nbsp;</li>



<li>Meta is on its way to roll out a cheaper headset with more compatibility (Quest 3), setting the stage for a big tech rivalry. </li>
</ul>



<p>The battle for the ideal metaverse platform enters top gear, with Meta and Apple leading the quest to create the perfect augmented reality experience despite a few roadblocks.</p>



<p>According to a Bloomberg <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-03-29/when-is-wwdc-2023-when-will-apple-announce-mixed-reality-headset-june-5">report</a>, Apple will launch its first virtual reality headset on June 5 at the company’s WWDC conference. The much-anticipated headset is termed a mixed reality headset because it offers both argument reality (AR) and virtual reality (VR) functionalities, although AR-specific hardware will be released subsequently.</p>



<p>Apple began planning its foray into the metaverse in 2015 and is currently on track to release multiple gaming experiences for its users. Based on its previous trademark filings, the high-end headset is reportedly called the Reality Pro or Reality One. </p>



<p>The Apple headset is expected to have two Micro OLED screens with a detailed 8K resolution which internal cameras will boost. Apple plans to erase criticisms heaped on Metaverse platforms for spending billions of dollars while delivering poor quality graphics and overall user experience.</p>



<p>The team also deployed the popular M2 processor from the company’s MacBook, including sensors that can recreate and detect user leg movements, a feature its rival Meta is yet to get a hang on. Furthermore, retina scanners will be incorporated for extra biometric security during logins and will be used for payments.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-meta-vs-apple-battle-for-the-metaverse"><strong>Meta vs Apple: Battle for the metaverse</strong></h2>



<p>Meta has more metaverse buzz around it, with its founder Mark Zuckerberg backing the creation despite losses encountered so far. Apple’s Tim Cook is very bullish on Augmented Reality, stressing the use cases it can bring to the real world.</p>



<p>“<em>I think AR is a profound technology that will affect everything. Imagine suddenly being able to teach with AR and demonstrate things that way. Or medically, and so on. Like I said, we are going to look back and think about how we once lived without AR,” </em>he stated.&nbsp;</p>



<p>Analyzing the business model of both companies, one can predict that Meta will offer more interoperability than Apple because of the former’s “wall garden” approach to products. Zuckerberg has also <a href="https://zycrypto.com/mark-zuckerberg-reiterates-metas-plan-for-an-open-interoperable-metaverse-heres-how/">noted</a> that an “<em>open and interoperable metaverse is better for everyone.”</em></p>



<p>Most observers expect Apple to beat Meta in terms of graphics and user interaction, a feature that Meta has struggled with in past releases. Meta has announced the launch of Quest 3, a cheaper headset many view as a direct response to Apple’s planned release.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/apple-set-to-launch-mixed-reality-headset-heres-what-we-know-so-far-and-the-battle-with-meta/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Coinbase Announces Launch Of BTC And ETH Futures On Its Derivatives Exchange</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/coinbase-announces-launch-of-btc-and-eth-futures-on-its-derivatives-exchange/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/coinbase-announces-launch-of-btc-and-eth-futures-on-its-derivatives-exchange/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aliyu Pokima]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 22:56:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=81734</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/04/BitMEX-Debuts-Ethereum-Quanto-Futures-With-Fixed-Bitcoin-BTC-Multiplier.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="BitMEX Debuts Ethereum Quanto Futures With Fixed Bitcoin (BTC) Multiplier" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/04/BitMEX-Debuts-Ethereum-Quanto-Futures-With-Fixed-Bitcoin-BTC-Multiplier.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/04/BitMEX-Debuts-Ethereum-Quanto-Futures-With-Fixed-Bitcoin-BTC-Multiplier-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/04/BitMEX-Debuts-Ethereum-Quanto-Futures-With-Fixed-Bitcoin-BTC-Multiplier-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/04/BitMEX-Debuts-Ethereum-Quanto-Futures-With-Fixed-Bitcoin-BTC-Multiplier-768x448.jpg 768w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/04/BitMEX-Debuts-Ethereum-Quanto-Futures-With-Fixed-Bitcoin-BTC-Multiplier-610x356.jpg 610w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>The United States leading digital asset Coinbase has announced its plans to launch institutional Bitcoin (BTC) and Ethereum (ETH) futures trading contracts on its derivatives exchange on June 5.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/04/BitMEX-Debuts-Ethereum-Quanto-Futures-With-Fixed-Bitcoin-BTC-Multiplier.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="BitMEX Debuts Ethereum Quanto Futures With Fixed Bitcoin (BTC) Multiplier" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/04/BitMEX-Debuts-Ethereum-Quanto-Futures-With-Fixed-Bitcoin-BTC-Multiplier.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/04/BitMEX-Debuts-Ethereum-Quanto-Futures-With-Fixed-Bitcoin-BTC-Multiplier-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/04/BitMEX-Debuts-Ethereum-Quanto-Futures-With-Fixed-Bitcoin-BTC-Multiplier-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/04/BitMEX-Debuts-Ethereum-Quanto-Futures-With-Fixed-Bitcoin-BTC-Multiplier-768x448.jpg 768w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/04/BitMEX-Debuts-Ethereum-Quanto-Futures-With-Fixed-Bitcoin-BTC-Multiplier-610x356.jpg 610w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<ul>
<li>Coinbase has unveiled plans to introduce Bitcoin and Ethereum futures contracts for institutional investors on June 5.&nbsp;</li>



<li>The institutional-sized futures contracts will be sized at 10 ETH and 1 BTC to reduce risk in the market.&nbsp;</li>



<li>Coinbase’s push for regulatory clarity takes center stage around crypto circles as the exchange seeks to release more products for users.&nbsp;</li>
</ul>



<p>The United States leading digital asset Coinbase has announced its plans to launch institutional Bitcoin (BTC) and Ethereum (ETH) futures trading contracts on its derivatives exchange on June 5.</p>



<p>The product, which will <a href="https://www.coinbase.com/blog/coinbase-derivatives-exchange-will-launch-institutional-sized-bitcoin-and">launch</a> on the Commodity and  Futures Trading Commission’s (CFTC) regulated derivatives exchange, will be sized at 1BTC and 10 ETH to help investors manage exposures. In its release, the exchange noted that this service would help investors “<em>target attractive returns” </em>for lower fees.</p>



<p>Coinbase Bitcoin (BTI) and Coinbase Ethereum (ETI) futures contracts will both be available to investors through regulated futures commission merchants (FCMs) and other associated brokers. The exchange also announced additional incentive programs for institutions that participate in the contracts.</p>



<p>The future trading contracts were borne out of popular demand as a result of its past products. The exchange introduced nano Bitcoin (BT) and Ethereum (ET) contracts and recorded a massive spike in institutional demand for advanced derivatives products.&nbsp;</p>



<p>The company reiterated its commitment to creating a secure and transparent trading system with the necessary tools to make participants successful.&nbsp;</p>



<p>”<em>Introducing institutional-sized contracts marks another milestone in our ongoing mission to provide accessible and cutting-edge financial instruments to market participants and underscores our dedication to solutions tailored to the needs of institutional clients,” </em>the statement reads.</p>



<p>On May 2, Coinbase announced its plans to open a derivatives exchange in Bermuda in its international expansion plan and will let users trade perpetual future contracts with 5X leverage. Per the announcement, all trades will be settled in USDC stablecoin as it seeks to balance and value for participants.&nbsp;</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-coinbase-march-on-amid-regulatory-uncertainty">Coinbase march on amid regulatory uncertainty</h2>



<p>Coinbase has restated its commitment to comply with regulatory practices across jurisdictions as it continues its international expansion. The announcement of futures trading contracts comes with the exchange seeking regulatory clarity from the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC).&nbsp;</p>



<p>The Commission in its reply to Coinbase&#8217;s writ of mandamus stated that the rulemaking process could stretch into many years but will continue to employ enforcement actions to bring clarity to the sector. The SEC also added that public statements do not constitute guidance or policy statements.&nbsp;</p>



<p>While regulations in the United States remain unclear, Coinbase continues its global push as it seeks to fight for a higher market share with competitors.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/coinbase-announces-launch-of-btc-and-eth-futures-on-its-derivatives-exchange/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Russian Bank Rosbank Pilots Cross-Border Cryptocurrency Transactions with Corporate and Private Clients</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/russian-bank-rosbank-pilots-cross-border-cryptocurrency-transactions-with-corporate-and-private-clients/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/russian-bank-rosbank-pilots-cross-border-cryptocurrency-transactions-with-corporate-and-private-clients/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Marco Tulio]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 21:32:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Russia]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=81722</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Russian-Bank-Rosbank-Pilots-Cross-Border-Cryptocurrency-Transactions-with-Corporate-and-Private-Clients.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Russian Bank Rosbank Pilots Cross-Border Cryptocurrency Transactions with Corporate and Private Clients" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Russian-Bank-Rosbank-Pilots-Cross-Border-Cryptocurrency-Transactions-with-Corporate-and-Private-Clients.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Russian-Bank-Rosbank-Pilots-Cross-Border-Cryptocurrency-Transactions-with-Corporate-and-Private-Clients-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Russian-Bank-Rosbank-Pilots-Cross-Border-Cryptocurrency-Transactions-with-Corporate-and-Private-Clients-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Russian-Bank-Rosbank-Pilots-Cross-Border-Cryptocurrency-Transactions-with-Corporate-and-Private-Clients-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>The Russian bank Rosbank has become the first biggest bank in the country to launch cross-border cryptocurrency payments, with the help of an intermediary fintech to carry out the transactions.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Russian-Bank-Rosbank-Pilots-Cross-Border-Cryptocurrency-Transactions-with-Corporate-and-Private-Clients.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Russian Bank Rosbank Pilots Cross-Border Cryptocurrency Transactions with Corporate and Private Clients" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Russian-Bank-Rosbank-Pilots-Cross-Border-Cryptocurrency-Transactions-with-Corporate-and-Private-Clients.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Russian-Bank-Rosbank-Pilots-Cross-Border-Cryptocurrency-Transactions-with-Corporate-and-Private-Clients-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Russian-Bank-Rosbank-Pilots-Cross-Border-Cryptocurrency-Transactions-with-Corporate-and-Private-Clients-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Russian-Bank-Rosbank-Pilots-Cross-Border-Cryptocurrency-Transactions-with-Corporate-and-Private-Clients-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>The Russian bank Rosbank has become the first <a href="https://zycrypto.com/russian-banking-giant-sber-adds-ethereum-and-metamask-support/">biggest bank</a> in the country to launch cross-border cryptocurrency payments, with the help of an intermediary fintech to carry out the transactions.</p>



<p>According to Vedomosti, a representative of Rosbank it was stated that the bank is already conducting tests with corporate and private clients. The new solution allows the purchase of cryptocurrencies abroad using the funds of the importer, which are then transferred to the foreign provider.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-rosbank-joins-forces-with-b-crypto-to-launch-new-services"><strong>Rosbank joins forces with B-crypto to launch new services</strong></h2>



<p>The Russian fintech company B-crypto is responsible for providing technical support for cryptocurrency transactions. Therefore, all Russian companies must go through a verification or KYC process that needs to be approved by both Rosbank and B-crypto in order to utilize the new cryptocurrency service.</p>



<p>Once the KYC verifications are approved, the importer and B-crypto sign a contract in which the client agrees to deposit fiat funds into an account at Rosbank to purchase cryptocurrencies. Subsequently, the bank transfers the money to B-crypto, which handles cryptocurrency purchases in friendly countries and transfers them to the foreign provider.</p>



<p>Alexei Voilukov, Vice President of the Russian Banks Association, affirmed that while Rosbank is the first major bank to offer this solution, larger banks still do not provide similar services &#8220;due to the lack of cryptocurrency liquidity&#8221; required to cater to their larger clients.</p>



<p>And that&#8217;s where smaller banks come in to meet the needs of retail customers.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Sanctioned countries embrace cryptocurrencies to evade sanctions</strong></h2>



<p>Eduard Davydov, Senior Partner at Emet Law Firm, stated that using cryptocurrencies in cross-border transfers may raise concerns regarding sanctions evasion, as many countries are taking measures to include cryptocurrency transactions in their sanction regimes.</p>



<p>In the long run, using cryptocurrencies for <a href="https://zycrypto.com/russia-to-legalize-crypto-for-cross-border-settlements/">cross-border payments</a> could lead to legal consequences for participating countries attempting to evade sanctions using cryptocurrencies.</p>



<p>Nevertheless, for a country under sanctions, legalities might not be their most pressing issue. Numerous such nations, including Cuba, Venezuela, Iran, Iraq, and <a href="https://zycrypto.com/russia-turns-to-stablecoins-in-droves-as-sanctions-bite-even-harder/">Russia</a>, find themselves denied the liberty to trade their primary commodities freely.</p>



<p>Currently, Russia is the most heavily sanctioned country in the world following the invasion of Ukraine, accumulating over 13,263 sanctions, mostly from the US and Switzerland, according to Castellum data.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/russian-bank-rosbank-pilots-cross-border-cryptocurrency-transactions-with-corporate-and-private-clients/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>XRP To Relist On Exchanges? Pro-Ripple Lawyer Sheds Light On Outcome Of SEC Lawsuit</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/xrp-to-relist-on-exchanges-pro-ripple-lawyer-sheds-light-on-outcome-of-sec-lawsuit/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/xrp-to-relist-on-exchanges-pro-ripple-lawyer-sheds-light-on-outcome-of-sec-lawsuit/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Newton Gitonga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 20:08:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=81719</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRP-Lawsuit-Ripple-And-SEC-Request-Additional-Time-to-Disclose-Hinman-Files-—-Is-A-Settlement-Looming.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="XRP Lawsuit: Ripple And SEC Request Additional Time to Disclose Hinman Files — Is A Settlement Looming?" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRP-Lawsuit-Ripple-And-SEC-Request-Additional-Time-to-Disclose-Hinman-Files-—-Is-A-Settlement-Looming.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRP-Lawsuit-Ripple-And-SEC-Request-Additional-Time-to-Disclose-Hinman-Files-—-Is-A-Settlement-Looming-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRP-Lawsuit-Ripple-And-SEC-Request-Additional-Time-to-Disclose-Hinman-Files-—-Is-A-Settlement-Looming-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRP-Lawsuit-Ripple-And-SEC-Request-Additional-Time-to-Disclose-Hinman-Files-—-Is-A-Settlement-Looming-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>Prominent pro-Ripple lawyer Jeremy Hogan has stressed the significance of addressing the contentious issue of "secondary market sales" of XRP in the ongoing legal dispute between Ripple and the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC).]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRP-Lawsuit-Ripple-And-SEC-Request-Additional-Time-to-Disclose-Hinman-Files-—-Is-A-Settlement-Looming.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="XRP Lawsuit: Ripple And SEC Request Additional Time to Disclose Hinman Files — Is A Settlement Looming?" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRP-Lawsuit-Ripple-And-SEC-Request-Additional-Time-to-Disclose-Hinman-Files-—-Is-A-Settlement-Looming.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRP-Lawsuit-Ripple-And-SEC-Request-Additional-Time-to-Disclose-Hinman-Files-—-Is-A-Settlement-Looming-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRP-Lawsuit-Ripple-And-SEC-Request-Additional-Time-to-Disclose-Hinman-Files-—-Is-A-Settlement-Looming-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRP-Lawsuit-Ripple-And-SEC-Request-Additional-Time-to-Disclose-Hinman-Files-—-Is-A-Settlement-Looming-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>Prominent pro-Ripple lawyer Jeremy Hogan has stressed the significance of addressing the contentious issue of &#8220;secondary market sales&#8221; of <a href="https://zycrypto.com/xrp-price-crosses-0-5-milestone-as-trading-volume-explodes-a-ripple-win-in-sec-case-imminent/">XRP</a> in the ongoing legal dispute between Ripple and the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC).</p>



<p>On Monday, Hogan also highlighted the significance of resolving the question of whether XRP is inherently classified as a security, as both of these issues directly influence XRP&#8217;s potential relisting on exchanges and the overall outcome of the case.</p>



<p>“<em>There has been discussion about how/if &#8220;secondary market sales&#8221; of XRP will (or won&#8217;t) be addressed in the Ripple case. It&#8217;s important because we are only confident XRP will be relisted on exchanges if the issue of whether XRP is inherently a security is addressed,” </em>Hogan <a href="https://twitter.com/attorneyjeremy1/status/1663082011358109698">tweeted</a>.</p>



<p>Notably, Hogan acknowledged the likelihood that the judge overseeing the case might not directly address the issue of securities stating the plaintiff did not explicitly raise it. However, he outlined scenarios that could address secondary sales concerns and influence the judge&#8217;s decision.</p>



<p>Firstly, the legal pundit proposed that Ripple could agree with the SEC to include language in the proposed final judgment, explicitly excluding secondary sales from its scope. According to him, this approach could clarify the treatment of secondary sales just like the precedent set by KIK Interactive&#8217;s case, where the SEC allowed language pertaining to continuing sales.</p>



<p>Secondly, the lawyer suggested that the judge consider the concerns raised by various amici, including those championed by XRP holders represented by attorney Deaton. In late March, attorney John Deaton predicted an &#8220;outright win&#8221; for Ripple while accusing the agency of significant overreach in the case. At the time, Deaton also <a href="https://zycrypto.com/why-pro-ripple-lawyer-says-xrp-cant-be-classed-as-a-security-even-if-it-was-sold-as-one/">expressed optimism</a> in Judge Analisa Torres&#8217; ruling that &#8220;XRP is not a security and ongoing and secondary sales are not securities.&#8221; He further emphasized that the judge recognized the importance of the public interest in reaching a decision, terming the amicus briefs and over 3500 affidavits filed by XRP holders as a “big deal”.</p>



<p>According to Hogan, Ripple could also benefit from the precedent set in the LBRY case, where the judge ruled earlier this year that Secondary sales are not securities, raising optimism that the judge in the XRP lawsuit may do the same.</p>



<p>That said, as the high-stakes lawsuit continues, the crypto community anxiously anticipates updates on secondary market sales, as a favourable ruling could potentially aid in XRP’s relisting on exchanges once the case concludes. This could have significant implications for cryptocurrency, potentially boosting its price to all-time highs after three rough years.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/xrp-to-relist-on-exchanges-pro-ripple-lawyer-sheds-light-on-outcome-of-sec-lawsuit/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin&#8217;s Resilience Prevails Despite 474 &#8216;BTC Deaths&#8217; Declarations</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/bitcoins-resilience-prevails-despite-474-btc-deaths-declarations/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/bitcoins-resilience-prevails-despite-474-btc-deaths-declarations/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Newton Gitonga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 18:54:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Featured]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XBTUSD]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=81716</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoins-Resilience-Prevails-Despite-474-BTC-Deaths-Declarations.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Bitcoin&#039;s Resilience Prevails Despite 474 &#039;BTC Deaths&#039; Declarations" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoins-Resilience-Prevails-Despite-474-BTC-Deaths-Declarations.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoins-Resilience-Prevails-Despite-474-BTC-Deaths-Declarations-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoins-Resilience-Prevails-Despite-474-BTC-Deaths-Declarations-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoins-Resilience-Prevails-Despite-474-BTC-Deaths-Declarations-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>Despite the significant achievements of Bitcoin, there are prominent critics who argue that it lacks inherent value.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoins-Resilience-Prevails-Despite-474-BTC-Deaths-Declarations.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Bitcoin&#039;s Resilience Prevails Despite 474 &#039;BTC Deaths&#039; Declarations" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoins-Resilience-Prevails-Despite-474-BTC-Deaths-Declarations.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoins-Resilience-Prevails-Despite-474-BTC-Deaths-Declarations-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoins-Resilience-Prevails-Despite-474-BTC-Deaths-Declarations-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoins-Resilience-Prevails-Despite-474-BTC-Deaths-Declarations-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC), the flagship asset of the cryptocurrency industry, has achieved remarkable success and widespread acceptance. However, Despite the significant achievements of Bitcoin, there are prominent critics who argue that it lacks inherent value.</p>



<p>According to <a href="https://99bitcoins.com/bitcoin-obituaries/">data</a> obtained from 99bitcoins, a cryptocurrency information platform, Bitcoin has faced 474 death declarations since its launch a decade ago, with 7 being made by prominent figures this year alone.</p>



<p>As per 99Bitcoins, for a declaration to qualify to be on the so-called “Bitcoin obituaries&#8221;, it must be produced by an individual with a notable following or a site with substantial traffic. It must also state explicitly that Bitcoin is or will become worthless without any ambiguous language such as &#8220;maybe&#8221; or &#8220;could.&#8221;</p>



<p>One of the earliest recorded predictions of Bitcoin&#8217;s demise dates back to December 15, 2010, when businessman Jordan Tuwiner, in an article titled &#8220;Why Bitcoin Can&#8217;t Be a Currency-The Underground Economist&#8221; expressed scepticism about its future. Notably, Bitcoin was trading at a mere $0.23 at the time of his post. Fortunately, Tuwiner recognized Bitcoin&#8217;s potential and subsequently changed his stance. He went on to found BuyBitcoinWorldwide in 2015, an educational resource for individuals interested in purchasing Bitcoin and entering the world of cryptocurrencies.</p>



<p>Interestingly, Bitcoin was even declared dead during its peak success in November 2021, when its price reached $67,567. Sam Leith of The Spectator wrote an article titled &#8220;The Bitcoin Delusion&#8221;, drawing a comparison between Bitcoin and a ticking time bomb.</p>



<p>Other notable figures have also made pessimistic statements about Bitcoin, including TV personality Jim Cramer and former SEC attorney John Reed Stark referred to cryptocurrency as a &#8220;big hustle”, JPMorgan Chase CEO Jamie Dimon, who <a href="https://zycrypto.com/bitcoin-is-a-hyped-up-fraud-jpmorgan-ceo-jamie-dimon-asserts/">called</a> Bitcoin a &#8220;hyped-up fraud&#8221;, and geopolitical analyst Peter Zeihan who said <em>“bitcoin will probably go negative”</em> on the Joe Rogan podcast in January.</p>



<p>As per 99Bitcoins, the latest Bitcoin Euology comes from renowned tech investor Chamath Palihapitiya who stated in April that “Crypto is dead in America&#8221; when the price of Bitcoin was at $27,817.</p>



<p>Despite the numerous death declarations and negative sentiment expressed by these critics, Bitcoin has continued to demonstrate resilience and positive market performance. Notably, since the first recorded declaration by Tuwiner in 2010, Bitcoin’s value has surged over 11,700,000%.</p>



<p>That said, various individuals have predicted Bitcoin is poised to grow further, with experts such as Ari Paul, the CIO of blockchain firm BlockTower and Bloomberg’s senior commodity strategist Mike McGlone, <a href="https://zycrypto.com/bloombergs-top-strategist-sees-bitcoin-tapping-100000-in-a-matter-of-time-says-bottom-may-be-in/">predicting</a> that its price will reach $100,000 soon.</p>



<p>Meanwhile, at press time, Bitcoin was trading at $27,164 up roughly 1% in the past 24 hours. Notably, since January 1<sup>st,</sup> the cryptocurrency has surged about 65%, restoring optimism in the market.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/bitcoins-resilience-prevails-despite-474-btc-deaths-declarations/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Circle Unveils Game-Changing Move: Launches USDC Natively On Arbitrum</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/circle-unveils-game-changing-move-launches-usdc-natively-on-arbitrum/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/circle-unveils-game-changing-move-launches-usdc-natively-on-arbitrum/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aaron Feuerstein]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 11:45:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Arbitrum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Circle]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USDC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=81709</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Circle-Unveils-Game-Changing-Move-Launches-USDC-Natively-On-Arbitrum.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Circle Unveils Game-Changing Move: Launches USDC Natively On Arbitrum" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Circle-Unveils-Game-Changing-Move-Launches-USDC-Natively-On-Arbitrum.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Circle-Unveils-Game-Changing-Move-Launches-USDC-Natively-On-Arbitrum-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Circle-Unveils-Game-Changing-Move-Launches-USDC-Natively-On-Arbitrum-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Circle-Unveils-Game-Changing-Move-Launches-USDC-Natively-On-Arbitrum-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>Circle intends to overcome the Ethereum network's scalability issues and give users quicker and more affordable transactions by introducing USDC natively on Arbitrum.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Circle-Unveils-Game-Changing-Move-Launches-USDC-Natively-On-Arbitrum.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Circle Unveils Game-Changing Move: Launches USDC Natively On Arbitrum" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Circle-Unveils-Game-Changing-Move-Launches-USDC-Natively-On-Arbitrum.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Circle-Unveils-Game-Changing-Move-Launches-USDC-Natively-On-Arbitrum-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Circle-Unveils-Game-Changing-Move-Launches-USDC-Natively-On-Arbitrum-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Circle-Unveils-Game-Changing-Move-Launches-USDC-Natively-On-Arbitrum-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>Circle, the company behind the popular stablecoin <a href="https://zycrypto.com/circle-rolls-out-usdc-cross-chain-transfer-protocol-for-ethereum-and-avalanche-networks/">USDC</a>, has announced a trailblazing move that is set to revolutionize the Arbitrum blockchain. Circle intends to introduce the official version of USDC natively on the Arbitrum network as part of a strategic cooperation with Arbitrum, creating new opportunities for quick and easy transactions.</p>



<p>Circle intends to overcome the Ethereum network&#8217;s scalability issues and give users quicker and more affordable transactions by introducing USDC natively on Arbitrum.</p>



<p>This change comes as a huge decision for both Circle and the larger crypto ecosystem. Due to its transparency, stability, and regulatory compliance, USDC, the stablecoin backed by the US dollar, has experienced tremendous growth in recent years. USDC is set to grow in flexibility and accessibility with its native integration on Arbitrum.</p>



<p>The announcement by Circle has sparked excitement among cryptocurrency enthusiasts and experts. The company stated its delight in the partnership and the possible effects it might have on the industry. The combination of USDC and Arbitrum would offer a seamless user experience and open the door to new applications for decentralized finance (DeFi).</p>



<p>The Arbitrum protocol developed by Offchain Labs is one of the best layer 2 scaling solutions for Ethereum. It makes an effort to lessen network sluggishness and high gas prices while maintaining the security and decentralization of the Ethereum blockchain by processing transactions off-chain. Circle&#8217;s involvement and USDC&#8217;s inclusion will considerably benefit from Arbitrum&#8217;s technology.</p>



<p>It is believed that the native integration of USDC on Arbitrum will assist consumers in several ways. First of all, it will drastically lower transaction costs, enabling users to carry out transactions more quickly. Additionally, it will make confirmation times faster, enabling almost immediate USDC transfers on the Arbitrum network.</p>



<p>Additionally, the interoperability between various DeFi protocols will be improved through the integration of USDC with Arbitrum. By enabling frictionless USDC transfers between different applications on the Arbitrum network, users will increase the potential for decentralized finance and foster ecosystem innovation.</p>



<p>Circle&#8217;s decision to deploy USDC natively on Arbitrum demonstrates the ongoing efforts being made to overcome the scalability problems the Ethereum network is currently experiencing. By &#8220;rolling&#8221; together groups of transactions on a sidechain, it uses a technique known as optimistic rollup to report back to Ethereum with a single transaction.</p>



<p>Layer 1 blockchains, in this example Ethereum, are layered with Layer 2 networks like Arbitrum, which benefit from the security architecture of the former. These L2 solutions typically see a migration of users looking for lower prices and quicker transactions. However, customers must transfer money from L1 to L2 to accomplish this. This is what is commonly referred to as &#8220;bridging.&#8221;</p>



<p>The usage of stablecoins is expected to rise as a result of USDC&#8217;s integration with Arbitrum, which is also projected to accelerate the development of decentralized finance. Scalable and effective blockchain solutions are likely to advance in the future as Circle and Arbitrum collaborate to make this game-changing decision a reality.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/circle-unveils-game-changing-move-launches-usdc-natively-on-arbitrum/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A New Boom for XRP? Record-Breaking Address Activity Indicates Upturn Ahead to $1 XRP Price</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/a-new-boom-for-xrp-record-breaking-address-activity-indicates-upturn-ahead-to-1-xrp-price/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/a-new-boom-for-xrp-record-breaking-address-activity-indicates-upturn-ahead-to-1-xrp-price/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Marco Tulio]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 19:37:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=81691</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/New-Highs-Seem-Imminent-For-XRP-Price-As-Ripple-Fosters-Massive-Adoption-Push-In-Asia.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="New Highs Seem Imminent For XRP Price As Ripple Fosters Massive Adoption Push In Asia" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/New-Highs-Seem-Imminent-For-XRP-Price-As-Ripple-Fosters-Massive-Adoption-Push-In-Asia.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/New-Highs-Seem-Imminent-For-XRP-Price-As-Ripple-Fosters-Massive-Adoption-Push-In-Asia-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/New-Highs-Seem-Imminent-For-XRP-Price-As-Ripple-Fosters-Massive-Adoption-Push-In-Asia-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/New-Highs-Seem-Imminent-For-XRP-Price-As-Ripple-Fosters-Massive-Adoption-Push-In-Asia-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>The XRP Network experienced a significant increase in address activity for two consecutive days, marking a historic milestone, as...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/New-Highs-Seem-Imminent-For-XRP-Price-As-Ripple-Fosters-Massive-Adoption-Push-In-Asia.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="New Highs Seem Imminent For XRP Price As Ripple Fosters Massive Adoption Push In Asia" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/New-Highs-Seem-Imminent-For-XRP-Price-As-Ripple-Fosters-Massive-Adoption-Push-In-Asia.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/New-Highs-Seem-Imminent-For-XRP-Price-As-Ripple-Fosters-Massive-Adoption-Push-In-Asia-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/New-Highs-Seem-Imminent-For-XRP-Price-As-Ripple-Fosters-Massive-Adoption-Push-In-Asia-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/New-Highs-Seem-Imminent-For-XRP-Price-As-Ripple-Fosters-Massive-Adoption-Push-In-Asia-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>The <a href="https://zycrypto.com/xrp-price-crosses-0-5-milestone-as-trading-volume-explodes-a-ripple-win-in-sec-case-imminent/">XRP Network</a> experienced a significant increase in address activity for two consecutive days, marking a historic milestone, as reported by the blockchain analysis platform, <a href="https://twitter.com/santimentfeed/status/1663349921205088257?t=b15mJpgi45JSK_OJYoDUJA&amp;s=19">Santiment</a>.</p>



<p>The growing activity in addresses suggests the possibility of a rally for XRP, Ripple’s native cryptocurrency, as it has previously experienced a notable increase following a similar rise in address activity.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="641" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-3-1024x641.png" alt="" class="wp-image-81689" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-3-1024x641.png 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-3-300x188.png 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-3-768x481.png 768w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-3-1536x962.png 1536w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-3.png 1600w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-increased-address-activity-suggests-a-potential-45-price-rise-for-xrp"><strong>Increased address activity suggests a potential 45%+ price rise for XRP</strong></h2>



<p>XRP&#8217;s price has risen by about 15% in the past week, from $0.4434 to $0.5053, which it currently maintains at the time of writing.</p>



<p>The price increase is in line with the increase in network address activity. Therefore, as Santiment suggests, it is possible that the price of XRP could increase by over 40%, similar to what happened in March when address activity saw a similar rise.</p>



<p>Similarly, there appears to be a slight disconnect between XRP and the rest of the crypto market, as XRP&#8217;s price is rising while many other coins are not. This could be an indication of a potentially more decisive trend change.</p>



<p>Currently, XRP is in a psychological price zone ($0.50), where bulls and bears are battling to determine the victor. Unless the price of XRP breaks strongly out of this zone, it is challenging to continue with a significant bullish movement.</p>



<p>Currently, several indicators such as moving averages, the squeeze momentum indicator, VPVP, and ADX suggest continuing a bullish movement on daily timeframes, which could lead XRP to reach or even surpass the previous high of $0.6 achieved in late March 2023.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="614" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-2-1024x614.png" alt="" class="wp-image-81688" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-2-1024x614.png 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-2-300x180.png 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-2-768x461.png 768w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image-2.png 1145w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Ripple&#8217;s potential legal win may boost XRP&#8217;s bullish trend</strong></h2>



<p>The spikes in address activity on the XRP network occur at a time when many enthusiasts suggest that Ripple could <a href="https://zycrypto.com/xrp-army-shower-confidence-on-a-ripple-win-in-sec-case-as-whales-load-up-heavily/">win the lawsuit</a> brought by the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) regarding the classification of XRP as a security.</p>



<p>Even Ripple&#8217;s CEO, Brad Garlinghouse, has <a href="https://zycrypto.com/xrp-lawsuit-sec-case-takes-surprising-turn-as-ripple-ceo-garlinghouse-expects-final-decision-in-weeks/">given optimistic signals</a> pointing to the case being resolved in a <a href="https://zycrypto.com/xrp-lawsuit-ripple-boss-confident-groundbreaking-verdict-is-coming-in-weeks-after-hinman-speech-docs-win/">few weeks</a>, which would help boost XRP&#8217;s price prospects by eliminating regulatory uncertainties.</p>



<p>Therefore, in the short term and according to several indicators, it is highly likely that XRP will experience a <a href="https://zycrypto.com/fomo-will-kick-into-high-gear-when-xrp-price-roars-past-2-predicts-pro-ripple-attorney">bullish movement</a>. Who knows, it may finally manage to emerge from the abyss created by U.S. regulatory pressure.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/a-new-boom-for-xrp-record-breaking-address-activity-indicates-upturn-ahead-to-1-xrp-price/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Bulls Put On Defensive Amid Fears Of “Damaging” Inflation and Job Data This Month</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/bitcoin-bulls-put-on-defensive-amid-fears-of-damaging-inflation-and-job-data-this-month/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/bitcoin-bulls-put-on-defensive-amid-fears-of-damaging-inflation-and-job-data-this-month/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aliyu Pokima]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 19:25:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=81687</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Over-10-Billion-Worth-Of-Bitcoin-Leaves-Exchanges-Spelling-Bullish-Sentiments-For-BTC.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Over $10 Billion Worth Of Bitcoin Leaves Exchanges, Spelling Bullish Sentiments For BTC" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Over-10-Billion-Worth-Of-Bitcoin-Leaves-Exchanges-Spelling-Bullish-Sentiments-For-BTC.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Over-10-Billion-Worth-Of-Bitcoin-Leaves-Exchanges-Spelling-Bullish-Sentiments-For-BTC-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Over-10-Billion-Worth-Of-Bitcoin-Leaves-Exchanges-Spelling-Bullish-Sentiments-For-BTC-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Over-10-Billion-Worth-Of-Bitcoin-Leaves-Exchanges-Spelling-Bullish-Sentiments-For-BTC-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>The digital asset market recorded slight gains last week but faces a huge test following macroeconomic factors, including inflation concerns, and reduced liquidity following the lifting of the debt ceiling. May is officially Bitcoin’s (BTC) worst-performing month since the collapse of FTX in Nov 2022, putting investors in a risky position. BTC plunged by 7.3% [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Over-10-Billion-Worth-Of-Bitcoin-Leaves-Exchanges-Spelling-Bullish-Sentiments-For-BTC.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Over $10 Billion Worth Of Bitcoin Leaves Exchanges, Spelling Bullish Sentiments For BTC" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Over-10-Billion-Worth-Of-Bitcoin-Leaves-Exchanges-Spelling-Bullish-Sentiments-For-BTC.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Over-10-Billion-Worth-Of-Bitcoin-Leaves-Exchanges-Spelling-Bullish-Sentiments-For-BTC-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Over-10-Billion-Worth-Of-Bitcoin-Leaves-Exchanges-Spelling-Bullish-Sentiments-For-BTC-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Over-10-Billion-Worth-Of-Bitcoin-Leaves-Exchanges-Spelling-Bullish-Sentiments-For-BTC-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<ul>
<li>Bitcoin has slipped below $27,000 to end May in the red zone as wider market factors stifle the expectations of bullish investors.</li>



<li>Loretta Mester, a Federal Reserve official, shares her opinion on potentially negative job and inflation data.</li>



<li>Observers suggest that investors should brace for a slight downturn in the market outlook as the Feds will resume tightening liquidity if the debt ceiling is raised.</li>
</ul>



<p>The digital asset market recorded slight gains last week but faces a huge test following macroeconomic factors, including inflation concerns, and reduced liquidity following the lifting of the debt ceiling.</p>



<p>May is officially Bitcoin’s (BTC) worst-performing month since the collapse of FTX in Nov 2022, putting investors in a risky position. BTC plunged by 7.3% in the last 30 days while the wider crypto market declined 5%, although some positives were recorded in altcoins. </p>



<p>Adding to the woes of BTC, a job report set to be released this week may wipe off little gains in the market. Loretta Mester, the President of the Federal Reserve Bank of Cleveland, stated in an interview with Financial Times that there is not enough evidence to pause the hikes in interest rates.</p>



<p>“<em>I don’t see a compelling reason to pause, meaning wait until you get more evidence to decide what to do.”&nbsp;</em></p>



<p>Stressing that the Feds must do more to tackle inflation, her comments rattled traders dragging the market leader below $27,000. Furthermore, a report from the Jobs Opening and Labour Turnover (JOLTS) showed an increase in openings from 9.3 million to 10.01 million, justifying Mester&#8217;s arguments of a tight labour market.</p>



<p>There have been <a href="https://zycrypto.com/bitcoin-bulls-set-eyes-above-30000-as-gold-taps-new-all-time-high/">reports</a> that the Feds could eventually pause the hike in interest rates with inflation cooling after ten previous hikes.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-market-leaders-not-fazed-by-price-drop"><strong>Market leaders not fazed by price drop</strong></h2>



<p>The recent negatives recorded by BTC and other top assets have rattled traders, but several industry executives suggest that the major <a href="https://zycrypto.com/key-bitcoin-metrics-signal-potential-bull-run-despite-price-drop/">drivers</a> of BTC are waxing strong. Michael Silberberg of Alt Tab Capital noted that institutional investors are still attracted to the volatility in Bitcoin.</p>



<p><em>“This is a highly volatile market, which is one of the traits that attract institutional investors in the first place.”</em></p>



<p>Similarly, Mikkel Morch, an executive at Ark36, is not perturbed by the current macroeconomic effects on the market, adding that institutional interest and adoption point higher.</p>



<p>“<em>While short-term volatility persists due to the Federal Reserve&#8217;s tightening measures and ongoing global economic uncertainties, our stance at ARK36 remains bullish on Bitcoin for the long term,” </em>he explained.&nbsp;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/bitcoin-bulls-put-on-defensive-amid-fears-of-damaging-inflation-and-job-data-this-month/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
