<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>News Archives &#8902; ZyCrypto</title>
	<atom:link href="https://zycrypto.com/category/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://zycrypto.com/category/news/</link>
	<description>ZyCrypto Is A Cryptocurrency News Media, Focusing On Daily News, Expert Opinions, Analysis, Reviews, And So Much More.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 21:40:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/cropped-ZyCrypto-Site-Logo-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News Archives &#8902; ZyCrypto</title>
	<link>https://zycrypto.com/category/news/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Cathie Wood Strongly Believes Bitcoin Price Is Going To $1.5 Million If This Scenario Unfolds</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/cathie-wood-strongly-believes-bitcoin-price-is-going-to-1-5-million-if-this-scenario-unfolds/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/cathie-wood-strongly-believes-bitcoin-price-is-going-to-1-5-million-if-this-scenario-unfolds/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Brenda Ngari]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 21:40:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XBTUSD]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=82952</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/1-BTC-to-1-Million-Cathie-Wood-Doubles-Down-On-Decade-long-Bitcoin-Price-Prediction.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="1 BTC to $1 Million: Cathie Wood Doubles Down On Decade-long Bitcoin Price Prediction" decoding="async" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/1-BTC-to-1-Million-Cathie-Wood-Doubles-Down-On-Decade-long-Bitcoin-Price-Prediction.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/1-BTC-to-1-Million-Cathie-Wood-Doubles-Down-On-Decade-long-Bitcoin-Price-Prediction-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/1-BTC-to-1-Million-Cathie-Wood-Doubles-Down-On-Decade-long-Bitcoin-Price-Prediction-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/1-BTC-to-1-Million-Cathie-Wood-Doubles-Down-On-Decade-long-Bitcoin-Price-Prediction-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>Cathie Wood of Ark Invest — known for her previously controversial $1 million price target for Bitcoin— has just upped the ante. ]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/1-BTC-to-1-Million-Cathie-Wood-Doubles-Down-On-Decade-long-Bitcoin-Price-Prediction.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="1 BTC to $1 Million: Cathie Wood Doubles Down On Decade-long Bitcoin Price Prediction" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/1-BTC-to-1-Million-Cathie-Wood-Doubles-Down-On-Decade-long-Bitcoin-Price-Prediction.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/1-BTC-to-1-Million-Cathie-Wood-Doubles-Down-On-Decade-long-Bitcoin-Price-Prediction-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/1-BTC-to-1-Million-Cathie-Wood-Doubles-Down-On-Decade-long-Bitcoin-Price-Prediction-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/1-BTC-to-1-Million-Cathie-Wood-Doubles-Down-On-Decade-long-Bitcoin-Price-Prediction-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>ARK Invest CEO Cathie Wood has updated her lofty Bitcoin price forecast. Wood now thinks the premier is going to $1.5 million by 2030. That&#8217;s under its bull-case scenario, while its base case sees BTC hitting $625,000 by that time.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-cathie-wood-says-her-confidence-in-btc-racing-toward-1-5-million-has-risen"><strong>Cathie Wood Says Her Confidence In BTC Racing Toward $1.5 Million Has Risen</strong></h2>



<p>Cathie Wood of Ark Invest — known for her previously <a href="https://zycrypto.com/cathie-wood-sticks-with-1-million-bitcoin-prediction-amid-maelstrom-of-regulatory-crackdowns-heres-why/">controversial $1 million price target</a> for Bitcoin— has just upped the ante.&nbsp;</p>



<p>Wood highlighted her firm’s internal analysis during her latest <a href="https://twitter.com/DocumentingBTC/status/1681277645768540161">interview </a>with <em>Bloomberg </em>to explain her bullish outlook. “Our bull case, I think it&#8217;s $1,500,000 per coin, the best case is $625,000 (something like that),” the asset management titan posited.</p>



<p>As far as why her confidence in Bitcoin has increased, her reasoning boils down to this: the U.S. banking system turmoil that happened in March reinforced the flagship crypto’s long-term outlook to the upside. For Wood, Bitcoin acts as a great hedge against counterparty risk.</p>



<p>&#8220;Bitcoin is an insurance policy. We won&#8217;t have another &#8217;08-&#8217;09 crisis with Bitcoin. It&#8217;s decentralized and transparent,” she opined.</p>



<p>Wood has made no secret of her ultra-bullish stance. She made her first bold prediction in early 2021, <a href="https://zycrypto.com/amid-crypto-market-armageddon-ark-invests-cathie-wood-still-thinks-bitcoin-can-go-to-500000/">forecasting that BTC would reach $500,000 by 2026</a>, owing to the fact that more institutional investors would be moving into the digital asset. Early last year, she ratcheted up her prediction to $1 million per coin by 2030. At the time, ARK based its long-term call on the argument that the top crypto had the potential to “usurp 50% of gold’s role”.</p>



<p>ARK Invest offers several actively managed exchange-traded funds and holds $15 billion in assets under management. It’s hoping to <a href="https://zycrypto.com/ark-invest-gains-edge-in-spot-bitcoin-etf-race-with-epic-surveillance-sharing-maneuver/">roll out a spot Bitcoin ETF product </a>in the near future.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Is Wood’s $1.5 Million Target Realistic Or Outlandish?</strong></h2>



<p>In this scenario, the market capitalization of Bitcoin — already the biggest token — would balloon to around $30 trillion from about $578 billion today, according to <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/bitcoin">CoinGecko</a>. For comparison, the total value of the physical gold supply in the world is estimated to be around $12 trillion. This means that Bitcoin would be roughly 2.5 times more valuable than the entire gold market.</p>



<p>For now, BTC is trading hands at $29,753 after rallying to a new 13-month high of $31,800 on Thursday in the wake of the <a href="https://zycrypto.com/major-ripple-victory-xrp-pops-in-ballistic-rally-as-judge-finally-rules-it-isnt-a-security/">favorable court ruling for Ripple&#8217;s XRP</a>. The crypto is still 56.91% down from its all-time high of $69,044 recorded in November 2021.</p>



<p>It’s hard to say whether or not Wood’s pie-in-the-sky figure of $1.5 million can be considered well justified. Nonetheless, even a $1 million price target seems to be a bit too rosy for BTC bulls. That would indicate a market capitalization of circa $22 trillion, which is nearly 10x the current market value of Apple.</p>



<p>Time will tell whether Wood’s $1.5 million price prediction comes to fruition.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/cathie-wood-strongly-believes-bitcoin-price-is-going-to-1-5-million-if-this-scenario-unfolds/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Taxing the Cryptoverse: IMF Report Claims AML Rules Not Enough to Stop Tax Evasion</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/taxing-the-cryptoverse-imf-report-claims-aml-rules-not-enough-to-stop-tax-evasion/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/taxing-the-cryptoverse-imf-report-claims-aml-rules-not-enough-to-stop-tax-evasion/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aaron Feuerstein]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 21:24:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=82949</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/US-Government-Looks-to-Increase-Revenue-By-30-Billion-Through-Cryptocurrency-Taxes.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="US Government Looks to Increase Revenue By $30 Billion Through Cryptocurrency Taxes" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/US-Government-Looks-to-Increase-Revenue-By-30-Billion-Through-Cryptocurrency-Taxes.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/US-Government-Looks-to-Increase-Revenue-By-30-Billion-Through-Cryptocurrency-Taxes-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/US-Government-Looks-to-Increase-Revenue-By-30-Billion-Through-Cryptocurrency-Taxes-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/US-Government-Looks-to-Increase-Revenue-By-30-Billion-Through-Cryptocurrency-Taxes-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>According to a report recently released by the International Monetary Fund (IMF), current anti-money laundering (AML) policies are inadequate for effectively dealing with tax evasion in the cryptocurrency industry. The paper emphasized the growth of centralized institutions in the trading of crypto assets, providing tax authorities with a chance to gather crucial ownership data. Contrary [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/US-Government-Looks-to-Increase-Revenue-By-30-Billion-Through-Cryptocurrency-Taxes.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="US Government Looks to Increase Revenue By $30 Billion Through Cryptocurrency Taxes" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/US-Government-Looks-to-Increase-Revenue-By-30-Billion-Through-Cryptocurrency-Taxes.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/US-Government-Looks-to-Increase-Revenue-By-30-Billion-Through-Cryptocurrency-Taxes-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/US-Government-Looks-to-Increase-Revenue-By-30-Billion-Through-Cryptocurrency-Taxes-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/US-Government-Looks-to-Increase-Revenue-By-30-Billion-Through-Cryptocurrency-Taxes-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>According to a report recently released by the International Monetary Fund (IMF), current anti-money laundering (AML) policies are inadequate for effectively dealing with tax evasion in the cryptocurrency industry. The paper emphasized the growth of centralized institutions in the trading of crypto assets, providing tax authorities with a chance to gather crucial ownership data.</p>



<p>Contrary to the initial vision of crypto designers, centralized institutions, particularly exchanges, now play a vital role in cryptocurrency transactions. These institutions possess the ability to gather ownership information, making them pivotal in ongoing efforts to acquire useful third-party data that can be shared with tax authorities. Incorporating AML provisions to cover services relating to crypto transactions is crucial in this regard.</p>



<p>According to the IMF, AML standards are essential in the fight against money laundering and in assisting tax authorities. The standards include &#8220;know your customer&#8221; (KYC) guidelines, the submission of suspicious transaction reports (STRs), and the inclusion of customer information with transactions (referred to as &#8220;travel rules&#8221;). The United States applied AML regulations to cryptocurrency transactions as early as 2013 while the Financial Action Task Force (FATF) published guidance on how to put those requirements into practice in 2015. Over in the European Union, past legislation in the block did not cover cryptocurrencies, with a proposal for an updated regulation that would align with FATF recommendations is currently pending Council approval.</p>



<p>KYC provisions have proven invaluable in serving &#8220;John Doe&#8221; notices to crypto brokers, allowing the Internal Revenue Service (IRS) to gather information on US taxpayers involved in cryptocurrency transactions exceeding $20,000 between 2016 and 2021. Similarly, the IMF points out, in the UK, HM Revenue and Customs (HMRC) has utilized KYC rules to inform and remind crypto owners of their tax obligations. Recognizing tax crimes as a predicate offence for money laundering enables tax authorities to access the information collected by financial institutions under AML rules. However, in practice, AML rules alone are often insufficient from a tax perspective.</p>



<p>The IMF report highlights the limitations of AML rules in facilitating effective taxation concerning cryptocurrencies and, more broadly. The OECD reported in 2015 that only 20% of tax administrations surveyed had direct access to STRs, relying heavily on financial intelligence units to share potentially tax-relevant information. Additionally, tax administrations face obstacles in accessing the information generated by compliant financial institutions due to non-compliance by some jurisdictions with FATF guidelines.</p>



<p>Tax authorities aspire to secure the direct and automatic sharing of information on crypto transactions to address these challenges, similar to the established practice for traditional financial transactions. In the United States, the Infrastructure Improvement and Jobs Act, passed in November 2021, mandates digital service providers to report customer transaction details annually to the IRS, mirroring reporting requirements for bonds and shares. Furthermore, businesses are required to report crypto asset transactions exceeding $10,000, resembling the pre-existing rule for cash payments. Similar measures have been introduced in Brazil, where legal entities and individuals are obligated to report operations involving crypto assets.</p>



<p>However, applying reporting rules to domestic institutions may inadvertently drive transactions to mechanisms not subject to these rules or foreign exchanges that do not share information with domestic tax authorities. The IMF states that research suggests that actions targeted at specific exchanges may decrease activity on those exchanges but increase legal avoidance activity in crypto markets overall. Effective cross-border exchange of information is crucial, but existing frameworks were not originally designed to accommodate cryptocurrencies, creating uncertainties and potential gaps. The OECD has proposed a framework for cross-border exchange of information on crypto transactions, which could be built upon by member states.</p>



<p>Tax administrations currently have a limited amount of directly usable data on crypto ownership and transactions. To learn more about blockchain topologies, users can use publicly accessible data on unpermissioned blockchains and forensic analysis tools. To discover potentially tax-relevant behaviours and create connections with data collected from sources outside the blockchain, artificial intelligence technologies and conventional investigative techniques can both be used.</p>



<p>While the challenges posed by quasi-anonymity and technical complexity persist, tax administrations can employ other measures to encourage self-reporting, such as taxpayer education and targeted nudges. Large-scale actions and seizures can serve as deterrents, sending a clear message that authorities can uncover sophisticated schemes and hold individuals accountable.</p>



<p>To effectively combat tax fraud within the cryptoverse, IMF research emphasises the need for stricter laws and global cooperation. By addressing the shortcomings of AML rules, implementing robust reporting requirements, and promoting cross-border information exchange, tax authorities can strive to ensure the integrity of tax systems in the evolving landscape of cryptocurrencies.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/taxing-the-cryptoverse-imf-report-claims-aml-rules-not-enough-to-stop-tax-evasion/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Sharks and Whales Aren&#8217;t Showing Any Signs of Slowing Down BTC Accumulation — Here&#8217;s Why</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/bitcoin-sharks-and-whales-arent-showing-any-signs-of-slowing-down-btc-accumulation-heres-why/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/bitcoin-sharks-and-whales-arent-showing-any-signs-of-slowing-down-btc-accumulation-heres-why/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Erie Maxwell]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 21:02:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XBTUSD]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=82942</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/Whales-Are-Gobbling-Up-Bitcoin-Even-With-The-Recent-Market-Slump.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Whales Are “Gobbling Up” Bitcoin Even With The Recent Market Slump" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/Whales-Are-Gobbling-Up-Bitcoin-Even-With-The-Recent-Market-Slump.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/Whales-Are-Gobbling-Up-Bitcoin-Even-With-The-Recent-Market-Slump-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/Whales-Are-Gobbling-Up-Bitcoin-Even-With-The-Recent-Market-Slump-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/Whales-Are-Gobbling-Up-Bitcoin-Even-With-The-Recent-Market-Slump-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>While recent market conditions have left some longing for excitement, the relentless pursuits of Bitcoin's formidable players—sharks and whales—continue unabated.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/Whales-Are-Gobbling-Up-Bitcoin-Even-With-The-Recent-Market-Slump.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Whales Are “Gobbling Up” Bitcoin Even With The Recent Market Slump" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/Whales-Are-Gobbling-Up-Bitcoin-Even-With-The-Recent-Market-Slump.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/Whales-Are-Gobbling-Up-Bitcoin-Even-With-The-Recent-Market-Slump-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/Whales-Are-Gobbling-Up-Bitcoin-Even-With-The-Recent-Market-Slump-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/Whales-Are-Gobbling-Up-Bitcoin-Even-With-The-Recent-Market-Slump-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>In the realm of cryptocurrencies, Bitcoin has long held the throne as the pioneering digital asset, capturing the attention of investors and enthusiasts worldwide. While recent market conditions have left some longing for excitement, the relentless pursuits of Bitcoin&#8217;s formidable players—sharks and whales—continue unabated.</p>



<p>Despite prices languishing within the $30,000 to $31,000 range, a fascinating trend has emerged: according to the data from <a href="https://twitter.com/santimentfeed/status/1677805758216556544?t=XheAGpRp5UH9SOL0dVFxJw&amp;s=19">Santiment</a>, from June 17th onwards, addresses holding 10 to 10,000 BTC have collectively acquired an impressive 71,000 additional coins, amassing a staggering value of $2.15 billion. This article explores the actions of these influential entities and the potential implications for the market.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-bitcoin-sharks-and-whales-the-dominant-forces-of-accumulation">Bitcoin Sharks and Whales: The Dominant Forces of Accumulation</h2>



<p>Within the complex ecosystem of Bitcoin, whales represent the largest and most influential players. With their immense holdings of Bitcoin, often ranging in the thousands or tens of thousands, they possess the power to steer market sentiment with their strategic movements. In recent weeks, these whales have showcased an unwavering appetite for <a href="https://zycrypto.com/bitcoin-price-fall-ignites-huge-buy-the-dip-moment-for-whales-as-btc-accumulation-heightens/">accumulation</a>, defying the perceived monotony in the market. Their substantial purchases suggest a steadfast belief in Bitcoin&#8217;s long-term prospects and resilience, irrespective of short-term price fluctuations.</p>



<p>Agile and opportunistic sharks complement the whales. These entities thrive on exploiting market volatility and capitalizing on price fluctuations. Although their holdings may not rival the whales, their impact on market dynamics should not be underestimated. Known for their ability to make swift, calculated trades, these sharks possess a keen sense of timing, allowing them to seize opportunities within the $30,000 to $31,000 price range. Their actions, alongside those of the whales, contribute to the narrative that Bitcoin&#8217;s elite players remain undeterred by the lack of excitement.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Market Implications: Concentration and Potential Volatility</h2>



<p>These prominent players&#8217; consistent accumulation of Bitcoin carries significant implications for the broader cryptocurrency market. As whales and sharks <a href="https://zycrypto.com/bitcoin-shrimps-and-crabs-accumulate-btc-aggressively-amid-heightened-institutional-interest/">accumulate</a> additional coins, the ecosystem&#8217;s wealth concentration intensifies. This concentration could amplify market volatility, as their actions have the potential to trigger cascading effects throughout the market. However, it is essential to consider alternative perspectives: their accumulation may reflect a belief in an imminent <a href="https://zycrypto.com/microstrategys-saylor-envisions-250k-btc-price-following-bitcoins-soaring-dominance/">price surge</a> or serve as a defensive strategy against market downturns. Ultimately, the motivations of these influential actors remain subject to interpretation and conjecture.</p>



<p>While market observers may perceive Bitcoin&#8217;s current price range as monotonous, the actions of its whales and sharks suggest a different narrative altogether. Their strategic acquisitions reflect a profound belief in Bitcoin&#8217;s long-term potential and contribute to the ongoing narrative surrounding the digital asset&#8217;s resilience. As the market continues to evolve, the activities of these dominant players will undoubtedly shape the future trajectory of Bitcoin, leaving investors and enthusiasts eagerly awaiting their next move.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/bitcoin-sharks-and-whales-arent-showing-any-signs-of-slowing-down-btc-accumulation-heres-why/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>XRP Unseats Bitcoin As The Most Traded Crypto Asset, Demonstrating High Confidence</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/xrp-unseats-bitcoin-as-the-most-traded-crypto-asset-demonstrating-high-confidence/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/xrp-unseats-bitcoin-as-the-most-traded-crypto-asset-demonstrating-high-confidence/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Brenda Ngari]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 18:15:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XBTUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=82940</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MicroStrategys-Saylor-Says-XRP-Is-A-Security-Touts-Bitcoin-As-The-Only-Crypto-Commodity.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="MicroStrategy&#039;s Saylor Says XRP Is A Security, Touts Bitcoin As The Only Crypto Commodity" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MicroStrategys-Saylor-Says-XRP-Is-A-Security-Touts-Bitcoin-As-The-Only-Crypto-Commodity.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MicroStrategys-Saylor-Says-XRP-Is-A-Security-Touts-Bitcoin-As-The-Only-Crypto-Commodity-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MicroStrategys-Saylor-Says-XRP-Is-A-Security-Touts-Bitcoin-As-The-Only-Crypto-Commodity-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MicroStrategys-Saylor-Says-XRP-Is-A-Security-Touts-Bitcoin-As-The-Only-Crypto-Commodity-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>The tides are shifting the crypto market of late. Frenzied trading has pushed XRP to garner trading volumes higher than those of Bitcoin, otherwise leading the pack in trading volumes.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MicroStrategys-Saylor-Says-XRP-Is-A-Security-Touts-Bitcoin-As-The-Only-Crypto-Commodity.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="MicroStrategy&#039;s Saylor Says XRP Is A Security, Touts Bitcoin As The Only Crypto Commodity" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MicroStrategys-Saylor-Says-XRP-Is-A-Security-Touts-Bitcoin-As-The-Only-Crypto-Commodity.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MicroStrategys-Saylor-Says-XRP-Is-A-Security-Touts-Bitcoin-As-The-Only-Crypto-Commodity-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MicroStrategys-Saylor-Says-XRP-Is-A-Security-Touts-Bitcoin-As-The-Only-Crypto-Commodity-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MicroStrategys-Saylor-Says-XRP-Is-A-Security-Touts-Bitcoin-As-The-Only-Crypto-Commodity-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>The tides are shifting the crypto market of late. Frenzied trading has pushed XRP to garner trading volumes higher than those of Bitcoin, otherwise leading the pack in trading volumes. The positive sentiment around XRP comes after <a href="https://zycrypto.com/major-ripple-victory-xrp-pops-in-ballistic-rally-as-judge-finally-rules-it-isnt-a-security/">Ripple’s legal win</a> against the U.S. Securities and Exchange (SEC).</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-xrp-trading-volume-dwarfs-bitcoin-s"><strong>XRP Trading Volume Dwarfs Bitcoin’s</strong></h2>



<p>XRP has flipped Bitcoin to become the crypto asset with the highest trading volume.</p>



<p>Data from CoinMarketCap shows that XRP has registered roughly $25 billion in total trading volume since July 13, suggesting investors are confident in the token. The rapid volume surge came after a judge <a href="https://zycrypto.com/the-good-bad-and-the-complicated-from-the-sec-vs-ripple-verdict-as-bulls-envision-10-xrp-price/">ruled </a>that the sale of Ripple’s XRP tokens on exchanges and via algorithms did not constitute securities following a two-year legal battle instigated by the SEC.</p>



<p>On the day of the ruling, July 13, the trading volume of XRP pairs on centralized exchanges hit over $10 billion, which is <a href="https://twitter.com/rovercrc/status/1679517125264785409">deemed </a>the biggest volume in the last one and a half years.&nbsp;</p>



<p>Digital asset market research firm Kaiko <a href="https://twitter.com/KaikoData/status/1680865430741700608">observed </a>that “XRP has surpassed BTC as the highest volume asset.” For context, XRP dominated a staggering 21% of all crypto trade volume, while BTC contributed 20%. Ether — the second-largest crypto by market capitalization — made up for 8% of all volume, whilst other altcoins combined were responsible for 51% of the crypto volume.</p>



<p>The trading frenzy happened as Coinbase, Kraken, and other cryptocurrency exchanges<a href="https://zycrypto.com/xrp-overtakes-bnb-coin-as-fourth-most-valuable-crypto-as-coinbase-announces-relisting/"> re-listed </a>or revealed plans to restart trading with the token on their platforms for U.S. customers after the partially favorable court decision on Thursday.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>New XRP ATH In The Coming Months?</strong></h2>



<p>In December 2020, the SEC <a href="https://zycrypto.com/xrp-holders-are-completely-fcked-messari-founder-predicts-drop-to-0-10-as-the-sec-sues-ripple/">filed </a>a civil complaint against Ripple, its CEO Bradley Garlinghouse, and co-founder Chris Larsen, claiming failure to register XRP as a security before selling over $1.2 billion worth to the public. Long years of Twitter spats and legal advances followed as Ripple tried to argue how fundamentally wrong it is to classify XRP as a security.</p>



<p>XRP’s price has endured periods of turmoil in the last few years since the suit was announced. But the recent days have seen the token enjoying a euphoric price rally.</p>



<p>According to Leonidas Hadjiloizou, a long-time cryptocurrency researcher, XRP’s July 13 $10 billion volume marked only the 76th largest daily trading volume.</p>



<p>“Even though this seems like a big number, historically, this was XRP’s 76th largest daily trading volume recorded on CMC. The highest was almost $37 billion on April 6th, 2021. We ain’t seen nothing yet,” he <a href="https://twitter.com/LeoHadjiloizou/status/1680595490185023488/">tweeted</a>.</p>



<p>This suggests that the XRP price could reach a new record high in the coming months, <a href="https://twitter.com/cryptoassetsguy/status/1680596315338571776">according to</a> some observers on Twitter.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/xrp-unseats-bitcoin-as-the-most-traded-crypto-asset-demonstrating-high-confidence/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bullish BTC Signal: SEC Formally Accepts Valkyrie Spot Bitcoin ETF Filing For Review</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/bullish-btc-signal-sec-formally-accepts-valkyrie-spot-bitcoin-etf-filing-for-review/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/bullish-btc-signal-sec-formally-accepts-valkyrie-spot-bitcoin-etf-filing-for-review/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Brenda Ngari]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 11:43:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XBTUSD]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=82937</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/Significant-Bullish-Events-That-Tesla-Accepting-Bitcoin-Payments-Have-Triggered.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Significant Bullish Events That Tesla Accepting Bitcoin Payments Have Triggered" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/Significant-Bullish-Events-That-Tesla-Accepting-Bitcoin-Payments-Have-Triggered.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/Significant-Bullish-Events-That-Tesla-Accepting-Bitcoin-Payments-Have-Triggered-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/Significant-Bullish-Events-That-Tesla-Accepting-Bitcoin-Payments-Have-Triggered-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/Significant-Bullish-Events-That-Tesla-Accepting-Bitcoin-Payments-Have-Triggered-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has officially acknowledged another Bitcoin Exchange-Traded Fund (ETF) proposal for regulatory review, marking another bullish signal for Bitcoin (BTC).]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/Significant-Bullish-Events-That-Tesla-Accepting-Bitcoin-Payments-Have-Triggered.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Significant Bullish Events That Tesla Accepting Bitcoin Payments Have Triggered" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/Significant-Bullish-Events-That-Tesla-Accepting-Bitcoin-Payments-Have-Triggered.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/Significant-Bullish-Events-That-Tesla-Accepting-Bitcoin-Payments-Have-Triggered-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/Significant-Bullish-Events-That-Tesla-Accepting-Bitcoin-Payments-Have-Triggered-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/Significant-Bullish-Events-That-Tesla-Accepting-Bitcoin-Payments-Have-Triggered-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has officially acknowledged another Bitcoin Exchange-Traded Fund (ETF) proposal for regulatory review, marking another bullish signal for Bitcoin (BTC). This time, SEC acceptance comes for the financial services firm Valkyrie, which has adopted ‘BRRR’ as the ticker for its ETF.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-valkyrie-spot-bitcoin-etf-application-acknowledged-by-sec"><strong>Valkyrie Spot Bitcoin ETF Application Acknowledged By SEC</strong></h2>



<p>The U.S. SEC has accepted Valkyrie’s application for a spot Bitcoin ETF following its <a href="https://zycrypto.com/approval-incoming-sec-officially-acknowledges-blackrocks-spot-bitcoin-etf-application/">acknowledgement of similar applications </a>by BlackRock and Bitwise in recent days.</p>



<p>The watchdog added Valkyrie&#8217;s proposal to launch the Valkyrie Bitcoin Fund to its <a href="https://www.sec.gov/rules/sro/nasdaq.htm#SR-NASDAQ-2023-019">official docket</a> on Monday.</p>



<p>The SEC’s acknowledgement signifies the start of the official review process for Valkyrie’s ETF bid. With Valkyrie’s proposal now on the SEC&#8217;s official calendar, it will be published in the Federal Register and trigger a 21-day public comment period. While it’s an initial step in a long regulatory journey, it suggests the SEC’s willingness to explore the idea of a spot Bitcoin ETF and assess its potential effects on the market. </p>



<p>Valkyrie <a href="https://zycrypto.com/spot-bitcoin-etf-craze-valkyrie-becomes-the-latest-firm-to-apply-for-sec-approval/">refiled </a>paperwork with the SEC for its longstanding Bitcoin ETF proposal last month, just five days after BlackRock&#8217;s novel ETF submission. The Tennessee-based asset manager has selected ‘BRRR’ as the ticker symbol for its ETF — alluding to the popular meme that symbolizes the sound of money printing.</p>



<p>Valkyrie adjusted its spot Bitcoin ETF application on July 5 to include an agreement for “surveillance-sharing” with cryptocurrency exchange Coinbase, just like BlackRock. BlackRock, the world’s largest asset manager, banging on the SEC’s door is significant owing to its prominence in finance.</p>



<p>A spot Bitcoin ETF has been deemed a holy grail for the industry and would mirror the value of BTC without requiring institutional investors to store the asset themselves. It would also be tradable on a conventional stock exchange, much like shares in popular companies such as Apple and Microsoft.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Acceptance Bullish For Bitcoin Price</strong></h2>



<p>The SEC is also reviewing applications for funds, including Wise Origin Bitcoin Trust, WisdomTree Bitcoin Trust, VanEck Bitcoin Trust, and Invesco Galaxy Bitcoin ETF, which also entered a three-week comment period.</p>



<p>Going back to 2013, the SEC has long stonewalled proposals for a spot Bitcoin ETF. Nonetheless, the latest competition among firms vying to be the first to launch a Bitcoin ETF in the United States is seen by many as a bullish development for the crypto industry.</p>



<p>The potential SEC endorsement of a spot ETF would equate to a seal of approval for Bitcoin from the securities watchdog. Moreover, the regulatory green light would introduce a fresh capital inflow into the BTC market.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/bullish-btc-signal-sec-formally-accepts-valkyrie-spot-bitcoin-etf-filing-for-review/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Judge Suggests Its Time For SEC To Settle With Ripple Following Historic XRP Win</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/judge-suggests-its-time-for-sec-to-settle-with-ripple-following-historic-xrp-win/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/judge-suggests-its-time-for-sec-to-settle-with-ripple-following-historic-xrp-win/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Brenda Ngari]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 11:37:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=82935</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/Ripple-Community-Pushes-For-Recognition-Of-XRP-As-A-Currency-Amid-Catastrophic-SEC-Lawsuit.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Ripple Community Pushes For Recognition Of XRP As A Currency Amid Catastrophic SEC Lawsuit" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/Ripple-Community-Pushes-For-Recognition-Of-XRP-As-A-Currency-Amid-Catastrophic-SEC-Lawsuit.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/Ripple-Community-Pushes-For-Recognition-Of-XRP-As-A-Currency-Amid-Catastrophic-SEC-Lawsuit-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/Ripple-Community-Pushes-For-Recognition-Of-XRP-As-A-Currency-Amid-Catastrophic-SEC-Lawsuit-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/Ripple-Community-Pushes-For-Recognition-Of-XRP-As-A-Currency-Amid-Catastrophic-SEC-Lawsuit-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>U.S. Judge Sarah Netburn has directed the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) and Ripple Labs to determine three mutually convenient days for a potential...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/Ripple-Community-Pushes-For-Recognition-Of-XRP-As-A-Currency-Amid-Catastrophic-SEC-Lawsuit.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Ripple Community Pushes For Recognition Of XRP As A Currency Amid Catastrophic SEC Lawsuit" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/Ripple-Community-Pushes-For-Recognition-Of-XRP-As-A-Currency-Amid-Catastrophic-SEC-Lawsuit.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/Ripple-Community-Pushes-For-Recognition-Of-XRP-As-A-Currency-Amid-Catastrophic-SEC-Lawsuit-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/Ripple-Community-Pushes-For-Recognition-Of-XRP-As-A-Currency-Amid-Catastrophic-SEC-Lawsuit-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/Ripple-Community-Pushes-For-Recognition-Of-XRP-As-A-Currency-Amid-Catastrophic-SEC-Lawsuit-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>U.S. Judge Sarah Netburn has directed the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) and Ripple Labs to determine three mutually convenient days for a potential settlement conference. This is the latest development following a recent legal ruling. The ruling stated that programmatic sales of XRP to retail investors did not constitute securities, resulting in a parabolic rally in the XRP price.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-ripple-v-sec-settlement-imminent"><strong>Ripple v. SEC Settlement Imminent?</strong></h2>



<p>SEC litigation against Ripple Labs Inc. has kept crypto on edge since late 2020 by presenting the prospect that crypto assets are securities that fall under the commission’s tough regulatory purview. But even as a ruling last week seemed to undermine the regulator’s case, the issue is far from settled. However, this could change soon.</p>



<p>Judge Sarah Netburn has<a href="https://twitter.com/eleanorterrett/status/1681032363873124357"> reportedly ordered </a>both Ripple and the SEC to find three mutually convenient dates for a possible settlement conference “if they believe it would be productive at this time”.</p>



<p>Netburn urged the two parties to schedule this meeting six to eight weeks in advance due to the court’s busy calendar.</p>



<p>A settlement conference refers to a meeting between the parties in a suit where they try to reach an amicable resolution to their brawl, therefore avoiding a lengthy trial. In the case of the Ripple vs SEC dispute, Judge Netburn&#8217;s proposal of scheduling a settlement conference signifies a chance for both parties to resolve the conflict without moving the case forward to a trial.&nbsp;</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>SEC Can Appeal Ripple Ruling</strong></h2>



<p>Netburn’s settlement recommendation comes after a <a href="https://zycrypto.com/major-ripple-victory-xrp-pops-in-ballistic-rally-as-judge-finally-rules-it-isnt-a-security/">crucial win for Ripple</a> on July 13. The judge in the proceedings ruled that the XRP token sales on digital asset exchanges weren’t securities even though sales and distribution of XRP directly to institutions were deemed investment contracts.&nbsp;</p>



<p>The cryptosphere delighted in the implication of likely limits to the SEC’s authority to extend a clampdown on an industry it contends is rife with dangerous practices. As a result of Ripple’s partial victory, XRP has been trending upward, potentially implying that it could <a href="https://zycrypto.com/the-good-bad-and-the-complicated-from-the-sec-vs-ripple-verdict-as-bulls-envision-10-xrp-price/">hit $10</a>. In fact, a lot of crypto exchanges in the U.S. felt that the ruling was a real win for Ripple and <a href="https://zycrypto.com/jpmorgan-calls-ripples-landmark-xrp-decision-a-milestone-win-for-crypto-industry-but-theres-a-catch/">relisted XRP</a>.</p>



<p>However, some spectators <a href="https://twitter.com/CGasparino/status/1681061448946991107">believe </a>that the summary judgment may rest on precarious ground and may not translate to the crypto sector’s much-anticipated change in the way it&#8217;s treated by the SEC. This is because SEC chairman Gary Gensler has <a href="https://twitter.com/EleanorTerrett/status/1680997005944934401">hinted </a>that the agency is strongly considering an appeal against Judge Torres’ recent decision in the high-profile enforcement case against Ripple and pledged to continue with enforcement actions.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/judge-suggests-its-time-for-sec-to-settle-with-ripple-following-historic-xrp-win/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance Announces Full Integration of Bitcoin On The Lightning Network</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/binance-announces-full-integration-of-bitcoin-on-the-lightning-network/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/binance-announces-full-integration-of-bitcoin-on-the-lightning-network/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Erie Maxwell]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 20:53:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XBTUSD]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=82927</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/Bitfinex-Launches-Bitcoin-Lightning-Network-Support-Huge-Step-For-Lightning-Adoption_.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/Bitfinex-Launches-Bitcoin-Lightning-Network-Support-Huge-Step-For-Lightning-Adoption_.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/Bitfinex-Launches-Bitcoin-Lightning-Network-Support-Huge-Step-For-Lightning-Adoption_-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/Bitfinex-Launches-Bitcoin-Lightning-Network-Support-Huge-Step-For-Lightning-Adoption_-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/Bitfinex-Launches-Bitcoin-Lightning-Network-Support-Huge-Step-For-Lightning-Adoption_-768x448.jpg 768w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/Bitfinex-Launches-Bitcoin-Lightning-Network-Support-Huge-Step-For-Lightning-Adoption_-610x356.jpg 610w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>Cryptocurrency exchange Binance announced today, June 17th, the integration of the Bitcoin Lightning Network, and it is now open to customers to use the Lightning Network to deposit and withdraw Bitcoin (BTC).]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/Bitfinex-Launches-Bitcoin-Lightning-Network-Support-Huge-Step-For-Lightning-Adoption_.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/Bitfinex-Launches-Bitcoin-Lightning-Network-Support-Huge-Step-For-Lightning-Adoption_.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/Bitfinex-Launches-Bitcoin-Lightning-Network-Support-Huge-Step-For-Lightning-Adoption_-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/Bitfinex-Launches-Bitcoin-Lightning-Network-Support-Huge-Step-For-Lightning-Adoption_-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/Bitfinex-Launches-Bitcoin-Lightning-Network-Support-Huge-Step-For-Lightning-Adoption_-768x448.jpg 768w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/Bitfinex-Launches-Bitcoin-Lightning-Network-Support-Huge-Step-For-Lightning-Adoption_-610x356.jpg 610w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>Cryptocurrency exchange <a href="https://zycrypto.com/binance-ceo-cz-bullish-on-defi-blackrock-speaks-on-impact-of-recent-xrp-ruling/">Binance</a> announced today, June 17th, the integration of the Bitcoin Lightning Network, and it is now open to customers to use the Lightning Network to deposit and withdraw Bitcoin (BTC).</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr"><a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Binance?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Binance</a> has completed the integration of Bitcoin ( <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/BTC?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#BTC</a> ) on the Lightning Network and deposits and withdrawals are now open. <br><br>More details here <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f447.png" alt="👇" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><a href="https://t.co/aIofPdtAGY">https://t.co/aIofPdtAGY</a></p>&mdash; Binance (@binance) <a href="https://twitter.com/binance/status/1680777249090576385?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">July 17, 2023</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>The Lightning Network is a second-layer expansion solution built on the Bitcoin blockchain. This network enables users to establish off-chain transaction pipelines, ensuring faster, more affordable, and scalable transactions while mitigating congestion issues on the cryptocurrency blockchain.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-bitcoin-explosion-spurs-binance-to-implement-lightning-network"><strong>Bitcoin Explosion Spurs Binance to Implement Lightning Network</strong></h2>



<p>In May, the Binance exchange confirmed that it would bring Lightning Network support after the exchange could not offer Bitcoin withdrawals smoothly even with high gas fees.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">There is a large volume of withdrawal transactions from Binance still pending as our set fees did not anticipate the recent surge in <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24BTC&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">$BTC</a> network gas fees.<br><br>Our team is working to accelerate the confirmation of all pending transactions.<br><br>We&#39;ll provide updates here.</p>&mdash; Binance (@binance) <a href="https://twitter.com/binance/status/1655402071435411457?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">May 8, 2023</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>Before Binance, only a certain number of cryptocurrency exchanges (such as Bitfinex, River Financial, OKX, Kraken, CoinCorner, etc.) offered Bitcoin withdrawals via the Lightning Network, but now Binance is on this list.</p>



<p>In April of this year, the U.S. public cryptocurrency exchange also confirmed that it will bring customers Bitcoin Lightning Network withdrawal support.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Binance and Regulatory Hurdles</strong></h2>



<p>Over the years, Binance has ranked among the top cryptocurrency exchanges for its highly secure and responsive services.</p>



<p>Despite the better service, the exchange faces a formidable legal hurdle in the U.S. due to regulatory action by two of the country’s top financial regulators against its cryptocurrency services.</p>



<p>Currently, the exchange is focused on making some major changes to its services to be able to easily comply with the new rules and regulations set out under the framework of the European Union (EU) Market in Cryptocurrency Assets (MiCA), which will at some stage in the coming years take effect.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/binance-announces-full-integration-of-bitcoin-on-the-lightning-network/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Rocket Fuel For $10 XRP Price Looks Nigh Based On These Key Factors Amid Ripple Win In SEC Fight</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/rocket-fuel-for-10-xrp-price-looks-nigh-based-on-these-key-factors-amid-ripple-win-in-sec-fight/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/rocket-fuel-for-10-xrp-price-looks-nigh-based-on-these-key-factors-amid-ripple-win-in-sec-fight/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Erie Maxwell]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 18:17:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=82914</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Rocket-Fuel-For-XRP-To-10-Price-Looks-Nigh-Based-On-These-Key-Factors-Amid-Ripple-Win-In-SEC-Fight.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Rocket Fuel For $10 XRP Price Looks Nigh Based On These Key Factors Amid Ripple Win In SEC Fight" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Rocket-Fuel-For-XRP-To-10-Price-Looks-Nigh-Based-On-These-Key-Factors-Amid-Ripple-Win-In-SEC-Fight.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Rocket-Fuel-For-XRP-To-10-Price-Looks-Nigh-Based-On-These-Key-Factors-Amid-Ripple-Win-In-SEC-Fight-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Rocket-Fuel-For-XRP-To-10-Price-Looks-Nigh-Based-On-These-Key-Factors-Amid-Ripple-Win-In-SEC-Fight-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Rocket-Fuel-For-XRP-To-10-Price-Looks-Nigh-Based-On-These-Key-Factors-Amid-Ripple-Win-In-SEC-Fight-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>One of the significant factors driving the excitement around XRP is the speculation surrounding Ripple's...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Rocket-Fuel-For-XRP-To-10-Price-Looks-Nigh-Based-On-These-Key-Factors-Amid-Ripple-Win-In-SEC-Fight.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Rocket Fuel For $10 XRP Price Looks Nigh Based On These Key Factors Amid Ripple Win In SEC Fight" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Rocket-Fuel-For-XRP-To-10-Price-Looks-Nigh-Based-On-These-Key-Factors-Amid-Ripple-Win-In-SEC-Fight.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Rocket-Fuel-For-XRP-To-10-Price-Looks-Nigh-Based-On-These-Key-Factors-Amid-Ripple-Win-In-SEC-Fight-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Rocket-Fuel-For-XRP-To-10-Price-Looks-Nigh-Based-On-These-Key-Factors-Amid-Ripple-Win-In-SEC-Fight-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Rocket-Fuel-For-XRP-To-10-Price-Looks-Nigh-Based-On-These-Key-Factors-Amid-Ripple-Win-In-SEC-Fight-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>In the past seven days, the price of XRP has experienced a remarkable surge, capturing the attention of traders and crypto enthusiasts alike. Notably, the interest in XRP has soared, with a 122% increase in Google searches for &#8216;Ripple news.&#8217; </p>



<p>This surge in interest suggests the potential for significant market activity in the coming months. Thomas Kralow, a crypto hedge fund manager, predicts that XRP could achieve an unprecedented milestone, reaching a record-breaking price range of $10 to $30 per coin in the next 3-4 months.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-ripple-s-ipo-and-its-potential-impact"><strong>Ripple&#8217;s IPO and its Potential Impact</strong></h2>



<p>One of the significant factors driving the excitement around XRP is the speculation surrounding Ripple&#8217;s initial public offering (IPO). </p>



<p>As Ripple, the company behind XRP, prepares to go public; there is immense speculation regarding the potential impact of this groundbreaking event on the crypto industry. </p>



<p>Many believe <a href="https://zycrypto.com/ripple-contemplates-ipo-as-sec-lawsuit-finally-nears-end-will-it-propel-xrp-to-10/">Ripple&#8217;s IPO</a> could lead to a nearly half-a-trillion dollars valuation, significantly increasing XRP&#8217;s market capitalization and bolstering its price.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>XRP Pops In Ballistic Rally As Judge Finally Rules It Isn’t A Security</strong></h2>



<p>Another factor fueling optimism is the <a href="https://zycrypto.com/major-ripple-victory-xrp-pops-in-ballistic-rally-as-judge-finally-rules-it-isnt-a-security/">latest Ripple victory</a> in court against the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). </p>



<p>U.S. District Judge Analisa Torres granted summary judgment in favor of Ripple, indicating that the XRP token is not a security.</p>



<p>The anticipation of a positive outcome has always spurred speculative buying, with experts believing that things going in Ripple&#8217;s favor would propel XRP from $2 to $10.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>The Price Target for XRP</strong></h2>



<p>Considering these factors, many experts and market observers are setting ambitious price targets for XRP. Thomas Kralow, with his extensive experience in the crypto industry, believes that XRP has the potential to reach a minimum price of <a href="https://zycrypto.com/xrp-at-10-envisioned-amid-growing-network-metrics-even-as-ripple-aims-to-claim-big-win-in-sec-case/">$10 per coin</a> and, optimistically, even achieve a target of $30. The combination of Ripple&#8217;s IPO, the anticipation surrounding the lawsuit&#8217;s outcome, and the increased public interest in XRP could poise the cryptocurrency for substantial growth in the coming months.</p>



<p>As XRP experiences a notable <a href="https://zycrypto.com/xrp-primed-for-massive-upsurge-as-sec-case-tilts-in-ripples-favor-amid-huge-reveal-of-hinman-docs/">price surge</a> of over 80%, the cryptocurrency community&#8217;s interest in this digital asset continues to grow. With experts like Thomas Kralow predicting price targets ranging from $10 to $30, it is clear that the cryptocurrency has the potential to achieve new heights. </p>



<p>However, it is essential to consider the factors influencing XRP&#8217;s trajectory, including the outcome of Ripple&#8217;s IPO and the next phase of the SEC case.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/rocket-fuel-for-10-xrp-price-looks-nigh-based-on-these-key-factors-amid-ripple-win-in-sec-fight/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>U.S. Senators Push for Cryptocurrency Commodity Status and CFTC Empowerment</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/u-s-senators-push-for-cryptocurrency-commodity-status-and-cftc-empowerment/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/u-s-senators-push-for-cryptocurrency-commodity-status-and-cftc-empowerment/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Erie Maxwell]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 17:57:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=82907</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Post-FTX-Saga-New-York-Banking-Regulator-Rolls-Out-New-Crypto-Guidelines.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Post FTX Saga: New York Banking Regulator Rolls Out New Crypto Guidelines" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Post-FTX-Saga-New-York-Banking-Regulator-Rolls-Out-New-Crypto-Guidelines.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Post-FTX-Saga-New-York-Banking-Regulator-Rolls-Out-New-Crypto-Guidelines-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Post-FTX-Saga-New-York-Banking-Regulator-Rolls-Out-New-Crypto-Guidelines-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Post-FTX-Saga-New-York-Banking-Regulator-Rolls-Out-New-Crypto-Guidelines-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>U.S. Senators Cynthia Lummis and Kirsten Gillibrand are set to introduce a revised version of the cryptocurrency regulation bill, aiming to establish a comprehensive regulatory framework for digital asset transactions and stablecoin issuance.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Post-FTX-Saga-New-York-Banking-Regulator-Rolls-Out-New-Crypto-Guidelines.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Post FTX Saga: New York Banking Regulator Rolls Out New Crypto Guidelines" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Post-FTX-Saga-New-York-Banking-Regulator-Rolls-Out-New-Crypto-Guidelines.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Post-FTX-Saga-New-York-Banking-Regulator-Rolls-Out-New-Crypto-Guidelines-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Post-FTX-Saga-New-York-Banking-Regulator-Rolls-Out-New-Crypto-Guidelines-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Post-FTX-Saga-New-York-Banking-Regulator-Rolls-Out-New-Crypto-Guidelines-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>U.S. Senators Cynthia Lummis and Kirsten Gillibrand are set to introduce a revised version of the cryptocurrency regulation bill to establish a comprehensive regulatory framework for digital asset transactions and stablecoin issuance. The revised version advocates treating crypto assets as &#8220;commodities,&#8221; expanding the CFTC&#8217;s powers and imposing stricter regulations on stablecoin issuers.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-crypto-assets-are-positioned-as-commodities"><strong>Crypto assets are positioned as “commodities”</strong></h2>



<p>The main goal of the revised bill is to define encrypted assets as &#8220;commodities&#8221; and give the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) more power in the spot market and digital asset exchanges. </p>



<p>This will enable crypto asset companies to create assets based on custom criteria and be subject to commodity laws. Additionally, stablecoin issuers would be required to be federal or state-level depository institutions and maintain high-quality liquid assets such as cash, short-term Treasury bills, and reserve certificates.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>CFTC competes with SEC for regulatory power</strong></h2>



<p>If the amended bill passes, the CFTC and the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) will each receive $500 million in additional funding. However, the SEC will be prohibited from using additional funds for law enforcement purposes. At the same time, the CFTC will only be able to use funds if it is a chartered cryptocurrency-only agency. Additionally, the Federal Trade Commission (FTC) will allocate $150 million over five years for consumer education and enforcement related to digital assets.&#x200d;</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Changes to the tax treatment of digital assets</strong></h2>



<p>Lummis and Gillibrand proposed changes to the tax treatment of digital assets, including improving the definition of a broker in the 2021 Infrastructure Act. The definition raises concerns about cryptocurrency developers and other online players being treated as financial intermediaries for tax purposes. It&#8217;s worth noting that the bill&#8217;s broad scope and the jurisdiction of multiple Senate committees could make it more challenging on the path to law.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/u-s-senators-push-for-cryptocurrency-commodity-status-and-cftc-empowerment/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Raoul Pal On Why A Massive Bitcoin, Crypto Rally Is Imminent</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/raoul-pal-on-why-a-massive-bitcoin-crypto-rally-is-imminent/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/raoul-pal-on-why-a-massive-bitcoin-crypto-rally-is-imminent/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Olivia Brooke]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 17:20:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XBTUSD]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=82906</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Binance-Boss-Zhao-Tips-When-The-Next-Unstoppable-Bitcoin-Bull-Run-Will-Begin.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Binance Boss Zhao Tips When The Next Unstoppable Bitcoin Bull Run Will Begin" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Binance-Boss-Zhao-Tips-When-The-Next-Unstoppable-Bitcoin-Bull-Run-Will-Begin.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Binance-Boss-Zhao-Tips-When-The-Next-Unstoppable-Bitcoin-Bull-Run-Will-Begin-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Binance-Boss-Zhao-Tips-When-The-Next-Unstoppable-Bitcoin-Bull-Run-Will-Begin-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Binance-Boss-Zhao-Tips-When-The-Next-Unstoppable-Bitcoin-Bull-Run-Will-Begin-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>Pal, who is known to be vocal about his sentiments on the market, is positive that Bitcoin, along with the rest of the crypto market, will experience a mega bull run in the near term.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Binance-Boss-Zhao-Tips-When-The-Next-Unstoppable-Bitcoin-Bull-Run-Will-Begin.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Binance Boss Zhao Tips When The Next Unstoppable Bitcoin Bull Run Will Begin" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Binance-Boss-Zhao-Tips-When-The-Next-Unstoppable-Bitcoin-Bull-Run-Will-Begin.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Binance-Boss-Zhao-Tips-When-The-Next-Unstoppable-Bitcoin-Bull-Run-Will-Begin-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Binance-Boss-Zhao-Tips-When-The-Next-Unstoppable-Bitcoin-Bull-Run-Will-Begin-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Binance-Boss-Zhao-Tips-When-The-Next-Unstoppable-Bitcoin-Bull-Run-Will-Begin-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>Former hedge fund manager Raoul Pal has made a bold statement about Bitcoin and the entire <a href="https://zycrypto.com/analyst-reveals-what-market-conditions-could-supercharge-bitcoin-price-to-310000/">cryptocurrency market</a>. Pal, who is known to be vocal about his sentiments on the market, is positive that Bitcoin, along with the rest of the crypto market, will experience a mega bull run in the near term.</p>



<p>Pal made this known in a recent <a href="https://twitter.com/realvision/status/1679913653452283906?s=46&amp;t=qzsvHvtDB3yjTaoaylh-2g">interview</a> on the Real Vision Crypto media, as he asserted that the market is imitating bullish patterns from the 2015 &#8211; 2016 cycle. Pal claims that the current market is mirroring a structure similar to that time.</p>



<p>As he further explains, in 2019, the market started off on a bullish note and saw a 300% pump over a period of time. The market later experienced a massive decline, and eventually rallied by more than 700% within a short period.</p>



<p>The market should expect to see more chaos within the banking sector, which will cause the Federal Reserve to intervene, Pal asserted.&nbsp;</p>



<p>As he’s quoted saying;</p>



<p><em>“I have a feeling we might go parabolic earlier here because I think we’re getting closer to a banking crisis within the regional banks that will require the Federal Reserve to step in. Interest rates are getting out of control, so interest rates going up and the yield curve inverted, bad news bears for the banks.”</em></p>



<p>Presently the KRE ETF (Regional Banking ETF) is valued at $43.13, and Pal is asserting that the KRE ETF can be used to decipher where the market currently is.</p>



<p>Once a breakout between the $35 and $30 mark begins, the Fed&#8217;s going to take action. Along with the banking crisis is the ongoing real estate crisis, which Pal believes could also play a role in influencing the Federal Reserve&#8217;s decisions.</p>



<p>Conclusively, Pal expects the Fed to backpedal on its current stance but also offer the liquidity necessary for the government to clear its National debt.</p>



<p><em>“Maybe that’s the reason the Fed is tightening rates even further is to create a crisis so they can cut rates, so they can monetize the debt. Because if they don’t, they have to print more money because the interest rates are higher to pay for the debt payments, and that becomes a total catastrophe.” He said. </em></p>



<p>Meanwhile, the cryptocurrency market is attempting to correct losses sustained over the week. <a href="https://zycrypto.com/bullish-bitcoin-on-chain-metrics-now-approaching-levels-associated-with-re-accumulation-period/">Bitcoin</a>, which is currently up by 0.03%, is trading at a press time price of $30,264.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/raoul-pal-on-why-a-massive-bitcoin-crypto-rally-is-imminent/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance CEO CZ Bullish On DeFi, BlackRock — Speaks On Impact of Latest XRP Ruling</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/binance-ceo-cz-bullish-on-defi-blackrock-speaks-on-impact-of-recent-xrp-ruling/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/binance-ceo-cz-bullish-on-defi-blackrock-speaks-on-impact-of-recent-xrp-ruling/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Olivia Brooke]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 21:08:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Changpeng Zhao]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=82886</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Binance-CEO-CZ-Bullish-On-DeFi-BlackRock-—-Speaks-On-Impact-of-Recent-XRP-Ruling.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Binance CEO CZ Bullish On DeFi, BlackRock — Speaks On Impact of Recent XRP Ruling" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Binance-CEO-CZ-Bullish-On-DeFi-BlackRock-—-Speaks-On-Impact-of-Recent-XRP-Ruling.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Binance-CEO-CZ-Bullish-On-DeFi-BlackRock-—-Speaks-On-Impact-of-Recent-XRP-Ruling-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Binance-CEO-CZ-Bullish-On-DeFi-BlackRock-—-Speaks-On-Impact-of-Recent-XRP-Ruling-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Binance-CEO-CZ-Bullish-On-DeFi-BlackRock-—-Speaks-On-Impact-of-Recent-XRP-Ruling-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>Leading cryptocurrency exchange, Binance turned six. The cryptocurrency exchange has hit several milestones since its creation and has...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Binance-CEO-CZ-Bullish-On-DeFi-BlackRock-—-Speaks-On-Impact-of-Recent-XRP-Ruling.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Binance CEO CZ Bullish On DeFi, BlackRock — Speaks On Impact of Recent XRP Ruling" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Binance-CEO-CZ-Bullish-On-DeFi-BlackRock-—-Speaks-On-Impact-of-Recent-XRP-Ruling.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Binance-CEO-CZ-Bullish-On-DeFi-BlackRock-—-Speaks-On-Impact-of-Recent-XRP-Ruling-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Binance-CEO-CZ-Bullish-On-DeFi-BlackRock-—-Speaks-On-Impact-of-Recent-XRP-Ruling-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Binance-CEO-CZ-Bullish-On-DeFi-BlackRock-—-Speaks-On-Impact-of-Recent-XRP-Ruling-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>Leading cryptocurrency exchange, Binance turned six. The cryptocurrency exchange has hit several milestones since its creation and has remained in business, despite the continuous crackdown on exchanges.</p>



<p>In a recent <a href="https://www.binance.com/en/blog/from-cz/binance-turns-6-8188278446020229815">blog post</a>, Changpeng Zhao, the CEO of Binance, details the company’s achievements over the years while laying down his expectations for the future.</p>



<p>CZ, as he is fondly called, is bullish on the DeFi space, which he believes will continue to accelerate. The Binance boss makes a massive prediction, asserting that DeFi will dethrone and outperform the CeFi industry within the next six years.</p>



<p>With new wallet technologies making it easier for users to hold their crypto assets without a third party, the adoption of DeFi products and direct integration with blockchains will continue to skyrocket. Additionally, <a href="https://zycrypto.com/solana-shakes-off-regulatory-pushback-from-q2-strengths-commitment-to-pioneering-defi-adoption/">DeFi</a> will create financial access for individuals that are unable to access TradeFi and banks.</p>



<p>“There are a few trends shaping up.” CZ writes as he touches on TradFi and institutional investors. The likes of BlackRock, Citadel Securities, and Fidelity are making a notable entry into the crypto industry in significant ways, he added.</p>



<p>CZ refers to the entrance of these big players as validation for the technology that is crypto and the entire industry. In the long term, he believes these industry players will ease the institutional adoption of crypto.</p>



<p>“As institutional investors own the majority of the equity market, with hundreds of trillions of dollars, even a single digit % conversion into crypto will easily multiply the size of the current crypto market.” CZ wrote.</p>



<p>Regarding regulation in the industry, CZ asserts that regulatory clarity and regulated exchanges will continue to grow. While he admits that the market is still plagued with uncertainty, he remains confident that progress is already in motion and at a faster pace in many countries. He cites the recent <a href="https://zycrypto.com/jpmorgan-calls-ripples-landmark-xrp-decision-a-milestone-win-for-crypto-industry-but-theres-a-catch/">XRP ruling</a> as one of the few examples that showcases notable progress in the regulatory sector.&nbsp;</p>



<p>“The XRP ruling on July 13, even though it wasn’t through a normal industry consultative process, is an example of that. The countries that get this right first will enjoy a huge advantage over countries that don’t, for centuries to come. We are at a pivotal moment in history.” CZ wrote.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/binance-ceo-cz-bullish-on-defi-blackrock-speaks-on-impact-of-recent-xrp-ruling/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>XRP Verdict: Ripple&#8217;s Garlinghouse On Taking Down the ‘Bully’ Amid Wake-Up Call for Congress to Regulate</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/xrp-verdict-ripples-garlinghouse-on-taking-down-the-bully-amid-wake-up-call-for-congress-to-regulate/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/xrp-verdict-ripples-garlinghouse-on-taking-down-the-bully-amid-wake-up-call-for-congress-to-regulate/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aaron Feuerstein]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 20:48:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Brad Garlinghouse]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=82884</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Ripples-Chief-Engineer-Calls-It-Quits-—-Will-His-Shocking-Departure-Upend-XRPs-Recovery.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Ripple’s Chief Engineer Calls It Quits — Will His Shocking Departure Upend XRP’s Recovery?" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Ripples-Chief-Engineer-Calls-It-Quits-—-Will-His-Shocking-Departure-Upend-XRPs-Recovery.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Ripples-Chief-Engineer-Calls-It-Quits-—-Will-His-Shocking-Departure-Upend-XRPs-Recovery-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Ripples-Chief-Engineer-Calls-It-Quits-—-Will-His-Shocking-Departure-Upend-XRPs-Recovery-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Ripples-Chief-Engineer-Calls-It-Quits-—-Will-His-Shocking-Departure-Upend-XRPs-Recovery-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>Just days after the major legal victory, Ripple Labs CEO Brad Garlinghouse spoke with...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Ripples-Chief-Engineer-Calls-It-Quits-—-Will-His-Shocking-Departure-Upend-XRPs-Recovery.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Ripple’s Chief Engineer Calls It Quits — Will His Shocking Departure Upend XRP’s Recovery?" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Ripples-Chief-Engineer-Calls-It-Quits-—-Will-His-Shocking-Departure-Upend-XRPs-Recovery.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Ripples-Chief-Engineer-Calls-It-Quits-—-Will-His-Shocking-Departure-Upend-XRPs-Recovery-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Ripples-Chief-Engineer-Calls-It-Quits-—-Will-His-Shocking-Departure-Upend-XRPs-Recovery-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Ripples-Chief-Engineer-Calls-It-Quits-—-Will-His-Shocking-Departure-Upend-XRPs-Recovery-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>Just days after the major <a href="https://zycrypto.com/major-ripple-victory-xrp-pops-in-ballistic-rally-as-judge-finally-rules-it-isnt-a-security/">legal victory</a>, Ripple Labs CEO Brad Garlinghouse spoke with CNBC on the recent court decision in the legal battle with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). Garlinghouse emphasized that the verdict in the lawsuit is good for the whole crypto industry, not just Ripple.</p>



<p>He stated, <em>&#8220;I think this is a huge win, not just for Ripple, but for the whole industry. It puts the SEC&#8217;s narrative and comments that they make publicly about all of these digital assets being securities in check.&#8221;</em></p>



<p>Garlinghouse stressed the need for clear rules to control the cryptocurrency sector. He voiced that it is unhealthy to try to regulate by enforcement. Instead, he pushed for unambiguous legislation that laid out the ground principles for all businesspeople operating in the cryptocurrency industry. According to the Ripple CEO, the SEC&#8217;s legal activities have stifled innovation in the US. He also stressed the significance of pushing the legislative process.</p>



<p>The SEC didn&#8217;t only not provide clear rules but also seemed to try and stop the sector from getting clarity. As Garlinghouse said to Bloomberg in another interview, “For the SEC,<em> its overreach […] to say everything is a security. It is the first time the SEC has lost a crypto case. I think the SEC has been a bully and has gone after weak players who couldn’t mount a defence.”</em></p>



<p>When asked who should oversee crypto tokens, Garlinghouse admitted that there is a regulatory gap. He emphasized, however, that most of those working in the sector are builders who want to enhance the financial system and investigate alternative applications for blockchain and cryptocurrency technologies. He noted that Ripple has focused on cross-border payments but anticipates various transformative use cases. Clear rules of the road, according to Garlinghouse, would encourage investment and allow entrepreneurs to flourish.</p>



<p>While the US lacked clarity, Garlinghouse said he was encouraged by developments overseas. He mentioned the UK&#8217;s proposed rules on crypto assets and highlighted the efforts of the European Union to create a unified framework through the Markets in Crypto-Assets Regulation (MiCA). He urged Congress to act but voiced irritation with the country&#8217;s lack of direction and leadership. While the regulatory certainty for XRP and Bitcoin is valuable, Garlinghouse stated that the lack of regulatory clarity for other digital assets is a matter of concern.</p>



<p>Garlinghouse concluded that Congress should take the court decision as a wake-up call to provide crypto with much-needed regulatory clarity. He hoped Washington would move forward since lawmakers like Tom Emmer were pressing for action.</p>



<p>In addition to being a significant victory for Ripple, the court ruling in the <a href="https://zycrypto.com/xrp-not-a-security-crypto-lawyer-muses-about-lessons-from-telegram-case-for-ripple-vs-sec-lawsuit/">SEC v. Ripple case</a> has wider ramifications for the whole crypto industry. It has highlighted the necessity of transparent policies that support investment and innovation while advising business owners.</p>



<p>The decision has called into question the SEC&#8217;s regulatory strategy and emphasized the significance of legislative action. Brad Garlinghouse, the CEO of Ripple, has pleaded with Congress to seize this chance to offer regulatory certainty, stressing that the United States must take the lead in this field. The pressure on Congress to act has increased as other nations make strides in creating regulatory systems.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/xrp-verdict-ripples-garlinghouse-on-taking-down-the-bully-amid-wake-up-call-for-congress-to-regulate/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>XRP Not A Security, But What Does It Mean For Coinbase, Others?</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/xrp-not-a-security-but-what-does-it-mean-for-coinbase-others/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/xrp-not-a-security-but-what-does-it-mean-for-coinbase-others/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aaron Feuerstein]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 17:19:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=82878</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Speculations-Mount-On-Coinbases-Move-To-Remove-XRP-From-Its-Wallet-Amid-Ripple-vs-SEC-Lawsuit.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Speculations Mount On Coinbase&#039;s Move To Remove XRP From Its Wallet Amid Ripple vs SEC Lawsuit" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Speculations-Mount-On-Coinbases-Move-To-Remove-XRP-From-Its-Wallet-Amid-Ripple-vs-SEC-Lawsuit.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Speculations-Mount-On-Coinbases-Move-To-Remove-XRP-From-Its-Wallet-Amid-Ripple-vs-SEC-Lawsuit-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Speculations-Mount-On-Coinbases-Move-To-Remove-XRP-From-Its-Wallet-Amid-Ripple-vs-SEC-Lawsuit-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Speculations-Mount-On-Coinbases-Move-To-Remove-XRP-From-Its-Wallet-Amid-Ripple-vs-SEC-Lawsuit-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>The SEC had previously declared that most cryptos other than Bitcoin are likely to be classed as securities; with the clarity that XRP has now received, observers look to cases such as SEC vs Coinbase.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Speculations-Mount-On-Coinbases-Move-To-Remove-XRP-From-Its-Wallet-Amid-Ripple-vs-SEC-Lawsuit.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Speculations Mount On Coinbase&#039;s Move To Remove XRP From Its Wallet Amid Ripple vs SEC Lawsuit" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Speculations-Mount-On-Coinbases-Move-To-Remove-XRP-From-Its-Wallet-Amid-Ripple-vs-SEC-Lawsuit.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Speculations-Mount-On-Coinbases-Move-To-Remove-XRP-From-Its-Wallet-Amid-Ripple-vs-SEC-Lawsuit-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Speculations-Mount-On-Coinbases-Move-To-Remove-XRP-From-Its-Wallet-Amid-Ripple-vs-SEC-Lawsuit-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Speculations-Mount-On-Coinbases-Move-To-Remove-XRP-From-Its-Wallet-Amid-Ripple-vs-SEC-Lawsuit-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>On July 13, <a href="https://zycrypto.com/major-ripple-victory-xrp-pops-in-ballistic-rally-as-judge-finally-rules-it-isnt-a-security/">Ripple Labs won part of its legal battle</a> with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) in the Southern District of New York&#8217;s federal district court. Concerning programmatic sales on digital asset exchanges, Judge Analisa Torres found in favour of Ripple Labs, granted summary judgment, and found that the XRP is not a security. However, the SEC also had a win since the judge determined that XRP meets the requirements of the Howey Test, making it a security when offered to institutional investors.</p>



<p>Not surprisingly, the <a href="https://zycrypto.com/xrp-non-security-verdict-triggers-astounding-wave-but-theres-more-to-expect-next-from-ripple-and-sec/">price of XRP shot up by over 80%</a> and took other Altcoins like Solana, Cardano, and Polygon with it, which all made impressive gains. With the partial loss of the SEC, especially with regards to crypto sales at exchanges not being classified as a security by Judge Torres, the question is how much will this influence other cases?</p>



<p>The SEC had previously declared that most cryptos other than Bitcoin are likely to be classed as securities; with the clarity that XRP has now received, observers look to cases such as SEC vs Coinbase.</p>



<p>James Murphy, also known as MetaLawMan, a popular crypto lawyer, said: <em>“While Judge Torres&#8217; decision is not &#8220;binding precedent&#8221; it is extremely well reasoned and will be cited in all motions to dismiss.”</em></p>



<p>This implies that the decision of Judge Torres may be persuasive and affect upcoming judicial cases involving the classification of XRP or other such coins. This could prove crucial for Coinbase in its defence against the SEC.</p>



<p>The SEC sued Coinbase claiming it served as a broker, an exchange, and a clearinghouse for unregistered securities. The SEC cited the U.S. Supreme Court&#8217;s Howey Test, a legal standard developed in the 1940s, supporting its argument that 13 cryptocurrencies listed on Coinbase satisfied its requirements.</p>



<p>The SEC will now have a hard time showing that Coinbase sold securities with Judge Torres confirming that XRP sales on exchanges are not more than mere asset sales where the buyer and seller don’t know each other, also called ‘blind sales’.</p>



<p>What is certainly something that other projects and altcoins have to pay attention to is the ruling in favour of the SEC, where the Judge argued that the initial sales to institutions and investors are securities because most ICOs under this ruling would be seen as selling unregistered securities.</p>



<p>Regarding Coinbase, Kraken, and Gemini&#8217;s previous delisting of XRP, these exchanges have all stated that they intend to <a href="https://zycrypto.com/xrp-overtakes-bnb-coin-as-fourth-most-valuable-crypto-as-coinbase-announces-relisting/">relist XRP</a> or have already done so. This choice was made following a three-year suspension of token trading due to the ongoing legal battle between Ripple and the SEC.</p>



<p>The re-listing shows that these exchanges have changed their positions, maybe due to recent developments in the lawsuit or their evaluation of the XRP-related regulatory landscape.</p>



<p>As far as the old feud of the XRP Community with Charles Hoskinson is concerned, a tweet by the Cardano founder seemed to be quite reconciliatory. <em>“Well done XRP. One Small step for XRP Nation, one Giant leap for Cryptocurrencies!”</em> he said on Twitter.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/xrp-not-a-security-but-what-does-it-mean-for-coinbase-others/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ahead of the US: Europe&#8217;s First Spot Bitcoin ETF Gears Up for Public Listing After Delayed Debut</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/ahead-of-the-us-europes-first-spot-bitcoin-etf-gears-up-for-public-listing-after-delayed-debut/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/ahead-of-the-us-europes-first-spot-bitcoin-etf-gears-up-for-public-listing-after-delayed-debut/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aaron Feuerstein]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 17:01:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XBTUSD]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=82876</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-ETFs-In-Motion-An-Analysis-Of-Open-Spot-BTC-ETF-Applications-In-The-Market.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Bitcoin ETFs In Motion: An Analysis Of Open Spot BTC ETF Applications In The Market" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-ETFs-In-Motion-An-Analysis-Of-Open-Spot-BTC-ETF-Applications-In-The-Market.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-ETFs-In-Motion-An-Analysis-Of-Open-Spot-BTC-ETF-Applications-In-The-Market-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-ETFs-In-Motion-An-Analysis-Of-Open-Spot-BTC-ETF-Applications-In-The-Market-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-ETFs-In-Motion-An-Analysis-Of-Open-Spot-BTC-ETF-Applications-In-The-Market-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>After long delays, it seems Europe is finally preparing for the eagerly awaited launch of its first spot Bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF). It is anticipated that the ETF will launch in the coming months, offering interested European customers a different path to invest in Bitcoin.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-ETFs-In-Motion-An-Analysis-Of-Open-Spot-BTC-ETF-Applications-In-The-Market.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Bitcoin ETFs In Motion: An Analysis Of Open Spot BTC ETF Applications In The Market" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-ETFs-In-Motion-An-Analysis-Of-Open-Spot-BTC-ETF-Applications-In-The-Market.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-ETFs-In-Motion-An-Analysis-Of-Open-Spot-BTC-ETF-Applications-In-The-Market-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-ETFs-In-Motion-An-Analysis-Of-Open-Spot-BTC-ETF-Applications-In-The-Market-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-ETFs-In-Motion-An-Analysis-Of-Open-Spot-BTC-ETF-Applications-In-The-Market-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>After long delays, it seems Europe is finally preparing for the eagerly awaited launch of its first spot <a href="https://zycrypto.com/a-spot-bitcoin-etf-could-turn-around-btcs-fortunes-says-galaxy-digitals-ceo/">Bitcoin</a> exchange-traded fund (ETF). It is anticipated that the ETF will launch in the coming months, offering interested European customers a different path to invest in Bitcoin.</p>



<p>The launch of the European ETF was previously planned for 2022, but delays and regulatory obstacles prevented that from happening. But current information from industry sources indicates that the rollout is finally approaching. The sponsors of the ETF, Swiss company 21Shares and WisdomTree, have stated their enthusiasm and dedication to bringing this innovative product to market.</p>



<p>Regulators, particularly the European Securities and Markets Authority (ESMA), which regulates financial markets throughout the European Union, are anticipated to give the ETF their OK. Although detailed information about the launch date and listing exchange have not yet been released, industry analysts believe it will probably happen soon.</p>



<p>Regulation-related difficulties and the requirement to address concerns about investor protection and market integrity are to blame for the ETF&#8217;s delayed launch. Despite the setbacks, industry participants are nonetheless upbeat about the prospects for Bitcoin ETFs in Europe. The successful launch of a regulated spot Bitcoin ETF, may pave the way for other possibilities to invest in digital assets and boost the institutional use of cryptocurrencies.</p>



<p>The European <a href="https://zycrypto.com/approval-incoming-sec-officially-acknowledges-blackrocks-spot-bitcoin-etf-application/">spot Bitcoin ETF</a> intends to meet the growing demand among European investors for exposure to Bitcoin as they carefully follow the events in the United States, where the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has denied all spot Bitcoin ETF applications so far. In response to prior attempts at a successful filing, the SEC has repeatedly stated that it can&#8217;t allow a spot Bitcoin ETF to proceed until one can show it will be appropriately structured to prevent fraud and manipulation, highlighting the need for investor protection.</p>



<p>The launch of a Bitcoin ETF in Europe before the US could herald a change in the cryptocurrency market environment. The European ETF&#8217;s popularity and performance could pressure US regulators to reconsider their position and offer a more specific path for Bitcoin ETFs in the nation. The prospective acceptance of a US Bitcoin ETF might significantly affect widespread adoption and strengthen cryptocurrencies&#8217; status as a class of investment asset.</p>



<p>The impending launch of Europe&#8217;s first Bitcoin ETF signifies an essential milestone in the cryptocurrency market. It shows a rising interest and need for regulated investment products in digital assets. The introduction of the European Bitcoin ETF is a step towards closing the gap between conventional finance and emerging cryptocurrencies, highlighting how Bitcoin is becoming more and more accepted as a real investment asset.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/ahead-of-the-us-europes-first-spot-bitcoin-etf-gears-up-for-public-listing-after-delayed-debut/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
