<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>News Archives &#8902; ZyCrypto</title>
	<atom:link href="https://zycrypto.com/category/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://zycrypto.com/category/news/</link>
	<description>ZyCrypto Is A Cryptocurrency News Media, Focusing On Daily News, Expert Opinions, Analysis, Reviews, And So Much More.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 15:49:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/cropped-ZyCrypto-Site-Logo-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News Archives &#8902; ZyCrypto</title>
	<link>https://zycrypto.com/category/news/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Europe’s First Spot Bitcoin ETF Goes Live, Beating U.S. To The Punch</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/europes-first-spot-bitcoin-etf-goes-live-beating-u-s-to-the-punch/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/europes-first-spot-bitcoin-etf-goes-live-beating-u-s-to-the-punch/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Brenda Ngari]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 15:49:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Europe]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XBTUSD]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=83700</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/SECs-Approval-Of-Spot-Bitcoin-ETFs-Wont-Be-A-Game-Changer-For-Crypto-Industry-JPMorgan-Strategists-Opine.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="SEC’s Approval Of Spot Bitcoin ETFs Won’t Be A Game-Changer For Crypto Industry, JPMorgan Strategists Opine" decoding="async" fetchpriority="high" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/SECs-Approval-Of-Spot-Bitcoin-ETFs-Wont-Be-A-Game-Changer-For-Crypto-Industry-JPMorgan-Strategists-Opine.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/SECs-Approval-Of-Spot-Bitcoin-ETFs-Wont-Be-A-Game-Changer-For-Crypto-Industry-JPMorgan-Strategists-Opine-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/SECs-Approval-Of-Spot-Bitcoin-ETFs-Wont-Be-A-Game-Changer-For-Crypto-Industry-JPMorgan-Strategists-Opine-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/SECs-Approval-Of-Spot-Bitcoin-ETFs-Wont-Be-A-Game-Changer-For-Crypto-Industry-JPMorgan-Strategists-Opine-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>Europe has usurped the United States with the listing of its first spot exchange-traded fund (ETF) on the Euronext Amsterdam stock exchange by London-based Jacobi Asset Management.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/SECs-Approval-Of-Spot-Bitcoin-ETFs-Wont-Be-A-Game-Changer-For-Crypto-Industry-JPMorgan-Strategists-Opine.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="SEC’s Approval Of Spot Bitcoin ETFs Won’t Be A Game-Changer For Crypto Industry, JPMorgan Strategists Opine" decoding="async" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/SECs-Approval-Of-Spot-Bitcoin-ETFs-Wont-Be-A-Game-Changer-For-Crypto-Industry-JPMorgan-Strategists-Opine.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/SECs-Approval-Of-Spot-Bitcoin-ETFs-Wont-Be-A-Game-Changer-For-Crypto-Industry-JPMorgan-Strategists-Opine-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/SECs-Approval-Of-Spot-Bitcoin-ETFs-Wont-Be-A-Game-Changer-For-Crypto-Industry-JPMorgan-Strategists-Opine-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/SECs-Approval-Of-Spot-Bitcoin-ETFs-Wont-Be-A-Game-Changer-For-Crypto-Industry-JPMorgan-Strategists-Opine-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>Europe has usurped the United States with the listing of its first spot exchange-traded fund (ETF) on the Euronext Amsterdam stock exchange by London-based Jacobi Asset Management. The spot ETF will trade under the ticker symbol &#8220;BCOIN” and has a focus on decarbonization.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-jacobi-asset-management-has-rolled-out-the-first-spot-bitcoin-etf-in-europe">Jacobi Asset Management has rolled out the first spot Bitcoin ETF in Europe</h2>



<p>After receiving the green light from the Guernsey Financial Services Commission (GFSC) in October 2021, the firm initially planned to launch its spot Bitcoin investment vehicle last year. It, however, decided to shelve the launch due to an inopportune time in the cryptosphere following the implosion of the Terra network and the bankruptcy of Sam Bankman-Fried’s FTX digital asset exchange.</p>



<p>But today, the Jacobi FT Wilshire Bitcoin ETF has finally been listed for trading. The physically-backed Bitcoin fund will charge investors a 1.5% annual management fee. Fidelity Digital Assets provides custodial services for the fund, and Flow Traders takes on the role of market maker. Jane Street and DRW have been added as Authorized Participants.</p>



<p>BCOIN makes use of the FT Wilshire Bitcoin Blended Price Index to access real-time average Bitcoin price data from select crypto exchanges. The ETF product will allow investors to gain access to trading and holding Bitcoin’s value without the hassle of holding the underlying asset.</p>



<p>Jacobi teamed up with Zumo to create a verifiable built-in Renewable Energy Certificate (REC) solution, which allows institutional-grade investors to invest in BTC while remaining compliant with their Environmental, Social, and Governance (ESG) objectives.</p>



<p>The spot BTC ETF is touted as the first decarbonized digital asset fund in line with Article 8 of the European Sustainable Finance Disclosure Regulation (SFDR), which applies to funds fostering environmental and social objectives.</p>



<p>“Jacobi has implemented a verifiable built-in Renewable Energy Certificate (REC) solution which allows institutional investors to access the benefits of Bitcoin whilst also meeting ESG goals.”</p>



<p>The rollout of Jacobi’s spot ETF marks a significant milestone for Europe, while the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission is yet to approve a new wave of similar applications from traditional finance heavyweights such as BlackRock and Fidelity Investments — which have even included &#8220;surveillance-sharing&#8221; agreements designed to safeguard against market manipulation in their filings.</p>



<p>Martin Bednall, the CEO of Jacobi Asset Management, remarked on the continent’s progressive stance toward crypto investment products as a potential driver for more adoption:</p>



<p>“It is exciting to see Europe moving ahead of the US in opening up Bitcoin investing for institutional investors who want safe, secure access to the benefits of digital assets using familiar and regulated structures like our ETF.”</p>



<p>Whether American investors soon get a <a href="https://zycrypto.com/multiple-spot-bitcoin-etf-approvals-on-the-way-cathie-wood-predicts/">spot Bitcoin ETF</a> like their European counterparts remains to be seen.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/europes-first-spot-bitcoin-etf-goes-live-beating-u-s-to-the-punch/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Sandbox Unlocks Over 300 Million Tokens, Sending SAND Price Tumbling</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/the-sandbox-unlocks-over-300-million-tokens-sending-sand-price-tumbling/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/the-sandbox-unlocks-over-300-million-tokens-sending-sand-price-tumbling/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aaron Feuerstein]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 15:47:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[The Sandbox]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=83697</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/The-Sandbox-Unlocks-Over-300-Million-Tokens-Sending-SAND-Price-Tumbling.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="The Sandbox Unlocks Over 300 Million Tokens, Sending SAND Price Tumbling" decoding="async" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/The-Sandbox-Unlocks-Over-300-Million-Tokens-Sending-SAND-Price-Tumbling.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/The-Sandbox-Unlocks-Over-300-Million-Tokens-Sending-SAND-Price-Tumbling-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/The-Sandbox-Unlocks-Over-300-Million-Tokens-Sending-SAND-Price-Tumbling-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/The-Sandbox-Unlocks-Over-300-Million-Tokens-Sending-SAND-Price-Tumbling-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>On Monday, August 14, the metaverse platform The Sandbox released approx. 16% of its circulating supply in a planned event.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/The-Sandbox-Unlocks-Over-300-Million-Tokens-Sending-SAND-Price-Tumbling.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="The Sandbox Unlocks Over 300 Million Tokens, Sending SAND Price Tumbling" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/The-Sandbox-Unlocks-Over-300-Million-Tokens-Sending-SAND-Price-Tumbling.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/The-Sandbox-Unlocks-Over-300-Million-Tokens-Sending-SAND-Price-Tumbling-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/The-Sandbox-Unlocks-Over-300-Million-Tokens-Sending-SAND-Price-Tumbling-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/The-Sandbox-Unlocks-Over-300-Million-Tokens-Sending-SAND-Price-Tumbling-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>On Monday, August 14, the metaverse platform The Sandbox released approx. 16% of its circulating supply in a planned event. SAND, the utility token used in The Sandbox web3 ecosystem, is utilized for interaction and transactions, with a maximum supply of 3,000,000,000 SAND.</p>



<p>The anticipated event saw 332 million SAND unlocked, equating to $129.9 million in funds. The latest unlock means that 79% of SAND is now in circulation, with only 616 million yet to be released. The next release of tokens is scheduled for February 14, 2024.</p>



<p>Data published in shows that 71 million tokens went to the team and 96.8 million flowed into company reserves, while 103 million tokens were unlocked for seed sale participants. The remaining 37.5 million went to advisers and 24 million to strategic sales buyers; however, all tokens can now be freely traded on the market.</p>



<p>An increased supply usually pushes the price downwards and it is expected that much of the distributed tokens will be sold off. Interest in the metaverse has decreased by 92%, in sharp contrast to the hype it experienced when Facebook changed its name to Meta and revealed its ambitious plans for the space.</p>



<p>So far, SAND continues its slow decline in value, with only a modest drop. SAND trades at $0.38 currently, down 12% from a month ago and well short of its all-time high of $8.44 in November 2021. It appears quite likely that the market had already priced in the release of SAND as the events are pre-planned.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-legal-uncertainty-and-developments"><strong>Legal Uncertainty and Developments</strong></h2>



<p>The United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), which had labelled several altcoin securities, had also included SAND in that list, alleging that The Sandbox provides information that the public would use to make investments. Sebastien Borget, the Chief Operating Officer of The Sandbox, refuted these claims saying, <em>“We do not necessarily agree with the characterization that’s been put in that litigation, including the qualification of SAND as a security there.”</em></p>



<p>Meanwhile, a partnership was established between The Sandbox and the British Museum. This partnership aims to develop a series of digital artefacts that reflect various things from the British Museum&#8217;s collections dating back to its founding in 1753. The British Museum, which houses the most extensive collection in the world, and is also the first public national museum, hopes to expand into the digital arena through its participation with The Sandbox.</p>



<p>This collaboration will create new immersive experiences that will allow visitors worldwide to examine and interact with artefacts from the British Museum&#8217;s collections. The cooperation includes the British Museum&#8217;s licensing partner, LaCollection, focusing on building digital collections and experiences showcasing the museum&#8217;s historical value and different artefacts.</p>



<p><em>“This is a great opportunity for The Sandbox players, regardless of where they are, to learn about and enjoy the amazing collections of human history, art, and culture in the British Museum,” Borget said.</em></p>



<p>It remains to be seen if the legal uncertainty and the future token release can be countered by positive developments such as the British Museum collaboration; it will certainly depend on a renewed interest in the metaverse, should that occur.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/the-sandbox-unlocks-over-300-million-tokens-sending-sand-price-tumbling/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Rich Dad Poor Dad Author Explains Why Bitcoin Will See $100,000 In Near Future</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/rich-dad-poor-dad-author-explains-why-bitcoin-will-see-100000-in-near-future/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/rich-dad-poor-dad-author-explains-why-bitcoin-will-see-100000-in-near-future/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Brenda Ngari]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 15:26:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Robert Kiyosaki]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=83695</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/05/Analyst_-Bitcoin-BTC-Will-Explode-To-100000-And-‘There’s-Nothing-You-Can-Do-About-It’.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Analyst: Bitcoin (BTC) Will Explode To $100,000 And ‘There’s Nothing You Can Do About It’" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/05/Analyst_-Bitcoin-BTC-Will-Explode-To-100000-And-‘There’s-Nothing-You-Can-Do-About-It’.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/05/Analyst_-Bitcoin-BTC-Will-Explode-To-100000-And-‘There’s-Nothing-You-Can-Do-About-It’-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/05/Analyst_-Bitcoin-BTC-Will-Explode-To-100000-And-‘There’s-Nothing-You-Can-Do-About-It’-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/05/Analyst_-Bitcoin-BTC-Will-Explode-To-100000-And-‘There’s-Nothing-You-Can-Do-About-It’-768x448.jpg 768w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/05/Analyst_-Bitcoin-BTC-Will-Explode-To-100000-And-‘There’s-Nothing-You-Can-Do-About-It’-610x356.jpg 610w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>The best-selling author of Rich Dad Poor Dad Robert Kiyosaki said yesterday that Bitcoin could shoot well past $100,000 in the near future spurred by a number of bullish factors.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/05/Analyst_-Bitcoin-BTC-Will-Explode-To-100000-And-‘There’s-Nothing-You-Can-Do-About-It’.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Analyst: Bitcoin (BTC) Will Explode To $100,000 And ‘There’s Nothing You Can Do About It’" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/05/Analyst_-Bitcoin-BTC-Will-Explode-To-100000-And-‘There’s-Nothing-You-Can-Do-About-It’.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/05/Analyst_-Bitcoin-BTC-Will-Explode-To-100000-And-‘There’s-Nothing-You-Can-Do-About-It’-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/05/Analyst_-Bitcoin-BTC-Will-Explode-To-100000-And-‘There’s-Nothing-You-Can-Do-About-It’-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/05/Analyst_-Bitcoin-BTC-Will-Explode-To-100000-And-‘There’s-Nothing-You-Can-Do-About-It’-768x448.jpg 768w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/05/Analyst_-Bitcoin-BTC-Will-Explode-To-100000-And-‘There’s-Nothing-You-Can-Do-About-It’-610x356.jpg 610w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>The best-selling author of Rich Dad Poor Dad, Robert Kiyosaki, said yesterday that Bitcoin could shoot well past $100,000 in the near future spurred by a number of bullish factors.</p>



<p>This news has reinvigorated Kiyosaki’s unwavering optimism in the premier cryptocurrency and its long-term investment potential.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-bitcoin-s-ascension-kiyosaki-sets-price-target-at-100k"><strong>Bitcoin’s Ascension: Kiyosaki Sets Price Target at $100K</strong></h2>



<p>Robert Kiyosaki, also a real estate mogul and an investor in precious metals, remains a steadfast Bitcoin supporter, despite recent incidents that have shaken mainstream investors&#8217; confidence in the world’s largest crypto.</p>



<p>Popular for his proven theories on market trends and investment strategies, Kiyosaki’s latest prediction boosts Bitcoin’s prospects. In an August 14 X post to his 2.4 million followers, he <a href="https://twitter.com/theRealKiyosaki/status/1691174700234477570">predicted </a>that Bitcoin’s price could hit an impressive $100,000 in the near future.</p>



<p>The rationale for his prediction is that Bitcoin is “people’s money” while gold and silver are “God’s money”. This can help BTC reach the elusive $100k mark, especially should the stock and bond markets plummet significantly, Kiyosaki says. This would also drive traditional safe-haven assets like gold and silver higher.</p>



<p>According to the famed investor, a situation where not only stocks and bonds crash but also the entire world economy collapse would supercharge Bitcoin’s price to $1 million. In such a scenario, gold would hit $75,000 per ounce, and silver would rocket to $60,000.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">August 22, 2023, in Johannesburg, South Africa, BRICS nations  announce gold backed crypto. US $ will die. Trillions of US $ rush home. Inflation through the roof. Buy Gold, <br>Silver. Bitcoin to $120k next year.</p>&mdash; Robert Kiyosaki (@theRealKiyosaki) <a href="https://twitter.com/theRealKiyosaki/status/1678652054951317504?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">July 11, 2023</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>Last month, Kiyosaki cited another factor he expects to catalyze Bitcoin’s run to the moon: the BRICS nations’ ((Brazil, Russia, India, China, and South Africa)&nbsp; meeting in South Africa scheduled for August 22, 2023.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-not-the-only-pundit-predicting-100-000-btc"><strong>Not The Only Pundit Predicting $100,000 BTC</strong></h2>



<p>Notably, Kiyosaki is not the only one making a sky-high price prediction as Adam Back, the chief executive officer of Blockstream, projects a surge in BTC’s value. Back <a href="https://zycrypto.com/pundits-100000-bitcoin-price-target-by-next-halving-sparks-exciting-bet/">forecasted </a>last month that Bitcoin will rise to $100,000 and beyond by the next halving slated for March 2024.</p>



<p>British Multinational Bank Standard Chartered also <a href="https://zycrypto.com/standard-chartered-bank-says-bitcoin-price-likely-to-hit-50000-this-year-120000-by-2024/">said </a>last month that it expected the flagship cryptocurrency to reach $50,000 by the end of this year and up to $120,000 by end-2024.</p>



<p>Kiyosaki’s comments come as the price of Bitcoin continues to trade around the $29,300 zone at press time. The top crypto has returned around 0.4% for investors in the past week — making it one of the lowest volatility periods.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/rich-dad-poor-dad-author-explains-why-bitcoin-will-see-100000-in-near-future/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Shiba Inu&#8217;s Shibarium Sees Super Bullish Momentum, But Can It Trigger SHIB Price to Astronomical Highs?</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/shiba-inus-shibarium-sees-super-bullish-momentum-but-can-it-trigger-shib-price-to-astronomical-highs/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/shiba-inus-shibarium-sees-super-bullish-momentum-but-can-it-trigger-shib-price-to-astronomical-highs/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Newton Gitonga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 19:43:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIB]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIBA INU]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIBUSD]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=83682</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Shiba-Inus-Shibarium-Renews-Bullish-Momentum-For-0.001-SHIB-As-Massive-Token-Burn-Expected.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Shiba Inu&#039;s Shibarium Renews Bullish Momentum For &#039;$0.001 SHIB&#039; As Massive Token Burn Expected" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Shiba-Inus-Shibarium-Renews-Bullish-Momentum-For-0.001-SHIB-As-Massive-Token-Burn-Expected.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Shiba-Inus-Shibarium-Renews-Bullish-Momentum-For-0.001-SHIB-As-Massive-Token-Burn-Expected-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Shiba-Inus-Shibarium-Renews-Bullish-Momentum-For-0.001-SHIB-As-Massive-Token-Burn-Expected-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Shiba-Inus-Shibarium-Renews-Bullish-Momentum-For-0.001-SHIB-As-Massive-Token-Burn-Expected-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>...unveiled the highlights of Shibarium, shedding light on its transformative features and benefits. ]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Shiba-Inus-Shibarium-Renews-Bullish-Momentum-For-0.001-SHIB-As-Massive-Token-Burn-Expected.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Shiba Inu&#039;s Shibarium Renews Bullish Momentum For &#039;$0.001 SHIB&#039; As Massive Token Burn Expected" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Shiba-Inus-Shibarium-Renews-Bullish-Momentum-For-0.001-SHIB-As-Massive-Token-Burn-Expected.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Shiba-Inus-Shibarium-Renews-Bullish-Momentum-For-0.001-SHIB-As-Massive-Token-Burn-Expected-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Shiba-Inus-Shibarium-Renews-Bullish-Momentum-For-0.001-SHIB-As-Massive-Token-Burn-Expected-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Shiba-Inus-Shibarium-Renews-Bullish-Momentum-For-0.001-SHIB-As-Massive-Token-Burn-Expected-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>Lucie, the Chief Marketing Strategist for Shiba Inu, has taken to Twitter to provide crucial insights into the upcoming launch of Shibarium&#8217;s Layer 2 solution, igniting a wave of excitement within the Shiba Inu community.</p>



<p>In a series of tweets on Sunday, Lucie unveiled the highlights of Shibarium, shedding light on its transformative features and benefits. Shibarium Layer 2 is poised to revolutionize the Shiba Inu blockchain experience, promising ultra-low transaction fees, rapid transactions, and freedom from centralized control. Lucie emphasized that to unlock the full potential of Shibarium; users will require $BONE, a key ingredient for accessing its capabilities.</p>



<p>One of the most intriguing aspects of <a href="https://zycrypto.com/shiba-inu-lead-dev-sees-shibarium-outshining-x-worldcoin-shib-price-at-0-001-looking-likely/">Shibarium Layer 2</a> is its focus on security. Lucie revealed that Shibarium has participated in hackathons to bolster its security infrastructure, ensuring a safe and robust platform for users. Furthermore, she revealed plans to integrate Self-Sovereign Identity (SSI), enhancing asset security and giving users greater control over their digital identities. Self-Sovereign Identity (SSI) in crypto is a concept where individuals control their own identity, thereby shifting control from central authorities.</p>



<p>Notably, every transaction conducted on Shibarium contributes to the burning of SHIB tokens, fueling what Lucie referred to as the &#8220;Shib bonfire.&#8221; This mechanism aligns with Shiba Inu&#8217;s deflationary model and highlights the ecosystem&#8217;s dedication to sustainability and tokenomics.</p>



<p>Notably, amidst the mounting excitement surrounding Shibarium&#8217;s impending launch, set to coincide with the Blockchain Futurist Conference in Toronto (August 13 to 17, 2023), Lucie promptly clarified that an official release date for Shibarium remains unconfirmed.</p>



<p><em>“I&#8217;m not saying it won&#8217;t come, just that there was no official announcement, and anything can happen until then,” </em>she said.</p>



<p>Meanwhile, as the launch nears, crypto platforms have positioned themselves to ride the wave with KuCoin, adding to the anticipation by hinting at the potential listing of tokens from the Shiba Inu ecosystem. On Saturday, the prominent crypto exchange <a href="https://twitter.com/Shibtoken/status/1690491024508960768">tweeted</a> out an image of the Shiba Inu dog positioned next to the date August 12, accompanied by a Bone icon beneath August 15/16. Notably, the timing coincides with the upcoming launch of Shibarium, further fueling excitement within the SHIB community.</p>



<p>As the launch closes in, SHIB has held its ground firmly, following a robust surge of more than 25% over the last week. The cryptocurrency traded at $0.000010 at press time after a 3.04% drop in the past 24 hours. On the other hand, BONE faced a sharp drop of roughly 11% over the same period to trade at $1.48&nbsp;at press time.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/shiba-inus-shibarium-sees-super-bullish-momentum-but-can-it-trigger-shib-price-to-astronomical-highs/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Despite USDT&#8217;s recent depeg, Tether&#8217;s market share is larger than it&#8217;s ever been</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/despite-usdts-recent-depeg-tethers-market-share-is-larger-than-its-ever-been/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/despite-usdts-recent-depeg-tethers-market-share-is-larger-than-its-ever-been/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Olivia Brooke]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 19:30:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=83680</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/Messari_-Tether-USDT-Likely-to-Surpass-Bitcoin-as-the-Dominant-Cryptocurrency.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Messari: Tether (USDT) Likely to Surpass Bitcoin as the Dominant Cryptocurrency" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/Messari_-Tether-USDT-Likely-to-Surpass-Bitcoin-as-the-Dominant-Cryptocurrency.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/Messari_-Tether-USDT-Likely-to-Surpass-Bitcoin-as-the-Dominant-Cryptocurrency-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/Messari_-Tether-USDT-Likely-to-Surpass-Bitcoin-as-the-Dominant-Cryptocurrency-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/Messari_-Tether-USDT-Likely-to-Surpass-Bitcoin-as-the-Dominant-Cryptocurrency-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>Tether (USDT) recently lost its peg to the U.S. dollar. Although USDT is the most valuable stablecoin by market cap, the market turbulence did not spare the asset. Last week, USDT depegged below $1 and stayed below the $1 peg for the longest time since the collapse of FTX, before making a recovery at the [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/Messari_-Tether-USDT-Likely-to-Surpass-Bitcoin-as-the-Dominant-Cryptocurrency.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Messari: Tether (USDT) Likely to Surpass Bitcoin as the Dominant Cryptocurrency" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/Messari_-Tether-USDT-Likely-to-Surpass-Bitcoin-as-the-Dominant-Cryptocurrency.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/Messari_-Tether-USDT-Likely-to-Surpass-Bitcoin-as-the-Dominant-Cryptocurrency-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/Messari_-Tether-USDT-Likely-to-Surpass-Bitcoin-as-the-Dominant-Cryptocurrency-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/Messari_-Tether-USDT-Likely-to-Surpass-Bitcoin-as-the-Dominant-Cryptocurrency-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>Tether (USDT) recently lost its peg to the U.S. dollar. Although USDT is the most valuable stablecoin by market cap, the market turbulence did not spare the asset.</p>



<p>Last week, USDT depegged below $1 and stayed below the $1 peg for the longest time since the collapse of FTX, before making a recovery at the end of the week.</p>



<p>Selling pressure is still significantly higher than the previous week, as trading volume has dropped by 77% over the last 24 hours, while market cap progressively heds value.</p>



<p>However, the cryptocurrency has succeeded in clearing off hourly losses. According to data from CoinMarketCap, USDT is now trading at a press time price of $0.9996.</p>



<p>It bears mentioning that it wasn’t all chaos for the stablecoin. According to MessariCrypto, a leading provider of crypto market intelligence products, USDT saw a major change in the movement of its circulating supply.</p>



<p>On previous occasions when USDT had traded below $1, Tether’s market cap dropped significantly. This time, USDT’s redemptions surged to levels last seen in 2022 while supply remained stable.</p>



<p>As Messari explained;</p>



<p><em>“USDT also saw the highest amount of redemptions ($325m) since November 2022. Unlike previous depegs, where Tether&#8217;s market cap decreased significantly as redemptions rose, USDT&#8217;s circulating supply remained at similar levels.” </em></p>



<p>The instability comes not long after Tether rolled out its newly attained milestones from the second quarter of 2023. As the report noted, the company generated more than $1 billion in operating profits.</p>



<p><em>“Tether’s operational profits are over $1B for the period of April 2023 to June 2023, which corresponds to a significant 30% increase quarter over quarter.” The report read. </em></p>



<p>Additionally, Tether’s $72.5B in exposure to US T-bills is greater than Australia, Mexico, and the UAE. Tether also holds an estimated 8.5% of its total assets in Bitcoin, other precious metals, and other investments in energy production.</p>



<p>Tether also made efforts to tackle the continuous scepticism surrounding its current reserve levels, stating that its reserves are extremely liquid.</p>



<p>The CTO of Tether, Paolo Ardoino, went on to explain that transparency is not just a buzzword for the Tether network. “It [transparency] is the cornerstone of our philosophy.” He stated.</p>



<p>Conclusively, Messari maintains that despite the instability of Tether and the USDT stablecoin, Tether’s market shares are larger than it has ever been.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/despite-usdts-recent-depeg-tethers-market-share-is-larger-than-its-ever-been/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Coinbase Officially Launches Crypto Services In Canada</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/coinbase-officially-launches-crypto-services-in-canada/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/coinbase-officially-launches-crypto-services-in-canada/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Brenda Ngari]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 19:01:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[canada]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=83677</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Coinbase-Officially-Launches-Crypto-Services-In-Canada.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Coinbase Officially Launches Crypto Services In Canada" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Coinbase-Officially-Launches-Crypto-Services-In-Canada.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Coinbase-Officially-Launches-Crypto-Services-In-Canada-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Coinbase-Officially-Launches-Crypto-Services-In-Canada-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Coinbase-Officially-Launches-Crypto-Services-In-Canada-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>Crypto exchange Coinbase has announced the expansion of its services to Canadian citizens, strengthening its already outstanding stronghold on the North American market.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Coinbase-Officially-Launches-Crypto-Services-In-Canada.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Coinbase Officially Launches Crypto Services In Canada" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Coinbase-Officially-Launches-Crypto-Services-In-Canada.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Coinbase-Officially-Launches-Crypto-Services-In-Canada-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Coinbase-Officially-Launches-Crypto-Services-In-Canada-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Coinbase-Officially-Launches-Crypto-Services-In-Canada-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>Crypto exchange Coinbase has announced the expansion of its services to Canadian citizens, strengthening its already outstanding stronghold on the North American market.</p>



<p>For its newly unveiled subscription service, Coinbase One, the exchange will waive membership fees for Canadian nationals for the first 30 days in an effort to onboard new users.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-coinbase-lands-in-canada"><strong>Coinbase Lands In Canada</strong></h2>



<p>Coinbase is making waves in Canada amid a promising local crypto regulatory climate.</p>



<p>Coinbase’s Canadian users are primed to enjoy a seamless transaction experience, thanks to an integration of Interac payment rails in partnership with local financial services firm Peoples Trust Company — which is part of Peoples Group.</p>



<p>“Coinbase is now providing access to Interac e-Transfers<em>® *</em> to 100% of Canadian Coinbase users, making it secure and simpler than ever to move money in and out of your account,” the Monday <a href="https://investor.coinbase.com/news/news-details/2023/Coinbase-Accelerates-International-Expansion-with-Official-Launch-in-Canada/default.aspx#:~:text=Through%20its%20partnership%20with%20Peoples,and%20out%20of%20your%20account">announcement </a>said.&nbsp;</p>



<p>Coinbase’s official entry into Canada also introduces its Coinbase One subscription product, bringing a couple of advantages to the Canadian cryptoverse, including zero trading fees, boosted staking rewards, and priority customer support. As an introductory offer, Coinbase is giving Canadian users a free 30-day trial.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-why-coinbase-is-expanding-in-canada-despite-rival-exits"><strong>Why Coinbase Is Expanding In Canada Despite Rival Exits</strong></h2>



<p>Coinbase explained that it has expanded its crypto services to Canada owing to the country’s high “crypto-awareness” along with what it believes is a robust regulatory framework.</p>



<p>According to Coinbase, Canada is presently the world&#8217;s third-most crypto-aware nation. In fact, the crypto exchange said it sees the Canadian market as its next “go deep” market, citing a report from the Ontario Securities Commission that claims more than 30% of Canadians said they’ll purchase cryptocurrencies within the year.</p>



<p>“Canada is well positioned to be a global leader in the crypto economy thanks to the high levels of crypto awareness, a passionate local tech ecosystem, and the progress towards a strong regulatory framework,” Coinbase&#8217;s Vice President for International and Business Development, Nana Murugesan, opined.</p>



<p>Further bolstering its commitment to Canadian users, Coinbase has named Lucas Matheson as the new Canadian Country Director. The firm is also strengthening its tech presence in the region by establishing a tech hub and investing in local startups.</p>



<p>Coinbase’s entrance to the Canadian market comes despite the recent exits of digital asset exchange competitors like <a href="https://www.reuters.com/technology/binance-will-proactively-withdraw-canada-2023-05-12/">Binance</a>, OKX, and Bybit, citing tightening regulations in the country. </p>



<p>Notably, Coinbase is <a href="https://zycrypto.com/coinbase-suffers-double-whammy-as-sec-and-state-regulators-act-against-exchange-for-unregistered-securities/">embroiled </a>in a lawsuit with the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) back at home, for allegedly failing to register as a securities exchange and broker, along with allegedly offering unregistered security tokens to its users.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/coinbase-officially-launches-crypto-services-in-canada/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Analyst Bullish on Chainlink as Whales Increase LINK Holdings</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/analyst-bullish-on-chainlink-as-whales-increase-link-holdings/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/analyst-bullish-on-chainlink-as-whales-increase-link-holdings/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aaron Feuerstein]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 21:22:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ChainLink]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LINKUSD]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=83664</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Chainlink-Targets-New-Highs-After-Release-Of-Updated-Roadmap-For-Introduction-Of-Staking.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Chainlink Targets New Highs After Release Of Updated Roadmap For Introduction Of Staking" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Chainlink-Targets-New-Highs-After-Release-Of-Updated-Roadmap-For-Introduction-Of-Staking.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Chainlink-Targets-New-Highs-After-Release-Of-Updated-Roadmap-For-Introduction-Of-Staking-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Chainlink-Targets-New-Highs-After-Release-Of-Updated-Roadmap-For-Introduction-Of-Staking-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Chainlink-Targets-New-Highs-After-Release-Of-Updated-Roadmap-For-Introduction-Of-Staking-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>Whales eager to stock up on LINK seem to have recognized Chainlink’s strength by acquiring over $90 million worth of the asset.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Chainlink-Targets-New-Highs-After-Release-Of-Updated-Roadmap-For-Introduction-Of-Staking.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Chainlink Targets New Highs After Release Of Updated Roadmap For Introduction Of Staking" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Chainlink-Targets-New-Highs-After-Release-Of-Updated-Roadmap-For-Introduction-Of-Staking.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Chainlink-Targets-New-Highs-After-Release-Of-Updated-Roadmap-For-Introduction-Of-Staking-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Chainlink-Targets-New-Highs-After-Release-Of-Updated-Roadmap-For-Introduction-Of-Staking-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Chainlink-Targets-New-Highs-After-Release-Of-Updated-Roadmap-For-Introduction-Of-Staking-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>Analyst Ali Martinez recently shared his thoughts about the price trajectory of LINK, the native cryptocurrency of oracle network <a href="https://zycrypto.com/chainlink-whales-splurge-over-100-million-on-link-buys-amid-surging-developer-activity/">Chainlink</a>. He wrote on ‘X’ (formerly Twitter) that Chainlink maintained support between $6.63 and $6.88, highlighting that 29,000 addresses bought 295 million LINK worth over $2 billion. Whales eager to stock up on LINK seem to have recognized Chainlink’s strength by acquiring over $90 million worth of the asset.</p>



<p>In his view, the outlook for LINK remains strong as long as it can keep above those levels, as very little in terms of barriers is in its path. He added that traders might not be as happy as long-term holders as <em>“On-chain data shows a decrease in network activity in the past three weeks, with the number of large transactions going from 527 to 118. Still, a spike in this metric might indicate a breakout.”</em></p>



<p>Data analytics platform Santiment echoes the positive attitude, stating, “Chainlink’s GitHub development activity has been notably higher this summer, leading to the asset cracking the top five most frequently developed assets,” further highlighting the bullish outlook. </p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-ccip-gaining-momentum"><strong>CCIP Gaining Momentum</strong></h2>



<p>Chainlink, of course, has some promising developments, for example, the partnership with SWIFT, the bank transfer network currently testing the eagerly anticipated Cross-Chain Interoperability Protocol (CCIP). This collaboration aims to connect financial institutions to blockchains using CCIP, which Chainlink&#8217;s co-founder Sergey Nazarov sees as a bridge between various chains, much like TCP/IP for finance.</p>



<p>CCIP&#8217;s security model is rooted in Chainlink&#8217;s reliable pricing oracles, known for thwarting risks like flash-loan attacks. CCIP&#8217;s availability on testnets like Ethereum and Polygon reflects Chainlink paving the way for CCIP&#8217;s wider adoption on the mainnet. Chainlink received validation from Coinbase when it became clear that its layer 2 BASE would use Chainlink as a price feed.</p>



<p>&#8220;Chainlink Price Feeds are one of the leading price data solutions for developers when it comes to security, reliability, and usability,&#8221; said Coinbase Head of Protocols Jesse Pollak, who also holds responsible for creating BASE.</p>



<p>Chainlink Price Feeds will allow developers to transition their current application to BASE, based on Ethereum but with much lower gas fees and in a highly scalable environment. This will provide developers with opportunities to enhance the capabilities of BASE by offering reliable price data and expanding the potential applications that can be built on its advanced infrastructure.</p>



<p>Additionally, a project by Lendvest aims to integrate CCIP for its decentralized credit scoring system. CCIP allows secure communication between blockchains, letting Lendvest aggregate borrowing and lending data from Ethereum and Avalanche. This integration will offer accurate credit scores through a secure and decentralized blockchain protocol, improving transparency and lending mechanisms in DeFi.</p>



<p>In a statement, Lendvest said: <em>“Currently, there is no established credit score framework that provides material benefits to crypto users. Lendvest aggregates on-chain data to create decentralized data feeds to form a verifiable credit score for DeFi protocols.”</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/analyst-bullish-on-chainlink-as-whales-increase-link-holdings/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Whales Load Up Their Bags as Price Teases Crucial $31,000 Resistance — A Breakout Incoming?</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/bitcoin-whales-load-up-their-bags-as-price-teases-crucial-31000-resistance-a-breakout-incoming/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/bitcoin-whales-load-up-their-bags-as-price-teases-crucial-31000-resistance-a-breakout-incoming/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Newton Gitonga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 18:32:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XBTUSD]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=83661</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/Whales-Are-Gobbling-Up-Bitcoin-Even-With-The-Recent-Market-Slump.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Whales Are “Gobbling Up” Bitcoin Even With The Recent Market Slump" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/Whales-Are-Gobbling-Up-Bitcoin-Even-With-The-Recent-Market-Slump.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/Whales-Are-Gobbling-Up-Bitcoin-Even-With-The-Recent-Market-Slump-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/Whales-Are-Gobbling-Up-Bitcoin-Even-With-The-Recent-Market-Slump-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/Whales-Are-Gobbling-Up-Bitcoin-Even-With-The-Recent-Market-Slump-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>Amidst a downturn in cryptocurrency market volatility, Bitcoin appears to be staging a pivotal showdown as its price flirts with a significant resistance level of $31,000.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/Whales-Are-Gobbling-Up-Bitcoin-Even-With-The-Recent-Market-Slump.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Whales Are “Gobbling Up” Bitcoin Even With The Recent Market Slump" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/Whales-Are-Gobbling-Up-Bitcoin-Even-With-The-Recent-Market-Slump.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/Whales-Are-Gobbling-Up-Bitcoin-Even-With-The-Recent-Market-Slump-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/Whales-Are-Gobbling-Up-Bitcoin-Even-With-The-Recent-Market-Slump-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/Whales-Are-Gobbling-Up-Bitcoin-Even-With-The-Recent-Market-Slump-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>Amidst a downturn in cryptocurrency market volatility, <a href="https://zycrypto.com/billionaire-investor-david-rubenstein-wishes-he-had-bought-bitcoin-at-100-for-this-sole-reason/">Bitcoin</a> appears to be staging a pivotal showdown as its price flirts with a significant resistance level of $31,000. As market participants hold their breath for a potential breakout, intriguing developments involving Bitcoin whales have added fuel to the speculative fire.</p>



<p>JA Maartunn, the community manager at the crypto analytics firm Cryptoquant, set the stage for anticipation with a tweet earlier this Sunday. Maartunn&#8217;s message highlighted a noticeable uptick in activity among Bitcoin whales, particularly those on the BitMEX crypto exchange.</p>



<p><em>&#8220;Bitmex whales have joined the party. During the last night, I&#8217;ve got 3 notifications from massive new long positions Something is brewing under the surface,&#8221;</em> said Maartunn.</p>



<p>This sentiment was echoed by the pundit’s previous observation on Saturday, highlighting substantial long positions on another notable exchange, Deribit. These observations point towards an atmosphere of anticipation, as major players seem to position themselves strategically in response to market dynamics.</p>



<p>Adding to the intrigue, prominent crypto analyst Ali Martinez provided additional weight to the idea of imminent market movements. In a Saturday tweet, Martinez highlighted the historical correlation between spikes in buy volume on BitMEX and Bitcoin&#8217;s subsequent price movements. According to the pundit, the recent surge in the taker buy-sell ratio on BitMEX raises the possibility of a continuation of the ongoing Bitcoin <a href="https://zycrypto.com/mike-novogratz-reveals-two-catalysts-for-bitcoin-to-surge-back-to-all-time-highs/">bull market</a>.</p>



<p><em>“You rarely see big spikes in buy volume on BitMEX, but when you do, $BTC tends to enjoy significant gains. In May 2020, the taker buy-sell ratio rose to 192, leading to a 567% price increase. And in January 2023, the taker buy-sell ratio spiked to 140, resulting in an 88% price jump,”</em> wrote Ali.</p>



<p><em>“Notice that the taker buy-sell ratio on BitMEX recently surged to 194. If history repeats itself, we could be preparing for the continuation of the BTC bull market,”</em> he added.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img decoding="async" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/0HTaUaQMOVXP8U6BNdVSUtzwM1wgp8bh-pgkvyW0RA-Nio_1ZGt1XkHKdtdUM1bC-GWJ2MVGxY5Pl9vuhbxhOW5_93AnCRjmgNQzcA5FyaQEGfI4ACSZfnATlxkt7RWtLZzys5iCNezP9_0WGyuWRQ" alt=""/></figure>



<p>The excitement doesn&#8217;t end there, as Martinez also revealed a fascinating development involving Bitcoin whales. As per a Sunday tweet from the pundit, in the last two weeks, approximately 10 Bitcoin whales, each holding a minimum of 1,000 BTC (equivalent to at least $29.4 million), have entered the network.</p>



<p>Such a notable influx of substantial holders brings a new dimension of uncertainty to the market landscape, potentially signalling that these whales are either seeking diversification for their portfolios or simply increasing their Bitcoin holdings.</p>



<p>That said, technically, Bitcoin seems poised to take out the $31,000 considering the price has been in a macro uptrend. Recently, veteran markets analyst Sonny Moulder <a href="https://twitter.com/MulderSonny/status/1688817860217307136">predicted</a> a larger move by Bitcoin toward the $45,000 region. But first, the pundit noted that strategically clearing weaker market participants is essential.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="594" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-1024x594.png" alt="" class="wp-image-83662" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-1024x594.png 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-300x174.png 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-768x445.png 768w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-1536x891.png 1536w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-2048x1188.png 2048w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /><figcaption class="wp-element-caption">BTCUSD Chart by <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BTCUSD/">TradingView</a></figcaption></figure>



<p>BTC was trading at $29,379 at press time after a mild drop of 0.39% over the past 24 hours.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/bitcoin-whales-load-up-their-bags-as-price-teases-crucial-31000-resistance-a-breakout-incoming/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Filing Reveals Donald Trump Holds $250,000-$500,000 Worth Of Ethereum</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/filing-reveals-donald-trump-holds-250000-500000-worth-of-ethereum/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/filing-reveals-donald-trump-holds-250000-500000-worth-of-ethereum/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Newton Gitonga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 17:57:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=83656</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Filing-Reveals-Donald-Trump-Holds-250000-500000-Worth-Of-Ethereum.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Filing Reveals Donald Trump Holds $250,000-$500,000 Worth Of Ethereum" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Filing-Reveals-Donald-Trump-Holds-250000-500000-Worth-Of-Ethereum.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Filing-Reveals-Donald-Trump-Holds-250000-500000-Worth-Of-Ethereum-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Filing-Reveals-Donald-Trump-Holds-250000-500000-Worth-Of-Ethereum-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Filing-Reveals-Donald-Trump-Holds-250000-500000-Worth-Of-Ethereum-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>A recent financial disclosure has revealed that former U.S. President Donald Trump holds a substantial Ethereum portfolio, estimated to be valued between $250,000 and $500,000.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Filing-Reveals-Donald-Trump-Holds-250000-500000-Worth-Of-Ethereum.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Filing Reveals Donald Trump Holds $250,000-$500,000 Worth Of Ethereum" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Filing-Reveals-Donald-Trump-Holds-250000-500000-Worth-Of-Ethereum.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Filing-Reveals-Donald-Trump-Holds-250000-500000-Worth-Of-Ethereum-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Filing-Reveals-Donald-Trump-Holds-250000-500000-Worth-Of-Ethereum-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Filing-Reveals-Donald-Trump-Holds-250000-500000-Worth-Of-Ethereum-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>A recent financial disclosure has revealed that former U.S. President Donald Trump holds a substantial Ethereum portfolio, estimated to be valued between $250,000 and $500,000.</p>



<p>The revelation, which had recently remained away from the public eye, has sparked intense speculation about Trump&#8217;s motivations and potential aspirations, given his <a href="https://zycrypto.com/former-us-president-donald-trump-has-just-revealed-latest-stance-on-bitcoin-cryptos/">historical skepticism</a> towards the cryptocurrency realm. Notably, the disclosure has ignited discussions around Trump&#8217;s possible foray into the world of decentralized finance (DeFi) and cryptocurrencies, which have garnered significant attention due to their promise of anonymity and efficient fundraising mechanisms.</p>



<p>The allure of DeFi platforms, in particular, lies in their ability to facilitate seamless transactions without a centralized intermediary, potentially enabling Trump to gather funds discreetly and securely for his 2024 presidential campaign, especially considering his continued bad blood with the Biden administration.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img decoding="async" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-ZiVmgknWiT2QobWbIPbnVExTmvakBKxEEUogTgClCmGz-kjSc0p-yVh6bZmYzKwe1TnaNM28oCSnZU84xC-Kai0Hf9ObZRQNuDcCQ0KltlAw8kNZHukr6cv22KP6V5ZV0bd5CoflaL1aN66c0DCSWj5LN9ZlrTBIm0CKgh7gn5kGY2jfDGAlpXofYw-J3VXC1jj1nw9tw" alt=""/></figure>



<p>Notably, the recent development is marked by a striking contrast to Trump&#8217;s remarks about cryptocurrencies. In the past, the former US president publicly criticized digital currencies, even labelling them a &#8220;scam&#8221; and asserting that they were a disaster waiting to happen. Interestingly, Trump would later soften his stand with his involvement in NFTs, although emphasizing he was in them for the art, not the money.</p>



<p>Further scrutiny of Trump&#8217;s recent cryptocurrency holdings reveals a connection to non-fungible tokens (NFTs). The asset listed in Trump&#8217;s disclosure as a &#8220;cryptocurrency wallet (Ethereum)&#8221; is linked to a collection of NFTs he launched post his presidential tenure. These NFTs took the form of unique digital trading cards, portraying Trump in various distinctive attires, ranging from a hunter&#8217;s camouflage to a superhero costume. The NFT collection garnered immense attention and quickly sold out, generating close to $10 million in sales. Trump&#8217;s share of the earnings from this venture amounted to about $300,000 in licensing fees.</p>



<p>While a sum in the hundreds of thousands might be inconsequential for someone with a net worth of approximately $2.5 billion, Trump&#8217;s involvement in cryptocurrency-related ventures underscores his willingness to explore new revenue streams. Notably, his wife, Melania Trump, has had a good relationship with cryptocurrencies, even <a href="https://zycrypto.com/melania-trump-celebrates-bitcoin-despite-donald-trump-predicting-an-ultimate-crypto-explosion/">praising Bitcoin</a> once on hitting its 13<sup>th</sup> year since the Genesis block. The former first lady was also involved with various NFT-related ventures, including partnering with crypto payments firm Moonpay for her NFT line.</p>



<p>With the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) intensifying its scrutiny of the cryptocurrency industry, it remains noteworthy that the regulatory agency has largely steered clear of intervening in the NFT sector, under which Trump&#8217;s NFT venture falls. Consequently, any potential legal ramifications from his cryptocurrency-related activities appear relatively limited. Trump&#8217;s involvement thus underscores the increasingly complex and dynamic relationship between influential figures and digital assets.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/filing-reveals-donald-trump-holds-250000-500000-worth-of-ethereum/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>New All-Time High Envisioned For XRP Price Even As SEC Seeks To Appeal Landmark Ripple Ruling</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/new-all-time-high-envisioned-for-xrp-price-even-as-sec-seeks-to-appeal-landmark-ripple-ruling/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/new-all-time-high-envisioned-for-xrp-price-even-as-sec-seeks-to-appeal-landmark-ripple-ruling/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aaron Feuerstein]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 18:33:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=83638</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/New-All-Time-High-Envisioned-For-XRP-Price-Even-As-SEC-Seeks-To-Appeal-Landmark-Ripple-Ruling.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="New All-Time High Envisioned For XRP Price Even As SEC Seeks To Appeal Landmark Ripple Ruling" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/New-All-Time-High-Envisioned-For-XRP-Price-Even-As-SEC-Seeks-To-Appeal-Landmark-Ripple-Ruling.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/New-All-Time-High-Envisioned-For-XRP-Price-Even-As-SEC-Seeks-To-Appeal-Landmark-Ripple-Ruling-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/New-All-Time-High-Envisioned-For-XRP-Price-Even-As-SEC-Seeks-To-Appeal-Landmark-Ripple-Ruling-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/New-All-Time-High-Envisioned-For-XRP-Price-Even-As-SEC-Seeks-To-Appeal-Landmark-Ripple-Ruling-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>While initial reactions to this have been negative, with some spreading “fear, uncertainty, and doubt” (FUD) that XRP’s status as a non-security may be under threat, this is clearly not the case.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/New-All-Time-High-Envisioned-For-XRP-Price-Even-As-SEC-Seeks-To-Appeal-Landmark-Ripple-Ruling.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="New All-Time High Envisioned For XRP Price Even As SEC Seeks To Appeal Landmark Ripple Ruling" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/New-All-Time-High-Envisioned-For-XRP-Price-Even-As-SEC-Seeks-To-Appeal-Landmark-Ripple-Ruling.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/New-All-Time-High-Envisioned-For-XRP-Price-Even-As-SEC-Seeks-To-Appeal-Landmark-Ripple-Ruling-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/New-All-Time-High-Envisioned-For-XRP-Price-Even-As-SEC-Seeks-To-Appeal-Landmark-Ripple-Ruling-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/New-All-Time-High-Envisioned-For-XRP-Price-Even-As-SEC-Seeks-To-Appeal-Landmark-Ripple-Ruling-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>XRP price is slightly up on the 24-hour timeframe while having retracted 4% in the past week, according to data from CoinMarketCap. This price development seems optimistic, given that the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has just filed a motion for leave to <a href="https://zycrypto.com/xrp-hanging-by-a-thread-as-sec-finally-moves-for-appeal-against-ripple-what-to-expect-next/">file an interlocutory appeal</a>.</p>



<p>While initial reactions to this have been negative, with some spreading “fear, uncertainty, and doubt” (FUD) that XRP’s status as a non-security may be under threat, this is clearly not the case. Judge Torres ruled that XRP is not a security and cited the SEC v Telegram case to establish digital assets like XRP as commodities. However, the focus of the SEC&#8217;s appeal pertains to allegations against Ripple and its executives regarding programmatic and individual XRP sales rather than individual peer-to-peer trading activities on exchanges.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-institutional-investors-see-ruling-positive-for-altcoins"><strong>Institutional Investors See Ruling Positive for Altcoins</strong></h2>



<p>According to a recent report, Fineqia International Inc., a well-known fintech and digital asset investment business, saw an increase in investor interest, which led to a 70% increase in the total Assets Under Management (AUM) for worldwide Exchange Traded Products (ETPs) related to digital assets.</p>



<p>The AUM increased by 70% this year to $34 billion at the end of July, exceeding the 47.7% increase in the underlying value of digital assets. During July, there was an inflow of funds into cryptocurrencies, notably XRP, which witnessed a 57% gain in AUM after the SEC v. Ripple Labs decision.</p>



<p>It should be noted that, unsurprisingly, Bitcoin and Ethereum still dominate the digital asset and fintech investment business. As Fineqia CEO Bundeep Singh Rangar puts it, <em>&#8220;Despite net inflows, the fact that more than 90% of digital asset ETP AUMs comprise of Bitcoin (BTC) and Ethereum (ETH) weighed down on the value of AUMs&#8221;.</em></p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-can-the-sec-win-on-appeal"><strong>Can the SEC Win on Appeal?</strong></h2>



<p>Regarding the certification for interlocutory appeal by the SEC, Ripple can still respond before Judge Torres casts her judgment. And even then, the chances of success for the agency are modest, as many legal commentators have noted. MetaLawMan<a href="https://twitter.com/MetaLawMan/status/1689654814219833344"> stated</a> on “X” that he believes it to be a close call, adding that interlocutory appeals have a low success rate but that <em>“Judge Rakoff&#8217;s decision in the Terraform Labs case makes it far more likely that Judge Torres will take that unusual step and certify the interlocutory appeal”.</em></p>



<p>So, will XRP return to all-time highs above $3 in the foreseeable future? While no one can predict the future, XRP and the XRPL use cases must be closely monitored as crypto adoption increases. For example, developments such as the <a href="https://zycrypto.com/palau-stablecoin-advances-to-next-phase-on-xrpl-transitioning-from-island-paradise-to-blockchain-frontier/">Palau Stablecoin project</a> and Ripple joining the International Swaps and Derivatives Association (ISDA) <a href="https://zycrypto.com/pundit-highlights-possibility-of-xrp-price-at-1800-as-ripple-enters-1-quadrillion-derivatives-market/">create euphoria</a>. One should note, however, that these developments, especially in the case of ISDA, do not impact XRP in the short term, and the investment in cryptocurrencies bears considerable risk.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/new-all-time-high-envisioned-for-xrp-price-even-as-sec-seeks-to-appeal-landmark-ripple-ruling/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>US SEC Slammed for Misusing XRP Reports in Ripple Lawsuit</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/us-sec-slammed-for-misusing-xrp-reports-in-ripple-lawsuit/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/us-sec-slammed-for-misusing-xrp-reports-in-ripple-lawsuit/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Marco Tulio]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 18:19:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=83633</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Legal-Expert-Has-‘No-Doubt-Ripple-Will-Win-Legal-War-Against-SEC-—-Can-It-Supercharge-XRP-To-1.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Legal Expert Has ‘No Doubt’ Ripple Will Win Legal War Against SEC — Can It Supercharge XRP To $1?" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Legal-Expert-Has-‘No-Doubt-Ripple-Will-Win-Legal-War-Against-SEC-—-Can-It-Supercharge-XRP-To-1.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Legal-Expert-Has-‘No-Doubt-Ripple-Will-Win-Legal-War-Against-SEC-—-Can-It-Supercharge-XRP-To-1-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Legal-Expert-Has-‘No-Doubt-Ripple-Will-Win-Legal-War-Against-SEC-—-Can-It-Supercharge-XRP-To-1-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Legal-Expert-Has-‘No-Doubt-Ripple-Will-Win-Legal-War-Against-SEC-—-Can-It-Supercharge-XRP-To-1-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>Ripple CEO Brad Garlinghouse recently criticized the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) for misinterpreting the company&#8217;s quarterly XRP market reports. Garlinghouse pointed out that the SEC used these reports against Ripple in the lawsuit, despite the fact that the company was never required to publish them. Nevertheless, they started doing so to provide transparency [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Legal-Expert-Has-‘No-Doubt-Ripple-Will-Win-Legal-War-Against-SEC-—-Can-It-Supercharge-XRP-To-1.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Legal Expert Has ‘No Doubt’ Ripple Will Win Legal War Against SEC — Can It Supercharge XRP To $1?" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Legal-Expert-Has-‘No-Doubt-Ripple-Will-Win-Legal-War-Against-SEC-—-Can-It-Supercharge-XRP-To-1.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Legal-Expert-Has-‘No-Doubt-Ripple-Will-Win-Legal-War-Against-SEC-—-Can-It-Supercharge-XRP-To-1-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Legal-Expert-Has-‘No-Doubt-Ripple-Will-Win-Legal-War-Against-SEC-—-Can-It-Supercharge-XRP-To-1-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Legal-Expert-Has-‘No-Doubt-Ripple-Will-Win-Legal-War-Against-SEC-—-Can-It-Supercharge-XRP-To-1-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>Ripple CEO Brad Garlinghouse recently criticized the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) for misinterpreting the company&#8217;s quarterly XRP market reports.</p>



<p>Garlinghouse pointed out that the SEC used these reports against Ripple in the lawsuit, despite the fact that the company was never required to publish them. Nevertheless, they started doing so to provide transparency about their XRP holdings.</p>



<p><em>&#8220;We began these reports voluntarily to provide updates on our XRP holdings. Unfortunately, they were used against us in the SEC lawsuit. However, we remain committed to transparency, though I expect they will look different going forward.&#8221;</em></p>



<p>Garlinghouse&#8217;s statements were supported by Ripple&#8217;s attorney, John E Deaton, who <a href="https://twitter.com/JohnEDeaton1/status/1686627185774166016">explained</a> on Twitter that the reports were published for transparency and not out of obligation, as Ripple, being a private company, was not required to share them.</p>



<p><em>&#8220;It is absolutely true that the SEC used the transparency of these reports against Ripple and its two executives. As a private company, Ripple was under no obligation to share this info. Other companies not only didn&#8217;t share token sales, but intentionally disguised those transactions.&#8221;</em></p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-the-sec-used-ripple-s-report-against-them"><strong>The SEC used Ripple&#8217;s report against them</strong></h2>



<p>The SEC attempted to use the information from Ripple&#8217;s XRP report against the company during the lawsuit, making allegations of fraud and market manipulation. This is despite the fact that the transparency of the reports was precisely intended to prove the opposite.</p>



<p>In the latest report for the second quarter of 2023, Ripple announced that it would change the format of the reports to focus on clarifying misunderstandings and providing transparency about its XRP holdings.</p>



<p>For example, Ripple highlighted that most of the monthly releases of XRP from the escrow account will be redeposited to be accessed in the future rather than being sold on the open market. However, Garlinghouse clarified that they may change the focus of the reports due to the SEC&#8217;s recent actions.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-the-sec-vs-ripple-case-is-still-ongoing"><strong>The SEC vs. Ripple case is still ongoing</strong></h2>



<p>On July 13, Ripple secured one of its <a href="https://zycrypto.com/ripple-to-expand-presence-in-u-s-market-after-xrp-court-win-top-executive-reveals-big-plans/">major victories</a> in the case against the SEC, as Judge Analisa Torres ruled in favor of Ripple, determining that XRP cannot be considered an unregistered security. This led to major exchanges such as Coinbase, Bitstamp, and Kraken relisting XRP for U.S. users.</p>



<p>XRP had been delisted from many platforms due to the SEC&#8217;s lawsuit filed in December 2020 and its intense regulatory scrutiny against cryptocurrency companies and exchanges, negatively impacting its price since then.</p>



<p>However, following Judge Torres&#8217; ruling, the price of XRP experienced an <a href="https://zycrypto.com/xrp-eyes-monster-move-as-ripple-seeks-crypto-license-in-ireland-and-uk-following-courtroom-win/">impressive increase</a> of 99.84%, going from approximately $0.47 to a peak of $0.93 in a day. Currently, the price of XRP stands at $0.66, representing a 41% increase since Judge Torres&#8217; ruling.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img decoding="async" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/k8ZWdCINTbd6dG6LZOW7YnUrtzKZ0IT5838eOt_aBl_tcRk-pj8V8KZxzSaH0DHKlG0NHBiLI9xnM1KF4n2z3cvfaupkvXX1wtijvqw2j7EM9Nz8D-dXF2keFIdkp6DmbB1ivjTlkBCbfr-WlToNQ_M" alt=""/></figure>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/us-sec-slammed-for-misusing-xrp-reports-in-ripple-lawsuit/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>XRPL Ecosystem With Impressive Gains: Sidechain Success and Revenue Growth</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/xrpl-ecosystem-with-impressive-gains-sidechain-success-and-revenue-growth/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/xrpl-ecosystem-with-impressive-gains-sidechain-success-and-revenue-growth/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aaron Feuerstein]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 17:54:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=83630</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/XRP-Army-Sees-Bullish-Prospects-As-Ripple-Starts-EVM-Compatibility-Tests-On-Its-XRPL-Sidechain.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="XRP Army Sees Bullish Prospects As Ripple Starts EVM Compatibility Tests On Its XRPL Sidechain" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/XRP-Army-Sees-Bullish-Prospects-As-Ripple-Starts-EVM-Compatibility-Tests-On-Its-XRPL-Sidechain.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/XRP-Army-Sees-Bullish-Prospects-As-Ripple-Starts-EVM-Compatibility-Tests-On-Its-XRPL-Sidechain-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/XRP-Army-Sees-Bullish-Prospects-As-Ripple-Starts-EVM-Compatibility-Tests-On-Its-XRPL-Sidechain-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/XRP-Army-Sees-Bullish-Prospects-As-Ripple-Starts-EVM-Compatibility-Tests-On-Its-XRPL-Sidechain-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>According to a new report by crypto analytics company Messari, the XRPL ecosystem, underpinned by the XRP Ledger, has recently experienced tremendous growth and accomplishments. Despite sharing a slight decline in Q2, the circulating market cap of XRP has seen an impressive year-to-date (YTD) increase of 42.5%. This growth can be attributed mainly to the [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/XRP-Army-Sees-Bullish-Prospects-As-Ripple-Starts-EVM-Compatibility-Tests-On-Its-XRPL-Sidechain.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="XRP Army Sees Bullish Prospects As Ripple Starts EVM Compatibility Tests On Its XRPL Sidechain" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/XRP-Army-Sees-Bullish-Prospects-As-Ripple-Starts-EVM-Compatibility-Tests-On-Its-XRPL-Sidechain.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/XRP-Army-Sees-Bullish-Prospects-As-Ripple-Starts-EVM-Compatibility-Tests-On-Its-XRPL-Sidechain-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/XRP-Army-Sees-Bullish-Prospects-As-Ripple-Starts-EVM-Compatibility-Tests-On-Its-XRPL-Sidechain-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/XRP-Army-Sees-Bullish-Prospects-As-Ripple-Starts-EVM-Compatibility-Tests-On-Its-XRPL-Sidechain-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>According to a new report by crypto analytics company Messari, the XRPL ecosystem, underpinned by the XRP Ledger, has recently experienced tremendous growth and accomplishments. Despite sharing a slight decline in Q2, the circulating market cap of XRP has seen an impressive year-to-date (YTD) increase of 42.5%. This growth can be attributed mainly to the significant surge witnessed in Q1. Although Q2 saw a 10.7% dip in market cap, the overall growth trajectory remains robust and promising.</p>



<p>The XRP Ledger (XRPL), a decentralised payment system, has operated for more than ten years and enables rapid, secure, and energy-efficient cross-border and cross-currency payments. The XRPL provides a range of features, including native-issued currencies, a decentralized exchange (DEX), escrow capabilities, and token administration. XRP, the native coin of the XRPL, holds a market capitalization of $24.8 billion, positioning it as the sixth-largest cryptocurrency in Q2 2023.</p>



<p>Notably, the average daily volume of nonfungible token (NFT) transactions on the XRPL has increased significantly. Daily NFT transactions increased by 12.7% in Q2 to 15,500 from 13,800 in the prior quarter. This highlights XRPL&#8217;s dominance and success in the NFT and decentralised finance (DeFi) ecosystems. The NFTokenCreateOffer transaction type now accounts for over 50% of all NFT transactions, further strengthening XRPL&#8217;s position as the industry leader.</p>



<p>The average daily transactions and active addresses on the XRPL decreased in Q2, but it nonetheless kept exploring new opportunities for expansion and improvement. For developers of XRPL, the arrival of sidechains like Coreum and Root Network has created attractive new opportunities. In contrast to Root Network, which focuses on advancing innovations in the metaverse, Coreum focuses on security tokenization. These sidechains improve programmability, enabling programmers to explore new blockchain application domains.</p>



<p>The advancements in the EVM sidechain and XLS-38d bridge greatly supplement sidechain efforts. Developers are testing a novel consensus algorithm, transfers between issued currencies and ERC-20s, and more. These developments help to increase the XRPL&#8217;s functionality and make it easier for it to interact with other blockchain networks seamlessly.</p>



<p>The XRPL network has experienced a net growth in accounts even if average daily transactions and active addresses have decreased. In Q2, the overall number of accounts increased by 0.7% to 4.68 million. While deleted addresses saw a considerable increase, driven primarily by activity from the Poloniex exchange, new addresses stayed fairly stable.</p>



<p>The daily active addresses (DAA) metric may be skewed by the XRPL&#8217;s distinctive address system, which supports destination tags and accommodates many users within a single address. However, a trustworthy metric of token adoption and usage on the XRPL continues to be the number of daily active addresses.</p>



<p>The ecosystem of the XRPL goes beyond the XRP Ledger, including partnerships and collaborations advancing blockchain research and innovation. Notably, Ripple&#8217;s University Blockchain Research Initiative (UBRI) has partnerships with seven of the world&#8217;s top 10 university blockchain programs. This partnership between Ripple and prominent academic institutions promotes scholarly investigation, technological advancement, and innovation in the blockchain and cryptocurrency industries.</p>



<p>Success and development at the XRPL have not been immune from market trends and outside influences. Price movements for the XRPL have been impacted by developments in the current SEC litigation against Ripple, which started in 2020. However, the XRPL&#8217;s tenacity and expansion highlight its potential in the constantly changing cryptocurrency sector.</p>



<p>In conclusion, the XRPL ecosystem shows tremendous growth, supported by a boost in NFT transactions and the circulating market cap. Adding sidechains and partnerships with academic institutions strengthen XRPL&#8217;s reputation as a leader in blockchain technology. Despite a fall in Q2 network activity numbers, the XRPL&#8217;s dedication to scalability, interoperability, and creative solutions is unshakable.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/xrpl-ecosystem-with-impressive-gains-sidechain-success-and-revenue-growth/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Analyst On Why Ethereum Flipping Bitcoin Won&#8217;t Happen Anytime Soon</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/analyst-on-why-ethereum-flipping-bitcoin-wont-happen-anytime-soon/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/analyst-on-why-ethereum-flipping-bitcoin-wont-happen-anytime-soon/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Olivia Brooke]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 13:51:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XBTUSD]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=83625</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Analyst-On-Why-Ethereum-Flipping-Bitcoin-Wont-Happen-Anytime-Soon.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Analyst On Why Ethereum Flipping Bitcoin Won&#039;t Happen Anytime Soon" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Analyst-On-Why-Ethereum-Flipping-Bitcoin-Wont-Happen-Anytime-Soon.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Analyst-On-Why-Ethereum-Flipping-Bitcoin-Wont-Happen-Anytime-Soon-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Analyst-On-Why-Ethereum-Flipping-Bitcoin-Wont-Happen-Anytime-Soon-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Analyst-On-Why-Ethereum-Flipping-Bitcoin-Wont-Happen-Anytime-Soon-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>While many Ether proponents remain convinced that the altcoin will overthrow Bitcoin, a prominent figure in the cryptocurrency market asserts that Ether still has a long way to go.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Analyst-On-Why-Ethereum-Flipping-Bitcoin-Wont-Happen-Anytime-Soon.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Analyst On Why Ethereum Flipping Bitcoin Won&#039;t Happen Anytime Soon" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Analyst-On-Why-Ethereum-Flipping-Bitcoin-Wont-Happen-Anytime-Soon.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Analyst-On-Why-Ethereum-Flipping-Bitcoin-Wont-Happen-Anytime-Soon-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Analyst-On-Why-Ethereum-Flipping-Bitcoin-Wont-Happen-Anytime-Soon-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Analyst-On-Why-Ethereum-Flipping-Bitcoin-Wont-Happen-Anytime-Soon-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>While many <a href="https://zycrypto.com/ethereum-whale-burns-2500-eth-crypto-community-questions-motive/">Ether</a> proponents remain convinced that the altcoin will overthrow Bitcoin, a prominent figure in the cryptocurrency market asserts that Ether still has a long way to go.</p>



<p>After the Ethereum network successfully carried out the highly anticipated merge, market players were on the lookout for a massive price rally that could result in Ether overthrowing Bitcoin in the long term.</p>



<p>However, a prominent crypto market analyst, Benjamin Cowen, has pushed back on these sentiments. Cowen noted that the ETH/BTC pairs have steadily declined since the merge.</p>



<p>“<em>The flippening narrative gets promoted a lot, and more so following the merge. But if the merge were a game changer that would lead to ETH flipping BTC, why has ETH / BTC been putting in lower highs and lower lows since the merge? Narratives are fun. Price action is king.”</em> Cowen wrote.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">The flippening narrative gets promoted a lot, and more so following the merge.<br><br>But if the merge were a game changer that would lead to ETH flipping BTC, why has <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/ETH?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#ETH</a> / <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/BTC?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#BTC</a> been putting in lower highs and lower lows since the merge?<br><br>Narratives are fun.<br><br>Price action is king. <a href="https://t.co/7VGv9p6CZX">pic.twitter.com/7VGv9p6CZX</a></p>&mdash; Benjamin Cowen (@intocryptoverse) <a href="https://twitter.com/intocryptoverse/status/1689074298026065920?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">August 9, 2023</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>While the merge has not triggered a flippening, it has enhanced Ethereum’s overall performance. The Merge was the co-joining of the Ethereum mainnet (the original execution layer of the Ethereum network) with the Beacon Chain (Proof of Stake blockchain).</p>



<p><a href="https://zycrypto.com/the-merge-goes-live-and-a-new-era-for-ethereum-begins-heres-the-whole-bushel/">The merge was essential</a> for Ethereum to fix some of its longstanding scalability issues. After the merge, Ethereum’s carbon footprint reduced significantly, while the network sustained security using staked ETH.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-market-participants-are-bullish-on-ether-nbsp"><strong>Market participants are bullish on Ether&nbsp;</strong></h2>



<p>The analyst’s comments come not long after a recent survey conducted by CryptoVantage found that 47% of Ether investors were hopeful that Ether will dethrone Bitcoin. For the survey, CryptoVantage interviewed 1,000 North Americans who also happen to have invested in Ether over the past five years.</p>



<p>Although there is no telling what could happen in the long term, the near-term predictions are notably bullish. Back in July, Fidelity Digital Assets rolled out its Q2 2023 Signals Report. The report highlighted a positive outlook for Ether, stating that the next 12 months are highly promising for the asset.</p>



<p>It is worth noting that Ether (ETH) has already seen its year-to-date gains surge by 62%, despite the constant fluctuation in price value.</p>



<p>At report time, Ether is trading for $1,851. The asset has sustained mild losses over the last 24 hours, although the bulls have successfully cleared out weekly losses.</p>



<p>On the other hand, Bitcoin is heading towards the $30,000 price mark after momentum last month. Bitcoin is now valued at a press time price of $29,410.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/analyst-on-why-ethereum-flipping-bitcoin-wont-happen-anytime-soon/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cardano Whales Loading Up as ADA Price Maintains Sideways Movement</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/cardano-whales-loading-up-as-ada-price-maintains-sideways-movement/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/cardano-whales-loading-up-as-ada-price-maintains-sideways-movement/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aaron Feuerstein]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 13:30:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADAUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=83623</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Cardano-Set-To-Get-A-Major-Performance-Upgrade-On-Valentines-Day-—-ADA-Boom-On-The-Way.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Cardano Set To Get A Major Performance Upgrade On Valentine’s Day — ADA Boom On The Way?" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Cardano-Set-To-Get-A-Major-Performance-Upgrade-On-Valentines-Day-—-ADA-Boom-On-The-Way.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Cardano-Set-To-Get-A-Major-Performance-Upgrade-On-Valentines-Day-—-ADA-Boom-On-The-Way-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Cardano-Set-To-Get-A-Major-Performance-Upgrade-On-Valentines-Day-—-ADA-Boom-On-The-Way-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Cardano-Set-To-Get-A-Major-Performance-Upgrade-On-Valentines-Day-—-ADA-Boom-On-The-Way-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>Data from blockchain analytics platform Santiment shows whales are eagerly stocking up on ADA, Cardano’s native cryptocurrency.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Cardano-Set-To-Get-A-Major-Performance-Upgrade-On-Valentines-Day-—-ADA-Boom-On-The-Way.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Cardano Set To Get A Major Performance Upgrade On Valentine’s Day — ADA Boom On The Way?" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Cardano-Set-To-Get-A-Major-Performance-Upgrade-On-Valentines-Day-—-ADA-Boom-On-The-Way.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Cardano-Set-To-Get-A-Major-Performance-Upgrade-On-Valentines-Day-—-ADA-Boom-On-The-Way-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Cardano-Set-To-Get-A-Major-Performance-Upgrade-On-Valentines-Day-—-ADA-Boom-On-The-Way-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Cardano-Set-To-Get-A-Major-Performance-Upgrade-On-Valentines-Day-—-ADA-Boom-On-The-Way-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>Data from blockchain analytics platform Santiment shows <a href="https://zycrypto.com/cardano-whales-re-emerge-as-on-chain-transactions-hit-6-month-high-1-ada-price-incoming/">whales are eagerly stocking up on ADA</a>, Cardano’s native cryptocurrency. The numbers of ADA added to existing wallets which hold between 100,000 and 10 million ADA, have soared to heights last seen in September 2022.</p>



<p>Santiment wrote: <em>“As Cardano sits just above $0.29, whales and sharks holding between 100K-10M $ADA have accumulated back to their highest level since September, 2022. Additionally, on-chain transaction volume has been rising nearly every week for the past 6 months.”</em></p>



<p>Despite the legal woes caused by the SEC’s blanket assumption that dozens of cryptocurrencies, including ADA, are securities, daily trading volumes have steadily risen to over 67 billion ADA. The whales and sharks in question have amassed $116.1 million more in ADA since May 21 of 2023.</p>



<p>The renewed interest has, however, attracted bad actors, it seems. According to some in the Cardano community, a potential rug pull of 60,000 ADA has occurred, it seems the associated Twitter account from blockchainmages has since been deleted.</p>



<p>Popular community member Cardano Whale, who regularly buys hundreds of thousands of ADA worth of DeFi (decentralized finance) tokens to jump-start emerging projects on Cardano, was among the victims, it appears.</p>



<p>The ADA whale said on Twitter: <em>“I have to own this one. Been too naive again.”</em> Prompting a timely reminder of the pitfalls that still exist in crypto. Of course, 60k ADA seems negligible compared to the over 600 million ADA that makes up the Cardano DeFi space, according to data from DefiLama.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-cardano-developments-gain-momentum"><strong>Cardano Developments Gain Momentum</strong></h2>



<p>Nevertheless, the increased interest during this bear market also comes from some interesting developments in the Cardano ecosystem. Currently, in the second last stage of development, called Basho, the network now focuses on scalability and predictability before the previous phase, Voltaire targets governance.</p>



<p>The main projects right now are Hydra which, as a layer 2 solution, increases scalability and resource utilization; Mithril, on the other hand, improves the speed and throughput of nodes on the network. Additionally, side chains will free up the main chain while optimizations will change block structure, leading to fewer resources being tied up on-chain.</p>



<p>Further, in late July, <a href="https://zycrypto.com/cardano-ada-network-achieves-zero-downtime-milestone-amidst-high-user-engagement/">Cardano achieved the milestone of zero downtime</a> in over 2,130 days, highlighting the network&#8217;s track record of reliability. At the time of writing, ADA traded for $0.29, a slight plus of 1% in the past 24 hours, according to CoinMarketCap.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/cardano-whales-loading-up-as-ada-price-maintains-sideways-movement/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
