<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>News Archives &#8902; ZyCrypto</title>
	<atom:link href="https://zycrypto.com/category/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://zycrypto.com/category/news/</link>
	<description>ZyCrypto Is A Cryptocurrency News Media, Focusing On Daily News, Expert Opinions, Analysis, Reviews, And So Much More.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 22:20:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/cropped-ZyCrypto-Site-Logo-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News Archives &#8902; ZyCrypto</title>
	<link>https://zycrypto.com/category/news/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Turkey Takes the Lead: Crypto Ownership Surges by 27%, Making it the Fastest-Growing Crypto Market</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/turkey-takes-the-lead-crypto-ownership-surges-by-27-making-it-the-fastest-growing-crypto-market/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/turkey-takes-the-lead-crypto-ownership-surges-by-27-making-it-the-fastest-growing-crypto-market/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aaron Feuerstein]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 22:20:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Turkey]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=81120</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/The-Death-Of-The-Lira-Is-Fueling-A-Massive-Spike-In-Bitcoin-USDT-Activity-In-Turkey.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="The &quot;Death Of The Lira&quot; Is Fueling A Massive Spike In Bitcoin, USDT Activity In Turkey" decoding="async" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/The-Death-Of-The-Lira-Is-Fueling-A-Massive-Spike-In-Bitcoin-USDT-Activity-In-Turkey.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/The-Death-Of-The-Lira-Is-Fueling-A-Massive-Spike-In-Bitcoin-USDT-Activity-In-Turkey-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/The-Death-Of-The-Lira-Is-Fueling-A-Massive-Spike-In-Bitcoin-USDT-Activity-In-Turkey-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/The-Death-Of-The-Lira-Is-Fueling-A-Massive-Spike-In-Bitcoin-USDT-Activity-In-Turkey-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>Turkey has seen a huge increase in cryptocurrency ownership as the country&#8217;s inflation rates skyrocket, according to GWI Research. With a 27.1% increase in ownership from July-September 2021 to July-September 2022, Turkey had the biggest growth in cryptocurrency ownership, according to the survey, which looked at people between the ages of 16 and 64. Argentina [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/The-Death-Of-The-Lira-Is-Fueling-A-Massive-Spike-In-Bitcoin-USDT-Activity-In-Turkey.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="The &quot;Death Of The Lira&quot; Is Fueling A Massive Spike In Bitcoin, USDT Activity In Turkey" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/The-Death-Of-The-Lira-Is-Fueling-A-Massive-Spike-In-Bitcoin-USDT-Activity-In-Turkey.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/The-Death-Of-The-Lira-Is-Fueling-A-Massive-Spike-In-Bitcoin-USDT-Activity-In-Turkey-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/The-Death-Of-The-Lira-Is-Fueling-A-Massive-Spike-In-Bitcoin-USDT-Activity-In-Turkey-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/The-Death-Of-The-Lira-Is-Fueling-A-Massive-Spike-In-Bitcoin-USDT-Activity-In-Turkey-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>Turkey has seen a huge increase in cryptocurrency ownership as the country&#8217;s inflation rates skyrocket, according to GWI Research. With a 27.1% increase in ownership from July-September 2021 to July-September 2022, <a href="https://zycrypto.com/ripple-to-donate-1-million-in-xrp-to-earthquake-victims-in-turkey-and-syria/">Turkey</a> had the biggest growth in cryptocurrency ownership, according to the survey, which looked at people between the ages of 16 and 64. Argentina and the Philippines were close behind, with increases of 23.5% and 23.4% in crypto ownership rates.</p>



<p>The soaring inflation rates in these nations can be blamed for the rise in crypto possession. The Turkish Lira had a sharp collapse in late 2021, losing 44% of its value in relation to the US dollar. Early in 2022, the country&#8217;s inflation rate exceeded 30%; by the end of the year, it was a startling 72.31%. The daily trading volume of cryptocurrencies in Turkey reached an average of $1.8 billion due to these economic considerations.</p>



<p>The use of cryptocurrencies in these nations has broad ramifications. Over 2.4 million Turks, or about 2.94% of the population, are now considered Bitcoin owners. The devaluation of the Turkish Lira, which impacted many Turkish families&#8217; savings and investments, has improved the environment for the adoption of cryptocurrencies. Additionally, the Turkish populace has come to favour cryptocurrencies due to their simplicity of use and perception of them as a hedge against inflation.</p>



<p>Trading is the only available alternative for people interested in the field due to Turkey&#8217;s lack of a regulatory framework, which has allowed cryptocurrency trading to grow. However, as the government prepares to introduce its central bank&#8217;s digital currency, the digital lira, in 2023, regulatory adjustments are anticipated in the upcoming years. Higher taxes and more precise regulations for cryptocurrency-related activity are predicted, yet a total ban on cryptocurrencies seems unlikely.</p>



<p>A loss of faith in fiat money and demand for alternative stores of value in Argentina and the Philippines has also sparked the popularity of cryptocurrencies. The public&#8217;s increased interest in cryptocurrencies is a sign that digital assets are becoming more widely accepted and that decentralised financial systems are becoming more prevalent.</p>



<p>Significant trading volumes are seen on major Turkish cryptocurrency exchanges like BtcTurk and Paribu, indicating that the rise in cryptocurrency ownership in these nations is not going unnoticed. Another sign of cryptocurrencies&#8217; expanding societal influence is their growth into other industries, like sports sponsorship and university courses.</p>



<p>Cryptocurrencies have become popular for people looking to secure their wealth as the global economy struggles with the pandemic&#8217;s aftermath and inflationary pressures. The rise in cryptocurrency ownership in Turkey, Argentina, and the Philippines demonstrates the growing acceptance and acknowledgement of cryptocurrencies as an alternative financial tool in times of economic upheaval, even though difficulties and concerns still exist.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/turkey-takes-the-lead-crypto-ownership-surges-by-27-making-it-the-fastest-growing-crypto-market/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ripple Launches A Novel Platform For Governments, Central Banks Developing CBDCs</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/ripple-launches-a-novel-platform-for-governments-central-banks-developing-cbdcs/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/ripple-launches-a-novel-platform-for-governments-central-banks-developing-cbdcs/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Brenda Ngari]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 20:23:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=81109</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Montenegro-Joins-Hands-With-Ripple-To-Pilot-First-National-Digital-Currency-—-Mammoth-Boost-to-XRP.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Montenegro Joins Hands With Ripple To Pilot First National Digital Currency — Mammoth Boost to XRP?" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Montenegro-Joins-Hands-With-Ripple-To-Pilot-First-National-Digital-Currency-—-Mammoth-Boost-to-XRP.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Montenegro-Joins-Hands-With-Ripple-To-Pilot-First-National-Digital-Currency-—-Mammoth-Boost-to-XRP-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Montenegro-Joins-Hands-With-Ripple-To-Pilot-First-National-Digital-Currency-—-Mammoth-Boost-to-XRP-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Montenegro-Joins-Hands-With-Ripple-To-Pilot-First-National-Digital-Currency-—-Mammoth-Boost-to-XRP-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>Described as “a frictionless end-to-end solution”, the new platform is based on Ripple's XRP Ledger and is an improved version of Ripple's Private Ledger.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Montenegro-Joins-Hands-With-Ripple-To-Pilot-First-National-Digital-Currency-—-Mammoth-Boost-to-XRP.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Montenegro Joins Hands With Ripple To Pilot First National Digital Currency — Mammoth Boost to XRP?" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Montenegro-Joins-Hands-With-Ripple-To-Pilot-First-National-Digital-Currency-—-Mammoth-Boost-to-XRP.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Montenegro-Joins-Hands-With-Ripple-To-Pilot-First-National-Digital-Currency-—-Mammoth-Boost-to-XRP-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Montenegro-Joins-Hands-With-Ripple-To-Pilot-First-National-Digital-Currency-—-Mammoth-Boost-to-XRP-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Montenegro-Joins-Hands-With-Ripple-To-Pilot-First-National-Digital-Currency-—-Mammoth-Boost-to-XRP-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>San Francisco-based blockchain payments firm <a href="https://zycrypto.com/ripple-acquires-crypto-custody-provider-metaco-for-250m-as-xrp-lawsuit-nears-end-game/">Ripple</a> has introduced a platform for governments, central banks, and financial institutions to create their own digital currency. Described as “a frictionless end-to-end solution”, the new platform is based on Ripple&#8217;s XRP Ledger and is an improved version of Ripple&#8217;s Private Ledger.</p>



<p>Ripple has also joined forces with the Hong Kong Monetary Authority, which acts as the defacto central bank, for the launch of the digital Hong Kong dollar (e-HKD) pilot program.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-what-is-the-point-of-ripple-s-new-cbdc-platform"><strong>What Is The Point Of Ripple’s New CBDC Platform?</strong></h2>



<p>CBDCs are a hot topic right now. Unlike crypto assets like Bitcoin or Ethereum, CBDCs are controlled and managed by a centralized entity. Per the Atlantic Council’s tracker, only 11 nations have rolled out a central bank digital currency so far, but many other countries are researching and testing the technology.</p>



<p>Ripple has waded further into the CBDC game via the launch of a new platform for creating blockchain-based digital currencies. The Ripple platform allows for the oversight and customization of the entire life cycle of the CBDC, including minting, distribution, redemption, and removal from circulation. The CBDC platform will also let institutions operate and conduct inter-institutional settlement and distribution functions.</p>



<p>Ripple will leverage the power of blockchain technology used for the <a href="https://zycrypto.com/automated-market-makers-finally-coming-to-xrpl-why-this-feature-could-be-super-bullish-for-1-xrp-price/">XRP Ledger</a> and provide a way for government institutions to increase financial inclusion and reduce the risk involved in domestic and cross-border payments.</p>



<p>President of the Republic of Palau, Surangel Whipps Jr, hailed Ripple’s new CBDC platform while describing how it’s enabling them to create their own solutions.</p>



<p>“<em>Partnering with Ripple to help create our national digital currency is part of our commitment to lead in financial innovation and technologies, which will provide the citizens of Palau with greater financial access”.</em></p>



<p>It will be possible for financial institutions to use the platform to oversee the distribution processes involving their digital currency, while end users — both corporate and retail — will be able to hold their CBDC securely and use them to pay and receive payment for goods and services, similar to how banking apps function today. This entails the convenience of offline transactions and as well as accommodating non-smartphone cases.</p>



<p>Ripple is also collaborating with Taiwan’s Fubon Bank to develop a real estate asset tokenization and equity release product using a retail version of the e-HKD CBDC.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/ripple-launches-a-novel-platform-for-governments-central-banks-developing-cbdcs/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Pakistan Announces Ban on Cryptocurrency Services and Firm Stance Against Legalizing Crypto Trading</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/pakistan-announces-ban-on-cryptocurrency-services-and-firm-stance-against-legalizing-crypto-trading/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/pakistan-announces-ban-on-cryptocurrency-services-and-firm-stance-against-legalizing-crypto-trading/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aaron Feuerstein]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 20:06:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[pakistan]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=81104</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Pakistan-Announces-Ban-on-Cryptocurrency-Services-and-Firm-Stance-Against-Legalizing-Crypto-Trading.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Pakistan Announces Ban on Cryptocurrency Services and Firm Stance Against Legalizing Crypto Trading" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Pakistan-Announces-Ban-on-Cryptocurrency-Services-and-Firm-Stance-Against-Legalizing-Crypto-Trading.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Pakistan-Announces-Ban-on-Cryptocurrency-Services-and-Firm-Stance-Against-Legalizing-Crypto-Trading-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Pakistan-Announces-Ban-on-Cryptocurrency-Services-and-Firm-Stance-Against-Legalizing-Crypto-Trading-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Pakistan-Announces-Ban-on-Cryptocurrency-Services-and-Firm-Stance-Against-Legalizing-Crypto-Trading-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>Aisha Ghaus Pasha, the minister of state for finance and revenue, declared that Pakistan would outlaw cryptocurrency services operating in the country and reaffirmed that the government has no plans to legalize cryptocurrency trading during a meeting of the Senate Standing Committee on Finance and Revenue on May 16.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Pakistan-Announces-Ban-on-Cryptocurrency-Services-and-Firm-Stance-Against-Legalizing-Crypto-Trading.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Pakistan Announces Ban on Cryptocurrency Services and Firm Stance Against Legalizing Crypto Trading" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Pakistan-Announces-Ban-on-Cryptocurrency-Services-and-Firm-Stance-Against-Legalizing-Crypto-Trading.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Pakistan-Announces-Ban-on-Cryptocurrency-Services-and-Firm-Stance-Against-Legalizing-Crypto-Trading-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Pakistan-Announces-Ban-on-Cryptocurrency-Services-and-Firm-Stance-Against-Legalizing-Crypto-Trading-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Pakistan-Announces-Ban-on-Cryptocurrency-Services-and-Firm-Stance-Against-Legalizing-Crypto-Trading-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>Aisha Ghaus Pasha, the minister of state for finance and revenue, declared that <a href="https://zycrypto.com/ripple-adoption-gets-major-boost-after-first-in-market-remittance-corridor-between-uae-and-pakistan-opens/">Pakistan</a> would outlaw cryptocurrency services operating in the country and reaffirmed that the government has no plans to legalize cryptocurrency trading during a meeting of the Senate Standing Committee on Finance and Revenue on May 16. </p>



<p>This attitude has been featured in numerous local media stories, and other officials, such as the Director of the State Bank of Pakistan (SBP), Sohail Jawad, have supported the choice. This article examines Pakistan&#8217;s stance on cryptocurrencies and their effects on the local cryptocurrency market.</p>



<p>The declaration by Minister Aisha Ghaus Pasha underscores Pakistan&#8217;s steadfast opposition to cryptocurrencies and its choice to outlaw their use. The government is most worried about potential cryptocurrency threats, like money laundering, financing of terrorism, and illegal activity. Pakistan wants to reduce these risks and safeguard its financial system and populace by enacting a ban.</p>



<p>Pakistan&#8217;s move to outlaw cryptocurrency services is motivated by a number of issues. First of all, the decentralized and anonymous nature of cryptocurrencies creates difficulties for governmental supervision and raises questions about possible abuse. Additionally, investors face risks due to the volatility and speculative character of cryptocurrencies, which may result in financial instability. The government claims to protect its citizens from these dangers by limiting access to crypto services.</p>



<p>The prohibition on cryptocurrency services has also received the approval of the State Bank of Pakistan, the nation&#8217;s national bank. Among other officials, SBP Director Sohail Jawad has emphasized the necessity of preserving the stability of Pakistan&#8217;s financial system and the possible dangers posed by cryptocurrencies. The government&#8217;s decision to outlaw crypto services in the nation was further supported by the SBP&#8217;s support of that position.</p>



<p>The Financial Action Task Force (FATF), despite not having the authority to impose sanctions on non-compliant nations, has a considerable impact on corporate and governmental policy globally. Pakistan, which is undergoing an economic crisis and negotiating a bailout with the International Monetary Fund, may prioritise receiving a positive FATF evaluation. Both the FATF and the IMF have raised concerns over crypto numerous times.</p>



<p>Pakistan has experienced significant cryptocurrency adoption despite the government&#8217;s objections, with its residents reportedly having $20 billion worth of cryptocurrencies in 2021. Since at least January, the State Bank of Pakistan has been pushing for a cryptocurrency ban. However, Pakistan recently established a national blockchain &#8216;Know Your Customer&#8217; infrastructure and aims to introduce a central bank digital currency in 2025.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/pakistan-announces-ban-on-cryptocurrency-services-and-firm-stance-against-legalizing-crypto-trading/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Did Satoshi Nakamoto Envision the NFT Era? Early JPEG Sale Suggests So</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/did-satoshi-nakamoto-envision-the-nft-era-early-jpeg-sale-suggests-so/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/did-satoshi-nakamoto-envision-the-nft-era-early-jpeg-sale-suggests-so/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Newton Gitonga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 15:18:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Featured]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Satoshi Nakamoto]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=81099</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Did-Satoshi-Nakamoto-Envision-the-NFT-Era-Early-JPEG-Sale-Suggests-So.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Did Satoshi Nakamoto Envision the NFT Era? Early JPEG Sale Suggests So" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Did-Satoshi-Nakamoto-Envision-the-NFT-Era-Early-JPEG-Sale-Suggests-So.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Did-Satoshi-Nakamoto-Envision-the-NFT-Era-Early-JPEG-Sale-Suggests-So-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Did-Satoshi-Nakamoto-Envision-the-NFT-Era-Early-JPEG-Sale-Suggests-So-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Did-Satoshi-Nakamoto-Envision-the-NFT-Era-Early-JPEG-Sale-Suggests-So-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>Despite still being fairly new, non-fungible tokens (NFTs) have taken the art and digital collectables market by storm. However, according to a recent finding, it appears that Bitcoin creator Satoshi Nakamoto anticipated this trend long before NFTs became a household name.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Did-Satoshi-Nakamoto-Envision-the-NFT-Era-Early-JPEG-Sale-Suggests-So.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Did Satoshi Nakamoto Envision the NFT Era? Early JPEG Sale Suggests So" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Did-Satoshi-Nakamoto-Envision-the-NFT-Era-Early-JPEG-Sale-Suggests-So.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Did-Satoshi-Nakamoto-Envision-the-NFT-Era-Early-JPEG-Sale-Suggests-So-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Did-Satoshi-Nakamoto-Envision-the-NFT-Era-Early-JPEG-Sale-Suggests-So-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Did-Satoshi-Nakamoto-Envision-the-NFT-Era-Early-JPEG-Sale-Suggests-So-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>Despite still being fairly new, non-fungible tokens (NFTs) have taken the art and digital collectables market by storm. However, according to a recent finding, it appears that Bitcoin creator Satoshi Nakamoto anticipated this trend long before NFTs became a household name.</p>



<p>The revelation came to light when Udi Wertheimer, a prominent figure in the crypto community, made an intriguing discovery in a post on the original Bitcointalk forum. On May 14, Wertheimer tweeted about finding evidence of the first-ever real-world Bitcoin payment made in 2010 to purchase an NFT.</p>



<p>The <a href="https://bitcointalk.org/index.php?topic=25.0">post</a> in question was made by a pseudonymous user named &#8220;Sabunir&#8221; on the Bitcointalk forum on January 24, 2010. Sabunir announced plans to sell a JPEG image for $1 worth of Bitcoin, which amounted to a staggering 500 BTC at the time. He then posted his address, telling any interested buyer to send him a private message.</p>



<p>Interestingly, Satoshi Nakamoto responded to the post, giving recommendations on how the seller would execute the sale using Bitcoin. Satoshi suggested sending BTC to a merchant&#8217;s static IP address with a comment or creating a new BTC address for the transaction. He even mentioned that this method could become the “standard way” for website software to handle such transactions.&nbsp;</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="248" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-18-1024x248.png" alt="" class="wp-image-81100" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-18-1024x248.png 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-18-300x73.png 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-18-768x186.png 768w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-18-1536x372.png 1536w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-18.png 1600w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>And while the discussion lacks conclusive evidence of a sale, ZyCrypto conducted an inquiry into the address and discovered a <a href="https://www.blockchain.com/explorer/addresses/btc/1BHtsCnpmTvpgJEP7eMKEVhpJFunxSM8vq">transaction</a> of 500 Bitcoin on 02/24/2010. This means that if this transaction is indeed connected to the image&#8217;s sale, it will precede the well-known first Bitcoin transaction of <a href="https://zycrypto.com/btc-reclaims-30000-as-crypto-community-celebrates-12th-anniversary-of-bitcoin-pizza-day/">10,000 for 2 pizzas</a>, which took place on 05/22/2010.</p>



<p>However, the claim of the NFT sale has been disputed by various observers, with Wertheimer suggesting that the JPEG sale was never executed, despite 500 BTC being sent to that address a month after the sale offer was made.</p>



<p><em>“It is possible that the 500 BTC were sent as a donation for a different interaction and that the JPEG sale was never executed. Only one way to know for sure… maybe one day Sabunir comes back and tells us what really happened,” </em>Wertheimer tweeted on Sunday, May 14.</p>



<p>Despite the uncertainty surrounding the specific transaction, some believe that Satoshi Nakamoto&#8217;s assistance and guidance in executing the potential sale implies his support for the concept of NFTs.</p>



<p><em>“The most notable thing of all is that Satoshi treated this all like it was the most normal thing in the world. He&#8217;d have absolutely been pro-ordinals,”</em> Mike McDonald <a href="https://twitter.com/MikeMcDonald89/status/1657862722317369344">tweeted</a>, responding to Wertheimer’s post.</p>



<p>Notably, Satoshi’s actions align with the actions of early Bitcoin developer <a href="https://zycrypto.com/remembering-the-life-of-hal-finney-early-bitcoin-user-who-received-the-first-bitcoin-transaction-from-satoshi-nakamoto/">Hal Finney</a>, who <a href="https://twitter.com/bullishbyte/status/1657882459567009792">received</a> the first Bitcoin transaction from Satoshi and expressed interest in &#8220;Crypto trading cards&#8221; in a 1993 email.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/did-satoshi-nakamoto-envision-the-nft-era-early-jpeg-sale-suggests-so/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>XRP Eyes &#8216;Monster Move&#8217; As New Lawsuit Outcomes Set Ripple On Path To Gigantic Win Against The SEC</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/xrp-eyes-monster-move-as-new-lawsuit-outcomes-set-ripple-on-path-to-gigantic-win-against-the-sec/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/xrp-eyes-monster-move-as-new-lawsuit-outcomes-set-ripple-on-path-to-gigantic-win-against-the-sec/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Erie Maxwell]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 18:44:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=81070</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/06/Ripples-Brad-Garlinghouse-Isnt-Taking-His-Feet-Off-SECs-Neck-Anytime-Soon-For-XRPs-Struggles.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Ripple&#039;s Brad Garlinghouse Isn&#039;t Taking His Feet Off SEC&#039;s Neck Anytime Soon For XRP’s Struggles" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/06/Ripples-Brad-Garlinghouse-Isnt-Taking-His-Feet-Off-SECs-Neck-Anytime-Soon-For-XRPs-Struggles.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/06/Ripples-Brad-Garlinghouse-Isnt-Taking-His-Feet-Off-SECs-Neck-Anytime-Soon-For-XRPs-Struggles-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/06/Ripples-Brad-Garlinghouse-Isnt-Taking-His-Feet-Off-SECs-Neck-Anytime-Soon-For-XRPs-Struggles-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/06/Ripples-Brad-Garlinghouse-Isnt-Taking-His-Feet-Off-SECs-Neck-Anytime-Soon-For-XRPs-Struggles-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>The SEC vs Ripple case has taken yet another intriguing turn, as Ripple's...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/06/Ripples-Brad-Garlinghouse-Isnt-Taking-His-Feet-Off-SECs-Neck-Anytime-Soon-For-XRPs-Struggles.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Ripple&#039;s Brad Garlinghouse Isn&#039;t Taking His Feet Off SEC&#039;s Neck Anytime Soon For XRP’s Struggles" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/06/Ripples-Brad-Garlinghouse-Isnt-Taking-His-Feet-Off-SECs-Neck-Anytime-Soon-For-XRPs-Struggles.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/06/Ripples-Brad-Garlinghouse-Isnt-Taking-His-Feet-Off-SECs-Neck-Anytime-Soon-For-XRPs-Struggles-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/06/Ripples-Brad-Garlinghouse-Isnt-Taking-His-Feet-Off-SECs-Neck-Anytime-Soon-For-XRPs-Struggles-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/06/Ripples-Brad-Garlinghouse-Isnt-Taking-His-Feet-Off-SECs-Neck-Anytime-Soon-For-XRPs-Struggles-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>The SEC vs Ripple case has taken yet <a href="https://zycrypto.com/xrp-lawsuit-sees-new-twists-and-turns-as-ripples-counsel-exposes-secs-slippery-slope-in-crypto-regulation/">another intriguing turn</a>, as Ripple&#8217;s legal officer Stuart Alderoty reveals new findings that go against the SEC&#8217;s arguments. Alderoty took to Twitter to make the statement, sharing his perspective on the SEC&#8217;s position and highlighting a past case that serves as a precedent for the Ripple lawsuit.</p>



<p>In his tweet, Alderoty referenced a 1946 Supreme Court case known as &#8220;Howey”, where the SEC unsuccessfully argued that an investment in a &#8220;common enterprise&#8221; was unnecessary if there was a &#8220;community of interest.&#8221; Alderoty argued that the SEC was wrong then and is still wrong now, stating that &#8220;Common Interest ≠ Common Enterprise.&#8221; This statement suggests that Ripple&#8217;s case is grounded in legal precedent, giving them a solid foundation to challenge the SEC&#8217;s claims.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-ripple-vs-sec-what-s-been-going-on"><strong>Ripple vs SEC: What’s Been Going On?</strong></h2>



<p>Ripple, a blockchain-based payment protocol, has been embroiled in a lawsuit with the SEC since December 2020 over allegations of selling unregistered securities. The Ripple lawsuit has been a topic of interest for many in the crypto world, as it has significant implications for the industry. The SEC alleges that Ripple and its executives engaged in selling unregistered securities, a violation of US securities laws.</p>



<p>Ripple has maintained its innocence in the case and has been fighting to have the lawsuit dismissed. The company claims that XRP, its native cryptocurrency, is not a security and, therefore, not subject to SEC regulation. Ripple has also accused the SEC of causing &#8220;multi-billion dollar losses to innocent third parties&#8221; through its actions against the company.</p>



<p>The case has been ongoing for over a year, with both parties presenting their arguments in court. However, Alderoty&#8217;s tweet suggests that Ripple&#8217;s legal team isn&#8217;t backing down and is continuing to build its case against the SEC. The reference to the &#8220;Howey&#8221; case is significant because it established the legal test for determining whether an asset is a security. If Ripple can show that XRP does not meet the &#8220;Howey&#8221; test, then it could be a <a href="https://zycrypto.com/what-a-ripple-sec-possible-settlement-could-mean-for-xrp-as-game-changing-ruling-nears/">game-changer</a> for the entire cryptocurrency industry.</p>



<p>The case has seen several developments in recent months, including a ruling by the court allowing Ripple to depose former SEC official William Hinman, who allegedly made comments indicating that XRP was not a security. The SEC has fought against Hinman&#8217;s deposition, arguing that it would be &#8220;unreasonable and oppressive.&#8221;</p>



<p>The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission’s motion to seal the controversial William Hinman Ethereum speech docs has <a href="https://zycrypto.com/groundbreaking-ripple-win-in-xrp-case-looking-likely-as-court-rejects-secs-request-to-keep-hinman-docs-hidden/">just been rejected</a> by Judge Analisa Torres — a move hailed by Ripple CEO Brad Garlinghouse as a remarkable step toward transparency.</p>



<p>It&#8217;s worth noting that the SEC&#8217;s case against Ripple has been controversial, with many in the crypto community criticizing the agency for its handling of the matter. Some have accused the SEC of attempting to regulate the crypto industry through litigation rather than through the proper channels of rule-making and legislation.</p>



<p>Despite the twists and turns of the case, it is clear that both Ripple and the SEC are taking the matter seriously. The lawsuit&#8217;s outcome will have far-reaching implications for the crypto industry, and it&#8217;s anyone&#8217;s guess which way it will go. However, with Stuart Alderoty and the rest of Ripple&#8217;s legal team continuing to build their case, it seems likely that the case will continue to make headlines for some time.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/xrp-eyes-monster-move-as-new-lawsuit-outcomes-set-ripple-on-path-to-gigantic-win-against-the-sec/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tether To Invest 15% Of Its Net Monthly Profits in Bitcoin</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/tether-to-invest-15-of-its-net-monthly-profits-in-bitcoin/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/tether-to-invest-15-of-its-net-monthly-profits-in-bitcoin/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Newton Gitonga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 18:28:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=81066</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Despite-U.S.-Treasury-Blacklisting-Tether-Wont-Freeze-Tornado-Cash-Addresses.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Despite U.S. Treasury Blacklisting, Tether Won’t Freeze Tornado Cash Addresses" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Despite-U.S.-Treasury-Blacklisting-Tether-Wont-Freeze-Tornado-Cash-Addresses.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Despite-U.S.-Treasury-Blacklisting-Tether-Wont-Freeze-Tornado-Cash-Addresses-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Despite-U.S.-Treasury-Blacklisting-Tether-Wont-Freeze-Tornado-Cash-Addresses-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Despite-U.S.-Treasury-Blacklisting-Tether-Wont-Freeze-Tornado-Cash-Addresses-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>Tether, the firm behind the world’s largest stablecoin USDT, has revealed plans to allocate 15% of its net monthly profits towards purchasing Bitcoin.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Despite-U.S.-Treasury-Blacklisting-Tether-Wont-Freeze-Tornado-Cash-Addresses.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Despite U.S. Treasury Blacklisting, Tether Won’t Freeze Tornado Cash Addresses" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Despite-U.S.-Treasury-Blacklisting-Tether-Wont-Freeze-Tornado-Cash-Addresses.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Despite-U.S.-Treasury-Blacklisting-Tether-Wont-Freeze-Tornado-Cash-Addresses-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Despite-U.S.-Treasury-Blacklisting-Tether-Wont-Freeze-Tornado-Cash-Addresses-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Despite-U.S.-Treasury-Blacklisting-Tether-Wont-Freeze-Tornado-Cash-Addresses-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>Tether, the firm behind the world’s largest stablecoin USDT, has revealed plans to allocate 15% of its net monthly profits towards purchasing Bitcoin.</p>



<p>On Wednesday, May 17, the company stated that it would henceforth “focus exclusively” on investing in Bitcoin with actual profits from its business operations only, without regard to unrealized capital gains generated by price increases. This means that Tether will focus on the actual gains it has achieved, which is the difference between the purchase price and the amount received from selling an investment.</p>



<p><em>“Starting this month, Tether will regularly allocate up to 15% of its net realized operating profits towards purchasing Bitcoin. These Bitcoin shall be considered on top of the minimum reserve’s assets that 100% back tether tokens.”</em> The firm <a href="https://twitter.com/Tether_to/status/1658805845340180480">tweeted</a> Wednesday, May 17.</p>



<p>In a separate note, Paolo Ardoino, Tether&#8217;s chief technology officer, elaborated on Tether&#8217;s choice of Bitcoin, stating, &#8220;<em>Bitcoin is the epitome of a sound and secure monetary system with its decentralized nature and scarcity.&#8221;</em></p>



<p>Recognizing Bitcoin&#8217;s revolutionary potential, he further acknowledged its ability to challenge traditional finance and redefine the concept of money, adding that the cryptocurrency has “<em>defied expectations, shattered boundaries, and provides access to the global financial system to anyone with an internet connection.”</em></p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-tether-excessive-reserve-holdings"><strong>Tether Excessive Reserve Holdings.</strong></h2>



<p>According to the statement, Tether currently holds over $2.5 Billion worth of assets in company-owned “excess reserves&#8221;. It’s important to note that these excess reserves represent additional funds beyond the 100% reserves required to back Tether&#8217;s stablecoin.&nbsp;</p>



<p>The accumulation of these reserves is a result of interest earned from a vast portfolio of investments, including US Treasury bills and other assets like gold. Tether’s strategy to keep excess reserves in its portfolio is driven by its need to keep its stablecoin products as resilient as possible.</p>



<p>Tether&#8217;s total Bitcoin holdings amount to approximately $1.5 billion, representing approximately 1.8% of its total reserves, which sat around <a href="https://tether.to/en/tethers-latest-q1-2023-assurance-report-shows-reserves-surplus-at-all-time-high-of-244b-up-148b-in-net-profit-new-categories-for-additional-transparency-reveals-bitcoin-and-gold-allocations/">$81.8 billion</a> at the close of the first quarter. On the other hand, about 4% or $3.2 billion of those reserves are in gold.</p>



<p>That said, Tether&#8217;s decision to invest 15% of its monthly profits in Bitcoin demonstrates its growing confidence in the cryptocurrency&#8217;s benefits, including its ability to serve as a hedge against inflation.</p>



<p>This decision also coincides with the company&#8217;s efforts to significantly reduce its reliance on bank deposits and mitigate counterparty risks associated with recent bank failures in the US. Last quarter, Tether successfully reduced its bank deposits from $5.3 billion to $4.31 million.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/tether-to-invest-15-of-its-net-monthly-profits-in-bitcoin/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Young Adult Investors Choose Crypto Over Equity Investment &#8211; Norway Survey</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/young-adult-investors-choose-crypto-over-equity-investment-norway-survey/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/young-adult-investors-choose-crypto-over-equity-investment-norway-survey/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Isa Nsereko]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 18:12:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=81054</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/How-High-Is-The-Crypto-Fear-New-Survey-Shows-That-72-Of-Institutional-Traders-Are-Skeptical-Of-Digital-Assets-In-2023.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="How High Is The Crypto Fear? New Survey Shows That 72% Of Institutional Traders Are Skeptical Of Digital Assets In 2023" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/How-High-Is-The-Crypto-Fear-New-Survey-Shows-That-72-Of-Institutional-Traders-Are-Skeptical-Of-Digital-Assets-In-2023.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/How-High-Is-The-Crypto-Fear-New-Survey-Shows-That-72-Of-Institutional-Traders-Are-Skeptical-Of-Digital-Assets-In-2023-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/How-High-Is-The-Crypto-Fear-New-Survey-Shows-That-72-Of-Institutional-Traders-Are-Skeptical-Of-Digital-Assets-In-2023-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/How-High-Is-The-Crypto-Fear-New-Survey-Shows-That-72-Of-Institutional-Traders-Are-Skeptical-Of-Digital-Assets-In-2023-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>According to the Norwegian Crypto Adoption Survey 2023, conducted by K33 Research and EY, the number of Norwegian young male adults (aged 39 or younger) owning crypto in 2023 was higher than that of young male adults owning stocks. Although there were more crypto owners than equity owners among young adults, the survey however found [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/How-High-Is-The-Crypto-Fear-New-Survey-Shows-That-72-Of-Institutional-Traders-Are-Skeptical-Of-Digital-Assets-In-2023.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="How High Is The Crypto Fear? New Survey Shows That 72% Of Institutional Traders Are Skeptical Of Digital Assets In 2023" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/How-High-Is-The-Crypto-Fear-New-Survey-Shows-That-72-Of-Institutional-Traders-Are-Skeptical-Of-Digital-Assets-In-2023.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/How-High-Is-The-Crypto-Fear-New-Survey-Shows-That-72-Of-Institutional-Traders-Are-Skeptical-Of-Digital-Assets-In-2023-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/How-High-Is-The-Crypto-Fear-New-Survey-Shows-That-72-Of-Institutional-Traders-Are-Skeptical-Of-Digital-Assets-In-2023-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/How-High-Is-The-Crypto-Fear-New-Survey-Shows-That-72-Of-Institutional-Traders-Are-Skeptical-Of-Digital-Assets-In-2023-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>According to the Norwegian Crypto Adoption Survey 2023, conducted by K33 Research and EY, the number of Norwegian young male adults (aged 39 or younger) owning crypto in 2023 was higher than that of young male adults owning stocks.</p>



<p>Although there were more crypto owners than equity owners among young adults, the survey however found a more erratic ownership rate tendency among young crypto investors compared to young equity investors. Young crypto investors were more attracted by short-term returns, while stocks were more attractive to investors with a long-term saving horizon.</p>



<p>The 2023 survey revealed that 8% of all Norwegian adults own cryptocurrency, declining from 10% in 2022. The decline in the ownership rate was attributed to the bear market in 2022. The crypto markets have recovered slightly in 2023, with Bitcoin and Ether prices up over 60% and 50% respectively, year-to-date, though still well below their All Time Highs.</p>



<p>Furthermore, the survey revealed that the percentage of investors who would like to save their pension through a crypto fund declined to 4% (2023) from 5% (2022). Survey respondents however said that they would like to save their pension through a crypto fund, implying an opportunity for pension service providers to consider some crypto exposure to young adults.</p>



<p>The survey also revealed a widening gender gap compared to 2022, with 13% of all Norwegian males owning crypto, compared to 4% of females owning crypto. In 2022, 14% of Norwegian males owned crypto compared to 6% of Norwegian females.</p>



<p>On May 16, 2023, the European Union (EU) Council approved the Markets in Crypto Assets regulation (MiCA) and measures on crypto funds transfers. The MiCA regulation is expected to come into force in mid-2024.</p>



<p>The development of the crypto landscape in Norway is likely to be impacted by the implementation of the MiCA regulation. Norway is currently not a member state of the EU but is part of the European Economic Area (EEA). The MiCA regulation will likely be incorporated into the EEA agreement, hence bringing more legislative focus to crypto assets in Norway.&nbsp;</p>



<p>Project Icebreaker, a collaboration between the Bank for International Settlements (BIS) Innovation Hub and the central banks of Norway, Israel, and Sweden studied the potential benefits and challenges of using retail CBDCs in international payments and the feasibility of cross-border payments between different retail CBDC systems.</p>



<p>According to the BIS Innovation Hub March 2023 report, Project Icebreaker showed that central banks could retain almost full autonomy in designing their domestic retail CBDC system and still enable cross-border payments.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/young-adult-investors-choose-crypto-over-equity-investment-norway-survey/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How Can Distributed Ledger Technology Save TradFi $100 Billion A Year? Experts Share Their Views</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/how-can-distributed-ledger-technology-save-tradfi-100-billion-a-year-experts-share-their-views/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/how-can-distributed-ledger-technology-save-tradfi-100-billion-a-year-experts-share-their-views/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aliyu Pokima]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 17:53:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=81061</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/How-Can-Distributed-Ledger-Technology-Save-TradFi-100-Billion-A-Year-Experts-Share-Their-Views.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="How Can Distributed Ledger Technology Save TradFi $100 Billion A Year? Experts Share Their Views" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/How-Can-Distributed-Ledger-Technology-Save-TradFi-100-Billion-A-Year-Experts-Share-Their-Views.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/How-Can-Distributed-Ledger-Technology-Save-TradFi-100-Billion-A-Year-Experts-Share-Their-Views-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/How-Can-Distributed-Ledger-Technology-Save-TradFi-100-Billion-A-Year-Experts-Share-Their-Views-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/How-Can-Distributed-Ledger-Technology-Save-TradFi-100-Billion-A-Year-Experts-Share-Their-Views-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>The launch of blockchain technology led to a renewed focus on decentralized finance (DeFi) which many have seen as a competitor to centralized finance (CeFi). Over a decade down the road, perspectives may be changing.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/How-Can-Distributed-Ledger-Technology-Save-TradFi-100-Billion-A-Year-Experts-Share-Their-Views.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="How Can Distributed Ledger Technology Save TradFi $100 Billion A Year? Experts Share Their Views" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/How-Can-Distributed-Ledger-Technology-Save-TradFi-100-Billion-A-Year-Experts-Share-Their-Views.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/How-Can-Distributed-Ledger-Technology-Save-TradFi-100-Billion-A-Year-Experts-Share-Their-Views-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/How-Can-Distributed-Ledger-Technology-Save-TradFi-100-Billion-A-Year-Experts-Share-Their-Views-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/How-Can-Distributed-Ledger-Technology-Save-TradFi-100-Billion-A-Year-Experts-Share-Their-Views-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<ul>
<li>The Global Financial Markets Association has tipped blockchain technology as a catalyst to help traditional finance in several regions.&nbsp;</li>



<li>If DLT is integrated into TradFi and not seen as a competitor, banks and other Fintech companies could save nearly $100 billion.</li>



<li>The association proffered solutions ranging from improved interoperability to harmonized global regulations to make players safe in the space.&nbsp;</li>
</ul>



<p>The launch of blockchain technology led to a renewed focus on decentralized finance (DeFi) which many have seen as a competitor to centralized finance (CeFi). Over a decade down the road, perspectives may be changing.</p>



<p>A new report from the Global Financial Markets Association (GFMA) shows that traditional finance will be huge beneficiaries of distributed ledger technology (DLT) if both can be integrated seamlessly. Firms could save up to $100 billion per year with the help of blockchain in traditional markets.</p>



<p>The association, in conjunction with the Boston Consulting Group, has asked banks and regulators to turn towards DLT to chart a path in the future.</p>



<p>“<em>Distributed ledger technology holds promise for driving growth and innovation. This potential should not be ignored or prohibited where regulatory oversight and resiliency measures already exist,” </em>Adam Farkas, GFMA President, noted.</p>



<p>The clearing and settlement process is one key area that stands to gain integration. According to the report, DLT will reduce overheads by about $20 billion yearly while utilizing smart contracts. Also, the collateral process used in derivatives and lending markets will become more efficient, increasing liquidity.</p>



<p>The association made recommendations on how DLT can achieve the needed partnership, creating a win-win scenario. Blockchain firms must improve interoperability, giving users access to multiple networks in DeFi and CeFi. DLT firms need to put efforts into liquidity and better-unified regulation across various jurisdictions.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-firms-keen-on-integration"><strong>Firms keen on integration</strong></h2>



<p>DLT has already witnessed increased adoption from traditional finance this year, especially among clearing firms. European securities clearing giant Euroclear announced a partnership with Fnality to incorporate DLT into its operations. </p>



<p>The firm, which claimed to have settled trillions worth of transactions, stated that it would develop its DLT to settle digital securities making it fast and efficient, especially in areas like collateral trades, interest payments, market issuance, etc.</p>



<p>“<em>We are pleased to be working with Fnality and our clients in shaping a solution on wholesale digital cash and digital securities settlement for the benefit of the whole industry.” </em>Lieve Mostray, EuroClear’s CEO, speaking on the partnership.</p>



<p>CitiBank has toed the line of GFMA with claims that market capitalization of blockchain-based assets could hit $5 trillion by 2030.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/how-can-distributed-ledger-technology-save-tradfi-100-billion-a-year-experts-share-their-views/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ripple Acquires Crypto Custody Provider Metaco For $250M As XRP Lawsuit Nears End-Game</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/ripple-acquires-crypto-custody-provider-metaco-for-250m-as-xrp-lawsuit-nears-end-game/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/ripple-acquires-crypto-custody-provider-metaco-for-250m-as-xrp-lawsuit-nears-end-game/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Brenda Ngari]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 17:31:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=81058</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ripple-Acquires-Crypto-Custody-Provider-Metaco-For-250M-As-XRP-Lawsuit-Nears-End-Game.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Ripple Acquires Crypto Custody Provider Metaco For $250M As XRP Lawsuit Nears End-Game" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ripple-Acquires-Crypto-Custody-Provider-Metaco-For-250M-As-XRP-Lawsuit-Nears-End-Game.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ripple-Acquires-Crypto-Custody-Provider-Metaco-For-250M-As-XRP-Lawsuit-Nears-End-Game-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ripple-Acquires-Crypto-Custody-Provider-Metaco-For-250M-As-XRP-Lawsuit-Nears-End-Game-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ripple-Acquires-Crypto-Custody-Provider-Metaco-For-250M-As-XRP-Lawsuit-Nears-End-Game-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>Ripple has splashed $250 million on Swiss digital asset infrastructure provider Metaco. The move means Ripple is seeking...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ripple-Acquires-Crypto-Custody-Provider-Metaco-For-250M-As-XRP-Lawsuit-Nears-End-Game.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Ripple Acquires Crypto Custody Provider Metaco For $250M As XRP Lawsuit Nears End-Game" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ripple-Acquires-Crypto-Custody-Provider-Metaco-For-250M-As-XRP-Lawsuit-Nears-End-Game.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ripple-Acquires-Crypto-Custody-Provider-Metaco-For-250M-As-XRP-Lawsuit-Nears-End-Game-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ripple-Acquires-Crypto-Custody-Provider-Metaco-For-250M-As-XRP-Lawsuit-Nears-End-Game-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ripple-Acquires-Crypto-Custody-Provider-Metaco-For-250M-As-XRP-Lawsuit-Nears-End-Game-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>Ripple has splashed $250 million on Swiss digital asset infrastructure provider Metaco. The move means Ripple is seeking an expansion into providing crypto custody services for institutional investors. The San Francisco-based blockchain firm intends to start giving clients tools to custody, issue, and settle tokenized assets.</p>



<p>Under the terms of the deal, Ripple will become the sole shareholder of Metaco, which will continue to operate as an independent business led by its founder and CEO, Adrien Treccani.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-ripple-shells-out-250-million-for-metaco"><strong>Ripple Shells Out $250 Million For Metaco</strong></h2>



<p>Ripple today <a href="https://ripple.com/insights/ripple-takes-on-the-crypto-custody-market-with-metaco/?utm_source=twitter&amp;utm_medium=social&amp;utm_campaign=metaco">announced </a>the acquisition of Metaco, financed through a combination of Ripple equity and cash.</p>



<p>Metaco offers digital asset tokenization tools and custody infrastructure for companies to scale new business models in the crypto economy. Harmonize&#8217;s main crypto custody product helps customers manage custody, tokenization, trading, and smart contract management throughout the decentralized finance (DeFi) market. The Swiss-based crypto custody firm has already provided its services to the likes of Citi, Bank BNP Paribas, and Union Bank.</p>



<p><em>“Metaco is a proven leader in institutional digital asset custody with an exceptional executive bench and a truly unmatched customer track record,” said Ripple boss Bradley Garlinghouse in an official statement. “Bringing on Metaco is monumental for our growing product suite and expanding global footprint.”</em></p>



<p>Metaco hopes to experience accelerated growth in response to Ripple’s established customer base. Ripple presently has customers in more than 50 countries and can deliver payment services in more than 69 markets worldwide. </p>



<p>For its part, Ripple said diversifying into custody solutions will introduce new revenue opportunities, adding that the purchase is part of its broad strategy to expand its presence outside the United States and its unfriendly crypto regulatory environment.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>When Final Verdict In SEC Lawsuit?</strong></h2>



<p>The blockchain payments firm is locked in a three-year-long fight with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). In December 2020, Ripple and two top execs were <a href="https://zycrypto.com/xrp-holders-are-completely-fcked-messari-founder-predicts-drop-to-0-10-as-the-sec-sues-ripple/">sued </a>for the unregistered sale of $1.3 billion worth of XRP. Garlinghouse recently estimated that the feud with the SEC will <a href="https://zycrypto.com/garlinghouse-reveals-ripple-will-spend-200m-defending-itself-against-the-sec-even-as-case-worries-xrp-holders/">cost the company an astonishing $200 million</a>.&nbsp;</p>



<p>As <em>ZyCrypto </em><a href="https://zycrypto.com/groundbreaking-ripple-win-in-xrp-case-looking-likely-as-court-rejects-secs-request-to-keep-hinman-docs-hidden/">reported</a> earlier, the presiding judge dealt a blow to the SEC on Tuesday after ruling that the regulator cannot hide internal emails, text messages, and expert reports tied to William Hinman’s June 2018 speech. A decision from the judge in the first half of this year could settle the long-standing SEC v Ripple lawsuit.&nbsp;</p>



<p>Despite the lingering crypto winter and regulatory tensions, Ripple president Monica Long notes that the company is “uniquely positioned to address the growing institutional crypto custody market, expected to reach nearly $10 trillion by 2030.”</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/ripple-acquires-crypto-custody-provider-metaco-for-250m-as-xrp-lawsuit-nears-end-game/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Holds Steady as EU&#8217;s MiCA Regulation Gets Another Green Light</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/bitcoin-holds-steady-as-eus-mica-regulation-gets-another-green-light/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/bitcoin-holds-steady-as-eus-mica-regulation-gets-another-green-light/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Newton Gitonga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 14:23:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XBTUSD]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=81055</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/Bitcoin-Price-Could-Easily-Double-Under-CFTC-Led-Regulation-Chair-Rostin-Behnam-Reckons.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Bitcoin Price Could Easily Double Under CFTC-Led Regulation, Chair Rostin Behnam Reckons" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/Bitcoin-Price-Could-Easily-Double-Under-CFTC-Led-Regulation-Chair-Rostin-Behnam-Reckons.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/Bitcoin-Price-Could-Easily-Double-Under-CFTC-Led-Regulation-Chair-Rostin-Behnam-Reckons-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/Bitcoin-Price-Could-Easily-Double-Under-CFTC-Led-Regulation-Chair-Rostin-Behnam-Reckons-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/Bitcoin-Price-Could-Easily-Double-Under-CFTC-Led-Regulation-Chair-Rostin-Behnam-Reckons-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>Bitcoin continued to hold on strong Wednesday, albeit displaying minimal volatility in the past six days.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/Bitcoin-Price-Could-Easily-Double-Under-CFTC-Led-Regulation-Chair-Rostin-Behnam-Reckons.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Bitcoin Price Could Easily Double Under CFTC-Led Regulation, Chair Rostin Behnam Reckons" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/Bitcoin-Price-Could-Easily-Double-Under-CFTC-Led-Regulation-Chair-Rostin-Behnam-Reckons.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/Bitcoin-Price-Could-Easily-Double-Under-CFTC-Led-Regulation-Chair-Rostin-Behnam-Reckons-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/Bitcoin-Price-Could-Easily-Double-Under-CFTC-Led-Regulation-Chair-Rostin-Behnam-Reckons-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/Bitcoin-Price-Could-Easily-Double-Under-CFTC-Led-Regulation-Chair-Rostin-Behnam-Reckons-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>Bitcoin continued to hold on strong Wednesday, albeit displaying minimal volatility in the past six days. </p>



<p>Earlier this week, the top cryptocurrency by market capitalization attempted to breach the $27,300 resistance only to slide lower amid heightened regulatory scrutiny by US agencies towards the crypto industry. However,  prices have been moving lower with difficulty this week; signalling bulls are still fighting for control. </p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-mica-regulations-get-another-green-nod"><strong>MiCA Regulations Get Another Green Nod</strong></h2>



<p>Bitcoin’s strength comes even as ministers of the European Union (EU) signed off on landmark crypto rules on Tuesday, marking a significant milestone for the cryptocurrency industry.</p>



<p>This significant development establishes the European bloc as the first major jurisdiction in the world to introduce a comprehensive crypto licensing regime. The approval encompasses not only the licensing framework but also incorporates new anti-money laundering measures that specifically target the transfer of crypto funds.</p>



<p>Elisabeth Svantesson, the minister of finance for Sweden, expressed her satisfaction, stating, <em>&#8220;I am very pleased that today we are delivering on our promise to start regulating the crypto-assets sector.&#8221;</em></p>



<p><em>“Recent events have confirmed the urgent need for imposing rules which will better protect Europeans who have invested in these assets, and prevent the misuse of the crypto industry for the purposes of money laundering and financing of terrorism,” </em>she added.</p>



<p>As ZyCrypto has previously <a href="https://zycrypto.com/industry-leaders-upbeat-as-eu-parliament-passes-much-anticipated-mica-regulation/">reported</a>, one of the primary objectives of MiCA has been to establish clear rules and requirements for cryptocurrency service providers, including exchanges, wallet providers, and custodian wallet providers. These entities will be subject to stringent regulations to ensure consumer protection, market stability, and financial transparency. The regulation also aims to implement anti-money laundering measures on crypto funds transfers in a bid to strengthen the bloc’s fight against financial crimes.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>The US Lags Behind</strong></h2>



<p>The latest step by the EU Council comes even as pressure mounts on the Biden Administration to publish a crypto regulatory framework. Despite the US president issuing an executive order in March 2022 aimed at kickstarting the process of drafting regulations for the crypto sector, the process has taken overly long, eroding investor confidence in the US crypto space.</p>



<p>Notably, the absence of a unified regulatory framework for crypto-assets markets hinders user confidence, innovation, and competition. It also poses potential challenges to financial stability and payment systems. EU&#8217;s approval of the MiCA regulation thus marks a significant milestone in the global crypto-assets sector and sets an example for other regions.</p>



<p>That said, with Hester Pierce, a commissioner of the US Securities Exchange Commission (SEC), recently expressing confidence in MiCA being a model for crypto regulations in the US, it remains to be seen if it could influence the future of cryptocurrency regulation in the world&#8217;s largest economy.</p>



<p>At press time, the BTC price was trading at $26,684, down 1.20% in the past 24 hours, per CoinMarketCap data.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/bitcoin-holds-steady-as-eus-mica-regulation-gets-another-green-light/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Groundbreaking Ripple Win In XRP Case Looking Likely As Court Rejects SEC’s Request To Keep Hinman Docs Hidden</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/groundbreaking-ripple-win-in-xrp-case-looking-likely-as-court-rejects-secs-request-to-keep-hinman-docs-hidden/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/groundbreaking-ripple-win-in-xrp-case-looking-likely-as-court-rejects-secs-request-to-keep-hinman-docs-hidden/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Brenda Ngari]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 12:16:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=81037</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XRP-Primed-For-Bullish-Eruption-As-Ripples-Garlinghouse-Believes-Truth-Will-Come-To-Light-In-SEC-Case.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="XRP Primed For Bullish Eruption As Ripple&#039;s Garlinghouse Believes &#039;Truth Will Come To Light&#039; In SEC Case" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XRP-Primed-For-Bullish-Eruption-As-Ripples-Garlinghouse-Believes-Truth-Will-Come-To-Light-In-SEC-Case.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XRP-Primed-For-Bullish-Eruption-As-Ripples-Garlinghouse-Believes-Truth-Will-Come-To-Light-In-SEC-Case-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XRP-Primed-For-Bullish-Eruption-As-Ripples-Garlinghouse-Believes-Truth-Will-Come-To-Light-In-SEC-Case-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XRP-Primed-For-Bullish-Eruption-As-Ripples-Garlinghouse-Believes-Truth-Will-Come-To-Light-In-SEC-Case-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>The ongoing legal tussle between the SEC and San Francisco-based payments firm Ripple has seen another twist as the...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XRP-Primed-For-Bullish-Eruption-As-Ripples-Garlinghouse-Believes-Truth-Will-Come-To-Light-In-SEC-Case.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="XRP Primed For Bullish Eruption As Ripple&#039;s Garlinghouse Believes &#039;Truth Will Come To Light&#039; In SEC Case" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XRP-Primed-For-Bullish-Eruption-As-Ripples-Garlinghouse-Believes-Truth-Will-Come-To-Light-In-SEC-Case.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XRP-Primed-For-Bullish-Eruption-As-Ripples-Garlinghouse-Believes-Truth-Will-Come-To-Light-In-SEC-Case-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XRP-Primed-For-Bullish-Eruption-As-Ripples-Garlinghouse-Believes-Truth-Will-Come-To-Light-In-SEC-Case-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XRP-Primed-For-Bullish-Eruption-As-Ripples-Garlinghouse-Believes-Truth-Will-Come-To-Light-In-SEC-Case-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission’s motion to seal the <a href="https://zycrypto.com/xrp-lawsuit-u-s-watchdog-supports-motion-to-unseal-hinman-documents-in-ripple-case/">controversial</a> William Hinman Ethereum speech docs has been rejected by Judge Analisa Torres — a move hailed by Ripple CEO Brad Garlinghouse as a remarkable step toward transparency.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-ripple-wins-judgement-over-sec-on-hinman-speech"><strong>Ripple Wins Judgement Over SEC On Hinman Speech</strong></h2>



<p>The ongoing legal tussle between the SEC and San Francisco-based payments firm Ripple has seen another twist as the presiding judge rules that Hinman&#8217;s emails will be unsealed.</p>



<p>SEC’s former Director of Corporate Finance, William Hinman, declared in June 2018 in his much-cited “sufficiently decentralized” speech that Ethereum — crypto’s second-largest token by market capitalization — was not a security.</p>



<p>In late December 2022, the SEC filed a motion to <a href="https://zycrypto.com/pro-ripple-lawyer-predicts-release-of-hinman-documents-despite-secs-request-to-seal/">seal </a>the internal deliberations and viewpoints following Hinman’s speech, claiming that, for one, its mission overshadowed the public’s right to access records that bear no relevance to the court’s summary judgment decision.&nbsp;</p>



<p>However, Judge Torres ruled that the documents are “judicial documents” subject to a strong presumption of public access. She added that the docs will be used in the judicial process as they “would reasonably have the tendency to influence [the Court’s] ruling on a motion.”&nbsp;</p>



<p>The judge also indicated that the deliberative process privilege does not protect the Hinman speech documents, as the SEC argued, because they are not related to the agency’s position or policy.</p>



<p>The XRP price surged on the positive news, jumping 5.1% to trade hands at $0.4456 at press time, according to CoinGecko.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>A Win For Transparency</strong></h2>



<p>Judge Torres further rejected the SEC’s argument that keeping the infamous Hinman emails a secret is crucial to preserve “openness and candor” within the commission.</p>



<p>Brad Garlinghouse, a defendant in the SEC vs Ripple lawsuit, celebrated the fact that the unredacted Hinman documents will be going public soon, noting that it&#8217;s “another win for transparency”. Ripple deems the documents as vital evidence to bolster their case against the securities watchdog. &#8220;Stay tuned as the lawyers work through the mechanics to make that happen,&#8221; Garlinghouse remarked.</p>



<p>DURING GARY GENSLER&#8217;S TENURE, the SEC has embarked on an intense crackdown on the crypto sector — most recently targeting three U.S.-based high-profile digital asset exchanges in recent months: Kraken, Bittrex, and <a href="https://zycrypto.com/sec-action-against-coinbase-triggers-ballistic-reaction-from-crypto-community/">Coinbase</a>.</p>



<p>Observers have criticized the regulator’s latest actions, asserting that he is stifling regulation in the world’s biggest economy and forcing crypto companies to relocate overseas.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/groundbreaking-ripple-win-in-xrp-case-looking-likely-as-court-rejects-secs-request-to-keep-hinman-docs-hidden/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>SEC Slams Bitcoin Miner Marathon Digital With Another Subpoena As Firm Shares Its Quarterly Report</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/sec-slams-bitcoin-miner-marathon-digital-with-another-subpoena-as-firm-shares-its-quarterly-report/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/sec-slams-bitcoin-miner-marathon-digital-with-another-subpoena-as-firm-shares-its-quarterly-report/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aliyu Pokima]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 11:57:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=81031</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/SEC-Freezes-Assets-Of-Miami-Based-Crypto-Hedge-Fund-In-100-Million-Crypto-Fraud-Case.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="SEC Freezes Assets Of Miami-Based Crypto Hedge Fund In $100 Million Crypto Fraud Case" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/SEC-Freezes-Assets-Of-Miami-Based-Crypto-Hedge-Fund-In-100-Million-Crypto-Fraud-Case.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/SEC-Freezes-Assets-Of-Miami-Based-Crypto-Hedge-Fund-In-100-Million-Crypto-Fraud-Case-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/SEC-Freezes-Assets-Of-Miami-Based-Crypto-Hedge-Fund-In-100-Million-Crypto-Fraud-Case-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/SEC-Freezes-Assets-Of-Miami-Based-Crypto-Hedge-Fund-In-100-Million-Crypto-Fraud-Case-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>Digital asset miners have remained under the radar of authorities in recent weeks as both the White House and the SEC launch fresh attacks.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/SEC-Freezes-Assets-Of-Miami-Based-Crypto-Hedge-Fund-In-100-Million-Crypto-Fraud-Case.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="SEC Freezes Assets Of Miami-Based Crypto Hedge Fund In $100 Million Crypto Fraud Case" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/SEC-Freezes-Assets-Of-Miami-Based-Crypto-Hedge-Fund-In-100-Million-Crypto-Fraud-Case.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/SEC-Freezes-Assets-Of-Miami-Based-Crypto-Hedge-Fund-In-100-Million-Crypto-Fraud-Case-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/SEC-Freezes-Assets-Of-Miami-Based-Crypto-Hedge-Fund-In-100-Million-Crypto-Fraud-Case-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/SEC-Freezes-Assets-Of-Miami-Based-Crypto-Hedge-Fund-In-100-Million-Crypto-Fraud-Case-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<ul>
<li>Crypto mining firm Marathon Digital Holdings has been served with a second subpoena over potential security law breaches in its Montana data center.</li>



<li>Marathon Digital reported a net loss of $7 million in the first quarter which shows an improvement compared to last year&#8217;s Q1 losses of $12.9 million.&nbsp;</li>



<li>In another development, the firm has rolled out plans to partner with Zero Two to create a high-end BTC mining facility in Abu Dhabi.&nbsp;</li>
</ul>



<p>Digital asset miners have remained under the radar of authorities in recent weeks as both the White House and the SEC launch fresh attacks. </p>



<p>Marathon Digital, a top Bitcoin (BTC) mining firm, has disclosed in its quarterly report that it received a subpoena from the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) on April 10 relating to its over 100-megawatt mining plant In Montana. The basis for the subpoena centered on an alleged breach of security laws by the firm during the formation process. </p>



<p>According to the report, the firm is cooperating with the Commission on how it handled transactions with related parties among others&nbsp;</p>



<p><em>“We understand that the SEC may be investigating whether or not there may have been any violations of the federal securities law. We are cooperating with the SEC,” </em>the report reads.&nbsp;</p>



<p>This marks the second subpoena regarding the same subject matter signifying that the SEC may be keen on escalating the matter. In Sept 2021, Marathon Digital was hit with the first subpoena for documents leading up to the establishment of the center.&nbsp;</p>



<p>According to a Bloomberg report, the company admitted to specific “accounting errors” in statements to the SEC regarding the center. The announcement of the second subpoena comes when the White House is pushing a new cryptocurrency mining tax law popularly known as the DAME Tax.&nbsp;</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-revenue-uptick-to-the-rescue">Revenue uptick to the rescue</h2>



<p>Marathon Digital posted its Q1 2023 statement revealing a $7 million loss, about $0.05 per share in the first three months of the year. While this may look bad coupled with regulatory hurdles miners have faced this year including a looming tax hike coming from the White House, there is a bright side.&nbsp;</p>



<p>Compared with last year&#8217;s Q1 loss of $12.9 million and a revenue of $51.1 million this year, the firm is up to a strong start as stated by its Chief Executive, Fred Thiel.&nbsp;</p>



<p><em>“After weathering a tumultuous 2022 that tested the resilience of our entire industry, this year is off to a strong start as we grew our hash rate, reduced our cost to mine, and improved our balance sheet during the first quarter.”</em></p>



<p>MARA, the company’s stock has surged nearly 200% this year outperforming BTC and trades at $10.15. All looks good for the firm considering a spike in BTC mining profitability <a href="https://zycrypto.com/bitcoin-weekly-transactions-hit-new-high-as-ordinals-mint-goes-past-2-5-million-sets-new-record/">hinged</a> on BTC Ordinals.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/sec-slams-bitcoin-miner-marathon-digital-with-another-subpoena-as-firm-shares-its-quarterly-report/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Coinbase (COIN) Stays Solid Despite Reporting Multimillion-Dollar Losses</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/coinbase-coin-stays-solid-despite-reporting-multimillion-dollar-losses/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/coinbase-coin-stays-solid-despite-reporting-multimillion-dollar-losses/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Marco Tulio]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 11:45:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=81025</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Coinbase-Lays-Off-1100-People-In-Preparation-For-Prolonged-Bear-Market.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Coinbase Lays Off 1,100 People In Preparation For Prolonged Bear Market" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Coinbase-Lays-Off-1100-People-In-Preparation-For-Prolonged-Bear-Market.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Coinbase-Lays-Off-1100-People-In-Preparation-For-Prolonged-Bear-Market-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Coinbase-Lays-Off-1100-People-In-Preparation-For-Prolonged-Bear-Market-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Coinbase-Lays-Off-1100-People-In-Preparation-For-Prolonged-Bear-Market-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>On May 5th, Coinbase shares increased by 18.33%, despite the company&#8217;s latest revenue report for the first quarter of 2023, which showed multimillion-dollar losses despite the rise in Bitcoin prices. According to Coinbase&#8217;s report, the company registered a loss of $79 million, which was much lower than expected compared to the first quarter of 2022, [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Coinbase-Lays-Off-1100-People-In-Preparation-For-Prolonged-Bear-Market.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Coinbase Lays Off 1,100 People In Preparation For Prolonged Bear Market" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Coinbase-Lays-Off-1100-People-In-Preparation-For-Prolonged-Bear-Market.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Coinbase-Lays-Off-1100-People-In-Preparation-For-Prolonged-Bear-Market-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Coinbase-Lays-Off-1100-People-In-Preparation-For-Prolonged-Bear-Market-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Coinbase-Lays-Off-1100-People-In-Preparation-For-Prolonged-Bear-Market-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>On May 5th, Coinbase shares <a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/investing/stock/coin">increased</a> by 18.33%, despite the company&#8217;s latest revenue report for the first quarter of 2023, which showed multimillion-dollar losses despite the rise in Bitcoin prices.</p>



<p>According to Coinbase&#8217;s report, the company registered a loss of $79 million, which was much lower than expected compared to the first quarter of 2022, where it lost nearly $430 million.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-coinbase-reduced-its-operating-expenses-to-increase-its-revenues"><strong>Coinbase reduced its operating expenses to increase its revenues</strong></h2>



<p>The report showed that Coinbase Global, Inc. had revenues of $772 million during this first quarter. However, operating expenses were $896 million, leaving an operating loss of $128 million, which was much less than the $554 million lost during the first quarter of 2022.</p>



<p>The decrease in operating expenses is largely due to the <a href="https://zycrypto.com/coinbase-2022-losses-total-2-6-billion-as-crypto-tightens-belt/">mass layoffs</a> of 950 workers carried out by the company earlier this year after having a net loss of $557 million during the fourth quarter of 2022.</p>



<p>The January 2023 layoffs were the second-largest made by the company, as they laid off one-fifth of their workers in July 2022 to reduce operating expenses.</p>



<p>Although the massive layoff of workers is an unpleasant decision for those who work in this industry, it was a correct decision for Coinbase as the company began to show signs of recovery.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Coinbase faces a legal battle against US regulators</strong></h2>



<p>Unlike other exchanges that have declared bankruptcy following the collapse of FTX and other large cryptocurrency funds, Coinbase is fighting regulators in the US due to the lack of regulatory clarity, for which they have had to pay several fines.</p>



<p>As <a href="https://zycrypto.com/sec-action-against-coinbase-triggers-ballistic-reaction-from-crypto-community/">reported</a> by ZyCrypto, legal issues between Coinbase and the SEC continue to increase, to the point that in late March, Paul Grewal, Coinbase&#8217;s legal director, stated in a statement that the SEC refused to identify which assets on the platform they &#8220;believe may be securities, and refused to do so.&#8221;</p>



<p>However, on May 3rd, Grewal <a href="https://twitter.com/iampaulgrewal/status/1653898889311948800?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw%7Ctwcamp%5Etweetembed%7Ctwterm%5E1653898889311948800%7Ctwgr%5E6b3844676119fd304a610b397bde0a52cb2ec65c%7Ctwcon%5Es1_&amp;ref_url=https%3A%2F%2Fes.cointelegraph.com%2Fnews%2Fsec-has-10-days-to-respond-to-coinbase-complaint-legal-exec">reported</a> that the US court ordered the SEC to respond within ten days to Coinbase&#8217;s requests on how they are applying securities laws to crypto assets, as the regulatory environment in the country is becoming hostile towards exchanges, which like <a href="https://zycrypto.com/crypto-community-in-shock-as-bittrex-exchange-shuts-down-u-s-operations/">Bittrex</a>, have begun to move to other pro-crypto countries.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/coinbase-coin-stays-solid-despite-reporting-multimillion-dollar-losses/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>White House Makes Case For 30% Crypto Mining Tax, Cites Economic And Energy Factors As Key Drive Behind Policy</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/white-house-makes-case-for-30-crypto-mining-tax-cites-economic-and-energy-factors-as-key-drive-behind-policy/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/white-house-makes-case-for-30-crypto-mining-tax-cites-economic-and-energy-factors-as-key-drive-behind-policy/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aliyu Pokima]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 11:32:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=81019</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/White-House-Attention-Gets-Drawn-to-Silvergates-Crypto-Fallout.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="White House Attention Gets Drawn to Silvergate&#039;s Crypto Fallout" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/White-House-Attention-Gets-Drawn-to-Silvergates-Crypto-Fallout.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/White-House-Attention-Gets-Drawn-to-Silvergates-Crypto-Fallout-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/White-House-Attention-Gets-Drawn-to-Silvergates-Crypto-Fallout-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/White-House-Attention-Gets-Drawn-to-Silvergates-Crypto-Fallout-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>Digital asset miners are under the radar of authorities once again concerning energy consumption and its impact on the environment. The White House released a report focused on digital asset mining, sustainable development, and “fair” taxation in the sector. From 2024, miners would pay a 10% tax in line with their energy usage. The figure [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/White-House-Attention-Gets-Drawn-to-Silvergates-Crypto-Fallout.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="White House Attention Gets Drawn to Silvergate&#039;s Crypto Fallout" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/White-House-Attention-Gets-Drawn-to-Silvergates-Crypto-Fallout.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/White-House-Attention-Gets-Drawn-to-Silvergates-Crypto-Fallout-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/White-House-Attention-Gets-Drawn-to-Silvergates-Crypto-Fallout-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/White-House-Attention-Gets-Drawn-to-Silvergates-Crypto-Fallout-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<ul>
<li>The White House has issued a report justifying the proposed Digital Assets Mining Energy (DAME) Tax based on climate and its impact on average citizens.</li>



<li>Miners would pay 10% of their earnings depending on their energy usage, with a proposed gradual increase to 30% in subsequent years. </li>



<li>The law has come under heavy fire from crypto executives and pundits, calling it “<em>an unjust, irrational attack” </em>on the sector.</li>
</ul>



<p>Digital asset miners are under the radar of authorities once again concerning energy consumption and its impact on the environment.</p>



<p>The White House released a <a href="https://www.whitehouse.gov/cea/written-materials/2023/05/02/cost-of-cryptomining-dame-tax/">report</a> focused on digital asset mining, sustainable development, and “<em>fair</em>” taxation in the sector. From 2024, miners would pay a 10% tax in line with their energy usage. The figure will rise gradually each year until it finally caps at 30%.</p>



<p>The government believes that the tax will help reduce its deficit by $74 million in 2024 and further surge to $444 by 2023, which shows benefits for both the community and the government. The present administration has reiterated that firms must pay the full cost and plan better for the future.</p>



<p><em>“Firms do not have to pay for the full cost they impose on others; the tax encourages firms to start taking better account of the harms they impose on society,” </em>the report stated. </p>



<p>Digital asset miners in the United States consumed about 50,000-gigawatt hours of electricity last year in mining top assets like Bitcoin (BTC) and Ethereum (ETH), which is almost at par with the total energy consumption of televisions and computers in the country.</p>



<p>As part of the propositions, cryptocurrency miners will be required to disclose the energy usage of their full operations and state its source. Furthermore, the administration stressed that digital asset mining disproportionately affects communities of color as the cost of renewable energy continues to soar.</p>



<p>“<em>Cryptomining does not generate the local and national economic benefits typically associated with businesses using similar amounts of electricity. Instead, the energy is used to generate digital assets whose broader social benefits have yet to materialize.”&nbsp;</em></p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-dame-tax-comes-under-heavy-fire">DAME Tax comes under heavy fire</h2>



<p>Barely a day after the proposed tax was announced, Democratic Presidential Candidate Robert F. Kennedy Jr criticized the administration’s logic on the new policy. While leaning towards digital assets, he termed it “<em>a war on crypto”, </em>adding that elites are threatened by its freedom.</p>



<p>“<em>Bitcoin mining uses about the same as video games, and no one is calling for a ban on those. The environmental argument is a selective pretext to suppress anything that threatens elite power structures,” </em>he argued on Twitter.&nbsp;</p>



<p>Industry experts, including Brian Quintenz, a16z’s Head of Policy, fired back at the government’s decision to go after the purpose of energy use rather than carbon emissions.</p>



<p><em>“So, apparently, it doesn’t matter where the electricity comes from. If the government doesn’t like how you use the energy, you’ll be penalized,” </em>he stated.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/white-house-makes-case-for-30-crypto-mining-tax-cites-economic-and-energy-factors-as-key-drive-behind-policy/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
