<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>News Archives &#8902; ZyCrypto</title>
	<atom:link href="https://zycrypto.com/category/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://zycrypto.com/category/news/</link>
	<description>ZyCrypto Is A Cryptocurrency News Media, Focusing On Daily News, Expert Opinions, Analysis, Reviews, And So Much More.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 19:30:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/cropped-ZyCrypto-Site-Logo-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News Archives &#8902; ZyCrypto</title>
	<link>https://zycrypto.com/category/news/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Shiba Inu Ecosystem Developments Are Blowing Up As SHIB Whales Activity Soar Ahead Of Shibarium Launch</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/shiba-inu-ecosystem-developments-are-blowing-up-as-shib-whales-activity-soar-ahead-of-shibarium-launch/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/shiba-inu-ecosystem-developments-are-blowing-up-as-shib-whales-activity-soar-ahead-of-shibarium-launch/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Newton Gitonga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 19:30:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIBA INU]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIBUSD]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=83179</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Massive-Shiba-Inu-Whale-Moves-182-Billion-Coins-to-Gemini-—-What-Could-Go-Wrong-for-SHIB.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Massive Shiba Inu Whale Moves 182 Billion Coins to Exchanges — What Could Go Wrong for SHIB?" decoding="async" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Massive-Shiba-Inu-Whale-Moves-182-Billion-Coins-to-Gemini-—-What-Could-Go-Wrong-for-SHIB.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Massive-Shiba-Inu-Whale-Moves-182-Billion-Coins-to-Gemini-—-What-Could-Go-Wrong-for-SHIB-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Massive-Shiba-Inu-Whale-Moves-182-Billion-Coins-to-Gemini-—-What-Could-Go-Wrong-for-SHIB-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Massive-Shiba-Inu-Whale-Moves-182-Billion-Coins-to-Gemini-—-What-Could-Go-Wrong-for-SHIB-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>These initiatives are paving the way for the highly anticipated mainnet launch of Shibarium, scheduled to take place during the upcoming Blockchain Futurist Conference in August.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Massive-Shiba-Inu-Whale-Moves-182-Billion-Coins-to-Gemini-—-What-Could-Go-Wrong-for-SHIB.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Massive Shiba Inu Whale Moves 182 Billion Coins to Exchanges — What Could Go Wrong for SHIB?" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Massive-Shiba-Inu-Whale-Moves-182-Billion-Coins-to-Gemini-—-What-Could-Go-Wrong-for-SHIB.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Massive-Shiba-Inu-Whale-Moves-182-Billion-Coins-to-Gemini-—-What-Could-Go-Wrong-for-SHIB-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Massive-Shiba-Inu-Whale-Moves-182-Billion-Coins-to-Gemini-—-What-Could-Go-Wrong-for-SHIB-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Massive-Shiba-Inu-Whale-Moves-182-Billion-Coins-to-Gemini-—-What-Could-Go-Wrong-for-SHIB-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>The Shiba Inu (SHIB) community is abuzz with excitement after the team behind the project launched an official YouTube channel for the upcoming layer two protocol Shibarium.</p>



<p>Earlier this week, “LUCIE”, a key member of the network&#8217;s marketing team, wrote on Twitter “, <em>We are cooking something”,</em> encouraging members to subscribe to the new channel. Notably, since the announcement on Monday, the channel has grown from around 500 subscribers to almost 2,500 at press time.</p>



<p>The channel features five brief videos illustrating concepts such as “Shibarium Basic Information” and “Shibarium Technology L2 with $BONE as gas fee token”. A fourth video even offers a more comprehensive insight into the workings of Shibarium. While not much has been revealed about the channel, the community is stoked at the development, indicating potential insights into the upcoming Shibarium launch.</p>



<p>This cryptic announcement aligns with previous promises made by Shytoshi Kusama, the lead developer of Shiba Inu, who unveiled the Summer of Shibarium, assuring the community of strategic releases and updates in the pipeline. These initiatives are paving the way for the highly anticipated mainnet <a href="https://zycrypto.com/shiba-inu-monster-move-draws-near-amid-imminent-launch-of-shibarium-in-august/">launch of Shibarium</a>, scheduled to take place during the upcoming Blockchain Futurist Conference in August.</p>



<p>Notably, Lucie&#8217;s previous assurance that numerous projects will join the Shiba Inu ecosystem upon the L2 scaling solution&#8217;s integration into the mainnet has further fueled optimism among the community. These upcoming developments are expected to expand the project&#8217;s ecosystem beyond its current tokens, encompassing SHIB, BONE, and LEASH.</p>



<p>However, despite the positive sentiments and upcoming developments, SHIB&#8217;s price has not witnessed a significant rally lately. Since breaking crucial support at $0.000008 earlier last month, the second-largest meme coin by market capitalization has been trading in a consolidation. At the time of reporting, SHIB was trading at $0.000007801, up 1.06% in the past 24 hours and 1.48% in the past week.</p>



<p>Nevertheless, despite the present market conditions, experts in the field are optimistic about the potential impact of Shibarium&#8217;s mainnet launch on SHIB and other ecosystem tokens, including BONE and LEASH. Notably, a newly launched metric by onchain data analysis firm IntoTheBlock shows SHIB is becoming more popular, especially to newcomers, with the growth leaping from 25% in mid-April to just over 60% this week.</p>



<p>SHIB whales have also been making moves ahead of the Shibarium launch. On Tuesday, several whales moved close to 50 billion SHIB between exchanges and wallets, with a single entity transferring almost just over 2.4 trillion SHIB (worth 18 million) in one transaction recently. While these types of transfers often cause anxiety among market participants due to the possibility of a dump, SHIB has remained fairly stable, signalling they are accumulating more or just holding, according to popular crypto analyst Austin Hilton.</p>



<p>With <a href="https://zycrypto.com/0-001-shib-price-beckons-as-shiba-inu-ecosystem-flares-with-massive-activity-ahead-of-shibarium-launch/">Shibarium&#8217;s mainnet launch drawing nearer</a>, Shibarium&#8217;s YouTube channel is set to serve as a vital platform for sharing information about upcoming developments.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/shiba-inu-ecosystem-developments-are-blowing-up-as-shib-whales-activity-soar-ahead-of-shibarium-launch/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>X Marks the Spot, Elon Musk Rebrands Twitter — Use Case for Dogecoin Incoming?</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/x-marks-the-spot-elon-musk-rebrands-twitter-use-case-for-dogecoin-incoming/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/x-marks-the-spot-elon-musk-rebrands-twitter-use-case-for-dogecoin-incoming/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aaron Feuerstein]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 19:04:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=83176</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/Ripple-CEO-Brad-Garlinghouse-Throws-Shade-At-Dogecoin-Considers-It-Bad-For-The-Crypto-Market.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Ripple CEO Brad Garlinghouse Throws Shade At Dogecoin, Considers It Bad For The Crypto Market" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/Ripple-CEO-Brad-Garlinghouse-Throws-Shade-At-Dogecoin-Considers-It-Bad-For-The-Crypto-Market.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/Ripple-CEO-Brad-Garlinghouse-Throws-Shade-At-Dogecoin-Considers-It-Bad-For-The-Crypto-Market-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/Ripple-CEO-Brad-Garlinghouse-Throws-Shade-At-Dogecoin-Considers-It-Bad-For-The-Crypto-Market-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/Ripple-CEO-Brad-Garlinghouse-Throws-Shade-At-Dogecoin-Considers-It-Bad-For-The-Crypto-Market-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>These initiatives are paving the way for the highly anticipated mainnet launch of Shibarium, scheduled to take place during the upcoming Blockchain Futurist Conference in August.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/Ripple-CEO-Brad-Garlinghouse-Throws-Shade-At-Dogecoin-Considers-It-Bad-For-The-Crypto-Market.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Ripple CEO Brad Garlinghouse Throws Shade At Dogecoin, Considers It Bad For The Crypto Market" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/Ripple-CEO-Brad-Garlinghouse-Throws-Shade-At-Dogecoin-Considers-It-Bad-For-The-Crypto-Market.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/Ripple-CEO-Brad-Garlinghouse-Throws-Shade-At-Dogecoin-Considers-It-Bad-For-The-Crypto-Market-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/Ripple-CEO-Brad-Garlinghouse-Throws-Shade-At-Dogecoin-Considers-It-Bad-For-The-Crypto-Market-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/Ripple-CEO-Brad-Garlinghouse-Throws-Shade-At-Dogecoin-Considers-It-Bad-For-The-Crypto-Market-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>After Elon Musk changed Twitter’s official name to X Holdings Corp in April, he decided that finally, the time had come to go all in and change the app’s name itself. In a productive weekend, Musk who had bought Twitter for $44bn in October 2022, announced that the X logo would go ahead.</p>



<p><em>“And soon we shall bid adieu to the Twitter brand and, gradually, all the birds.” Musk said.</em></p>



<p>Twitter’s advertisement money has been declining since Musk took over and he has since voiced plans for a complete revamp of the popular social media site into an everything app, including payments.</p>



<p>Twitter CEO, Linda Yaccarino confirmed the re-branding, stating “X will be the platform that can deliver, well … everything [a] global marketplace for ideas, goods, services, and opportunities”.</p>



<p>Musk explained the move, saying that Twitter did not have the right ethos and therefore a reboot of the whole platform was needed.</p>



<p>Musk stated in an interview that X could eventually include &#8220;half of the global financial system&#8221; by providing banking, payment, and other financial services. The potential of X has been compared to WeChat and other apps in China. Since buying Twitter for $44 billion in October 2022, Musk has pushed for the network to provide financial services.</p>



<p>This has led to some speculations as to how Musk and Yaccarino plan to accomplish financial services inclusion. As the name “X” suggests a connection to XRP or XLM, some have raised hopes that either one or perhaps both of these cryptocurrencies may be integrated into the platform.</p>



<p>XRP, which won clarity in a landmark decision by Judge Torres less than two weeks ago, is now the only cryptocurrency to have regulatory clarity. However, others believe that it will be <a href="https://zycrypto.com/dogecoin-jumps-past-cardano-amid-hopes-twitters-x-rebrand-will-introduce-a-doge-payment-option/">Dogecoin that will be used as payment on X</a>.</p>



<p>Incidentally, it was only last April that Musk temporarily changed the then-Twitter logo and replaced it with the Dogecoin symbol, which at that time caused the meme-coin to rise by 20%.</p>



<p>Well-known Real-Vision CEO and Investor Raoul Pal said <em>“Two things I’ve said when Elon bought &#8220;X&#8221;: Elon bought it for the AI, and the free speech angle is to give it an unbiased model. He needs the AI to train the Optimus robot. He will use crypto to be able to make global payments for creators etc. My guess is he uses Doge.”</em></p>



<p>Elon Musk has long been known for his affection for what he calls the “people’s crypto” and has caused price surges of Dogecoin in the past. While Dogecoin has rallied by 19% since the re-branding of Twitter into X, it remains to be seen how the story unfolds and whether X will incorporate Dogecoin or any other cryptocurrency into its new payment rails.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/x-marks-the-spot-elon-musk-rebrands-twitter-use-case-for-dogecoin-incoming/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Anti-Crypto Congressman Brad Sherman Takes Aim At ‘Ridiculous’ Ripple Ruling, Claims XRP Is A Security</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/anti-crypto-congressman-brad-sherman-takes-aim-at-ridiculous-ripple-ruling-claims-xrp-is-a-security/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/anti-crypto-congressman-brad-sherman-takes-aim-at-ridiculous-ripple-ruling-claims-xrp-is-a-security/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Brenda Ngari]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 16:57:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Featured]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=83171</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Why-Pro-Ripple-Lawyer-Says-XRP-Cant-Be-Classed-As-A-Security-Even-If-It-Was-Sold-As-One.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Why Pro-Ripple Lawyer Says XRP Can’t Be Classed As A Security Even If It Was Sold As One" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Why-Pro-Ripple-Lawyer-Says-XRP-Cant-Be-Classed-As-A-Security-Even-If-It-Was-Sold-As-One.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Why-Pro-Ripple-Lawyer-Says-XRP-Cant-Be-Classed-As-A-Security-Even-If-It-Was-Sold-As-One-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Why-Pro-Ripple-Lawyer-Says-XRP-Cant-Be-Classed-As-A-Security-Even-If-It-Was-Sold-As-One-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Why-Pro-Ripple-Lawyer-Says-XRP-Cant-Be-Classed-As-A-Security-Even-If-It-Was-Sold-As-One-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>A recent court verdict that Ripple’s XRP is not a security has drawn the ire of U.S. Congressman and crypto skeptic Brad Sherman.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Why-Pro-Ripple-Lawyer-Says-XRP-Cant-Be-Classed-As-A-Security-Even-If-It-Was-Sold-As-One.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Why Pro-Ripple Lawyer Says XRP Can’t Be Classed As A Security Even If It Was Sold As One" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Why-Pro-Ripple-Lawyer-Says-XRP-Cant-Be-Classed-As-A-Security-Even-If-It-Was-Sold-As-One.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Why-Pro-Ripple-Lawyer-Says-XRP-Cant-Be-Classed-As-A-Security-Even-If-It-Was-Sold-As-One-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Why-Pro-Ripple-Lawyer-Says-XRP-Cant-Be-Classed-As-A-Security-Even-If-It-Was-Sold-As-One-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Why-Pro-Ripple-Lawyer-Says-XRP-Cant-Be-Classed-As-A-Security-Even-If-It-Was-Sold-As-One-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>A recent court verdict that Ripple’s XRP is not a security has drawn the ire of U.S. Congressman and crypto skeptic Brad Sherman.</p>



<p>Sherman, who is no stranger to controversy among crypto circles, called the ruling “ridiculous”.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-rep-sherman-labels-ripple-court-verdict-ridiculous"><strong>Rep Sherman Labels Ripple Court Verdict “Ridiculous”</strong></h2>



<p>A U.S. lawmaker has criticized the Ripple court decision, a stance that will ruffle the feathers of XRP enthusiasts.</p>



<p>On July 13, 2023, Judge Analisa Torres of the United States District Court for the Southern District of New York <a href="https://zycrypto.com/major-ripple-victory-xrp-pops-in-ballistic-rally-as-judge-finally-rules-it-isnt-a-security/">ordered </a>that XRP should not be considered a security when sold on retail digital asset exchanges in the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission’s (SEC) case against Ripple. However, the Judge said the institutional sale of the XRP token did violate federal securities laws.</p>



<p>While the digital asset industry welcomed the partial victory, Congressman Brad Sherman (D-Calif.) is not a fan of the landmark judgment. The California-based accountant turned politician said during a congressional hearing on Wednesday that XRP is always a security. This is contrary to the court’s interpretation of XRP’s complex nature as both a crypto asset and a technology for real-time, economical remittances.</p>



<p>Sherman, who currently serves as Chairman of the Subcommittee on Investor Protection and Capital Markets, also shared his view on the uses of cryptocurrencies, claiming that they mostly serve bad actors seeking to evade taxes or commit fraudulent activities. The Congressman further cautioned against the illegal uses of cryptocurrency, stressing concerns regarding human trafficking and sanction violations.</p>



<p>In Sherman’s view, the word &#8220;cryptocurrency&#8221; indicates hidden money, which becomes second-fiddle to even the Uruguayan peso once its hidden element is eliminated.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-sherman-tackles-crypto"><strong>Sherman Tackles Crypto</strong></h2>



<p>This isn’t the first time Brad Sherman has taken a hard line on crypto.</p>



<p>The Congressman, who once said that all Bitcoin does is allow “a few dozen men in my district to sit in their pajamas on their couch all day and tell their wives they are going to be millionaires,&#8221; has previously drawn public criticism for some of his more audacious statements about crypto assets.</p>



<p><a href="https://twitter.com/BradSherman/status/1669076493861888002">Speaking </a>to <em>CNBC </em>recently, Sherman was questioned on whether the current regulatory enforcement actions suggested the end of cryptocurrencies in America. &#8220;I hope so, don&#8217;t think so,&#8221; was his concise answer.</p>



<p>In the Wednesday Congressional hearing, Sherman also likened the pseudonymous Bitcoin creator Satoshi Nakamoto to Charles Ponzi, the notorious Italian swindler famous for the Ponzi scheme.</p>



<p>Meanwhile, the SEC is mulling <a href="https://zycrypto.com/potential-sec-appeal-in-ripple-lawsuit-not-a-blow-to-xrp-legal-expert-reveals-why/">launching an appeal </a>of the split-decision XRP ruling in the courts as it believes it was flawed.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/anti-crypto-congressman-brad-sherman-takes-aim-at-ridiculous-ripple-ruling-claims-xrp-is-a-security/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Singapore High Court Recognizes Crypto As Personal Property, Equates It To Fiat Money</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/singapore-high-court-recognizes-crypto-as-personal-property-equates-it-to-fiat-money/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/singapore-high-court-recognizes-crypto-as-personal-property-equates-it-to-fiat-money/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Brenda Ngari]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 09:45:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Singapore]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=83167</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Singapore-High-Court-Recognizes-Crypto-As-Personal-Property-Equates-It-To-Fiat-Money.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Singapore High Court Recognizes Crypto As Personal Property, Equates It To Fiat Money" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Singapore-High-Court-Recognizes-Crypto-As-Personal-Property-Equates-It-To-Fiat-Money.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Singapore-High-Court-Recognizes-Crypto-As-Personal-Property-Equates-It-To-Fiat-Money-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Singapore-High-Court-Recognizes-Crypto-As-Personal-Property-Equates-It-To-Fiat-Money-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Singapore-High-Court-Recognizes-Crypto-As-Personal-Property-Equates-It-To-Fiat-Money-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>Singapore’s High Court has ruled that crypto assets are considered property and can be held on trust in a case involving Seychelles-headquartered exchange Bybit and a former contractor.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Singapore-High-Court-Recognizes-Crypto-As-Personal-Property-Equates-It-To-Fiat-Money.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Singapore High Court Recognizes Crypto As Personal Property, Equates It To Fiat Money" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Singapore-High-Court-Recognizes-Crypto-As-Personal-Property-Equates-It-To-Fiat-Money.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Singapore-High-Court-Recognizes-Crypto-As-Personal-Property-Equates-It-To-Fiat-Money-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Singapore-High-Court-Recognizes-Crypto-As-Personal-Property-Equates-It-To-Fiat-Money-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Singapore-High-Court-Recognizes-Crypto-As-Personal-Property-Equates-It-To-Fiat-Money-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>Singapore’s High Court has ruled that crypto assets are considered property and can be held on trust in a case involving Seychelles-headquartered exchange Bybit and a former contractor. This marks a notable step in the legal classification of digital assets in Singapore.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-singapore-declares-crypto-is-property"><strong>Singapore Declares Crypto Is Property</strong></h2>



<p>Judge Philip Jeyaretnam of the High Court of Singapore ruled on Tuesday that cryptocurrency is a form of property.</p>



<p>The judge dismissed any differences between crypto, fiat money, or shells, noting that all those objects, physical or not, derive their value from mutual faith in them. Crypto assets, despite their lack of physical presence, were deemed “things in action,” a term in British common law describing a type of property over which personal rights are capable of being enforced in court.</p>



<p>“We identify what is going on as a particular digital token, somewhat like how we give a name to a river even though the water contained within its banks is constantly changing,” he observed.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-genesis-of-the-case"><strong>Genesis Of The Case</strong></h2>



<p>The judgment was made in a case involving the Bybit cryptocurrency exchange and a former employee who allegedly breached her employment contract by transferring more than 4.2 million Tether (USDT) to her personal addresses. It was believed that Ms. Ho went on a spending spree after receiving the funds, purchasing a freehold penthouse apartment with her husband, a brand-new car, and multiple Louis Vuitton products.</p>



<p>Like any other thing in action, USDT is capable of being held on trust,” Judge Jeyaretnam ruled.</p>



<p>The judge further dismissed the common belief that crypto assets have no “real” value, concluding that value is “a judgment made by an aggregate of human minds.”</p>



<p>Judge Jeyaretnam referenced the <a href="https://zycrypto.com/singapore-financial-regulator-seeks-stakeholder-input-on-proposals-for-digital-payments/">consultation paper</a> by the Monetary Authority of Singapore (MAS) in her decision. The paper outlined potential requirements for segregation and custody of digital payment tokens, declaring that if digital assets can be practically identified and segregated, they could be legally held on trust.</p>



<p>The ruling also cites Order 22 of Singapore’s Rules of Court 2021, which includes crypto or other digital currency, cash, debt, a cash balance at a bank, bonds, shares, and other securities, in the definition of “movable property”.</p>



<p>The court has now ordered Ho, who accused a non-present cousin “Jason Teo” of gaining unauthorized access to her work laptop and controlling the relevant addresses, to return the assets to Bybit.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/singapore-high-court-recognizes-crypto-as-personal-property-equates-it-to-fiat-money/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Presidential Hopeful Robert F. Kennedy Jr. Discloses Buying Two Bitcoins For Each Of His Seven Kids</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/presidential-hopeful-robert-f-kennedy-jr-discloses-buying-two-bitcoins-for-each-of-his-seven-kids/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/presidential-hopeful-robert-f-kennedy-jr-discloses-buying-two-bitcoins-for-each-of-his-seven-kids/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Brenda Ngari]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 07:37:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XBTUSD]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=83159</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Presidential-Hopeful-Robert-F.-Kennedy-Jr.-Discloses-Buying-Two-Bitcoins-For-Each-Of-His-Seven-Kids.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Presidential Hopeful Robert F. Kennedy Jr. Discloses Buying Two Bitcoins For Each Of His Seven Kids" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Presidential-Hopeful-Robert-F.-Kennedy-Jr.-Discloses-Buying-Two-Bitcoins-For-Each-Of-His-Seven-Kids.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Presidential-Hopeful-Robert-F.-Kennedy-Jr.-Discloses-Buying-Two-Bitcoins-For-Each-Of-His-Seven-Kids-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Presidential-Hopeful-Robert-F.-Kennedy-Jr.-Discloses-Buying-Two-Bitcoins-For-Each-Of-His-Seven-Kids-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Presidential-Hopeful-Robert-F.-Kennedy-Jr.-Discloses-Buying-Two-Bitcoins-For-Each-Of-His-Seven-Kids-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>Kennedy has admitted he is a Bitcoin bag holder, contradicting his earlier denial during a Miami conference.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Presidential-Hopeful-Robert-F.-Kennedy-Jr.-Discloses-Buying-Two-Bitcoins-For-Each-Of-His-Seven-Kids.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Presidential Hopeful Robert F. Kennedy Jr. Discloses Buying Two Bitcoins For Each Of His Seven Kids" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Presidential-Hopeful-Robert-F.-Kennedy-Jr.-Discloses-Buying-Two-Bitcoins-For-Each-Of-His-Seven-Kids.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Presidential-Hopeful-Robert-F.-Kennedy-Jr.-Discloses-Buying-Two-Bitcoins-For-Each-Of-His-Seven-Kids-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Presidential-Hopeful-Robert-F.-Kennedy-Jr.-Discloses-Buying-Two-Bitcoins-For-Each-Of-His-Seven-Kids-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Presidential-Hopeful-Robert-F.-Kennedy-Jr.-Discloses-Buying-Two-Bitcoins-For-Each-Of-His-Seven-Kids-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>Democratic U.S. presidential candidate Robert F. Kennedy Jr has not shied away from controversy nor discussing views that might not be aligned with mainstream narratives. One such topic: Bitcoin (BTC).</p>



<p>Kennedy has admitted he is a Bitcoin bag holder, contradicting his earlier denial during a Miami conference. He claimed he took the money from his Monsanto case check and acquired 2 Bitcoins for each of his 7 children.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-rfk-jr-purchased-bitcoin-for-his-kids"><strong>RFK Jr. Purchased Bitcoin For His Kids</strong></h2>



<p>Robert F. Kennedy Jr. has finally confirmed owning Bitcoin.</p>



<p>The presidential candidate made the confirmation during a Twitter Spaces conversation with Scott Melker, a popular trader and podcast host known as “The Wolf of All Streets. Kennedy spoke in depth about how investments in crypto assets have the ability to pull the poor out of poverty.</p>



<p>In his opinion, Bitcoin lets small investors have an inflation-proof currency that is censorship-resistant and gives them freedom, unlike holding fiat currencies which are at the mercy of the system.&nbsp;</p>



<p>Robert, whose family is political royalty, then dropped the bombshell. The 69-year-old said he had “decided to put my money where my mouth is and bought two bitcoin for each of my seven children” right after the Miami Bitcoin conference held in May this year.</p>



<p>Kennedy <a href="https://zycrypto.com/pro-crypto-presidential-candidate-robert-kennedy-jr-lauds-bitcoin-throws-shade-at-oppressive-cbdcs/">made history</a> in May 2023 by becoming the first presidential candidate to announce that his campaign would accept donations in Bitcoin. However, he told revelers in Miami that he did not have any exposure to the classic cryptocurrency and that his endorsement of the asset was not investment advice. Nonetheless, a financial <a href="https://fm.cnbc.com/applications/cnbc.com/resources/editorialfiles/2023/07/07/Candidate_Report_RFK_Jr.pdf">document </a>obtained by <em>CNBC </em>showed that Kennedy held up to $250,000 worth of Bitcoin.</p>



<p>RFK Jr. recently <a href="https://zycrypto.com/crypto-booster-robert-f-kennedy-jr-promises-to-use-bitcoin-to-stabilize-us-dollar-if-he-becomes-president/">announced a bold plan to back the U.S. dollar with Bitcoin </a>and exempt BTC from capital gains tax. The nephew of former president John F. Kennedy is among a cadre of pro-crypto hopefuls that spans Republican Senator <a href="https://zycrypto.com/u-s-senator-ted-cruz-bought-as-much-as-50000-bitcoin-during-the-latest-crypto-market-meltdown/">Ted Cruz</a> and other presidential candidates like Florida governor <a href="https://zycrypto.com/no-cbdc-in-florida-asserts-pro-crypto-governor/">Ron DeSantis</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/presidential-hopeful-robert-f-kennedy-jr-discloses-buying-two-bitcoins-for-each-of-his-seven-kids/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Stays Flat At $29.5K After Federal Reserve Hikes Interest Rate To 22-Year Highs</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/bitcoin-stays-flat-at-29-5k-after-federal-reserve-hikes-interest-rate-to-22-year-highs/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/bitcoin-stays-flat-at-29-5k-after-federal-reserve-hikes-interest-rate-to-22-year-highs/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Brenda Ngari]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 22:00:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XBTUSD]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=83147</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Bitcoin-Pierces-30000-For-First-Time-Since-June-As-Bernstein-Calls-BTC-‘Faster-Horse-Compared-To-Gold.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Bitcoin Pierces $30,000 For First Time Since June As Bernstein Calls BTC ‘Faster Horse’ Compared To Gold" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Bitcoin-Pierces-30000-For-First-Time-Since-June-As-Bernstein-Calls-BTC-‘Faster-Horse-Compared-To-Gold.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Bitcoin-Pierces-30000-For-First-Time-Since-June-As-Bernstein-Calls-BTC-‘Faster-Horse-Compared-To-Gold-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Bitcoin-Pierces-30000-For-First-Time-Since-June-As-Bernstein-Calls-BTC-‘Faster-Horse-Compared-To-Gold-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Bitcoin-Pierces-30000-For-First-Time-Since-June-As-Bernstein-Calls-BTC-‘Faster-Horse-Compared-To-Gold-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>Bitcoin and the rest of the crypto market have held steady following the Federal Reserve’s announcement today that the central bank has hiked its benchmark interest rates by 25 basis points, bringing them to their highest level since 2001.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Bitcoin-Pierces-30000-For-First-Time-Since-June-As-Bernstein-Calls-BTC-‘Faster-Horse-Compared-To-Gold.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Bitcoin Pierces $30,000 For First Time Since June As Bernstein Calls BTC ‘Faster Horse’ Compared To Gold" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Bitcoin-Pierces-30000-For-First-Time-Since-June-As-Bernstein-Calls-BTC-‘Faster-Horse-Compared-To-Gold.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Bitcoin-Pierces-30000-For-First-Time-Since-June-As-Bernstein-Calls-BTC-‘Faster-Horse-Compared-To-Gold-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Bitcoin-Pierces-30000-For-First-Time-Since-June-As-Bernstein-Calls-BTC-‘Faster-Horse-Compared-To-Gold-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Bitcoin-Pierces-30000-For-First-Time-Since-June-As-Bernstein-Calls-BTC-‘Faster-Horse-Compared-To-Gold-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>Bitcoin and the rest of the crypto market have held steady following the Federal Reserve’s announcement today that the central bank has hiked its benchmark interest rates by 25 basis points, bringing them to their highest level since 2001.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-5-25-5-50-range"><strong>5.25%-5.50% Range</strong></h2>



<p>The U.S. Federal Reserve is pushing on its war against inflation.</p>



<p>The central bank announced today during the Federal Open Market Committee that it would be raising federal interest rates by a quarter of a percentage point.</p>



<p>The move, which aligned with market expectations, raises rates to a range of 5.25%-5.50%. This is the highest the federal funds rate has been in 22 years. In so doing, the bank increases the cost of borrowing, which strengthens the dollar&#8217;s value.</p>



<p>Today’s rate hike is a resumption of tightener monetary conditions by the Federal Reserve, which at its last meeting in June had halted what had then been a 15-month cycle of successive rate hikes.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-rate-hike-offers-bitcoin-bulls-little-fuel"><strong>Rate Hike Offers Bitcoin Bulls Little Fuel</strong></h2>



<p>Bitcoin, the world’s largest cryptocurrency by market value, was at the time of writing trading for $29,512 — a 0.9% increase over the past 24 hours, according to CoinGecko data. It’s now down 57.09% from its all-time high of $69,044.&nbsp;</p>



<p>Ether, the second biggest crypto asset, was up 0.7% over the same timeframe, trading hands for $1,882.87. ETH is down 61.38% from its peak of $4,878, while many other altcoins have fared much worse over the past year.</p>



<p>At his post-meeting press conference, Fed Chair Jerome Powell revealed that the central bank was still committed to bringing down inflation — which currently hovers at 3% — to 2%. Notably, inflation in the U.S. stood at over 9% a year ago.</p>



<p>&#8220;We’ve covered a lot of ground, and the full effects of our tightening are yet to be felt,&#8221; Powell noted. &#8220;Inflation remains well above our longer-run goal of 2%.&#8221;</p>



<p>Chair Powell further indicated no decisions regarding the pace of future rate hikes or pauses had been made. He added that the Federal Open Market Committee (FOMC) would “assess the need for further tightening” on a “meeting by meeting” basis and further said he doesn&#8217;t expect inflation to drop to 2% until 2025.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/bitcoin-stays-flat-at-29-5k-after-federal-reserve-hikes-interest-rate-to-22-year-highs/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dogecoin Jumps Past Cardano Amid Hopes Twitter’s X Rebrand Will Introduce A DOGE Payment Option</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/dogecoin-jumps-past-cardano-amid-hopes-twitters-x-rebrand-will-introduce-a-doge-payment-option/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/dogecoin-jumps-past-cardano-amid-hopes-twitters-x-rebrand-will-introduce-a-doge-payment-option/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Brenda Ngari]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 21:56:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADAUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Doge]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DOGEUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Twitter]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=83146</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/Robinhood-CEO-Tenev-Sees-Dogecoin-As-The-Future-Currency-Of-The-Internet-But-Much-Has-To-Be-Done.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Robinhood CEO Tenev Sees Dogecoin As The Future Currency Of The Internet, But Much Has To Be Done" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/Robinhood-CEO-Tenev-Sees-Dogecoin-As-The-Future-Currency-Of-The-Internet-But-Much-Has-To-Be-Done.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/Robinhood-CEO-Tenev-Sees-Dogecoin-As-The-Future-Currency-Of-The-Internet-But-Much-Has-To-Be-Done-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/Robinhood-CEO-Tenev-Sees-Dogecoin-As-The-Future-Currency-Of-The-Internet-But-Much-Has-To-Be-Done-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/Robinhood-CEO-Tenev-Sees-Dogecoin-As-The-Future-Currency-Of-The-Internet-But-Much-Has-To-Be-Done-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>OG meme coin Dogecoin has overtaken Cardano in terms of market capitalization as investors scoop up DOGE in hopes of the token playing a bigger role on Twitter, which rebranded as “everything app” X on July 24.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/Robinhood-CEO-Tenev-Sees-Dogecoin-As-The-Future-Currency-Of-The-Internet-But-Much-Has-To-Be-Done.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Robinhood CEO Tenev Sees Dogecoin As The Future Currency Of The Internet, But Much Has To Be Done" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/Robinhood-CEO-Tenev-Sees-Dogecoin-As-The-Future-Currency-Of-The-Internet-But-Much-Has-To-Be-Done.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/Robinhood-CEO-Tenev-Sees-Dogecoin-As-The-Future-Currency-Of-The-Internet-But-Much-Has-To-Be-Done-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/Robinhood-CEO-Tenev-Sees-Dogecoin-As-The-Future-Currency-Of-The-Internet-But-Much-Has-To-Be-Done-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/Robinhood-CEO-Tenev-Sees-Dogecoin-As-The-Future-Currency-Of-The-Internet-But-Much-Has-To-Be-Done-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>OG meme coin Dogecoin has overtaken Cardano in terms of market capitalization as investors scoop up DOGE in hopes of the token playing a bigger role on Twitter, which rebranded as “everything app” X on July 24.</p>



<p>At the time of publication, DOGE was up around 2.5% in the past 24 hours, according to data from CoinGecko, changing hands for $0.0789. And in the past week, it&#8217;s up 13.8%, making it the best-performing coin among the top 10 cryptocurrencies. Cardano (ADA), on the other hand, has lost 4.5% over the last seven days, with its market cap falling below Dogecoin&#8217;s.</p>



<p>Cryptic tweets from Twitter owner Elon Musk fueled the Dogecoin upsurge. On Tuesday, Musk <a href="https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1683877911315599360">tweeted </a>a promo of the social media giant’s new logo — which was originally shared by a Dogecoin designer — and also added the Dogecoin ticker logo to the location field in his Twitter bio.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Anyone else notice the Dogecoin (Ɖ) symbol in Elon Musks location <a href="https://t.co/Y1OGT42hD2">pic.twitter.com/Y1OGT42hD2</a></p>&mdash; Morgan (@Helloimmorgan) <a href="https://twitter.com/Helloimmorgan/status/1683607928169742336?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">July 24, 2023</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>Musk adding Dogecoin’s symbol to his bio reignited rumours DOGE may soon be used for payments on X, given the eccentric billionaire’s infatuation with the meme coin.</p>



<p>Such speculations aren’t completely unfounded. Last April, Musk <a href="https://zycrypto.com/elon-musks-proposal-to-add-dogecoin-payments-for-twitter-blue-puts-a-meteoric-rally-into-play-for-doge/">hinted </a>at making dogecoin a payment mechanism for Twitter Blue, the site’s subscription service with premium features. His EV maker Tesla already <a href="https://zycrypto.com/tesla-boots-bitcoin-but-retains-once-joke-crypto-dogecoin-as-a-means-of-payment/">accepts DOGE payments</a> for merch purchases. Musk also teased Dogecoin payments for his other enterprises, <a href="https://zycrypto.com/with-spacex-poised-to-accept-dogecoin-payments-for-merch-soon-will-doge-get-its-glory-back/">SpaceX </a>and <a href="https://zycrypto.com/elon-musk-drops-major-signal-about-spacexs-starlink-accepting-dogecoin-payments-after-tesla/">Starlink</a>. </p>



<p>If Dogecoin is indeed integrated into X’s payment infrastructure, the cryptocurrency could see a bull breather and possibly surge to new record highs.</p>



<p>But Musk’s fondness for Dogecoin has attracted some negative attention. In June last year, a group of beleaguered Dogecoin investors <a href="https://zycrypto.com/dogefather-elon-musk-slapped-with-mammoth-258-billion-lawsuit-for-allegedly-pumping-dogecoin/">lodged a $258 billion class action suit</a> against Musk, Tesla, and SpaceX. The complaint accuses the self-proclaimed Dogefather of operating a pyramid scheme to pump Dogecoin’s price “more than 36,000% over two years and then letting it crash”.&nbsp;</p>



<p>Musk’s lawyers have <a href="https://zycrypto.com/elon-musk-tesla-want-258-billion-dogecoin-case-dismissed/">requested </a>a United States judge to dismiss the lawsuit, arguing that it&#8217;s a “fanciful work of fiction”.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/dogecoin-jumps-past-cardano-amid-hopes-twitters-x-rebrand-will-introduce-a-doge-payment-option/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dogecoin Whales Scoop Over $200M Worth of Coins in Under a Month Amid Bullish Price Outlook</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/dogecoin-whales-scoop-over-200m-worth-of-coins-in-under-a-month-amid-bullish-price-outlook/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/dogecoin-whales-scoop-over-200m-worth-of-coins-in-under-a-month-amid-bullish-price-outlook/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Newton Gitonga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 19:46:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Doge]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DOGEUSD]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=83142</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Dogecoins-Future-Could-Follow-This-Bullish-Trajectory-To-1-DOGE-Price-Thanks-To-Elon-Musk.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Dogecoin&#039;s Future Could Follow This Bullish Trajectory To $1 DOGE Price Thanks To Elon Musk" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Dogecoins-Future-Could-Follow-This-Bullish-Trajectory-To-1-DOGE-Price-Thanks-To-Elon-Musk.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Dogecoins-Future-Could-Follow-This-Bullish-Trajectory-To-1-DOGE-Price-Thanks-To-Elon-Musk-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Dogecoins-Future-Could-Follow-This-Bullish-Trajectory-To-1-DOGE-Price-Thanks-To-Elon-Musk-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Dogecoins-Future-Could-Follow-This-Bullish-Trajectory-To-1-DOGE-Price-Thanks-To-Elon-Musk-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>Dogecoin whales have made a significant splash in the crypto market in recent weeks, acquiring $225 million worth of DOGE coins, according to data from the on-chain analytics platform IntoTheBlock.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Dogecoins-Future-Could-Follow-This-Bullish-Trajectory-To-1-DOGE-Price-Thanks-To-Elon-Musk.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Dogecoin&#039;s Future Could Follow This Bullish Trajectory To $1 DOGE Price Thanks To Elon Musk" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Dogecoins-Future-Could-Follow-This-Bullish-Trajectory-To-1-DOGE-Price-Thanks-To-Elon-Musk.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Dogecoins-Future-Could-Follow-This-Bullish-Trajectory-To-1-DOGE-Price-Thanks-To-Elon-Musk-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Dogecoins-Future-Could-Follow-This-Bullish-Trajectory-To-1-DOGE-Price-Thanks-To-Elon-Musk-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Dogecoins-Future-Could-Follow-This-Bullish-Trajectory-To-1-DOGE-Price-Thanks-To-Elon-Musk-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>Dogecoin whales have made a significant splash in the crypto market in recent weeks, acquiring $225 million worth of DOGE coins, according to data from the on-chain analytics platform IntoTheBlock.</p>



<p>Crypto analyst Ali Martinez brought attention to this astounding purchase on Tuesday, stating that these whales bought around 3 billion DOGE in the last three weeks alone.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img decoding="async" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/2oki2oWciUsA_WGY2eylDhQxKxkGGBe1bkiv35STuIoGNCF_ae09_yQ-4cgEahKCzspghu4bTODi8yM7fjYLzijEVRPH8PG01YBjwbiDOhvZZOrX7Xz7n0Gb6BQuYXue26PkE9buDrsqVuDX0Res1Q" alt=""/></figure>



<p>The surge in Dogecoin acquisitions comes amidst a bullish price outlook, driven further by influential figures such as Elon Musk. The billionaire tech entrepreneur has been a vocal supporter of Dogecoin, often causing notable price fluctuations with his tweets. Musk&#8217;s recent strategic move on Twitter has amplified the buzz around Dogecoin.</p>



<p>On Monday, he revamped Twitter&#8217;s logo, replacing the iconic blue bird with an &#8220;X&#8221; symbol. Musk updated his Twitter bio to display the Dogecoin symbol alongside this change, further cementing his backing of the meme-inspired cryptocurrency.</p>



<p>This move did not go unnoticed in the crypto community, leading to speculation about the potential integration of Dogecoin into the Twitter platform. Given Musk&#8217;s history of publicly endorsing DOGE, many believe his actions hint at the possibility of utilizing Dogecoin as a tipping currency for the app. As a result, investors rushed to capitalize on the positive sentiment, resulting in an immediate 9% surge in Dogecoin&#8217;s price.</p>



<p>Musk&#8217;s interest in cryptocurrencies is no secret. After acquiring Twitter for a staggering $44 billion last year, he merged it into his privately-held corporation, X Corp. In October 2022, Musk expressed his vision of creating an &#8220;everything app&#8221; with the acquisition, and now, his recent Twitter bio update has only fueled speculation of potential <a href="https://zycrypto.com/tesla-boots-bitcoin-but-retains-once-joke-crypto-dogecoin-as-a-means-of-payment/">Dogecoin integration</a>.</p>



<p>Cryptocurrency analysts have also been observing these developments closely. Popular crypto analyst Kaleo “@Cryptokaleo” weighed in, suggesting that Musk&#8217;s inclusion of Dogecoin in his bio alongside the X rebranding may not be a mere coincidence. The pundit believed that Musk might reveal his plans for integrating DOGE into the X app in the coming days or weeks. </p>



<p>Kaleo also emphasized the importance of being patient with DOGE, noting that the charts continue to indicate positive trends even after a minor correction.</p>



<p><em>“In the meantime, Dogecoin cools off a bit and catches up with the blood we’re seeing across the rest of the market. Why? People are impatient and they want immediate results. Rumours and hope only holds up for so long in a bear market. So, I think it’s a pretty solid move to continue to accumulate on any dips we get from here. The charts continue to look great and should even after a minor correction. Just gotta be a little patient,”</em> wrote Kaleo.</p>



<p>At press time, DOGE was trading at 0.079, up just over 2% in the past 24 hours. In the past 48 hours, the top meme cryptocurrency has toppled Cardano to become the seven largest coin by market capitalization.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/dogecoin-whales-scoop-over-200m-worth-of-coins-in-under-a-month-amid-bullish-price-outlook/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>XRP Verdict: SEC Appeal Could Actually ‘Amplify’ Ripple’s Landmark Victory, CLO Asserts</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/xrp-verdict-sec-appeal-could-actually-amplify-ripples-landmark-victory-clo-asserts/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/xrp-verdict-sec-appeal-could-actually-amplify-ripples-landmark-victory-clo-asserts/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Brenda Ngari]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 18:22:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=83139</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Garlinghouse-Reveals-Ripple-Will-Spend-200M-Defending-Itself-Against-The-SEC-Even-As-Case-Worries-XRP-Holders.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Garlinghouse Reveals Ripple Will Spend $200M Defending Itself Against The SEC Even As Case Worries XRP Holders" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Garlinghouse-Reveals-Ripple-Will-Spend-200M-Defending-Itself-Against-The-SEC-Even-As-Case-Worries-XRP-Holders.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Garlinghouse-Reveals-Ripple-Will-Spend-200M-Defending-Itself-Against-The-SEC-Even-As-Case-Worries-XRP-Holders-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Garlinghouse-Reveals-Ripple-Will-Spend-200M-Defending-Itself-Against-The-SEC-Even-As-Case-Worries-XRP-Holders-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Garlinghouse-Reveals-Ripple-Will-Spend-200M-Defending-Itself-Against-The-SEC-Even-As-Case-Worries-XRP-Holders-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>Stuart Alderoty, legal chief at Ripple, has dismissed concerns about a likely appeal by the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) to the historic XRP ruling earlier this month.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Garlinghouse-Reveals-Ripple-Will-Spend-200M-Defending-Itself-Against-The-SEC-Even-As-Case-Worries-XRP-Holders.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Garlinghouse Reveals Ripple Will Spend $200M Defending Itself Against The SEC Even As Case Worries XRP Holders" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Garlinghouse-Reveals-Ripple-Will-Spend-200M-Defending-Itself-Against-The-SEC-Even-As-Case-Worries-XRP-Holders.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Garlinghouse-Reveals-Ripple-Will-Spend-200M-Defending-Itself-Against-The-SEC-Even-As-Case-Worries-XRP-Holders-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Garlinghouse-Reveals-Ripple-Will-Spend-200M-Defending-Itself-Against-The-SEC-Even-As-Case-Worries-XRP-Holders-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Garlinghouse-Reveals-Ripple-Will-Spend-200M-Defending-Itself-Against-The-SEC-Even-As-Case-Worries-XRP-Holders-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>Stuart Alderoty, legal chief at Ripple, has dismissed concerns about a likely appeal by the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) to the historic XRP ruling earlier this month. Alderoty said the company is prepared in the event of an appeal by the SEC. In fact, he believes such a move could see the company further consolidate its win over the watchdog.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-ripple-legal-team-not-backing-down"><strong>Ripple Legal Team Not Backing Down</strong></h2>



<p>The SEC recently <a href="https://zycrypto.com/sec-prepares-to-challenge-ripple-court-victory-heres-what-this-could-mean-for-xrp/">suggested </a>that it was mulling an appeal of the Ripple ruling, as per a filing in the ongoing legal brawl against Terraform Labs and its founder, Do Kwon.</p>



<p><a href="https://techcrunch.com/2023/07/25/ripple-sec-ruling-xrp/?guccounter=1&amp;guce_referrer=aHR0cHM6Ly9jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS8&amp;guce_referrer_sig=AQAAAHMyPy3fSfi6xX_qhmJRWm4FS9DTNFf-LVivQ7bwS2fjTRbjm7aOhDIOdqB2E22TLA6Y5_uuHVFjMv8ShxkyGpoCCt6_FBNvM4CA64M7I0NwXUATJnQ34-3dqXmjw-TgBtI7Sm9Q0c9PJiER6HBeQbqYc2Nn_lAmd9sJYv2Tq8cO">Speaking </a>on the TechCrunch podcast on Wednesday, Ripple’s chief legal officer Stuart Alderoty maintained that XRP is not an investment contract and that the Ripple legal team would not back down from an appeal initiated in the court by the SEC.</p>



<p>“We think the judge got that right, and we think that was a faithful application of the law, and I think a court of appeals will not only affirm that but maybe even amplify that to even a greater extent.”</p>



<p>Federal district judge Analisa Torres <a href="https://zycrypto.com/major-ripple-victory-xrp-pops-in-ballistic-rally-as-judge-finally-rules-it-isnt-a-security/">ruled </a>on July 13 that XRP, the token that powers Ripple’s payments network, is “not necessarily a security on its face”, except for instances when it was offered to hedge funds and other institutional buyers. This was largely considered a glorious triumph for Ripple and the crypto industry at large.</p>



<p>Last week, the SEC expressed its displeasure with the verdict and hinted that it would later challenge it. “SEC staff is considering the various avenues that are available for further review and intends to recommend that the SEC seek such review,” the agency’s lawyers noted.</p>



<p>Alderoty further forecasted that the SEC would begin losing ongoing cases where it attempts to contend that crypto assets are securities.&nbsp;</p>



<p>“Our case and the decision rendered by our judge [Torres] will comfort other judges that the SEC is just misguided.”&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>



<p>Although Ripple’s win in court lifted a regulatory cloud that had hung over the project for years, Alderoty noted that the coast is still not clear regarding where crypto stands in the eyes of U.S. law. The CLO also criticized the SEC’s regulation-by-enforcement approach that has effectively stifled crypto in America.&nbsp;</p>



<p>“We still need a rational, comprehensive, and understandable regulatory framework for crypto in the U.S.,” Alderoty posited. “Because of the SEC’s refusal to faithfully apply the law […] the U.S. has been visibly falling behind the rest of the world.”</p>



<p>The price of XRP sits above $0.70 as of this writing, according to data from <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/xrp">CoinGecko</a>, marking a 0.4% increase over the last 24 hours.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/xrp-verdict-sec-appeal-could-actually-amplify-ripples-landmark-victory-clo-asserts/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Rebranding Twitter to X Sends Dogecoin On A Rally — Here&#8217;s Why DOGE Could Explode to $1</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/rebranding-twitter-to-x-sends-dogecoin-on-a-rally-heres-why-doge-could-explode-soon/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/rebranding-twitter-to-x-sends-dogecoin-on-a-rally-heres-why-doge-could-explode-soon/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aliyu Pokima]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 13:45:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Doge]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DOGEUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elon Musk]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Twitter]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=83123</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Dogecoin-Set-For-Gargantuan-Gains-As-Elon-Musk-Moves-To-Proceed-With-44B-Twitter-Purchase-Agreement.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Dogecoin Set For Gargantuan Gains As Elon Musk Moves To Proceed With $44B Twitter Purchase Agreement" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Dogecoin-Set-For-Gargantuan-Gains-As-Elon-Musk-Moves-To-Proceed-With-44B-Twitter-Purchase-Agreement.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Dogecoin-Set-For-Gargantuan-Gains-As-Elon-Musk-Moves-To-Proceed-With-44B-Twitter-Purchase-Agreement-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Dogecoin-Set-For-Gargantuan-Gains-As-Elon-Musk-Moves-To-Proceed-With-44B-Twitter-Purchase-Agreement-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Dogecoin-Set-For-Gargantuan-Gains-As-Elon-Musk-Moves-To-Proceed-With-44B-Twitter-Purchase-Agreement-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>At the start of the week, Twitter ditched the bird logo for X in a rebrand that has sent the community buzzing, but amid the chatter, Dogecoin (DOGE) has ridden the wave to go on a strong rally.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Dogecoin-Set-For-Gargantuan-Gains-As-Elon-Musk-Moves-To-Proceed-With-44B-Twitter-Purchase-Agreement.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Dogecoin Set For Gargantuan Gains As Elon Musk Moves To Proceed With $44B Twitter Purchase Agreement" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Dogecoin-Set-For-Gargantuan-Gains-As-Elon-Musk-Moves-To-Proceed-With-44B-Twitter-Purchase-Agreement.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Dogecoin-Set-For-Gargantuan-Gains-As-Elon-Musk-Moves-To-Proceed-With-44B-Twitter-Purchase-Agreement-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Dogecoin-Set-For-Gargantuan-Gains-As-Elon-Musk-Moves-To-Proceed-With-44B-Twitter-Purchase-Agreement-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Dogecoin-Set-For-Gargantuan-Gains-As-Elon-Musk-Moves-To-Proceed-With-44B-Twitter-Purchase-Agreement-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>At the start of the week, Twitter ditched the bird logo for X in a rebrand that has sent the community buzzing, but amid the chatter, Dogecoin (DOGE) has ridden the wave to go on a strong rally.</p>



<p>Within hours of the rebrand, DOGE climbed by 8% to trade at $0.0771 after weeks of seemingly inactivity. The rally puts DOGE as the seventh largest virtual currency, with a market capitalization of $10.8 billion above Cardano (ADA) and Solana (SOL).</p>



<p>The meme coin began its rally after Twitter’s owner Elon Musk added Dogecoin’s logo to his bio minutes after the rebrand. The move triggered a wave of speculation among community members that DOGE will play a significant role in the newly rebranded micro-blogging site and possibly go up to the much-coveted $1 price.</p>



<p>It is widely expected that DOGE will serve as the primary means of payment in the new “everything app” X, a sentiment shared across the digital asset community since Musk took over the platform. Given the success of the Bitcoin (BTC) tipping feature, Dogecoin’s community is rippling with enthusiasm that a similar feature will be rolled out on the platform leveraging the meme coin.</p>



<p>In the weeks leading up to the rebrand, Dogecoin whales have steadily bolstered their holdings. Data from IntoTheBlock indicates that whales snagged up 3 billion DOGE worth $225 million, laying the foundation for a future surge for the token.</p>



<p>Musk has been nursing ambitions to transform Twitter into a super app in the same mould as the Chinese social media platform WeChat. Musk enlisted the <a href="https://zycrypto.com/doge-floki-go-ballistic-after-elon-musk-teases-new-twitter-ceo/">services</a> of Linda Yaccarino in May to serve as the platform’s CEO to bring his vision to reality, making X the default app for mobile users.</p>



<p><em>“If you’re China, you kind of live on WeChat, it does everything,”</em> said Musk.<em> “It’s sort of like Twitter, plus PayPal, plus a whole bunch of other things. And all rolled into one.”</em></p>



<p>Musk is no stranger to jarring changes since taking over the reins at Twitter with the Tesla CEO increasing the number of premium users on the app, cracking down on bots, and laying off a chunk of employees.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-not-the-only-one-riding-the-wave">Not the only one riding the wave</h2>



<p>DOGE is not the only virtual currency riding the wave of Twitter’s rebrand to embark on a rally. A cross-section of XRP’s community interpreted the X rebrand as a nod to their “<a href="https://zycrypto.com/potential-sec-appeal-in-ripple-lawsuit-not-a-blow-to-xrp-legal-expert-reveals-why/">victory</a>” over the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC).</p>



<p>Barely hours after the rebrand, virtual currency investors sunk funds into an unrelated X token, sending prices up by over 2,000%. X, the native token of the X NFT marketplace, surged on the backs of the rebrand, with speculators hoping to make a quick buck.</p>



<p>Other assets failed to latch onto the wave, with BTC falling below the <a href="https://zycrypto.com/is-bitcoin-eyeing-new-highs-by-holding-the-30-5k-zone/">$30,000</a> mark and SOL slumping by over 10%. Ethereum (ETH) and Polygon (MATIC) recorded their fair share of losses in what experts speculate to be a long week for the ecosystem.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/rebranding-twitter-to-x-sends-dogecoin-on-a-rally-heres-why-doge-could-explode-soon/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ripple CEO Calls For Legislative Clarity To Protect Retail Investors Amid SEC&#8217;s Enforcement Chaos</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/ripple-ceo-calls-for-legislative-clarity-to-protect-retail-investors-amid-secs-enforcement-chaos/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/ripple-ceo-calls-for-legislative-clarity-to-protect-retail-investors-amid-secs-enforcement-chaos/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Newton Gitonga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 22:55:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=83125</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ripple-Buys-Shares-In-European-Crypto-Exchange-Bitstamp-Massive-XRP-Growth-Ahead.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Ripple Buys Shares In European Crypto Exchange Bitstamp: Massive XRP Growth Ahead?" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ripple-Buys-Shares-In-European-Crypto-Exchange-Bitstamp-Massive-XRP-Growth-Ahead.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ripple-Buys-Shares-In-European-Crypto-Exchange-Bitstamp-Massive-XRP-Growth-Ahead-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ripple-Buys-Shares-In-European-Crypto-Exchange-Bitstamp-Massive-XRP-Growth-Ahead-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ripple-Buys-Shares-In-European-Crypto-Exchange-Bitstamp-Massive-XRP-Growth-Ahead-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>Ripple CEO Brad Garlinghouse has called out the U.S. Securities Exchange Commission (SEC) for its regulatory overreach over crypto, arguing that it is hurting retail investors and small enterprises.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ripple-Buys-Shares-In-European-Crypto-Exchange-Bitstamp-Massive-XRP-Growth-Ahead.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Ripple Buys Shares In European Crypto Exchange Bitstamp: Massive XRP Growth Ahead?" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ripple-Buys-Shares-In-European-Crypto-Exchange-Bitstamp-Massive-XRP-Growth-Ahead.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ripple-Buys-Shares-In-European-Crypto-Exchange-Bitstamp-Massive-XRP-Growth-Ahead-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ripple-Buys-Shares-In-European-Crypto-Exchange-Bitstamp-Massive-XRP-Growth-Ahead-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ripple-Buys-Shares-In-European-Crypto-Exchange-Bitstamp-Massive-XRP-Growth-Ahead-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>Ripple CEO Brad Garlinghouse has called out the U.S. Securities Exchange Commission (SEC) for its regulatory overreach over crypto, arguing that it is hurting retail investors and small enterprises.</p>



<p>In a bold and outspoken tweet on Sunday, Garlinghouse addressed the SEC’s handling of cryptocurrency regulations, calling for legislative clarity to protect retail investors and small enterprises from the repercussions of the SEC&#8217;s enforcement approach in the crypto space. Notably, Garlinghouse&#8217;s tweet raised crucial concerns about the SEC&#8217;s actions and their impact on the crypto community.</p>



<p>“<em>An important topic has come up about protecting retail. The SEC created this mess by proclaiming it was the cop on the crypto beat when it had no legal jurisdiction. Where’s that gotten us? Consumers left holding the bag in bankruptcy court while the SEC holds press conferences.&#8221; </em>He wrote.</p>



<p>He further highlighted the consequences faced by retail investors due to the SEC&#8217;s regulatory overreach in the cryptocurrency sector, emphasizing the need for legislative intervention to avoid confusion, resulting in retail investors being left vulnerable to the inherent risks of the crypto market.</p>



<p><em>&#8220;It’s absurd to blame a Judge for faithfully applying the law. We all know legislation – not more regulation by enforcement – is the only way forward to provide clear rules and protect retail,”</em> he added.</p>



<p>According to him, this call for legislative clarity reflects the growing sentiment among industry leaders that regulatory frameworks must be established to protect investors and promote innovation without stifling growth. Garlinghouse also expressed appreciation for members of Congress who have been advocating for more comprehensive cryptocurrency legislation.</p>



<p>Garlinghouse&#8217;s comments come approximately a week after the court delivered a <a href="https://zycrypto.com/major-ripple-victory-xrp-pops-in-ballistic-rally-as-judge-finally-rules-it-isnt-a-security/">landmark decision</a> in favor of Ripple, ruling that XRP is not a security. This ruling brought clarity to XRP&#8217;s status and underscored the need for a more robust and predictable regulatory framework to govern the crypto market.</p>



<p>Over the years, the SEC&#8217;s handling of cryptocurrency enforcement has drawn considerable criticism, primarily centred around its potential negative effects on innovation and investment within the industry. While President Biden’s administration has been slow to take decisive action on this matter, several lawmakers have proposed pro-cryptocurrency regulations. However, none of these proposals has been successfully passed yet. Concurrently, a growing chorus of voices has been calling for the removal of SEC chair Gary Gensler.</p>



<p>That said, even though the recent court ruling in favour of Ripple&#8217;s XRP may have provided some relief for the crypto sector, the overall regulatory landscape remains uncertain. Notably, the SEC has recently <a href="https://zycrypto.com/sec-prepares-to-challenge-ripple-court-victory-heres-what-this-could-mean-for-xrp/">hinted</a> at appealing the court’s judgement which it argues goes against “fundamental securities laws principles” such as the Howey test.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/ripple-ceo-calls-for-legislative-clarity-to-protect-retail-investors-amid-secs-enforcement-chaos/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Whales Make Up A Large Chunk Of Exchange Inflows, Reaching A New High Along The Way</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/bitcoin-whales-make-up-a-large-chunk-of-exchange-inflows-reaching-a-new-high-along-the-way/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/bitcoin-whales-make-up-a-large-chunk-of-exchange-inflows-reaching-a-new-high-along-the-way/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aliyu Pokima]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 21:44:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XBTUSD]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=83121</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/Whales-Are-Gobbling-Up-Bitcoin-Even-With-The-Recent-Market-Slump.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Whales Are “Gobbling Up” Bitcoin Even With The Recent Market Slump" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/Whales-Are-Gobbling-Up-Bitcoin-Even-With-The-Recent-Market-Slump.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/Whales-Are-Gobbling-Up-Bitcoin-Even-With-The-Recent-Market-Slump-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/Whales-Are-Gobbling-Up-Bitcoin-Even-With-The-Recent-Market-Slump-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/Whales-Are-Gobbling-Up-Bitcoin-Even-With-The-Recent-Market-Slump-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>Bitcoin (BTC) whales have recorded an uptick in trading activity in recent weeks with short-term holders (STH) surprisingly at the fore.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/Whales-Are-Gobbling-Up-Bitcoin-Even-With-The-Recent-Market-Slump.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Whales Are “Gobbling Up” Bitcoin Even With The Recent Market Slump" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/Whales-Are-Gobbling-Up-Bitcoin-Even-With-The-Recent-Market-Slump.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/Whales-Are-Gobbling-Up-Bitcoin-Even-With-The-Recent-Market-Slump-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/Whales-Are-Gobbling-Up-Bitcoin-Even-With-The-Recent-Market-Slump-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/Whales-Are-Gobbling-Up-Bitcoin-Even-With-The-Recent-Market-Slump-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC) whales have recorded an uptick in trading activity in recent weeks, with short-term holders (STH) surprisingly at the fore. </p>



<p>In its latest newsletter, “The Week On-Chain”, digital asset analytics firm Glassnode explained that since the price of BTC soared above $30,000 in June, there has been a slight shift among different levels of investors in Bitcoin.</p>



<p><a href="https://zycrypto.com/bitcoin-whales-transaction-count-of-1m-signal-declining-market-sentiment-here-are-its-implications-for-btc/">Bitcoin whales</a> exchange inflows hit a one-year high in July at 41%, following positive activity on the broader market. Observers have long noted that the actions of whales show an asset&#8217;s market health, leading to bulls understanding their ‘netflow to exchanges.’</p>



<p>“<em>Whale-to-exchange net flows have tended to oscillate between ±5k BTC/day over the last five years. However, throughout June and July this year, whale inflows have sustained an elevated inflow bias of between 4.0k to 6.5k BTC/day,” </em>Glassnode wrote.</p>



<p>Closely following whales, miners are also driving Bitcoin activities in exchanges as all-time high hash rates and mining difficulty looms. According to a report from Bitfinex, mining pools are deploying multiple strategies to sell large volumes of Bitcoin on exchanges.</p>



<p>Mining pool, Poolin accounts for most of the inflow as the report shows that overall, miners are hedging positions with derivatives exchanges tapping a 70,000 BTC 30-day volume this month.</p>



<p>“<em>Miners are clearly bullish on Bitcoin as they commit more resources to mining, hence triggering the mining difficulty, but they are hedging their position, hence the despatch of more Bitcoin to exchanges,” </em>the report stated.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-short-term-holders-light-the-way">Short-term holders light the way </h2>



<p>The notion that BTC whales hold for extended periods may have slowed following a speculative investor trend in recent weeks. Short-term holders tend to keep assets for a maximum of 155 days, a trend that is now more common in exchanges.</p>



<p>Short-term holder dominance has spiked to 82% miles above the long-term holders&#8217; range, which fluctuates between 55-65% in the last five years.</p>



<p>Short-term trading activity among whales boomed with the infamous implosion of FTX, leading to whales looking to tap into the volatile price movements in the market.</p>



<p>“<em>From this, we can establish a case that much of the recent trading activity is driven by Whales active within the 2023 market (and thus classified as STHs). If we look at the degree of Profit/Loss realized by Short-Term Holder volume flowing into exchanges, it becomes evident that these newer investors are trading local market conditions,” </em>Glassnode added.&nbsp;</p>



<p>BTC trades at $29,238 at press time, with outflows recorded in Bitcoin-related products after five weeks of consecutive inflows.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/bitcoin-whales-make-up-a-large-chunk-of-exchange-inflows-reaching-a-new-high-along-the-way/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>XRP Price To $10 By September? Market Watchers Outline Bullish Trajectory Amid Ripple&#8217;s &#8220;Big Win&#8221;</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/xrp-price-to-10-by-september-market-watchers-outline-bullish-trajectory-amid-ripples-big-win/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/xrp-price-to-10-by-september-market-watchers-outline-bullish-trajectory-amid-ripples-big-win/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aaron Feuerstein]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 10:34:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=83100</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/XRP-Army-Sees-Bullish-Prospects-As-Ripple-Starts-EVM-Compatibility-Tests-On-Its-XRPL-Sidechain.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="XRP Army Sees Bullish Prospects As Ripple Starts EVM Compatibility Tests On Its XRPL Sidechain" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/XRP-Army-Sees-Bullish-Prospects-As-Ripple-Starts-EVM-Compatibility-Tests-On-Its-XRPL-Sidechain.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/XRP-Army-Sees-Bullish-Prospects-As-Ripple-Starts-EVM-Compatibility-Tests-On-Its-XRPL-Sidechain-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/XRP-Army-Sees-Bullish-Prospects-As-Ripple-Starts-EVM-Compatibility-Tests-On-Its-XRPL-Sidechain-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/XRP-Army-Sees-Bullish-Prospects-As-Ripple-Starts-EVM-Compatibility-Tests-On-Its-XRPL-Sidechain-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>According to market watchers, XRP Price could hit $10 this year. This is not based on underlying fundamentals but rather on...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/XRP-Army-Sees-Bullish-Prospects-As-Ripple-Starts-EVM-Compatibility-Tests-On-Its-XRPL-Sidechain.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="XRP Army Sees Bullish Prospects As Ripple Starts EVM Compatibility Tests On Its XRPL Sidechain" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/XRP-Army-Sees-Bullish-Prospects-As-Ripple-Starts-EVM-Compatibility-Tests-On-Its-XRPL-Sidechain.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/XRP-Army-Sees-Bullish-Prospects-As-Ripple-Starts-EVM-Compatibility-Tests-On-Its-XRPL-Sidechain-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/XRP-Army-Sees-Bullish-Prospects-As-Ripple-Starts-EVM-Compatibility-Tests-On-Its-XRPL-Sidechain-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/XRP-Army-Sees-Bullish-Prospects-As-Ripple-Starts-EVM-Compatibility-Tests-On-Its-XRPL-Sidechain-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>According to market watchers, <a href="https://zycrypto.com/the-good-bad-and-the-complicated-from-the-sec-vs-ripple-verdict-as-bulls-envision-10-xrp-price/">XRP Price</a> could hit $10 this year. This is not based on underlying fundamentals but rather on technical chart analysis. According to past trends, the price could reach $1.70 early this quarter, $6 in August, and over $10 in September if the monthly percentage sees the same trajectory as in the past.</p>



<p>However, it should be noted that technical analysis uses chart patterns based on historical data to predict the future. Not surprisingly, this method has its flaws and regularly receives criticism. Analysts admit that it is incomprehensible to ascertain if that price will be attained by Q3 2023.</p>



<p>While this price prediction seems a massive move from the current 70 Cents, it would still be far from another target some have. Based on a popular Simpsons meme, wild online speculations around XRP have reached $589 per coin.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="646" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1-1024x646.png" alt="" class="wp-image-83101" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1-1024x646.png 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1-300x189.png 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1-768x485.png 768w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1-1536x970.png 1536w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1-2048x1293.png 2048w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /><figcaption class="wp-element-caption">XRPUSD Chart by <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/XRPUSD/">TradingView</a></figcaption></figure>



<p>While nothing is impossible, expecting such colossal price movements in such short periods seems highly speculative. On the other side, many have been disappointed with XRP’s performance after <a href="https://zycrypto.com/major-ripple-victory-xrp-pops-in-ballistic-rally-as-judge-finally-rules-it-isnt-a-security/">Judge Torres ruled partially in favour of Ripple</a>.</p>



<p>On July 13, Judge Analisa Torres granted that XRP sold on exchanges did not constitute a security. The Judge said, however, that sales to institutions represent the sale of securities which in Ripple’s case means those sales were illegal.</p>



<p>Judge Torres has now passed on the case to Magistrate Judge Sarah Netburn, who has <a href="https://zycrypto.com/judge-suggests-its-time-for-sec-to-settle-with-ripple-following-historic-xrp-win/">suggested that both parties come to a settlement</a> before a trial commencing on the remaining issues.  Given this, the market may have priced in fines and future uncertainties, which may well be why the price has not seen new highs.</p>



<p>Nevertheless, XRP still has many positive developments, and the long-term growth outlook for the XRP-Ledger (XRPL) remains solid. From the announcement of the Canadian Imperial Bank to use XRP for cross-border settlement and payment to <a href="https://zycrypto.com/xrp-set-for-price-explosion-amid-ripples-expectations-for-250-trillion-cross-border-payments/">Ripple’s projections for $250 trillion in cross-border payments</a> by 2027, the outlook overall is good.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/xrp-price-to-10-by-september-market-watchers-outline-bullish-trajectory-amid-ripples-big-win/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Vitalik Buterin Raises Alarm Over Worldcoin As Binance And Other Crypto Exchanges List Newly Launched Token</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/vitalik-buterin-raises-alarm-over-worldcoin-as-binance-and-other-crypto-exchanges-list-newly-launched-token/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/vitalik-buterin-raises-alarm-over-worldcoin-as-binance-and-other-crypto-exchanges-list-newly-launched-token/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Brenda Ngari]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 21:41:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Vitalik Buterin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=83088</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Vitalik-Buterin-Raises-Alarm-Over-Worldcoin-As-Binance-And-Other-Crypto-Exchanges-List-Newly-Launched-Token.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Vitalik Buterin Raises Alarm Over Worldcoin As Binance And Other Crypto Exchanges List Newly Launched Token" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Vitalik-Buterin-Raises-Alarm-Over-Worldcoin-As-Binance-And-Other-Crypto-Exchanges-List-Newly-Launched-Token.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Vitalik-Buterin-Raises-Alarm-Over-Worldcoin-As-Binance-And-Other-Crypto-Exchanges-List-Newly-Launched-Token-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Vitalik-Buterin-Raises-Alarm-Over-Worldcoin-As-Binance-And-Other-Crypto-Exchanges-List-Newly-Launched-Token-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Vitalik-Buterin-Raises-Alarm-Over-Worldcoin-As-Binance-And-Other-Crypto-Exchanges-List-Newly-Launched-Token-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>Ethereum co-founder Vitalik Buterin has expressed serious concern about Worldcoin, the highly anticipated and controversial project co-founded by OpenAI's Sam Altman, which launched its WLD token on Monday.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Vitalik-Buterin-Raises-Alarm-Over-Worldcoin-As-Binance-And-Other-Crypto-Exchanges-List-Newly-Launched-Token.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Vitalik Buterin Raises Alarm Over Worldcoin As Binance And Other Crypto Exchanges List Newly Launched Token" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Vitalik-Buterin-Raises-Alarm-Over-Worldcoin-As-Binance-And-Other-Crypto-Exchanges-List-Newly-Launched-Token.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Vitalik-Buterin-Raises-Alarm-Over-Worldcoin-As-Binance-And-Other-Crypto-Exchanges-List-Newly-Launched-Token-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Vitalik-Buterin-Raises-Alarm-Over-Worldcoin-As-Binance-And-Other-Crypto-Exchanges-List-Newly-Launched-Token-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Vitalik-Buterin-Raises-Alarm-Over-Worldcoin-As-Binance-And-Other-Crypto-Exchanges-List-Newly-Launched-Token-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>Ethereum co-founder Vitalik Buterin has expressed serious concern about Worldcoin, the highly anticipated and controversial project co-founded by OpenAI&#8217;s Sam Altman, which <a href="https://zycrypto.com/sam-altmans-crypto-project-worldcoin-targets-2-billion-users-with-worldwide-launch/">launched its WLD token on Monday</a>.</p>



<p>In a blog post, Buterin raised questions about its centralization, privacy, and security.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-the-risks-and-issues-with-worldcoin"><strong>The Risks And Issues With Worldcoin</strong></h2>



<p>The newly launched Wordcoin project is among the crypto sector’s most polarizing. Its goal is to help people prove their identity online with credentials verified in person by iris-scanning orbs. This step provides “proof-of-personhood” that is cryptographically secured and used as a World ID. According to the company, the tailor-made device that uses the scan to create a unique identifier doesn’t actually process or store any related data locally.</p>



<p>In an extensive July 25 <a href="https://vitalik.eth.limo/general/2023/07/24/biometric.html">blog post</a>, Ethereum creator Vitalik Buterin outlined this system’s potential problems.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">What do I think about biometric proof of personhood?<a href="https://t.co/yozo1buW24">https://t.co/yozo1buW24</a></p>&mdash; vitalik.eth (@VitalikButerin) <a href="https://twitter.com/VitalikButerin/status/1683404462314999814?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">July 24, 2023</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>For starters, Buterin identified four key issues with its biometric proof-of-personhood: privacy, accessibility, centralization within the Worldcoin Foundation, and security. Although he thinks some can be solved with technological improvements, “others seem to be fundamental limitations.”</p>



<p>Worldcoin Orbs will be distributed around the world to allow users to create their respective digital IDs. Buterin contended that there is no way to prove that the orb was “constructed correctly and does not have backdoors.” He theorized that “the Worldcoin Foundation still has the ability to insert a backdoor into the system, letting it create arbitrarily many fake human identities.”</p>



<p>His perspective was echoed by Bitcoin proponent Anita Posch, who <a href="https://twitter.com/AnitaPosch/status/1683404618070466560">indicated </a>that the centralized nature of the Worldcoin project and the sheer amount of data it handles could be a potential point of failure.</p>



<p>Buterin also argued that World IDs won’t be readily accessible to all interested participants as acquiring an “Orb” device can be challenging. In addition, he noted that the registry of iris may provide more details than planned. Case in point, if someone else scans your iris, they can verify it against the Worldcoin database to see if you have a World ID.&nbsp;</p>



<p>Buterin recognized there is no perfect solution for these concerns. He sees the potential for a blend of various approaches to the issue. Community accountability, audits, and checks are paramount to this process, Buterin elaborated. However:</p>



<p>“Not having any proof-of-personhood at all has its risks too: a world with no proof-of-personhood seems more likely to be a world dominated by centralized identity solutions, money, small closed communities, or some combination of all three.”</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>WLD Token Performance</strong></h2>



<p>WLD, issued on Ethereum and the popular layer-2 scaling solution Optimism soared double digits on Monday as <a href="https://www.binance.com/en/support/announcement/binance-will-list-worldcoin-wld-9bc08522433c44b1b0b9978d65c4f5e5">Binance</a>, <a href="https://twitter.com/Bybit_Official/status/1683477134147215364">Bybit</a>, OKX, <a href="https://twitter.com/HuobiGlobal/status/1683373651532591105">Huobi</a>, and <a href="https://twitter.com/gate_io/status/1683379305210949632">Gate </a>digital asset exchanges were all quick to reveal that they had kicked off trading for the Worldcoin token. </p>



<p>WLD is currently changing hands at $2.12 and is up by over 50% from its launch price, according to CoinGecko. The Worldcoin project has enrolled more than 2 million people around the world as of publication time.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/vitalik-buterin-raises-alarm-over-worldcoin-as-binance-and-other-crypto-exchanges-list-newly-launched-token/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
