<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>News Archives &#8902; ZyCrypto</title>
	<atom:link href="https://zycrypto.com/category/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://zycrypto.com/category/news/</link>
	<description>ZyCrypto Is A Cryptocurrency News Media, Focusing On Daily News, Expert Opinions, Analysis, Reviews, And So Much More.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 21:03:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/cropped-ZyCrypto-Site-Logo-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News Archives &#8902; ZyCrypto</title>
	<link>https://zycrypto.com/category/news/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>$1 ADA Price Beckons As Cardano&#8217;s Djed Stablecoin Is Finally Scheduled For Launch Next Week</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/1-ada-price-beckons-as-cardanos-djed-stablecoin-is-finally-scheduled-for-launch-next-week/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/1-ada-price-beckons-as-cardanos-djed-stablecoin-is-finally-scheduled-for-launch-next-week/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Newton Gitonga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 21:03:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADAUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=77484</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Cardano-Is-Buzzing-With-Super-Bullish-Activity-As-ADA-Adoption-Expands-To-New-Realms.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Cardano Is Buzzing With Super Bullish Activity As ADA Adoption Expands To New Realms" decoding="async" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Cardano-Is-Buzzing-With-Super-Bullish-Activity-As-ADA-Adoption-Expands-To-New-Realms.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Cardano-Is-Buzzing-With-Super-Bullish-Activity-As-ADA-Adoption-Expands-To-New-Realms-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Cardano-Is-Buzzing-With-Super-Bullish-Activity-As-ADA-Adoption-Expands-To-New-Realms-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Cardano-Is-Buzzing-With-Super-Bullish-Activity-As-ADA-Adoption-Expands-To-New-Realms-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>The much-anticipated Djed stablecoin is scheduled for launch next week, fostering expansion and novel applications in the rapidly developing decentralized finance (DeFi) sector of the Cardano ecosystem.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Cardano-Is-Buzzing-With-Super-Bullish-Activity-As-ADA-Adoption-Expands-To-New-Realms.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Cardano Is Buzzing With Super Bullish Activity As ADA Adoption Expands To New Realms" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Cardano-Is-Buzzing-With-Super-Bullish-Activity-As-ADA-Adoption-Expands-To-New-Realms.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Cardano-Is-Buzzing-With-Super-Bullish-Activity-As-ADA-Adoption-Expands-To-New-Realms-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Cardano-Is-Buzzing-With-Super-Bullish-Activity-As-ADA-Adoption-Expands-To-New-Realms-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Cardano-Is-Buzzing-With-Super-Bullish-Activity-As-ADA-Adoption-Expands-To-New-Realms-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>The much-anticipated Djed stablecoin is scheduled for launch <a href="https://zycrypto.com/cardano-centered-stablecoin-djed-set-to-debut-in-january-ada-poised-for-rapid-adoption/">next week</a>, fostering expansion and novel applications in the rapidly developing decentralized finance (DeFi) sector of the Cardano ecosystem.</p>



<p><em>“We are pleased to share another update about Djed’s progress and to inform you that the launch is scheduled for next week,”</em> COTI, a platform optimized for creating price-stable coins and the soon-to-be official issuer of Djed, announced Tuesday.</p>



<p>Without hinting at a specific date for the launch, the COTI team, however, noted that there are technological developments they were currently working on. Key among them was the so-called “chain indexing process”, which they said would take 14 days to complete before Djed launches. Chain index syncing refers to a process aimed at ensuring that all the nodes in a blockchain network are updated on issues such as transactions and block to keep the network healthy and secure. According to the team, this is currently the only technical bottleneck holding the launch.</p>



<p>The team also noted that they were developing a snapshot feature and user interface (UI) to be integrated into DJED. This will facilitate the staking of ADA and generate additional rewards for $SHEN holders, allowing $SHEN holders to monitor extra rewards. Additionally, they had added the “refund button”, a feature that allows users to cancel their orders as long as they haven’t been processed.</p>



<p>Since the Djed Public Testnet went live on May 4, 2022, the team has made significant progress with most of the work in configuration management, UI integration and final design out of the way. Moreover, over 40 platforms, including exchanges such as Wingriders and Bitrue have already expressed the intention to support Djed and Shen through listing as well as other partnerships.</p>



<p>When launched, Djed will become the first decentralized and overcollateralized stablecoin built on Cardano. Djed will be backed by ADA and use Shen as a reserve coin. Shen will ensure Djed’s stability by guaranteeing the peg and collateralization rate of the stablecoin.</p>



<p>Meanwhile, while the news is yet to impact the price of Cardano’s native token, ADA, the crypto community is stoked at the <a href="https://zycrypto.com/cardano-unveils-djed-an-innovative-stablecoin-for-the-fast-growing-ecosystem-issued-by-coti/">vast improvements</a> and capabilities that the stablecoin will bring to the ecosystem.</p>



<p>At press time, ADA was trading at $0.36, down about 3.26% in the past 24 hours. Despite the asset’s price being down 88.33%- which is a far cry from its all-time high of $3.10, many hope that the launch of Djed will give the price the much-needed boost towards $1.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/1-ada-price-beckons-as-cardanos-djed-stablecoin-is-finally-scheduled-for-launch-next-week/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Embattled Signature Bank Caps SWIFT Access For Binance, Raising Concerns</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/embattled-signature-bank-caps-swift-access-for-binance-raising-concerns/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/embattled-signature-bank-caps-swift-access-for-binance-raising-concerns/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Collins K.O]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 20:45:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=77482</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Promoting-Bitcoin-Could-Damage-The-Reputation-Of-Banks-ECB-Warns.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Promoting Bitcoin Could Damage The Reputation Of Banks, ECB Warns" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Promoting-Bitcoin-Could-Damage-The-Reputation-Of-Banks-ECB-Warns.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Promoting-Bitcoin-Could-Damage-The-Reputation-Of-Banks-ECB-Warns-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Promoting-Bitcoin-Could-Damage-The-Reputation-Of-Banks-ECB-Warns-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Promoting-Bitcoin-Could-Damage-The-Reputation-Of-Banks-ECB-Warns-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>A recent update by Binance has revealed that Signature Bank, a major SWIFT gateway service provider, will partially terminate access to Binance customers starting in February. The update sent by Binance, which a customer tweeted, read thus:  “The banking partner that serves your account has advised that they are no longer able to process SWIFT [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Promoting-Bitcoin-Could-Damage-The-Reputation-Of-Banks-ECB-Warns.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Promoting Bitcoin Could Damage The Reputation Of Banks, ECB Warns" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Promoting-Bitcoin-Could-Damage-The-Reputation-Of-Banks-ECB-Warns.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Promoting-Bitcoin-Could-Damage-The-Reputation-Of-Banks-ECB-Warns-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Promoting-Bitcoin-Could-Damage-The-Reputation-Of-Banks-ECB-Warns-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Promoting-Bitcoin-Could-Damage-The-Reputation-Of-Banks-ECB-Warns-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>A recent update by Binance has revealed that Signature Bank, a major SWIFT gateway service provider, will partially terminate access to Binance customers starting in February.</p>



<p>The update sent by Binance, which a customer tweeted, read thus: </p>



<p><em>“The banking partner that serves your account has advised that they are no longer able to process SWIFT fiat (USD) transactions for individuals of less than 100,000 USD as of 1st of February 2023.”</em></p>



<p>Hours after the announcement, concerns were raised about the possibility of other US banks limiting exposure to cryptocurrencies by regulating their SWIFT gateway. However, a section of the crypto community expressed optimism about the unlikelihood of a widespread SWIFT ban, adding that this appears to be a lone case of limiting crypto exposure by the New York-based bank, which recently came under scrutiny for its in-house blockchain feature, Signet.</p>



<p>Signature Bank disclosed in December its plans to cut back exposure to crypto deposits after the impact of the fall of FTX tanked its share price 67% lower. In 2018, the bank launched Signet, a blockchain-based multipurpose instant payment platform for commercial users. Going toe-to-toe with global banking giants like JP Morgan, the bank boasted a platform that reduced traditional SWIFT delays from 3 days to 30 seconds and a thorough FinCEN-compliant KYC measure for preventing bad actors. It had onboarded the crème de la crème of crypto in a short time, sparking surprise amongst financial analysts familiar with the watertight regulatory terrain of the US.</p>



<p>Following the fallout of FTX, alleged reports now reveal a number of other crypto firms—like Binance, Nexo, Huobi, and Genesis Trading—under investigation that received Signature’s approval to use Signet. This leaves a lot to be answered on Signature’s due diligence.</p>



<p>SWIFT, which stands for Society for Worldwide Interbank Transactions, is a unified gateway for the exchange of information and transactions by financial institutions worldwide. Within the crypto sector, SWIFT is crucial for the institutional adoption of crypto as it is the most widely used gateway for attracting inflows from new users into crypto. </p>



<p>A shutdown of SWIFT will mean significant paralysis for crypto, which still relies on the inflow of fiat to grow its ecosystem. The war in Russia witnessed the first time SWIFT access was terminated, prompting the rise of crypto through illegal platforms like Bitzlato to circumvent restrictions.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/embattled-signature-bank-caps-swift-access-for-binance-raising-concerns/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>New York’s Financial Regulator Takes Aim At Firms Commingling Funds After New FTX Regulations</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/new-yorks-financial-regulator-takes-aim-at-firms-commingling-funds-after-new-ftx-regulations/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/new-yorks-financial-regulator-takes-aim-at-firms-commingling-funds-after-new-ftx-regulations/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aliyu Pokima]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 16:53:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=77478</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/New-Yorks-Financial-Regulator-Takes-Aim-At-Firms-Commingling-Funds-After-New-FTX-Regulations.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="New York’s Financial Regulator Takes Aim At Firms Commingling Funds After New FTX Regulations" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/New-Yorks-Financial-Regulator-Takes-Aim-At-Firms-Commingling-Funds-After-New-FTX-Regulations.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/New-Yorks-Financial-Regulator-Takes-Aim-At-Firms-Commingling-Funds-After-New-FTX-Regulations-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/New-Yorks-Financial-Regulator-Takes-Aim-At-Firms-Commingling-Funds-After-New-FTX-Regulations-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/New-Yorks-Financial-Regulator-Takes-Aim-At-Firms-Commingling-Funds-After-New-FTX-Regulations-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>As more revelations trickle in from the FTX saga, authorities around the world are ramping up regulations to avoid a repeat of the infamous incident.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/New-Yorks-Financial-Regulator-Takes-Aim-At-Firms-Commingling-Funds-After-New-FTX-Regulations.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="New York’s Financial Regulator Takes Aim At Firms Commingling Funds After New FTX Regulations" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/New-Yorks-Financial-Regulator-Takes-Aim-At-Firms-Commingling-Funds-After-New-FTX-Regulations.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/New-Yorks-Financial-Regulator-Takes-Aim-At-Firms-Commingling-Funds-After-New-FTX-Regulations-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/New-Yorks-Financial-Regulator-Takes-Aim-At-Firms-Commingling-Funds-After-New-FTX-Regulations-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/New-Yorks-Financial-Regulator-Takes-Aim-At-Firms-Commingling-Funds-After-New-FTX-Regulations-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<ul>
<li>The New York Department of Financial Services has released a new guideline to regulate how firms handle customer assets.&nbsp;</li>



<li>The department takes the bull by the horn as it reacts to new revelations in the demystification of FTX.&nbsp;</li>



<li>Digital asset analysts laud the move to add more data regulations to protect user assets though some feel it’s “over-controlling.”</li>
</ul>



<p>As more revelations trickle in from the FTX saga, authorities around the world are ramping up regulations to avoid a repeat of the infamous incident.</p>



<p>The New York Department of Financial Services (NYDFS) has issued a new guideline on how digital asset firms are to handle user assets. In a letter to the industry, the department stated that user assets should be separated from each other to avoid commingling with the firm’s assets.</p>



<p>The statement also addressed how firms should apply customer funds and make proper disclosures to clients when applying user funds in line with best practices.</p>



<p>“<em>As stewards of others’ assets, virtual currency entities that act as custodians [&#8230;] must have robust processes in place, akin to traditional financial service providers”, </em>per the statement.</p>



<p>The robust statement by the NYDFS warns custodians to keep separate asset records both on-chain and in the firm&#8217;s internal records. To keep users informed on the status of their assets, custodians are now required to furnish customers with written notices that show the arrangements, application of funds, and how those funds have been separated from others, as well as the interest accrued, if any.</p>



<p>Furthermore, the regulation now makes user funds held by custodians for only safekeeping “<em>without creating a debtor-creditor relationship with the customer” </em>when funds are transferred.</p>



<p>The regulations apply to cryptocurrency-related firms that hold a BitLicense, a license issued by New York authorities to regulate the activities of virtual asset companies.</p>



<h2 id="h-mixed-reactions-follow-the-regulation"><strong>Mixed reactions follow the regulation</strong></h2>



<p>While many have lauded and pushed digital asset regulations in <a href="https://zycrypto.com/french-central-bank-governor-calls-for-stricter-crypto-regulations-ahead-of-mica-vote/">recent</a> months, several quarters have maintained scepticism over previous regulatory decisions. The NYDFS decision to roll out BitLicense in 2015 is a classic example leading to Kraken’s pull out of the state. </p>



<p>Last year, the CEO of Kraken, Jesse Powell, continued to criticize BitLicenses as a burden to digital asset firms.</p>



<p><em>“After all this time, I mean, if we just looked back and did a study of the economic damage done by the BitLicense, I&#8217;m sure it would be tremendous in the billions of dollars.”&nbsp;</em></p>



<p>However, those in support of the regulations and BitLicenses are more and point to the protection of user assets even if it slows the pace of development in the sector.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/new-yorks-financial-regulator-takes-aim-at-firms-commingling-funds-after-new-ftx-regulations/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>“SEC’s Shallow Approach Is Limiting BTC” Grayscale CEO Takes A Swipe At US Regulators</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/secs-shallow-approach-is-limiting-btc-grayscale-ceo-takes-a-swipe-at-us-regulators/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/secs-shallow-approach-is-limiting-btc-grayscale-ceo-takes-a-swipe-at-us-regulators/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aliyu Pokima]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 16:46:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XBTUSD]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=77475</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/SECs-Shallow-Approach-Is-Limiting-BTC-Grayscale-CEO-Takes-A-Swipe-At-US-Regulators.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="“SEC’s Shallow Approach Is Limiting BTC” Grayscale CEO Takes A Swipe At US Regulators" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/SECs-Shallow-Approach-Is-Limiting-BTC-Grayscale-CEO-Takes-A-Swipe-At-US-Regulators.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/SECs-Shallow-Approach-Is-Limiting-BTC-Grayscale-CEO-Takes-A-Swipe-At-US-Regulators-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/SECs-Shallow-Approach-Is-Limiting-BTC-Grayscale-CEO-Takes-A-Swipe-At-US-Regulators-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/SECs-Shallow-Approach-Is-Limiting-BTC-Grayscale-CEO-Takes-A-Swipe-At-US-Regulators-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>Grayscale Investments CEO Michael Sonnenshein joins the bandwagon of industry players to call out the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) over its regulatory practices in the sector.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/SECs-Shallow-Approach-Is-Limiting-BTC-Grayscale-CEO-Takes-A-Swipe-At-US-Regulators.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="“SEC’s Shallow Approach Is Limiting BTC” Grayscale CEO Takes A Swipe At US Regulators" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/SECs-Shallow-Approach-Is-Limiting-BTC-Grayscale-CEO-Takes-A-Swipe-At-US-Regulators.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/SECs-Shallow-Approach-Is-Limiting-BTC-Grayscale-CEO-Takes-A-Swipe-At-US-Regulators-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/SECs-Shallow-Approach-Is-Limiting-BTC-Grayscale-CEO-Takes-A-Swipe-At-US-Regulators-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/SECs-Shallow-Approach-Is-Limiting-BTC-Grayscale-CEO-Takes-A-Swipe-At-US-Regulators-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<ul>
<li>Michael Sonnenshein has criticized the SEC’s regulatory approach, describing it as shallow and one-sided.</li>



<li>He calls for the SEC to work round the clock to remove bad actors from the industry but should not hinder the growth of digital assets.&nbsp;</li>



<li>Debate on the thin line between proper and excessive burdensome regulation considering the nature of digital assets, makes rounds in the industry.</li>
</ul>



<p>Grayscale Investments CEO Michael Sonnenshein joins the bandwagon of industry players to call out the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) over its regulatory practices in the sector.</p>



<p>In his recent <a href="https://www.wsj.com/amp/articles/ftx-sbf-crypto-regulation-sec-11674493234?mod=opinion_major_pos16&amp;linkId=198344712">letter</a> published in the Wall Street Journal, Sonnenshein stated that the SEC’s approach to digital asset firms had stalled the growth of Bitcoin (BTC) in the country. He concurs with the widespread allegations that the SEC is “<em>late to the game” </em>with its regulations leading to the collapse of FTX.</p>



<p>“<em>Late’ doesn’t capture what transpired here. The problem is the Securities and Exchange Commission’s one-dimensional approach to regulation by enforcement,” </em>he added.</p>



<p>He further expressed the need for the SEC to rid the sector of bad actors as they continue to cripple the market. Sonnenshein wrote that the actions of the SEC have also limited the sector forcing American investors to pitch their tents offshore.</p>



<p>“<em>We are seeing the consequence of SEC priorities play out in real-time at the expense of US investors,”</em> Sommenshein said.</p>



<p>According to him, the SEC should be quick to block loopholes in the sector without making tight regulations for digital asset firms to limit the growth of BTC.</p>



<p>Grayscale is currently suing the SEC for “<em>arbitrarily denying</em>” the conversion of its Grayscale’s BTC trust (GBTC) to a spot ETF. The SEC has issued a reply to the company citing the proposal’s lack of disclosure in ways to protect user funds and fraud manipulations as reasons for denying the proposal.</p>



<h2 id="h-how-strict-should-regulators-get"><strong>How strict should regulators get?</strong></h2>



<p>Several industry players believe that the nature of digital assets requires special regulations different from traditional ones. The SEC v Ripple case <a href="https://zycrypto.com/sec-commissioner-makes-controversial-case-for-eth-xrp-faults-howeys-test/">encapsulates</a> this debate in applying the Howey Test to determine if digital assets classify as securities. </p>



<p>While tougher regulations will stifle growth in several areas of the industry, many users would prefer it to be in place because of the growing rates of fraud. The recent implosion of FTX, which resulted in investor losses hitting billions, has now sparked renewed enthusiasm in regulators.</p>



<p>As authorities ramp up regulations and push for more audits to the pleasure of users, many fear that the thin line between effective and harsh regulations will be crossed, leading to limitations not needed in the industry. </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/secs-shallow-approach-is-limiting-btc-grayscale-ceo-takes-a-swipe-at-us-regulators/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>$0.001 SHIB Price Beckons As Shiba Inu Developer Hints At Shibarium Beta Launch In February</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/0-001-shib-price-beckons-as-shiba-inu-developer-hints-at-shibarium-beta-launch-in-february/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/0-001-shib-price-beckons-as-shiba-inu-developer-hints-at-shibarium-beta-launch-in-february/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Newton Gitonga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 19:13:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIBA INU]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIBUSD]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=77465</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Shiba-Inus-Shibarium-Renews-Bullish-Momentum-For-0.001-SHIB-As-Massive-Token-Burn-Expected.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Shiba Inu&#039;s Shibarium Renews Bullish Momentum For &#039;$0.001 SHIB&#039; As Massive Token Burn Expected" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Shiba-Inus-Shibarium-Renews-Bullish-Momentum-For-0.001-SHIB-As-Massive-Token-Burn-Expected.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Shiba-Inus-Shibarium-Renews-Bullish-Momentum-For-0.001-SHIB-As-Massive-Token-Burn-Expected-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Shiba-Inus-Shibarium-Renews-Bullish-Momentum-For-0.001-SHIB-As-Massive-Token-Burn-Expected-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Shiba-Inus-Shibarium-Renews-Bullish-Momentum-For-0.001-SHIB-As-Massive-Token-Burn-Expected-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>The eagerly awaited Shibarium layer-2 scaling solution for Shiba Inu (SHIB) is nearing its beta launch, with the lead developer...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Shiba-Inus-Shibarium-Renews-Bullish-Momentum-For-0.001-SHIB-As-Massive-Token-Burn-Expected.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Shiba Inu&#039;s Shibarium Renews Bullish Momentum For &#039;$0.001 SHIB&#039; As Massive Token Burn Expected" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Shiba-Inus-Shibarium-Renews-Bullish-Momentum-For-0.001-SHIB-As-Massive-Token-Burn-Expected.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Shiba-Inus-Shibarium-Renews-Bullish-Momentum-For-0.001-SHIB-As-Massive-Token-Burn-Expected-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Shiba-Inus-Shibarium-Renews-Bullish-Momentum-For-0.001-SHIB-As-Massive-Token-Burn-Expected-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Shiba-Inus-Shibarium-Renews-Bullish-Momentum-For-0.001-SHIB-As-Massive-Token-Burn-Expected-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>The eagerly awaited Shibarium layer-2 scaling solution for Shiba Inu (SHIB) is nearing its beta launch, with the lead developer Shytoshi Kusama hinting in his Twitter bio that Shibarium may come as soon as February or earlier.</p>



<p>On Friday, Kusama inadvertently exposed a likely date for the beta launch, veiled in a word puzzle, through his Twitter profile, which reads;</p>



<p><em>“Tending the Pine Tree of Life. Quickly learning to play the flute before putting Shibarium in a heart-shaped box with a bow.”</em></p>



<p>Following the profile update, the<a href="https://zycrypto.com/explosive-moves-in-the-offing-for-shiba-inu-bonk-and-dogecoin-as-trading-volume-tops-25-billion/"> Shiba Inu (SHIB)</a> community has been trying to decode the message, with some concluding that Shibarium will be released on Valentine’s Day, February 14.</p>



<p><em>“Hints from the core developer suggest a Beta release on February 14th, based on tweets from Shytoshi Kusama and the SHIB HOLDER,”</em> one tweep wrote, echoing the thoughts of thousands of Shiba Inu adherents.</p>



<p>Late last week, Kusama issued another hint when he mysteriously tweeted;</p>



<p>&#8220;<em>During fall, the tree may have only a few leaves, but then spring appears…Luckily, Shibarium, in this context, is a Pine Tree. Still, it needs water, sunlight and proper soil. But pines survive and thrive during the harshest winters. (I also hear the needle tea is good for you.)</em>&#8220;</p>



<p>On Saturday, Kusama launched an official Telegram Group for Shibarium, which has over 12,000 members at the time of writing. He then stated that the channel would not communicate until the Layer-2 network is released, thus furthering speculation that it will be launched soon.</p>



<p>The latest developments have piqued the interest of the crypto community, with many speculating about the project’s potential and impact on the industry. Shibarium’s launch is <a href="https://zycrypto.com/shiba-inus-shibarium-renews-bullish-momentum-for-0-001-shib-as-massive-token-burn-expected/">expected</a> to scale performance for the Shiba Inu ecosystem and signals a shift in the industry as more projects are now looking to layer-2 solutions to boost scalability, privacy, and security. </p>



<p>Meanwhile, the Shib army has been eagerly awaiting the launch, with some speculating that it will cause the prices of SHIB and BONE to increase, potentially sending SHIB past $0.001.</p>



<p>In the last 48 hours, SHIB has jumped by over 5% and in the last week by a remarkable 21%, with the current price at $0.00001209. SHIB is trading at its highest level since November 2022, with a 43% increase from the start of the year.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/0-001-shib-price-beckons-as-shiba-inu-developer-hints-at-shibarium-beta-launch-in-february/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>China Unveils Ripple&#8217;s Competitor for Stablecoins and CBDC Payments</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/china-unveils-ripples-competitor-for-stablecoins-and-cbdc-payments-in-davos/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/china-unveils-ripples-competitor-for-stablecoins-and-cbdc-payments-in-davos/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jared Kirui]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 15:23:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=77459</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/XRP-Lawsuit-Attorney-Says-Ripples-Defense-Will-Receive-Massive-Boost-If-These-Notes-Are-Produced.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="XRP Lawsuit: Attorney Says Ripple’s Defense Will Receive Massive Boost If These Notes Are Produced" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/XRP-Lawsuit-Attorney-Says-Ripples-Defense-Will-Receive-Massive-Boost-If-These-Notes-Are-Produced.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/XRP-Lawsuit-Attorney-Says-Ripples-Defense-Will-Receive-Massive-Boost-If-These-Notes-Are-Produced-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/XRP-Lawsuit-Attorney-Says-Ripples-Defense-Will-Receive-Massive-Boost-If-These-Notes-Are-Produced-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/XRP-Lawsuit-Attorney-Says-Ripples-Defense-Will-Receive-Massive-Boost-If-These-Notes-Are-Produced-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>A Chinese firm is developing a new payment system interoperable with stablecoins and CBDCs -  that acts as a link for central banks to transfer and swap regulated digital currencies - recently unveiled at the World Economic Forum in Davos, Switzerland.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/XRP-Lawsuit-Attorney-Says-Ripples-Defense-Will-Receive-Massive-Boost-If-These-Notes-Are-Produced.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="XRP Lawsuit: Attorney Says Ripple’s Defense Will Receive Massive Boost If These Notes Are Produced" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/XRP-Lawsuit-Attorney-Says-Ripples-Defense-Will-Receive-Massive-Boost-If-These-Notes-Are-Produced.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/XRP-Lawsuit-Attorney-Says-Ripples-Defense-Will-Receive-Massive-Boost-If-These-Notes-Are-Produced-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/XRP-Lawsuit-Attorney-Says-Ripples-Defense-Will-Receive-Massive-Boost-If-These-Notes-Are-Produced-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/XRP-Lawsuit-Attorney-Says-Ripples-Defense-Will-Receive-Massive-Boost-If-These-Notes-Are-Produced-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<ul>
<li>The developers of UDPN describe it as equivalent to SWIFT.</li>



<li>Some of the major banks expected to participate in the pilot phase include HSBC, Standard Chartered, and Deutsche Bank.</li>
</ul>



<p>A Chinese firm is developing a new payment system interoperable with stablecoins and CBDCs &#8211;  that acts as a link for central banks to transfer and swap regulated digital currencies &#8211; recently unveiled at the World Economic Forum in Davos, Switzerland.</p>



<p>Dubbed the Universal Digital Payments Network (UDPN) and developed by Red Date Technology, the new system would reportedly work with the private sector, unlike the rival Ripple network, which mostly serves central banks. According to the announcement, several major banks, including HSBC, Deutsche Bank, and Standard Chartered, have been selected to participate in the pilot phase.</p>



<p>UDPN, in particular, noted that it would not work with decentralized public cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin, perhaps underscoring its efforts to comply with the ongoing Chinese ban on cryptocurrencies. Beijing is keen to prevent any form of capital outflow in the form of stablecoins or digital assets.</p>



<h2 id="h-the-commercialization-of-udpn-is-scheduled-for-mid-2023"><strong>The Commercialization of UDPN is Scheduled for Mid-2023</strong></h2>



<p>Per the project’s whitepaper, UDPN is planned to debut with two separate stablecoins, with the pilot commercialization set for mid-year. In the near term, the project team expects the network to support most of the global CBDCs and regulated fiat-based stablecoins. The system would also be extended to include the interoperability of the traditional messaging networks.</p>



<p>UDPN has a common messaging standard in multiple digital currency systems, which is essential in enhancing interoperability in CBDC and stablecoins. The system will also accelerate access to a fully decentralized economy by commercial banks with a system managed by an alliance of financial institutions and fintech firms.</p>



<p>Technically, UDPN would have four main nodes – the validator nodes and the transactions nodes – all operated on-chain. The validator nodes would have a hyperledger and governance systems. The next set of nodes, which would operate off-chain, is the business and the transaction nodes. Compared to the SWIFT network, which has led to an increase in cross-border and inter-bank transactions, UDPN is touted by its developers as an important link in the future of digital currencies.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/china-unveils-ripples-competitor-for-stablecoins-and-cbdc-payments-in-davos/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum Releases ‘Shadow Fork’ For The Much-Anticipated Shanghai Upgrade</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/ethereum-releases-shadow-fork-for-the-much-anticipated-shanghai-upgrade/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/ethereum-releases-shadow-fork-for-the-much-anticipated-shanghai-upgrade/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jared Kirui]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 21:16:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=77438</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Ethereums-Next-Big-Upgrade-Slated-For-2023-—-Heres-why-Its-Super-Bullish-For-ETH.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Ethereum’s Next Big Upgrade Slated For 2023 — Here’s why It’s Super Bullish For ETH" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Ethereums-Next-Big-Upgrade-Slated-For-2023-—-Heres-why-Its-Super-Bullish-For-ETH.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Ethereums-Next-Big-Upgrade-Slated-For-2023-—-Heres-why-Its-Super-Bullish-For-ETH-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Ethereums-Next-Big-Upgrade-Slated-For-2023-—-Heres-why-Its-Super-Bullish-For-ETH-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Ethereums-Next-Big-Upgrade-Slated-For-2023-—-Heres-why-Its-Super-Bullish-For-ETH-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>Blockchain developers successfully launched a ‘shadow fork’ for the upcoming Shanghai upgrade in the Ethereum blockchain.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Ethereums-Next-Big-Upgrade-Slated-For-2023-—-Heres-why-Its-Super-Bullish-For-ETH.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Ethereum’s Next Big Upgrade Slated For 2023 — Here’s why It’s Super Bullish For ETH" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Ethereums-Next-Big-Upgrade-Slated-For-2023-—-Heres-why-Its-Super-Bullish-For-ETH.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Ethereums-Next-Big-Upgrade-Slated-For-2023-—-Heres-why-Its-Super-Bullish-For-ETH-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Ethereums-Next-Big-Upgrade-Slated-For-2023-—-Heres-why-Its-Super-Bullish-For-ETH-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Ethereums-Next-Big-Upgrade-Slated-For-2023-—-Heres-why-Its-Super-Bullish-For-ETH-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<ul>
<li>The fork is a test environment for the upcoming Shanghai upgrade.</li>



<li>Shanghai is expected to unlock the withdrawals of the staked ETH in the Beacon chain.</li>
</ul>



<p>Blockchain developers successfully launched a ‘shadow fork’ for the upcoming <a href="https://zycrypto.com/ethereums-next-big-upgrade-slated-for-2023-heres-why-its-super-bullish-for-eth/">Shanghai upgrade</a> in the Ethereum blockchain. The shadow fork – a test model for the actual mainnet that lets developers check if the code for the proposed upgrade functions well on a real blockchain – happened Monday at 5:30 am ET.</p>



<p>Shanghai upgrade is expected to take place by March, and among the proposed amendments is to allow for the withdrawals of the staked coins, which happened during the proof of stake transition. Ethereum developers have also noted that more shadow forks will be released in the coming week in the run-up to the network upgrade.</p>



<p>Amidst the upgrade, technical problems were reported for some of the Ethereum’s nodes using Geth clients, according to developer Marius Van Der Wijden, who said that the network was working to have the clients synchronized with the rest of the network.</p>



<h2 id="h-the-next-update-a-testnet-is-expected-before-the-end-of-february"><strong>The Next Update, a Testnet, Is Expected Before the End of February</strong></h2>



<p>Also in the offing is a public testnet proposed by the developers to take place before the end of February. The test network is set to bring on board the staking firms to test the Shanghai upgrade. Ahead of the update, the blockchain developers have also noted that additional forks would copy the network&#8217;s data to the testing environment or the shadow fork.</p>



<p>The Ethereum community has been concerned about how soon they can access their staked assets. There have been delays in the past for such forks in Ethereum, including the most recent PoS merge. On-chain data shows that the number of staked Ether in the validator contract to be unstaked is 16,167,572.</p>



<p>In November, the team behind the Shanghai update introduced the Shandong testnet but later replaced it with an enhanced alternative. Ahead of last year&#8217;s big change to the Ethereum network, the Merge, the blockchain underwent several test forks before the final deployment.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/ethereum-releases-shadow-fork-for-the-much-anticipated-shanghai-upgrade/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Vitalik Buterin Uncovers ‘Missing Link’ For Creating Transaction Privacy on Ethereum</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/vitalik-buterin-uncovers-missing-link-for-creating-transaction-privacy-on-ethereum/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/vitalik-buterin-uncovers-missing-link-for-creating-transaction-privacy-on-ethereum/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Collins K.O]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 20:50:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Vitalik Buterin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=77435</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Vitalik-Buterin-Uncovers-‘Missing-Link-For-Creating-Transaction-Privacy-on-Ethereum.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Vitalik Buterin Uncovers ‘Missing Link’ For Creating Transaction Privacy on Ethereum" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Vitalik-Buterin-Uncovers-‘Missing-Link-For-Creating-Transaction-Privacy-on-Ethereum.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Vitalik-Buterin-Uncovers-‘Missing-Link-For-Creating-Transaction-Privacy-on-Ethereum-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Vitalik-Buterin-Uncovers-‘Missing-Link-For-Creating-Transaction-Privacy-on-Ethereum-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Vitalik-Buterin-Uncovers-‘Missing-Link-For-Creating-Transaction-Privacy-on-Ethereum-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>Vitalik Buterin, the co-founder of Ethereum, recently released a guideline for bringing privacy to transactions on the Ethereum network.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Vitalik-Buterin-Uncovers-‘Missing-Link-For-Creating-Transaction-Privacy-on-Ethereum.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Vitalik Buterin Uncovers ‘Missing Link’ For Creating Transaction Privacy on Ethereum" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Vitalik-Buterin-Uncovers-‘Missing-Link-For-Creating-Transaction-Privacy-on-Ethereum.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Vitalik-Buterin-Uncovers-‘Missing-Link-For-Creating-Transaction-Privacy-on-Ethereum-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Vitalik-Buterin-Uncovers-‘Missing-Link-For-Creating-Transaction-Privacy-on-Ethereum-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Vitalik-Buterin-Uncovers-‘Missing-Link-For-Creating-Transaction-Privacy-on-Ethereum-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>Vitalik Buterin, the co-founder of Ethereum, recently released a <a href="https://vitalik.ca/general/2023/01/20/stealth.html">guideline</a> for bringing privacy to transactions on the Ethereum network.</p>



<p>In a comprehensive blog post tweeted on Friday, the 23-year-old billionaire broke down the concept of stealth addresses, adding that Ethereum is working to develop the concept as a solution to the &#8216;last remaining challenge&#8217; for the blockchain.</p>



<p>Given the transparent nature of public blockchains, all transactions are easily viewable and traceable by default. &#8220;Anything that goes onto a public blockchain is public….and as such &#8220;, using the entire suite of <a href="https://zycrypto.com/report-shows-growth-in-multiple-ethereum-layer-2-networks-polygon-leads-the-pack/">Ethereum</a> involves making a significant portion of your life public for anyone to see and analyze.&#8221;</p>



<h2 id="h-stealth-address-system-explained"><strong>Stealth Address System Explained</strong></h2>



<p>Vitalik describes a stealth address as an address generated by either party in a transaction, with the power of control in the hands of only one party. Using a hypothetical Bob and Alice, a stealth address will depend on the creation of a secret key comprising elements of both party addresses to veil transactions from public notice.</p>



<p>The central idea, according to Vitalik, is to have the transaction registered on the blockchain, but the knowledge of the receiver is totally unknown through a method akin to OTPs that generate a unique validation code for a user with every transaction.</p>



<p>The stealth address system will serve as an impressive upgrade from the methods used by the asset-mixing platform Tornado Cash, which uses a mixing smart contract to mash multiple transactions together, making tracing difficult.</p>



<p>To solve the problem of settling Transaction fees which automatically makes the identity and destination of transactions public, Vitalik proposes either cost-intensive Zero Knowledge Proofs, also known as ZK-Snarks or the employment of &#8220;specialized transaction aggregators.&#8221;</p>



<h2 id="h-privacy-and-regulations"><strong>Privacy and Regulations</strong></h2>



<p>Brilliant as it seems, experience has shown that the concept of masking identities and hiding recipients may pose a challenge to regulatory compliance. Last year, key programmers for Tornado Cash became targets of government bodies over the mechanism of the platform, which is believed to encourage the escape of bad actors.</p>



<p>Ethereum, since migrating over to Proof-of-stake, many analysts have expressed concern about the network&#8217;s potential to tilt towards centralization and become susceptible to control.</p>



<p>It remains to be seen how Vitalik will tackle these challenges while promoting blockchain privacy. ETH has since gained over $100 in the last three days and is currently trading at $1638. The top-tier token netted 0.76% worth of intraday gains and is still on a cruise following the breath of fresh air sweeping across the crypto market.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/vitalik-buterin-uncovers-missing-link-for-creating-transaction-privacy-on-ethereum/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>XRP Primed For Bullish Eruption As Ripple&#8217;s Garlinghouse Believes &#8216;Truth Will Come To Light&#8217; In SEC Case</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/xrp-primed-for-bullish-eruption-as-ripples-garlinghouse-believes-truth-will-come-to-light-in-sec-case/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/xrp-primed-for-bullish-eruption-as-ripples-garlinghouse-believes-truth-will-come-to-light-in-sec-case/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Olivia Brooke]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 15:09:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Brad Garlinghouse]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=77429</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XRP-Primed-For-Bullish-Eruption-As-Ripples-Garlinghouse-Believes-Truth-Will-Come-To-Light-In-SEC-Case.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="XRP Primed For Bullish Eruption As Ripple&#039;s Garlinghouse Believes &#039;Truth Will Come To Light&#039; In SEC Case" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XRP-Primed-For-Bullish-Eruption-As-Ripples-Garlinghouse-Believes-Truth-Will-Come-To-Light-In-SEC-Case.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XRP-Primed-For-Bullish-Eruption-As-Ripples-Garlinghouse-Believes-Truth-Will-Come-To-Light-In-SEC-Case-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XRP-Primed-For-Bullish-Eruption-As-Ripples-Garlinghouse-Believes-Truth-Will-Come-To-Light-In-SEC-Case-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XRP-Primed-For-Bullish-Eruption-As-Ripples-Garlinghouse-Believes-Truth-Will-Come-To-Light-In-SEC-Case-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>Ripple CEO Brad Garlinghouse expresses optimism about the case closing in its favour. ]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XRP-Primed-For-Bullish-Eruption-As-Ripples-Garlinghouse-Believes-Truth-Will-Come-To-Light-In-SEC-Case.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="XRP Primed For Bullish Eruption As Ripple&#039;s Garlinghouse Believes &#039;Truth Will Come To Light&#039; In SEC Case" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XRP-Primed-For-Bullish-Eruption-As-Ripples-Garlinghouse-Believes-Truth-Will-Come-To-Light-In-SEC-Case.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XRP-Primed-For-Bullish-Eruption-As-Ripples-Garlinghouse-Believes-Truth-Will-Come-To-Light-In-SEC-Case-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XRP-Primed-For-Bullish-Eruption-As-Ripples-Garlinghouse-Believes-Truth-Will-Come-To-Light-In-SEC-Case-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XRP-Primed-For-Bullish-Eruption-As-Ripples-Garlinghouse-Believes-Truth-Will-Come-To-Light-In-SEC-Case-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>Brad Garlinghouse, the CEO of Ripple, has made some notable comments about <a href="https://zycrypto.com/ripples-brad-garlinghouse-tells-where-crypto-market-is-headed-as-xrp-lawsuit-heads-for-conclusion/">Ripple’s ongoing case</a> with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC).</p>



<p>As the 2023 World Economic Forum kicked off in Davos, Garlinghouse, amongst the many cryptocurrency CEOs present at the summit, spoke about emails from the SEC Director,&nbsp;Bill Hinman.&nbsp;</p>



<p>Garlinghouse explains that the emails, which will soon be handed over to the judge, who ordered that they be turned over to him, might help give Ripple another upper hand in the ongoing case.</p>



<p>Garlinghouse asserts with certainty that said emails might be harmful to the SEC&#8217;s case, as the content contained in the emails could be condemnatory.</p>



<p>In his words;&nbsp;</p>



<p><em>“When those come to light, I think that we will see more kind of like &#8216;How is it possible the SEC decided to bring a case against Ripple given what they were saying within their walls.”&nbsp;</em></p>



<p>He also expresses optimism about the case closing in its favour. He added that although the judges might spend a lot of time on the case, he’s sure of a resolution within the first half of 2023.</p>



<p><em>“Judges take however long the judges will take. We&#8217;re optimistic that this will certainly be resolved in 2023, and maybe [in] the first half. So we&#8217;ll see how it plays out from here. But I feel very good about where we are relative to the law and the facts.&#8221; the CEO said while speaking to CNBC at Davos.</em></p>



<h2 id="h-ongoing-lawsuit-fails-to-deter-ripple-from-hitting-new-milestones"><strong>Ongoing lawsuit fails to deter Ripple from hitting new milestones</strong></h2>



<p>Even though market players have maintained that the ongoing SEC vs Ripple case has cost Ripple a lot, the network can still boast about hitting some notable milestones.</p>



<p>Garlinghouse noted that Ripple still sits on billions of dollars, thanks to its revenue skyrocketing in the past years.</p>



<p>Ripple has partnered with a handful of leading companies over the past years. More recently, Ripple partnered with Palau to launch its national stablecoin.</p>



<p>With Ripple <a href="https://zycrypto.com/ripples-win-in-xrp-lawsuit-against-sec-proves-pivotal-what-to-expect-from-the-market-this-year/">scoring major wins</a>, despite the ongoing lawsuit, market players are predicting that XRP is primed for a bullish eruption once the case comes to a close, especially if the verdict plays in Ripple’s favour.</p>



<p>However, if Ripple doesn’t emerge victorious, key figures like attorney John Deaton sights the downfall of many other cryptocurrencies and crypto platforms.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/xrp-primed-for-bullish-eruption-as-ripples-garlinghouse-believes-truth-will-come-to-light-in-sec-case/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>SEC Commissioner Makes Controversial Case For ETH, XRP, Faults Howey’s Test</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/sec-commissioner-makes-controversial-case-for-eth-xrp-faults-howeys-test/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/sec-commissioner-makes-controversial-case-for-eth-xrp-faults-howeys-test/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aliyu Pokima]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 14:59:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=77426</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Ethereums-Buterin-Throws-Jab-At-XRP-As-He-Propels-Fight-Against-Canadas-New-Crypto-Regulation.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Ethereum&#039;s Buterin Throws Jab At XRP As He Propels Fight Against Canada’s New Crypto Regulation" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Ethereums-Buterin-Throws-Jab-At-XRP-As-He-Propels-Fight-Against-Canadas-New-Crypto-Regulation.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Ethereums-Buterin-Throws-Jab-At-XRP-As-He-Propels-Fight-Against-Canadas-New-Crypto-Regulation-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Ethereums-Buterin-Throws-Jab-At-XRP-As-He-Propels-Fight-Against-Canadas-New-Crypto-Regulation-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Ethereums-Buterin-Throws-Jab-At-XRP-As-He-Propels-Fight-Against-Canadas-New-Crypto-Regulation-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>The Howey test has been used by the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) to determine if assets are to be classified as securities since 1946, but it is not without its flaws. SEC’s Commissioner Hester Pierce has concurred with the point of most digital asset executives for the greater part of the year concerning the [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Ethereums-Buterin-Throws-Jab-At-XRP-As-He-Propels-Fight-Against-Canadas-New-Crypto-Regulation.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Ethereum&#039;s Buterin Throws Jab At XRP As He Propels Fight Against Canada’s New Crypto Regulation" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Ethereums-Buterin-Throws-Jab-At-XRP-As-He-Propels-Fight-Against-Canadas-New-Crypto-Regulation.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Ethereums-Buterin-Throws-Jab-At-XRP-As-He-Propels-Fight-Against-Canadas-New-Crypto-Regulation-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Ethereums-Buterin-Throws-Jab-At-XRP-As-He-Propels-Fight-Against-Canadas-New-Crypto-Regulation-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Ethereums-Buterin-Throws-Jab-At-XRP-As-He-Propels-Fight-Against-Canadas-New-Crypto-Regulation-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<ul>
<li>SEC’s Commissioner Hester Pierce points out loopholes in the popular Howey’s test used to classify assets as securities.</li>



<li>Disgruntled with the back and forths in the regulatory framework, she calls for actual positive movements in the digital asset space.</li>



<li>Crypto enthusiasts on Twitter users see this as a step in the right direction by the SEC while they hope for a better year ahead.</li>
</ul>



<p>The Howey test has been used by the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) to determine if assets are to be classified as securities since 1946, but it is not without its flaws.</p>



<p>SEC’s Commissioner Hester Pierce has concurred with the point of most digital asset executives for the greater part of the year concerning the shortcomings of the Howey test. According to her, the test does not address the true status of Bitcoin (BTC) and Ethereum (ETH) when scrutinized holistically.</p>



<p>She explained that the test works with anticipated profits from an “investment contract” dragging in digital assets because of the expected profits by users at the initial purchase of tokens with a promise by creators to “<em>build a better network.”</em></p>



<p>Pierce argues that the investment contract should not be lumped together with the asset as they are meant to be exclusive though related.&nbsp;</p>



<p>“<em>Just because I sold you the orange grove as part of an investment contract doesn&#8217;t turn the orange grove into a security,” Well, look, a lot of these initial sales sure look like securities offerings, but then the question is, is that token, is the crypto asset itself, a security?” </em>she added.&nbsp;</p>



<p>For Pierce and many others, digital assets should not be lumped as securities in perpetuity but particular transactions singled out when they breach Security laws. Pointing to transactions rather than digital assets is imperative because Howey’s test alone is insufficient to place cryptocurrencies as securities.</p>



<h2 id="h-sec-must-find-positive-movements"><strong>SEC must find positive movements</strong></h2>



<p>For the SEC to grasp the digital asset market, there must be a proper regulatory framework to guide crypto executives and users. In 2018, SEC’s director on Corporate Finance, William Hinman, stated that BTC and ETH cannot be classified as securities because they are “<em>sufficiently decentralized.”</em></p>



<p>This benchmark has shifted with SEC’s chairman Gary Gensler hinting that ETH can be <a href="https://zycrypto.com/post-merge-concerns-heres-why-eth-could-be-viewed-as-a-security/">classified</a> as a security after its Merge. Pierce believes that this back-and-forth created by the lacuna in Howey’s test has slowed positive movements by the Commission in the sector. She went further to criticize the overall lack of clarity surrounding several aspects of the industry hoping for a change of events in the future.&nbsp;</p>



<p><em>“The wheels of regulation and legislation move very slowly, and I think that can be both good and bad. In the crypto world, we&#8217;ve seen for a long time that there&#8217;s been a lack of clarity, which I think has led people to do things that they wouldn&#8217;t have done had there been clear guidelines.”</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/sec-commissioner-makes-controversial-case-for-eth-xrp-faults-howeys-test/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cardano Network Roars Back to Life as Developers Fix Brief Node Outage in Minutes</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/cardano-network-roars-back-to-life-as-developers-fix-brief-node-outage-in-minutes/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/cardano-network-roars-back-to-life-as-developers-fix-brief-node-outage-in-minutes/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Newton Gitonga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 14:03:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADAUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=77424</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Cardano-Now-‘Better-Than-Ever-Declares-Ecosystem-Dev-Who-Warned-Of-Catastrophic-Testnet-Issues.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Cardano Now ‘Better Than Ever,’ Declares Ecosystem Dev Who Warned Of Catastrophic Testnet Issues" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Cardano-Now-‘Better-Than-Ever-Declares-Ecosystem-Dev-Who-Warned-Of-Catastrophic-Testnet-Issues.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Cardano-Now-‘Better-Than-Ever-Declares-Ecosystem-Dev-Who-Warned-Of-Catastrophic-Testnet-Issues-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Cardano-Now-‘Better-Than-Ever-Declares-Ecosystem-Dev-Who-Warned-Of-Catastrophic-Testnet-Issues-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Cardano-Now-‘Better-Than-Ever-Declares-Ecosystem-Dev-Who-Warned-Of-Catastrophic-Testnet-Issues-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>Yesterday, Cardano suffered an outage, with multiple Stake Pool Operators (SPOs) reporting that at least 50% of the network’s nodes went offline over the weekend.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Cardano-Now-‘Better-Than-Ever-Declares-Ecosystem-Dev-Who-Warned-Of-Catastrophic-Testnet-Issues.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Cardano Now ‘Better Than Ever,’ Declares Ecosystem Dev Who Warned Of Catastrophic Testnet Issues" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Cardano-Now-‘Better-Than-Ever-Declares-Ecosystem-Dev-Who-Warned-Of-Catastrophic-Testnet-Issues.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Cardano-Now-‘Better-Than-Ever-Declares-Ecosystem-Dev-Who-Warned-Of-Catastrophic-Testnet-Issues-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Cardano-Now-‘Better-Than-Ever-Declares-Ecosystem-Dev-Who-Warned-Of-Catastrophic-Testnet-Issues-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Cardano-Now-‘Better-Than-Ever-Declares-Ecosystem-Dev-Who-Warned-Of-Catastrophic-Testnet-Issues-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>Yesterday, Cardano suffered an outage, with multiple Stake Pool Operators (SPOs) reporting that at least 50% of the network’s nodes went offline over the weekend.</p>



<p>According to a Telegram post by Input Output Global-the developer firm behind the <a href="https://zycrypto.com/cardano-is-buzzing-with-super-bullish-activity-as-ada-adoption-expands-to-new-realms/">Cardano blockchain</a>, the anomaly happened at approximately 00:09:00 UTC (between block 8300569 and 8300570) on Sunday, causing approximately 50% of Cardano nodes to disconnect and restart.</p>



<p>Developers pointed the outage to a “transient anomaly” affecting nodes, noting that while it impacted relay and block-producing nodes, edge nodes were unaffected.</p>



<p><em>“This appears to have been triggered by a transient anomaly causing one of two reactions in the node; some disconnected from a peer, others threw an exception and restarted”, </em>the post read.</p>



<p>The incident caused a brief interruption in the production of new blocks, resulting in some nodes becoming out of sync with the rest of the network. Nodes are network stakeholders responsible for processing and validating transactions. They are essential to the health and upkeep of any blockchain network.</p>



<p>According to the developers, “such transient issues”-even if they were to affect all nodes, were considered in the design of the Cardano node and consensus. Notably, they noted that “the systems behaved exactly as expected”, which explains the short period before the network’s recovery.</p>



<p><em>“It’s software, bugs happen, but it appears that Cardano’s design allows for things of this nature to happen and the blockchain will simply restart itself to keep going. This is what decentralization and smart software design are about &#8211; no single point of failure.”</em></p>



<p>And although the network sync had recovered to almost 100% at noon on Monday, the IOG team promised to conduct further investigations into the incident and implement further logging measures alongside their regular monitoring procedures.</p>



<p>Network outages have been a big issue for networks such as Solana. Validators on Solana have severally been forced to restart the network after <a href="https://zycrypto.com/after-over-10-network-outages-solana-proposes-a-genius-solution-to-solve-debacle/">outages persisted</a>, at times for several hours.</p>



<p>Meanwhile, despite the incident, the community has praised Cardano, particularly for the network’s ability to recover in minutes without any external help.</p>



<p><em>“Very glad to see how the network reacted to this incident, makes me believe in the project even more,”</em> one Redditor commented.</p>



<p>Another said, <em>“What makes me confident is that Cardano is built solid and without shortcuts. The fact that these kinds of problems were thought of and handled long before they occur is impressive.”</em></p>



<p>Notably, ADA, the native token for Cardano, continued to hold up strongly during and after the incident. At press time, the crypto asset was trading at $0.37, down 1.62% in the past 24 hours, according to data from CoinMarketCap.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/cardano-network-roars-back-to-life-as-developers-fix-brief-node-outage-in-minutes/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Takes The Spotlight As Brazil And Argentina Mulls Creating A Common Currency</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/bitcoin-takes-the-spotlight-as-brazil-and-argentina-mulls-creating-a-common-currency/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/bitcoin-takes-the-spotlight-as-brazil-and-argentina-mulls-creating-a-common-currency/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Newton Gitonga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 11:24:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Argentina]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Brazil]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XBTUSD]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=77421</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-Takes-The-Spotlight-As-Brazil-And-Argentina-Mulls-Creating-A-Common-Currency.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Bitcoin Takes The Spotlight As Brazil And Argentina Mulls Creating A Common Currency" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-Takes-The-Spotlight-As-Brazil-And-Argentina-Mulls-Creating-A-Common-Currency.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-Takes-The-Spotlight-As-Brazil-And-Argentina-Mulls-Creating-A-Common-Currency-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-Takes-The-Spotlight-As-Brazil-And-Argentina-Mulls-Creating-A-Common-Currency-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-Takes-The-Spotlight-As-Brazil-And-Argentina-Mulls-Creating-A-Common-Currency-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>This week, Brazil and Argentina are set to declare the initiation of preparations for a shared currency, a move that could result in the formation of the world’s second-largest currency bloc.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-Takes-The-Spotlight-As-Brazil-And-Argentina-Mulls-Creating-A-Common-Currency.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Bitcoin Takes The Spotlight As Brazil And Argentina Mulls Creating A Common Currency" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-Takes-The-Spotlight-As-Brazil-And-Argentina-Mulls-Creating-A-Common-Currency.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-Takes-The-Spotlight-As-Brazil-And-Argentina-Mulls-Creating-A-Common-Currency-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-Takes-The-Spotlight-As-Brazil-And-Argentina-Mulls-Creating-A-Common-Currency-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-Takes-The-Spotlight-As-Brazil-And-Argentina-Mulls-Creating-A-Common-Currency-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>This week, Brazil and Argentina are set to declare the initiation of preparations for a shared currency, a move that could result in the formation of the world’s second-largest currency bloc.</p>



<p>According to a report by Financial Times, the two countries will discuss the concept at an upcoming summit in Buenos Aires and invite other Latin American nations to join. Further, they will discuss how the new currency, which <a href="https://zycrypto.com/brazils-congress-passes-bill-legalizing-bitcoin-ether-payments/">Brazil</a> suggests calling “Sur”, could help reduce reliance on the US dollar and boost regional trade.</p>



<p><em>“There will be  a decision to start studying the parameters needed for a common currency, which includes everything from fiscal issues to the size of the economy and the role of central banks,” said Sergio Massa,</em> Argentina’s economy minister.</p>



<p><em>“It would be a study of mechanisms for trade integration. I don’t want to create any false expectations. It’s the first step on a long road which Latin America must travel,”</em> he added.</p>



<p>Mr Sergio further confirmed that, although the project would initially be bilateral, they would invite other nations in Latin America. </p>



<p>The development comes even as the two economies fight to stay afloat amid a gloomy global economic outlook. Apart from its annual inflation approaching stubbornly high levels, Argentina has also been struggling to get funding from international debt markets since 2020, with its <a href="https://zycrypto.com/imfs-hidden-role-in-argentinas-crypto-pushback-rattles-crypto-community/">debts to IMF</a> alone standing at more than $40B.</p>



<p>Meanwhile, the upcoming meeting has sparked discussions in the crypto community, with some observers proposing Bitcoin as the best option for the two Latin countries.</p>



<p><em>“Wonder if they would consider moving to Bitcoin &#8211; that would probably be the right long-term bet,”</em> Brian Armstrong, the CEO of crypto exchange Coinbase, wrote early Monday. Others called on the two countries to follow El Salvador’s <a href="https://zycrypto.com/bitcoin-officially-becomes-legal-tender-in-el-salvador-country-secures-first-400-btc-purchase/">footsteps</a> by making Bitcoin legal tender.</p>



<p><em>“Definitely would be a risky bet financially; El Salvador seems to be doing well for themselves since buying BTC daily. I’d be curious to see if Brazil will ever convert to BTC,” </em>another wrote.</p>



<p>However, some members seemed opposed to the idea, with Real Vision CEO Raoul Pal casting doubt on the cryptocurrencies volatility. According to the businessman, “<em>no one can have a national currency with 100% volatility that declines 65% in the down part of the business cycle and rises 10x in the upcycle.”</em></p>



<p>He was, however, quickly reminded that onboarding a combined population of 265M million people with hopes of expanding to other Latin American countries would help considerably with volatility. Moreover, unlike Bitcoin, fiat currencies were at risk of losing their value to zero due to external pressures.</p>



<p><em>“That (BTC) still sounds better than using the peso that has 90% annual inflation, controlled by a government that has a history of 9 debt defaults in the last 80 years. Argentina needs Bitcoin,”</em> one tweep told Pal.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/bitcoin-takes-the-spotlight-as-brazil-and-argentina-mulls-creating-a-common-currency/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>El Salvador&#8217;s Exposure to Bitcoin Is Still &#8220;Minimal&#8221;, Asserts Regional Banker</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/el-salvadors-exposure-to-bitcoin-is-still-minimal-asserts-regional-banker/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/el-salvadors-exposure-to-bitcoin-is-still-minimal-asserts-regional-banker/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Newton Gitonga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2023 22:05:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[El Salvador]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XBTUSD]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=77416</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/El-Salvadors-Wild-Bitcoin-Experiment-Is-Crumbling-—-Bombshell-Study-Reveals.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="El Salvador’s Wild Bitcoin Experiment Is &#039;Crumbling&#039; — Bombshell Study Reveals" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/El-Salvadors-Wild-Bitcoin-Experiment-Is-Crumbling-—-Bombshell-Study-Reveals.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/El-Salvadors-Wild-Bitcoin-Experiment-Is-Crumbling-—-Bombshell-Study-Reveals-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/El-Salvadors-Wild-Bitcoin-Experiment-Is-Crumbling-—-Bombshell-Study-Reveals-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/El-Salvadors-Wild-Bitcoin-Experiment-Is-Crumbling-—-Bombshell-Study-Reveals-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>Dante Mossi, the Chairman of the Central American Bank for Economic Integration (CABEI), has claimed that El Salvador’s exposure to cryptocurrencies is “minimal”.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/El-Salvadors-Wild-Bitcoin-Experiment-Is-Crumbling-—-Bombshell-Study-Reveals.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="El Salvador’s Wild Bitcoin Experiment Is &#039;Crumbling&#039; — Bombshell Study Reveals" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/El-Salvadors-Wild-Bitcoin-Experiment-Is-Crumbling-—-Bombshell-Study-Reveals.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/El-Salvadors-Wild-Bitcoin-Experiment-Is-Crumbling-—-Bombshell-Study-Reveals-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/El-Salvadors-Wild-Bitcoin-Experiment-Is-Crumbling-—-Bombshell-Study-Reveals-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/El-Salvadors-Wild-Bitcoin-Experiment-Is-Crumbling-—-Bombshell-Study-Reveals-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>Dante Mossi, the Chairman of the Central American Bank for Economic Integration (CABEI), has claimed that El Salvador’s exposure to cryptocurrencies is “minimal”.</p>



<p>Speaking to Bloomberg Friday, Mossi noted that whereas Bitcoin’s popularity and adoption had grown since the top cryptocurrency was <a href="https://zycrypto.com/bitcoin-officially-becomes-legal-tender-in-el-salvador-country-secures-first-400-btc-purchase/">made legal tender</a> in El Salvador about two years ago, the population’s exposure to it was too small.</p>



<p><em>“We have seen that exposure, and we consider it very small “- it is a not significant one,”</em> said Mossi<em>. “We are interested that investors also know the real situation of El Salvador.”</em></p>



<p>The banker’s comments come amid growing criticism and uncertainty about El Salvador’s Bitcoin experiment, especially after the crypto asset’s price plunged by over half its value in recent months. On September 7, 2021, El Salvador became the first country in the world to adopt Bitcoin as a legal tender, <a href="https://zycrypto.com/el-salvadors-losses-swell-even-as-president-nayib-bukele-adds-another-1-5-million-bitcoin/">purchasing</a> the crypto asset severally. As of July 2022, the President Bukele-led government had purchased 2,381 Bitcoin, according to his announcements on Twitter.</p>



<p>Bukele has been criticized for failing to disclose the country’s holdings officially, particularly after a November 17 announcement that they would continue buying one Bitcoin daily. Assuming that Bukele has lived up to his announcement, the Nayib Bukele Portfolio Tracker estimates that the country has spent more than $109 million on bitcoin but is down over $51 million based on current prices.</p>



<p>El Salvador’s unrealized paper losses have also been weighing down on the nation’s ability to access capital from lenders. Last month, Mossi’s multinational lender recently gave El Salvador a $450 million loan, most of which is expected to be used in repaying a bond next week. According to the banker, El Salvador was barred from using the financing to buy crypto assets, noting that the use of proceeds will be audited in six months.</p>



<p>CABEI has been working with the nation to compile information, which is expected to include disclosures on cryptocurrencies, before presenting it to the <a href="https://zycrypto.com/imf-issues-fresh-warning-to-el-salvador-over-bitcoin-adoption-but-president-bukele-focuses-on-the-positives/">International Monetary Fund</a> (IMF) for review and recommendations.</p>



<p>Recently, Cristosal, a human rights group in Central America, also called out Bukele’s administration for its “absolute opacity about the use of public funds” related to bitcoin.</p>



<p><em>“The lack of transparency leaves citizens without knowing the beneficiaries, quantities or reasons for granting the funds,”</em> Cristosal said.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/el-salvadors-exposure-to-bitcoin-is-still-minimal-asserts-regional-banker/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Report Shows Growth In Multiple Ethereum Layer 2 Networks; Polygon Leads The Pack</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/report-shows-growth-in-multiple-ethereum-layer-2-networks-polygon-leads-the-pack/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/report-shows-growth-in-multiple-ethereum-layer-2-networks-polygon-leads-the-pack/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aliyu Pokima]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2023 21:19:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MATIC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MATICUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Polygon]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=77413</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Report-Shows-Growth-In-Multiple-Ethereum-Layer-2-Networks-Polygon-Leads-The-Pack.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Report Shows Growth In Multiple Ethereum Layer 2 Networks; Polygon Leads The Pack" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Report-Shows-Growth-In-Multiple-Ethereum-Layer-2-Networks-Polygon-Leads-The-Pack.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Report-Shows-Growth-In-Multiple-Ethereum-Layer-2-Networks-Polygon-Leads-The-Pack-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Report-Shows-Growth-In-Multiple-Ethereum-Layer-2-Networks-Polygon-Leads-The-Pack-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Report-Shows-Growth-In-Multiple-Ethereum-Layer-2-Networks-Polygon-Leads-The-Pack-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>The importance of Layer 2 solutions is becoming much more glaring as web3 adoption continues to grow paving a way for developers to launch without compromising speed for scalability.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Report-Shows-Growth-In-Multiple-Ethereum-Layer-2-Networks-Polygon-Leads-The-Pack.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Report Shows Growth In Multiple Ethereum Layer 2 Networks; Polygon Leads The Pack" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Report-Shows-Growth-In-Multiple-Ethereum-Layer-2-Networks-Polygon-Leads-The-Pack.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Report-Shows-Growth-In-Multiple-Ethereum-Layer-2-Networks-Polygon-Leads-The-Pack-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Report-Shows-Growth-In-Multiple-Ethereum-Layer-2-Networks-Polygon-Leads-The-Pack-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Report-Shows-Growth-In-Multiple-Ethereum-Layer-2-Networks-Polygon-Leads-The-Pack-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<ul>
<li>Recent data shows an astonishing growth of users and transactions among Ethereum’s growing list of layer 2 networks.&nbsp;</li>



<li>Polygon, Optimism, and Arbitrum have recorded increased daily user activity by 30%, 180%, and 40%, respectively. </li>



<li>Polygon has been tipped for massive successes this year with several network upgrades and more web3 projects before Q2 2023.</li>
</ul>



<p>The importance of Layer 2 solutions is becoming much more glaring as web3 adoption continues to grow, paving the way for developers to launch without compromising speed for scalability.</p>



<p>Layer 2 solutions have recorded a significant rise in the past three months in major metrics, including daily users, transaction volumes, and increased network fees. According to a report by blockchain analysis provider Token Terminal, the amount of assets locked in these networks is also rising. </p>



<p>Data from Token Terminal shows that Polygon has seen a surge in daily users since Oct 2022. As of October, daily users stood at 313,400 a figure that has nearly doubled to over 600,000 daily users. The increased transaction has led to nearly $55,000 in daily network fees for Polygon.</p>



<p>According to the data, Arbitrum One has grown by 40% and now has 41,695 daily users making daily fees over $40,000. Arbitrum also dominates the market share in terms of total value locked (TVL) on its network. TVL on Arbitrum is at $2.5 billion, accounting for 52% of the total assets locked on Ethereum’s layer 2 platforms.</p>



<p>Optimism has recorded gains of over 180% in daily network fees, which is a significantly higher increase than Polygon. The last three months have also seen daily users on Optimism spike by 190%. TVL on Optimism currently stands at $1.46 billion with a market share of 30%.</p>



<h2 id="h-polygon-s-developers-are-working-round-the-clock"><strong>Polygon’s developers are working round the clock</strong></h2>



<p>Among layer 2 networks, Polygon is tipped to have a more robust development in 2023. The network’s recent <a href="https://zycrypto.com/polygon-successfully-completes-performance-boosting-hard-fork-as-matic-targets-2-price-high/">hard fork</a>, which will reduce gas fees and improve its overall performance, can be described as an early sign of future developments.</p>



<p>Multiple projects are also set to migrate to Polygon from rival networks, including Solana’s yOOTs. Polygon has partnered with Xternity to migrate Synergy Land, a web3 game, from Solana. Last week Mastercard announced a <a href="https://zycrypto.com/polygon-to-host-mastercards-web3-artist-accelerator-and-a-limited-time-release-nft/">partnership with Polygon</a> as it launched its web3 musician accelerator program aimed at helping artists build their brands leveraging on web3.</p>



<p>Polygon climbed back into the top 10 cryptocurrencies by market capitalization after it was pushed out briefly by Solana this week.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/report-shows-growth-in-multiple-ethereum-layer-2-networks-polygon-leads-the-pack/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
