<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>News Archives &#8902; ZyCrypto</title>
	<atom:link href="https://zycrypto.com/category/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://zycrypto.com/category/news/</link>
	<description>ZyCrypto Is A Cryptocurrency News Media, Focusing On Daily News, Expert Opinions, Analysis, Reviews, And So Much More.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 21:08:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/cropped-ZyCrypto-Site-Logo-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News Archives &#8902; ZyCrypto</title>
	<link>https://zycrypto.com/category/news/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Why Billionaire Paul Tudor Jones Now Believes Bitcoin Has Become Less Attractive</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/why-billionaire-paul-tudor-jones-now-believes-bitcoin-has-become-less-attractive/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/why-billionaire-paul-tudor-jones-now-believes-bitcoin-has-become-less-attractive/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Brenda Ngari]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 21:08:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Featured]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XBTUSD]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=80941</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Why-Billionaire-Paul-Tudor-Jones-Now-Believes-Bitcoin-Has-Become-Less-Attractive.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Why Billionaire Paul Tudor Jones Now Believes Bitcoin Has Become Less Attractive" decoding="async" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Why-Billionaire-Paul-Tudor-Jones-Now-Believes-Bitcoin-Has-Become-Less-Attractive.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Why-Billionaire-Paul-Tudor-Jones-Now-Believes-Bitcoin-Has-Become-Less-Attractive-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Why-Billionaire-Paul-Tudor-Jones-Now-Believes-Bitcoin-Has-Become-Less-Attractive-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Why-Billionaire-Paul-Tudor-Jones-Now-Believes-Bitcoin-Has-Become-Less-Attractive-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>Billionaire hedge fund manager Paul Tudor-Jones — who previously touted bitcoin's allure as an inflationary hedge — now thinks the benchmark cryptocurrency is less attractive, suggesting it has lost some of its luster.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Why-Billionaire-Paul-Tudor-Jones-Now-Believes-Bitcoin-Has-Become-Less-Attractive.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Why Billionaire Paul Tudor Jones Now Believes Bitcoin Has Become Less Attractive" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Why-Billionaire-Paul-Tudor-Jones-Now-Believes-Bitcoin-Has-Become-Less-Attractive.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Why-Billionaire-Paul-Tudor-Jones-Now-Believes-Bitcoin-Has-Become-Less-Attractive-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Why-Billionaire-Paul-Tudor-Jones-Now-Believes-Bitcoin-Has-Become-Less-Attractive-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Why-Billionaire-Paul-Tudor-Jones-Now-Believes-Bitcoin-Has-Become-Less-Attractive-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>Billionaire hedge fund manager Paul Tudor-Jones — who previously touted bitcoin&#8217;s allure as an inflationary hedge — now thinks the benchmark cryptocurrency is less attractive, suggesting it has lost some of its luster.</p>



<p>Jones cited the challenging regulatory environment in the U.S. and the inflation slowdown as fundamental headwinds for Bitcoin.</p>



<p>Regardless, the billionaire American investor — whose company controls approximately $40 billion in assets under management — said he still has a minor allocation in Bitcoin even though it has lost its appeal.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-bitcoin-has-a-real-problem"><strong>“Bitcoin Has A Real Problem”</strong></h2>



<p>One of the all-time great investors, Paul Tudor-Jones, told <em>CNBC’s Squawk Box</em> today that Bitcoin has a grave problem amid regulatory challenges in the United States.</p>



<p>“Bitcoin has a real problem because, in the United States, you have the entire regulatory apparatus against it,” Jones said during the interview.</p>



<p>In recent months, the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has indeed stepped up its enforcement actions against crypto startups and platforms in the country, alleging wide breaches of securities laws. The multi-billion dollar implosion of crypto exchange FTX initiated a particularly intense wave of crypto regulatory clampdowns, including those on well-known exchanges, including <a href="https://zycrypto.com/coinbase-goes-offensive-against-the-sec-with-lawsuit-targeted-at-regulatory-clarity/">Coinbase </a>and Kraken. Coinbase has even <a href="https://zycrypto.com/coinbase-ceo-is-considering-relocating-company-outside-of-the-u-s-due-to-unfavorable-regulation/">threatened </a>to move away from the U.S. if legal and regulatory certainty does not come forth.</p>



<p>Jones further said he thinks inflation will continue to cool off, adding to the less-bullish picture for Bitcoin.</p>



<p>Bitcoin is far and away the most famous cryptocurrency. Crypto propounders consider Bitcoin a store of value asset like gold, owing to the programmed code that reduces its pace of supply expansion by 50% quadrennially. Back in 2020, when central banks started money-printing sprees in a bid to keep the economy and financial system afloat in the wake of COVID-19 lockdowns, Jones <a href="https://zycrypto.com/paul-tudor-discloses-he-has-1-2-of-his-assets-in-bitcoin-calls-it-a-great-speculation/">wrote </a>a compelling investor letter, generally viewed as a logical case for hedging one’s portfolio against inflation with the OG crypto.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Tudor-Jones Still Has Bitcoin Exposure</strong></h2>



<p>While Jones&#8217;s recent remarks weren’t exactly an endorsement of Bitcoin, given his major bullishness roughly three years ago, the hedge fund manager is not ready to completely cut ties with the number one cryptocurrency.</p>



<p>For Jones, Bitcoin remains intriguing, with its appeal mainly coming from the fact that a single individual or company cannot manipulate its supply.</p>



<p>“It is the only thing that humans can&#8217;t adjust the supply in, so I am sticking with it, and I am always going to stick with it,” the billionaire emphasized, adding that bitcoin accounts for a “small diversification” in his portfolio.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/why-billionaire-paul-tudor-jones-now-believes-bitcoin-has-become-less-attractive/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Zimbabwe Defies IMF Directive to Sell Millions of Gold-Backed Crypto Assets; Terms It a Success</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/zimbabwe-defies-imf-directive-to-sell-millions-of-gold-backed-crypto-assets-terms-it-a-success/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/zimbabwe-defies-imf-directive-to-sell-millions-of-gold-backed-crypto-assets-terms-it-a-success/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jared Kirui]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 20:49:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=80937</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/CBDC-or-Bitcoin-Zimbabwe-Sways-Both-Sides-As-Conflicting-Reports-Emerge.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="CBDC or Bitcoin Zimbabwe Sways Both Sides As Conflicting Reports Emerge" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/CBDC-or-Bitcoin-Zimbabwe-Sways-Both-Sides-As-Conflicting-Reports-Emerge.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/CBDC-or-Bitcoin-Zimbabwe-Sways-Both-Sides-As-Conflicting-Reports-Emerge-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/CBDC-or-Bitcoin-Zimbabwe-Sways-Both-Sides-As-Conflicting-Reports-Emerge-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/CBDC-or-Bitcoin-Zimbabwe-Sways-Both-Sides-As-Conflicting-Reports-Emerge-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>The Reserve Bank of Zimbabwe (RBZ) has sold gold-backed cryptocurrencies valued at 14 billion Zimbabwean dollars despite a warning by the International Monetary Fund against adopting the digital currency to address the country’s macroeconomic problems. RBZ Governor Dr John Mangudya announced in a statement on May 12 that the central bank had received 135 applications [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/CBDC-or-Bitcoin-Zimbabwe-Sways-Both-Sides-As-Conflicting-Reports-Emerge.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="CBDC or Bitcoin Zimbabwe Sways Both Sides As Conflicting Reports Emerge" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/CBDC-or-Bitcoin-Zimbabwe-Sways-Both-Sides-As-Conflicting-Reports-Emerge.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/CBDC-or-Bitcoin-Zimbabwe-Sways-Both-Sides-As-Conflicting-Reports-Emerge-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/CBDC-or-Bitcoin-Zimbabwe-Sways-Both-Sides-As-Conflicting-Reports-Emerge-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/CBDC-or-Bitcoin-Zimbabwe-Sways-Both-Sides-As-Conflicting-Reports-Emerge-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<ul>
<li>The southern African country is battling hyperinflation and a depreciating local currency.</li>



<li>RBZ Gold-backed Digital token would be used for payments and as a store of value.</li>
</ul>



<p>The Reserve Bank of Zimbabwe (RBZ) has sold gold-backed cryptocurrencies valued at 14 billion Zimbabwean dollars despite a warning by the International Monetary Fund against adopting the digital currency to address the country’s macroeconomic problems.</p>



<p>RBZ Governor Dr John Mangudya announced in a statement on May 12 that the central bank had received 135 applications from the participating lenders, of which 132 of the bids were submitted in local currencies, while three were in USD.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-gold-backed-crypto-as-a-solution-to-hyperinflation"><strong>Gold-Backed Crypto as a Solution to Hyperinflation</strong></h2>



<p><a href="https://zycrypto.com/cbdc-or-bitcoin-zimbabwe-sways-both-sides-as-conflicting-reports-emerge/">Zimbabwe</a> is turning to gold-backed digital currency to address hyperinflation and the diminishing value of its local currency. According to Mangudya, the digital currency aims to expand value-preserving instruments, enhance investment divisibility and expand public access.</p>



<p>‘‘The issuance of the gold-backed digital tokens is meant to expand the value-preserving instruments available in the economy and enhance divisibility of the investment instruments and widen their access and usage by the public,’’ he said, adding that the depreciation of the local currency because of the increase in demand for the US dollar was causing volatility in exchange rates.</p>



<p>RBZ Gold-backed Digital Token, whose first sale was backed by nearly 140 kilograms of gold, fetched a minimum price of $10 for individuals and $5,000 for corporations, with a minimum vesting period of 180 days.</p>



<p>The cryptocurrencies, held in e-gold wallets or e-gold cards, are tradeable through person-to-person and person-to-business transactions. Further, users with physical gold exchange them for gold-backed digital tokens through commercial banks, according to the report, allowing their use as a payment and a store of value.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-imf-s-objection"><strong>IMF’s Objection</strong></h2>



<p>The IMF has warned the southern African country against adopting the gold-backed crypto, saying that conventional means of addressing the pressing macroeconomic challenges should be considered instead.</p>



<p>‘‘A careful assessment should be conducted to ensure the benefits from this measure outweigh the costs and potential risks including, for instance, macroeconomic and financial stability risks, legal and operational risks, governance risks, cost of foregone FX reserves,’’ said IMF representative who spoke to Bloomberg.</p>



<p>The IMF has raised similar concerns against <a href="https://zycrypto.com/us-senators-reintroduce-bill-to-investigate-bitcoin-adoption-in-el-salvador/">El Salvador</a> and the Central African Republic, which adopted Bitcoin as a legal tender in their respective jurisdictions.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/zimbabwe-defies-imf-directive-to-sell-millions-of-gold-backed-crypto-assets-terms-it-a-success/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>PEPE Coin Gains Broader Acceptance After Gemini Exchange Listing</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/pepe-coin-gains-broader-acceptance-after-gemini-exchange-listing/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/pepe-coin-gains-broader-acceptance-after-gemini-exchange-listing/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Erie Maxwell]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 20:35:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gemini]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PEPE]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=80930</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/PEPE-Whale-Takes-540000-Paper-Loss-in-Two-Days-as-Token-Plunges-Over-30.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="PEPE Whale Takes $540,000 Paper Loss in Two Days as Token Plunges Over 30%" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/PEPE-Whale-Takes-540000-Paper-Loss-in-Two-Days-as-Token-Plunges-Over-30.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/PEPE-Whale-Takes-540000-Paper-Loss-in-Two-Days-as-Token-Plunges-Over-30-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/PEPE-Whale-Takes-540000-Paper-Loss-in-Two-Days-as-Token-Plunges-Over-30-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/PEPE-Whale-Takes-540000-Paper-Loss-in-Two-Days-as-Token-Plunges-Over-30-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>In a move that thrilled the members of the #PEPEARMY, the Gemini cryptocurrency exchange announced the listing of the $PEPE meme token for trading on its platform. The news was first shared on the official Twitter handle of Gemini on May 10, 2023, and generated a lot of excitement among the online community. As per [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/PEPE-Whale-Takes-540000-Paper-Loss-in-Two-Days-as-Token-Plunges-Over-30.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="PEPE Whale Takes $540,000 Paper Loss in Two Days as Token Plunges Over 30%" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/PEPE-Whale-Takes-540000-Paper-Loss-in-Two-Days-as-Token-Plunges-Over-30.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/PEPE-Whale-Takes-540000-Paper-Loss-in-Two-Days-as-Token-Plunges-Over-30-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/PEPE-Whale-Takes-540000-Paper-Loss-in-Two-Days-as-Token-Plunges-Over-30-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/PEPE-Whale-Takes-540000-Paper-Loss-in-Two-Days-as-Token-Plunges-Over-30-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>In a move that thrilled the members of the #PEPEARMY, the Gemini cryptocurrency exchange announced the listing of the $PEPE meme token for trading on its platform. The news was first shared on the official Twitter handle of Gemini on May 10, 2023, and generated a lot of excitement among the online community.</p>



<p>As per the tweet by @Gemini, $PEPE is now available for trading on their platform. This announcement comes as a major development for the rapidly growing cryptocurrency, which has already amassed a significant online following. With this listing, $PEPE is set to gain even more popularity and broader acceptance in the digital currency market.</p>



<p>Gemini is a well-respected cryptocurrency exchange platform with a reputation for listing only high-quality digital assets. Its decision to list $PEPE clearly indicates the growing importance of meme coins in the crypto world. The move also highlights the increasing demand for alternative digital assets that go beyond mainstream cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin and Ethereum.</p>



<p>The $PEPE token has been <a href="https://zycrypto.com/binances-listing-of-pepe-and-floki-in-its-innovation-zone-strikes-further-eruption/">making waves</a> in the cryptocurrency space since its launch. It is a community-driven project that aims to create a decentralized platform for creators, artists, and influencers to showcase their work and monetize their content. The token is based on the popular Pepe the Frog meme and has already gained a large following on social media platforms such as Twitter and Reddit.</p>



<p>With the listing on Gemini, $PEPE holders can now trade the token on one of the most respected cryptocurrency exchanges in the world. This listing also adds to the growing number of platforms where $PEPE can be traded, which includes other major exchanges like Binance and Coinbase.</p>



<p>The $PEPE token has shown impressive growth in the past few weeks, with its price rising by over 300% in just a month. This surge in price has been attributed to the growing popularity of the token, as well as the increasing adoption of meme coins in the cryptocurrency space. With the listing on Gemini, the $PEPE token is set to gain even more momentum and could potentially reach new all-time highs.</p>



<p>The listing of $PEPE on the Gemini exchange shows a significant development for the meme token and its growing community. With the support of a reputable exchange like Gemini, $PEPE is poised to become a major player in the cryptocurrency market. As more and more investors flock to meme coins like $PEPE, it is clear that the crypto world is evolving to embrace a wider variety of digital assets beyond traditional cryptocurrencies.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/pepe-coin-gains-broader-acceptance-after-gemini-exchange-listing/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>U.S. DOJ Vows To Beef Up Scrutiny Of Crypto Exchanges To Curb Illicit Behavior</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/u-s-doj-vows-to-beef-up-scrutiny-of-crypto-exchanges-to-curb-illicit-behavior/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/u-s-doj-vows-to-beef-up-scrutiny-of-crypto-exchanges-to-curb-illicit-behavior/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Brenda Ngari]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 14:11:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USA]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=80912</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/U.S.-DOJ-Vows-To-Beef-Up-Scrutiny-Of-Crypto-Exchanges-To-Curb-Illicit-Behavior.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="U.S. DOJ Vows To Beef Up Scrutiny Of Crypto Exchanges To Curb Illicit Behavior" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/U.S.-DOJ-Vows-To-Beef-Up-Scrutiny-Of-Crypto-Exchanges-To-Curb-Illicit-Behavior.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/U.S.-DOJ-Vows-To-Beef-Up-Scrutiny-Of-Crypto-Exchanges-To-Curb-Illicit-Behavior-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/U.S.-DOJ-Vows-To-Beef-Up-Scrutiny-Of-Crypto-Exchanges-To-Curb-Illicit-Behavior-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/U.S.-DOJ-Vows-To-Beef-Up-Scrutiny-Of-Crypto-Exchanges-To-Curb-Illicit-Behavior-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>The U.S. Justice Department is planning to increase its scrutiny of crypto trading platforms to target illicit behaviour.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/U.S.-DOJ-Vows-To-Beef-Up-Scrutiny-Of-Crypto-Exchanges-To-Curb-Illicit-Behavior.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="U.S. DOJ Vows To Beef Up Scrutiny Of Crypto Exchanges To Curb Illicit Behavior" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/U.S.-DOJ-Vows-To-Beef-Up-Scrutiny-Of-Crypto-Exchanges-To-Curb-Illicit-Behavior.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/U.S.-DOJ-Vows-To-Beef-Up-Scrutiny-Of-Crypto-Exchanges-To-Curb-Illicit-Behavior-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/U.S.-DOJ-Vows-To-Beef-Up-Scrutiny-Of-Crypto-Exchanges-To-Curb-Illicit-Behavior-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/U.S.-DOJ-Vows-To-Beef-Up-Scrutiny-Of-Crypto-Exchanges-To-Curb-Illicit-Behavior-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>The U.S. Justice Department is planning to increase its scrutiny of crypto trading platforms to target illicit behaviour.</p>



<p>According to Eun Young Choi, director of the National Cryptocurrency Enforcement Team (NCET), the DOJ is targeting cryptocurrency exchanges that engage in crimes themselves or allow “other criminal actors to easily profit from their crimes and cash out.”</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-doj-on-the-hunt-for-crypto-bad-actors"><strong>DOJ On The Hunt For Crypto Bad Actors</strong></h2>



<p>In a <em>Financial Times</em> <a href="https://www.ft.com/content/5aac457e-cc80-44ae-ac40-9b51d9b601a3">report </a>on Monday, National Cryptocurrency Enforcement Team director Eun Young Choi noted that crypto crime has grown &#8220;significantly&#8221; in the last four years. As such, the department will be going after crypto exchanges that skirt anti-money laundering or know-your-customer laws or who do not invest in comprehensive compliance and risk mitigation processes.</p>



<p>“And so we hope that by focusing on those types of platforms, we’re going to have a multiplier effect,” Choi remarked.</p>



<p>The DOJ also aims to focus on crimes in the decentralized finance (DeFi) space, specifically relating to chain bridges, where users are vulnerable to hacks and thefts. Notably, cross-chain bridges have been a prime target for hackers in recent years, with billions worth of cryptocurrencies lost in a slew of exploits and attacks. Choi, who was announced as the first director of the NCET in February 2022, acknowledged that this was a critical issue for the DOJ, given North Korean state-sponsored hackers have emerged as “key actors” in the crypto sector.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Crypto Companies Are Fleeing The U.S. Amid Regulatory Tensions</strong></h2>



<p>The United States has notably taken a short-sighted and enforcement-heavy approach that is extinguishing innovation and entrepreneurship in the crypto space.</p>



<p>The DOJ crypto enforcement unit under the Biden Administration has become one of the government bodies with the most stringent stance on crypto globally. The Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) and the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) have also ramped up their scrutiny on cryptocurrency exchanges following the collapse of Sam Bankman-Fried’s FTX empire last November.</p>



<p>The predictable consequence of the brutal crackdown on the nascent sector is that more crypto companies are leaving the U.S. in search of friendlier jurisdictions. For instance, Binance.US <a href="https://zycrypto.com/voyager-legal-team-left-shell-shocked-as-binance-us-walks-away-from-1-billion-acquisition-deal/">canceled </a>its $1B asset buy deal with Voyager, while Coinbase <a href="https://zycrypto.com/coinbase-debuts-offshore-exchange-with-bitcoin-and-ethereum-perpetual-futures-amid-regulatory-challenges-in-the-us/">opened </a>a crypto derivatives exchange in Bermuda as a prescient measure in response to the regulatory uncertainty in the U.S.</p>



<p>American policymakers should just allow crypto innovation to flourish by providing a realistic registration rulebook for centralized exchanges to operate within the country and letting permissionless competition deliver the perks of decentralized exchanges. Regulators should not be wary of U.S. markets’ innovative potential. They should instead fear killing it with impossible rules.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/u-s-doj-vows-to-beef-up-scrutiny-of-crypto-exchanges-to-curb-illicit-behavior/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>XRP Lawsuit Sees New Twists And Turns As Ripple&#8217;s Counsel Exposes SEC&#8217;s Slippery Slope in Crypto Regulation</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/xrp-lawsuit-sees-new-twists-and-turns-as-ripples-counsel-exposes-secs-slippery-slope-in-crypto-regulation/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/xrp-lawsuit-sees-new-twists-and-turns-as-ripples-counsel-exposes-secs-slippery-slope-in-crypto-regulation/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aaron Feuerstein]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 12:57:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=80889</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/XRP-Army-Gleeful-As-Rumors-Of-SECs-Lawsuit-Against-Ripple-Wrapping-Up-Next-Week-Swirl.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="XRP Army Gleeful As Rumors Of SEC’s Lawsuit Against Ripple Wrapping Up Next Week Swirl" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/XRP-Army-Gleeful-As-Rumors-Of-SECs-Lawsuit-Against-Ripple-Wrapping-Up-Next-Week-Swirl.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/XRP-Army-Gleeful-As-Rumors-Of-SECs-Lawsuit-Against-Ripple-Wrapping-Up-Next-Week-Swirl-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/XRP-Army-Gleeful-As-Rumors-Of-SECs-Lawsuit-Against-Ripple-Wrapping-Up-Next-Week-Swirl-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/XRP-Army-Gleeful-As-Rumors-Of-SECs-Lawsuit-Against-Ripple-Wrapping-Up-Next-Week-Swirl-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>Just ahead of an expected ruling in the ongoing court case between the SEC and Ripple...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/XRP-Army-Gleeful-As-Rumors-Of-SECs-Lawsuit-Against-Ripple-Wrapping-Up-Next-Week-Swirl.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="XRP Army Gleeful As Rumors Of SEC’s Lawsuit Against Ripple Wrapping Up Next Week Swirl" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/XRP-Army-Gleeful-As-Rumors-Of-SECs-Lawsuit-Against-Ripple-Wrapping-Up-Next-Week-Swirl.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/XRP-Army-Gleeful-As-Rumors-Of-SECs-Lawsuit-Against-Ripple-Wrapping-Up-Next-Week-Swirl-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/XRP-Army-Gleeful-As-Rumors-Of-SECs-Lawsuit-Against-Ripple-Wrapping-Up-Next-Week-Swirl-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/XRP-Army-Gleeful-As-Rumors-Of-SECs-Lawsuit-Against-Ripple-Wrapping-Up-Next-Week-Swirl-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>Just ahead of an <a href="https://zycrypto.com/what-a-ripple-sec-possible-settlement-could-mean-for-xrp-as-game-changing-ruling-nears/">expected ruling</a> in the ongoing court case between the SEC and Ripple, Stuart Alderoty, Chief Legal Officer at Ripple, said: &#8220;The Revak case exposes yet another SEC sleight of hand. Without a [common enterprise], it matters not whether [the fortunes of investors] are tied to the efforts of others. The Howey test is not [so easily satisfied].&#8221;</p>



<p>By broadly interpreting &#8220;common enterprise,&#8221; the SEC&#8217;s approach to regulating cryptocurrencies enables the agency to avoid tying the term to specific transactions and instead concentrate on the adjective &#8220;common.&#8221; The legal counsel for Ripple has recognized this and is contending that all that is required is a common interest in opposing the SEC&#8217;s attempt to extend the Howey test.</p>



<p>Australian Crypto Law commentator Bill Morgan added his views. &#8220;To put this and Stuart&#8217;s tweet in context, the starting point is to recognize that the SEC is trying to massively stretch the Howey test to cover crypto on the grounds the Court intended to be flexible.&#8221; He said in a tweet.</p>



<p>The SEC has cited evidence showing that Ripple boasted about the alignment of its interests with those who have XRP, but Ripple&#8217;s attorneys have refuted this claim by arguing that this is just a common interest using the example of gold. Nevertheless, other cryptocurrencies may be affected by the SEC&#8217;s attempt to reduce common enterprise to common interest.</p>



<p>The use of the Howey test by the SEC has been a source of controversy in the crypto industry, as the agency has attempted to apply the test to cryptocurrencies and initial coin offerings (ICOs). As a result, many in the industry have argued that the test does not apply to crypto and that the SEC has been overreaching in its attempts to regulate the space.</p>



<p>The decision in Revak raises the bar for the SEC to establish the existence of a common enterprise, which is considered a victory for those who disagree with the agency&#8217;s expansive interpretation of the Howey test. However, it also emphasizes the necessity of a more sophisticated strategy for regulating the cryptocurrency market, one that takes into consideration the unique features of cryptocurrencies and ICOs.</p>



<p>The SEC vs Ripple case is ongoing, and a ruling from district judge Analisa Torress is expected anytime now.</p>



<p>The SEC alleges that Ripple raised $1.3 billion by selling XRP as an unregistered security. Ripple denies the allegations and argues that XRP is not a security. The <a href="https://zycrypto.com/how-the-outcome-of-sec-v-ripple-case-could-shape-crypto-markets-as-xrp-army-eagerly-awaits-verdict/">case outcome</a> could significantly impact the cryptocurrency industry, as it could clarify the regulatory status of cryptocurrencies.</p>



<p>At the time of writing, XRP was traded at $0.42, up 0.45% in the past 24 hours, according to data from CoinMarketCap.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/xrp-lawsuit-sees-new-twists-and-turns-as-ripples-counsel-exposes-secs-slippery-slope-in-crypto-regulation/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Congress House Committees Deliberate On Innovation And Regulation Of Digital Assets In The U.S.</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/congress-house-committees-deliberate-on-innovation-and-regulation-of-digital-assets-in-the-u-s/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/congress-house-committees-deliberate-on-innovation-and-regulation-of-digital-assets-in-the-u-s/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Isa Nsereko]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 12:37:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=80887</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Industry-Leaders-Upbeat-as-EU-Parliament-Passes-Much-Anticipated-MiCA-Regulation.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Industry Leaders Upbeat as EU Parliament Passes Much-Anticipated MiCA Regulation" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Industry-Leaders-Upbeat-as-EU-Parliament-Passes-Much-Anticipated-MiCA-Regulation.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Industry-Leaders-Upbeat-as-EU-Parliament-Passes-Much-Anticipated-MiCA-Regulation-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Industry-Leaders-Upbeat-as-EU-Parliament-Passes-Much-Anticipated-MiCA-Regulation-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Industry-Leaders-Upbeat-as-EU-Parliament-Passes-Much-Anticipated-MiCA-Regulation-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>In a May 9, 2023 letter to the United States House Appropriations Committee, the U.S. House Financial Services Committee Chairman Patrick McHenry outlined the Committee Republicans’ priorities for fiscal year (FY) 2024 appropriations. Among the priorities listed is nurturing innovation for digital assets and blockchain technology in the United States (U.S.). In his letter, McHenry [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Industry-Leaders-Upbeat-as-EU-Parliament-Passes-Much-Anticipated-MiCA-Regulation.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Industry Leaders Upbeat as EU Parliament Passes Much-Anticipated MiCA Regulation" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Industry-Leaders-Upbeat-as-EU-Parliament-Passes-Much-Anticipated-MiCA-Regulation.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Industry-Leaders-Upbeat-as-EU-Parliament-Passes-Much-Anticipated-MiCA-Regulation-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Industry-Leaders-Upbeat-as-EU-Parliament-Passes-Much-Anticipated-MiCA-Regulation-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Industry-Leaders-Upbeat-as-EU-Parliament-Passes-Much-Anticipated-MiCA-Regulation-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>In a May 9, 2023 letter to the United States House Appropriations Committee, the U.S. House Financial Services Committee Chairman Patrick McHenry outlined the Committee Republicans’ priorities for fiscal year (FY) 2024 appropriations. Among the priorities listed is nurturing innovation for digital assets and blockchain technology in the United States (U.S.).</p>



<p>In his letter, McHenry requested the House Appropriations Committee to prevent the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) from continuing to regulate by enforcement. McHenry said that establishing clear rules for all players will ensure that innovation remains within the United States.</p>



<p>McHenry requested the Committee to prevent a budget increase for the SEC Enforcement Division. He also requested the House Appropriations Committee to prohibit funding for the SEC’s Staff Accounting Bulletin 121, which precludes banking organizations from serving clients seeking digital asset safeguarding services. </p>



<p>McHenry further called upon the House Appropriations Committee to prohibit funding for enforcing the custody rule. The custody rule requires investment advisers to hold client assets only with “qualified custodians”, such as a bank, broker-dealer, or futures commission merchant. McHenry said that the proposed custody rule would limit the number of qualified crypto custodians and hence offer less consumer protection.</p>



<p>On May 10, 2023, the House Financial Services Subcommittee on Digital Assets, Financial Technology &amp; Inclusion held a joint hearing with the House Agriculture Committee’s Subcommittee on Commodity Markets, Digital Assets, and Rural Development. The Committees discussed measuring regulatory gaps in the digital asset markets.</p>



<p>In his remarks, Chairman French Hill pointed out the need to provide a functional framework for digital assets in the U.S. Hill said that failure would result in digital asset frameworks developing offshore rather than in a regulated U.S. environment.&nbsp;</p>



<p>Hill acknowledged that there is no workable framework by the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) or the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) to regulate digital asset issuers and intermediaries. He called upon both federal agencies to work with the House Committees to develop digital asset legislation.</p>



<p>“That’s why we’re here today. No one here is claiming that crypto should be exempt from the rules or that we should create an entirely new regime for it”, Hill said.</p>



<p>Hill said that the goal is to bring consumer protections seen in the current financial regulatory structure to digital asset-related activities and intermediaries.&nbsp;</p>



<p>Hill stated that the decisions taken in Congress this year will determine how the digital asset ecosystem will develop in the U.S.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/congress-house-committees-deliberate-on-innovation-and-regulation-of-digital-assets-in-the-u-s/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ether Falls Silent As Ethereum Suffers 2 Network Disruptions Within 24 Hours</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/ether-falls-silent-as-ethereum-suffers-2-network-disruptions-within-24-hours/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/ether-falls-silent-as-ethereum-suffers-2-network-disruptions-within-24-hours/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aaron Feuerstein]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 12:19:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=80885</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Vitalik-Buterin-Uncovers-‘Missing-Link-For-Creating-Transaction-Privacy-on-Ethereum.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Vitalik Buterin Uncovers ‘Missing Link’ For Creating Transaction Privacy on Ethereum" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Vitalik-Buterin-Uncovers-‘Missing-Link-For-Creating-Transaction-Privacy-on-Ethereum.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Vitalik-Buterin-Uncovers-‘Missing-Link-For-Creating-Transaction-Privacy-on-Ethereum-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Vitalik-Buterin-Uncovers-‘Missing-Link-For-Creating-Transaction-Privacy-on-Ethereum-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Vitalik-Buterin-Uncovers-‘Missing-Link-For-Creating-Transaction-Privacy-on-Ethereum-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>The second-largest cryptocurrency platform in the world, the Ethereum network, experienced two failures in the span of just 24 hours, severely disrupting its users.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Vitalik-Buterin-Uncovers-‘Missing-Link-For-Creating-Transaction-Privacy-on-Ethereum.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Vitalik Buterin Uncovers ‘Missing Link’ For Creating Transaction Privacy on Ethereum" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Vitalik-Buterin-Uncovers-‘Missing-Link-For-Creating-Transaction-Privacy-on-Ethereum.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Vitalik-Buterin-Uncovers-‘Missing-Link-For-Creating-Transaction-Privacy-on-Ethereum-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Vitalik-Buterin-Uncovers-‘Missing-Link-For-Creating-Transaction-Privacy-on-Ethereum-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Vitalik-Buterin-Uncovers-‘Missing-Link-For-Creating-Transaction-Privacy-on-Ethereum-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>The second-largest cryptocurrency platform in the world, the <a href="https://zycrypto.com/ethereum-whale-population-sinks-post-shapella-what-does-it-mean-for-long-term-eth-holders/">Ethereum network</a>, experienced two failures in the span of just 24 hours, severely disrupting its users. The platform&#8217;s stability was scrutinised after the first outage on May 12, when the network failed to complete transactions for 25 minutes. The second outage, which happened the next day, lasted for roughly 45 minutes and caused a sizable lag in transaction processing.</p>



<p>Apparently, a flaw in the Ethereum blockchain stopped nodes from executing transactions, which led to the first downtime. Due to the network&#8217;s decentralized architecture, which allowed nodes to continue running independently of one another, the network was able to escape a full-blown outage.</p>



<p>The second outage was caused by a problem with the Ethereum software&#8217;s transaction finality mechanism. In response to these outages, the Ethereum development team quickly released a patch to fix the transaction finality issue. Ethereum developer Superphiz stated on Twitter:</p>



<p><em>&#8220;No transactions were halted. The network continued as expected. While the chain did not halt, this is more technical, finalization wasn&#8217;t reached. Finalization is a novel concept in Ethereum that prevents chain re-orgs. This had zero impact on chain activity.&#8221;</em></p>



<p>Although the root cause is still unknown, Superphiz stated that a lack of diverse clientele may have contributed to the problem. In addition, he claimed that because no client had a supermajority, the blockchain avoided forking.</p>



<p>The recent outages highlight decentralized networks like Ethereum face challenges in maintaining stability and reliability. While the decentralized architecture of the network makes it more resistant to attacks and censorship, it also makes it more vulnerable to bugs and other technical issues.</p>



<p>Despite these challenges, Ethereum remains a key player in the cryptocurrency ecosystem, with a market capitalization of over $220 billion and a wide range of applications, including decentralized finance (DeFi), non-fungible tokens (NFTs), and more.</p>



<p>Looking ahead, the Ethereum development team is working on several upgrades to the platform, including cheaper transactions, extra security, better user experience and future-proofing.</p>



<p>In conclusion, the recent outages on the Ethereum network serve as a reminder of the importance of maintaining a robust and reliable infrastructure for decentralized systems. While the Ethereum development team has taken steps to address these issues, it will be crucial for the network to continue evolving and adapting to meet the needs of its users and the wider cryptocurrency community.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/ether-falls-silent-as-ethereum-suffers-2-network-disruptions-within-24-hours/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Regulation Key To Solutions Crypto Could Offer To The De-dollarization Debate</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/regulation-key-to-solutions-crypto-could-offer-to-the-de-dollarization-debate/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/regulation-key-to-solutions-crypto-could-offer-to-the-de-dollarization-debate/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Isa Nsereko]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 19:57:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=80878</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Regulation-Key-To-Solutions-Crypto-Could-Offer-To-The-De-dollarization-Debate.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Regulation Key To Solutions Crypto Could Offer To The De-dollarization Debate" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Regulation-Key-To-Solutions-Crypto-Could-Offer-To-The-De-dollarization-Debate.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Regulation-Key-To-Solutions-Crypto-Could-Offer-To-The-De-dollarization-Debate-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Regulation-Key-To-Solutions-Crypto-Could-Offer-To-The-De-dollarization-Debate-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Regulation-Key-To-Solutions-Crypto-Could-Offer-To-The-De-dollarization-Debate-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>The promotion of local currencies for trade and payments and the calls for an alternative international reserve currency less dependent on the US dollar are increasing.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Regulation-Key-To-Solutions-Crypto-Could-Offer-To-The-De-dollarization-Debate.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Regulation Key To Solutions Crypto Could Offer To The De-dollarization Debate" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Regulation-Key-To-Solutions-Crypto-Could-Offer-To-The-De-dollarization-Debate.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Regulation-Key-To-Solutions-Crypto-Could-Offer-To-The-De-dollarization-Debate-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Regulation-Key-To-Solutions-Crypto-Could-Offer-To-The-De-dollarization-Debate-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Regulation-Key-To-Solutions-Crypto-Could-Offer-To-The-De-dollarization-Debate-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>During the 42nd Association of Southeast Asian Nations (ASEAN) summit in Labuan Bajo, Indonesia, from 10-11 May 2023, the ASEAN leaders committed to promoting the use of local currencies to deepen regional financial integration and strengthen financial stability in the region.</p>



<p>Per the Chairman’s statement, the 42nd ASEAN summit adopted the “Declaration on Advancing Regional Payment Connectivity and Promoting Local Currency Transaction” to foster bilateral and multilateral economic integration and enable more affordable cross-border payments across the region.</p>



<p>The promotion of local currencies for trade and payments and the calls for an alternative international reserve currency less dependent on the US dollar are increasing. The recent wave of interest rate hikes by the Federal Reserve (Fed) to fight inflation has led to other central banks raising interest rates to stem capital outflows and depreciation of their currencies.</p>



<p>The emerging markets of Brazil, Russia, India, China, and South Africa (BRICS) are reported to be increasing the use of their currencies in trade. They are also exploring an international reserve currency less dependent on the US dollar. Similarly, other economies in the Middle East, North Africa, and South America are considering their options.</p>



<p>Does the de-dollarization debate provide an opportunity for cryptocurrencies? Looking at the economies exploring de-dollarization poses several questions and issues that must be assessed.</p>



<p>Do these economies give up their national currencies for one another currency, or do they adopt a new common currency? Could these economies consider adopting private money as a cryptocurrency or a stablecoin or opt for a Central Bank Digital Currency (CBDC)?</p>



<p>One thing for sure is that some of the economies exploring de-dollarisation belong to different regional blocs. Pursuing regional bloc economic objectives could conflict with adopting a different currency outside the bloc. Other challenges lie within the agreement, the management, and the distribution of the adopted currency.</p>



<p>Another issue is crypto regulation. The regional blocs are at different levels of developing crypto regulatory frameworks. Some of the economies only have country-specific positions regarding crypto legislation. Adopting a cryptocurrency, stablecoin, or CBDC whilst having different or no crypto legislation would pose challenges for these economies in pursuing a de-dollarisation strategy.</p>



<p>It appears that there are no outright or easy solutions to de-dollarisation. The formulation of global cryptocurrency frameworks is one of the critical issues that must be addressed if cryptocurrencies offer any alternatives to de-dollarisation.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/regulation-key-to-solutions-crypto-could-offer-to-the-de-dollarization-debate/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>US Senators Reintroduce Bill To Investigate Bitcoin Adoption In El Salvador</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/us-senators-reintroduce-bill-to-investigate-bitcoin-adoption-in-el-salvador/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/us-senators-reintroduce-bill-to-investigate-bitcoin-adoption-in-el-salvador/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Marco Tulio]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 17:35:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Featured]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[El Salvador]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USA]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=80872</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/US-Senators-Reintroduce-Bill-To-Investigate-Bitcoin-Adoption-In-El-Salvador.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="US Senators Reintroduce Bill To Investigate Bitcoin Adoption In El Salvador" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/US-Senators-Reintroduce-Bill-To-Investigate-Bitcoin-Adoption-In-El-Salvador.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/US-Senators-Reintroduce-Bill-To-Investigate-Bitcoin-Adoption-In-El-Salvador-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/US-Senators-Reintroduce-Bill-To-Investigate-Bitcoin-Adoption-In-El-Salvador-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/US-Senators-Reintroduce-Bill-To-Investigate-Bitcoin-Adoption-In-El-Salvador-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>On May 11, Senators Bob Menendez and Jim Risch reintroduced the Accountability for Cryptocurrency in El Salvador (ACES) Act in the United States Senate.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/US-Senators-Reintroduce-Bill-To-Investigate-Bitcoin-Adoption-In-El-Salvador.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="US Senators Reintroduce Bill To Investigate Bitcoin Adoption In El Salvador" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/US-Senators-Reintroduce-Bill-To-Investigate-Bitcoin-Adoption-In-El-Salvador.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/US-Senators-Reintroduce-Bill-To-Investigate-Bitcoin-Adoption-In-El-Salvador-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/US-Senators-Reintroduce-Bill-To-Investigate-Bitcoin-Adoption-In-El-Salvador-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/US-Senators-Reintroduce-Bill-To-Investigate-Bitcoin-Adoption-In-El-Salvador-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>On May 11, Senators Bob Menendez and Jim Risch reintroduced the Accountability for Cryptocurrency in El Salvador (ACES) Act in the United States Senate. The purpose of this act is to periodically oversee the process of Bitcoin adoption in the Latin American country.</p>



<p>According to the Senate&#8217;s <a href="https://www.foreign.senate.gov/press/rep/release/risch-menendez-reintroduce-legislation-to-mitigate-risks-of-el-salvadors-adoption-of-bitcoin">statement</a>, the bill aims to assess the impact of BTC on the economic stability and governance of the Central American country. It also seeks to analyze potential risks related to cybersecurity and malicious actors.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-legislation-demands-reports-on-bitcoin-s-use-and-impact-on-stability-and-remittances"><strong>Legislation demands reports on Bitcoin&#8217;s use and impact on stability and remittances</strong></h2>



<p>The reports must include detailed information about the flow of cryptocurrency remittances sent from the United States to El Salvador. This is to understand the risks associated with using BTC for illicit activities.</p>



<p>The bill was initially <a href="https://zycrypto.com/us-senate-on-the-verge-of-passing-new-legislation-to-closely-monitor-the-risks-associated-with-el-salvadors-bitcoin-adoption/">introduced</a> in Congress in February 2022 by Senators Jim Risch, Menendez, and Cassidy. Risch <a href="https://www.foreign.senate.gov/press/rep/release/risch-menendez-cassidy-introduce-legislation-to-mitigate-risks-of-el-salvadors-adoption-of-bitcoin">stated</a> that adopting Bitcoin as a legal tender in El Salvador &#8220;raises significant concerns about the economic stability and financial integrity of a vulnerable U.S. trading partner in Central America.&#8221;</p>



<p>On the other hand, Cassidy emphasized that if the U.S. wants to combat money laundering, it &#8220;must tackle this issue head-on.&#8221; However, it seems Congress does not share the senators&#8217; opinion, as the bill has not been discussed again until now.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>The proposed plan aims to mitigate potential risks to the U.S. financial system</strong></h2>



<p>One year after introducing the bill and not receiving a favourable response, Senator Risch continues to assert that the use of cryptocurrencies &#8220;as legal tender could weaken economic and financial stability and empower malign actors.&#8221;</p>



<p>Similarly, Risch emphasized that the interests of the U.S. are to ensure prosperity and economic transparency in Central America, gaining a clearer understanding of how the adoption of BTC can affect the financial and economic stability of El Salvador.</p>



<p>However, considering the geopolitical and macroeconomic scenario of the U.S., it could be said that the senators want to study the impact of BTC in El Salvador to understand better how implementing cryptocurrencies as legal tender can affect the country&#8217;s financial stability.</p>



<p>Perhaps, having access to such data could help them comprehend the potential advantages and disadvantages of implementing a CBDC based on the dollar.</p>



<p>Currently, the President of El Salvador, <a href="https://zycrypto.com/if-el-salvador-succeeds-every-country-will-follow-asserts-president-bukele-as-bitcoins-price-soars/">Nayib Bukele</a>, has not commented on the bill&#8217;s reintroduction. This might be because he is more focused on continuing to drive <a href="https://zycrypto.com/nayib-bukele-signs-bill-to-eliminate-technology-taxes-in-el-salvador/">technological innovations</a> and the adoption of cryptocurrencies rather than responding to politicians from a country with no jurisdiction over his own.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/us-senators-reintroduce-bill-to-investigate-bitcoin-adoption-in-el-salvador/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Automated Market Makers Finally Coming To XRPL — Why This Feature Could Be Super Bullish For &#8216;$1 XRP Price&#8217;</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/automated-market-makers-finally-coming-to-xrpl-why-this-feature-could-be-super-bullish-for-1-xrp-price/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/automated-market-makers-finally-coming-to-xrpl-why-this-feature-could-be-super-bullish-for-1-xrp-price/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aaron Feuerstein]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 May 2023 10:10:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=80845</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Automated-Market-Makers-Finally-Coming-To-XRPL-—-Why-This-Feature-Could-Be-Super-Bullish-For-XRP-Price.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Automated Market Makers Finally Coming To XRPL — Why This Feature Could Be Super Bullish For XRP Price" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Automated-Market-Makers-Finally-Coming-To-XRPL-—-Why-This-Feature-Could-Be-Super-Bullish-For-XRP-Price.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Automated-Market-Makers-Finally-Coming-To-XRPL-—-Why-This-Feature-Could-Be-Super-Bullish-For-XRP-Price-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Automated-Market-Makers-Finally-Coming-To-XRPL-—-Why-This-Feature-Could-Be-Super-Bullish-For-XRP-Price-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Automated-Market-Makers-Finally-Coming-To-XRPL-—-Why-This-Feature-Could-Be-Super-Bullish-For-XRP-Price-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>A brief explanation of AMM, their strength and limitations and how investors could benefit from this, plus what it may mean for XRP price long-term.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Automated-Market-Makers-Finally-Coming-To-XRPL-—-Why-This-Feature-Could-Be-Super-Bullish-For-XRP-Price.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Automated Market Makers Finally Coming To XRPL — Why This Feature Could Be Super Bullish For XRP Price" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Automated-Market-Makers-Finally-Coming-To-XRPL-—-Why-This-Feature-Could-Be-Super-Bullish-For-XRP-Price.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Automated-Market-Makers-Finally-Coming-To-XRPL-—-Why-This-Feature-Could-Be-Super-Bullish-For-XRP-Price-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Automated-Market-Makers-Finally-Coming-To-XRPL-—-Why-This-Feature-Could-Be-Super-Bullish-For-XRP-Price-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Automated-Market-Makers-Finally-Coming-To-XRPL-—-Why-This-Feature-Could-Be-Super-Bullish-For-XRP-Price-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p><em>A brief explanation of AMM, their strength and limitations, how users could benefit from this, and what it may mean for XRP price long-term.</em></p>



<p>Users can trade cryptocurrencies and other assets using Automated Market Makers (AMMs), a decentralised exchange (DEX) mechanism, without using conventional order books or a centralised entity to arrange trades. Instead, AMMs create a pool of tokens with varying levels of liquidity to establish asset prices and facilitate trades.</p>



<p>The liquidity pool calculates the asset price based on the ratio of tokens in the pool, receives tokens from users who want to trade and uses those tokens to fund the trade. To maintain a stable price for the asset being traded and to encourage the addition of more liquidity to the pool, the AMM then assesses a fee for the transaction, which is added to the liquidity pool.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-why-amm-is-a-significant-development-for-xrp-and-xrp-ledger"><strong>Why AMM is a significant development for XRP and XRP Ledger</strong></h2>



<p>First, AMMs will give XRP holders a more decentralised means to trade their tokens because XRP is a well-known cryptocurrency. AMMs make trading easier and may provide more XRP liquidity, which is advantageous for traders and investors.</p>



<p>Second, including AMMs in XRP will facilitate developers&#8217; creation of decentralised apps (dApps) on the <a href="https://zycrypto.com/colombian-government-launches-national-land-registry-on-xrp-ledger-for-over-50-million-people/">XRP Ledger</a>. Developers can use the liquidity pools offered by the AMM to construct new dApps that are more effective and economical with the addition of AMMs.</p>



<p>Thirdly, XRP&#8217;s acceptance as a cryptocurrency may increase with the arrival of AMMs. Users may be more likely to utilise XRP and other cryptocurrencies that enable AMMs as more users get familiar with AMMs. This can result in higher XRP prices and increased demand.</p>



<p>Last but not least, the inclusion of AMMs in XRP can enhance the XRP Ledger&#8217;s overall decentralised nature. By utilising AMMs, XRP might lessen its dependency on centralised exchanges, susceptible to security breaches and cyberattacks. AMMs, on the other hand, enable a more decentralised and trustless method of trading XRP.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Strengths and weakness of AMMs</strong></h2>



<p>Strengths of AMMs include greater decentralization, greater liquidity, simplicity and flexibility, as well as being cost-effective.</p>



<p>Some limitations include impermanent loss, price slippage, loss of funds due to volatility and dependency on liquidity.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Will it affect the XRP price?</strong></h2>



<p>Given that the long-term <a href="https://zycrypto.com/as-ripple-vs-sec-verdict-nears-1-xrp-price-looks-nigh-following-launch-of-ripples-liquidity-hub/">price of XRP</a> is dependent on several variables, including market circumstances, adoption rates, and regulatory changes, it is challenging to make a firm prediction about it. On the other hand, the inclusion of AMMs in XRP might have a favourable effect on its long-term price to $1.</p>



<p>Greater liquidity for XRP can be provided through AMMs, which could enhance demand and possibly drive up prices. Additionally, the introduction of AMMs on XRP may contribute to greater decentralisation and security for the XRP Ledger overall, raising XRP&#8217;s perceived value.</p>



<p>Additionally, the inclusion of AMMs would make it simpler for programmers to create decentralised applications on the XRP Ledger, which might enhance XRP adoption and possibly place a higher demand on XRP.</p>



<p>In conclusion, while AMMs provide several advantages, some drawbacks must be considered. Before employing AMMs for trading or investing, traders and investors should carefully assess the benefits and drawbacks of doing so and their level of risk tolerance.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/automated-market-makers-finally-coming-to-xrpl-why-this-feature-could-be-super-bullish-for-1-xrp-price/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>XRP Holders&#8217; Attorney Supports Chamber&#8217;s Allegations of SEC&#8217;s Overreach in Digital Asset Industry</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/xrp-holders-attorney-supports-chambers-allegations-of-secs-overreach-in-digital-asset-industry/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/xrp-holders-attorney-supports-chambers-allegations-of-secs-overreach-in-digital-asset-industry/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Marco Tulio]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 21:08:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=80842</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/SEC-Assault-On-Ripple-Hasnt-Negatively-Impacted-XRP-Price-—-Billionaire-Mike-Novogratz.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="SEC Assault On Ripple Hasn’t Negatively Impacted XRP Price — Billionaire Mike Novogratz" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/SEC-Assault-On-Ripple-Hasnt-Negatively-Impacted-XRP-Price-—-Billionaire-Mike-Novogratz.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/SEC-Assault-On-Ripple-Hasnt-Negatively-Impacted-XRP-Price-—-Billionaire-Mike-Novogratz-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/SEC-Assault-On-Ripple-Hasnt-Negatively-Impacted-XRP-Price-—-Billionaire-Mike-Novogratz-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/SEC-Assault-On-Ripple-Hasnt-Negatively-Impacted-XRP-Price-—-Billionaire-Mike-Novogratz-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>On May 11, John Deaton, the attorney and legal representative of XRP holders in the collective lawsuit against the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), supported the...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/SEC-Assault-On-Ripple-Hasnt-Negatively-Impacted-XRP-Price-—-Billionaire-Mike-Novogratz.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="SEC Assault On Ripple Hasn’t Negatively Impacted XRP Price — Billionaire Mike Novogratz" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/SEC-Assault-On-Ripple-Hasnt-Negatively-Impacted-XRP-Price-—-Billionaire-Mike-Novogratz.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/SEC-Assault-On-Ripple-Hasnt-Negatively-Impacted-XRP-Price-—-Billionaire-Mike-Novogratz-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/SEC-Assault-On-Ripple-Hasnt-Negatively-Impacted-XRP-Price-—-Billionaire-Mike-Novogratz-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/SEC-Assault-On-Ripple-Hasnt-Negatively-Impacted-XRP-Price-—-Billionaire-Mike-Novogratz-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>On May 11, John Deaton, the attorney and legal representative of XRP holders in the collective lawsuit against the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), supported the report presented by the U.S. Chamber of Commerce, a major business interest group, opposing the country&#8217;s current regulatory environment driven by the SEC.</p>



<p>According to the Chamber of Commerce, the SEC is misusing its powers, destabilizing the regulatory environment of cryptocurrencies and causing significant economic harm to Coinbase and the broader business community.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-xrp-holders-attorney-endorses-chamber-s-report-denouncing-sec-s-overreach"><strong>XRP holders&#8217; attorney endorses Chamber&#8217;s report, denouncing SEC&#8217;s overreach</strong></h2>



<p>XRP holders&#8217; attorney, Deaton, stated that the Chamber of Commerce was not the first to denounce the SEC&#8217;s overreach in the uncertain regulatory environment. For over two years, XRP holders have pointed out that the SEC won&#8217;t stop after its attack on Ripple.</p>



<p><em>&#8220;XRP holders were the first to call out the SEC&#8217;s gross overreach, but clearly, we aren&#8217;t the last. Over two years ago, we warned that this wouldn&#8217;t end with XRP. Even when the government&#8217;s overreach targets a project you dislike, you must stand against it.&#8221;</em></p>



<p>Stuart Alderoty, Ripple&#8217;s Chief Legal Officer with over 35 years of legal experience in regulatory affairs and complex litigation, noted that the current uncertain regulatory environment is not just a crypto problem but a &#8220;We The People&#8221; problem. The regulations affect not only the crypto ecosystem but all individuals and businesses involved.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">For this SEC Chair the judicial process is a weapon to be wielded and Congressional oversight is a game of hide and seek. This isn’t a crypto problem, this is a “We The People” problem.</p>&mdash; Stuart Alderoty (@s_alderoty) <a href="https://twitter.com/s_alderoty/status/1657016970267484168?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">May 12, 2023</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Chamber&#8217;s submission could impact crypto regulation</strong></h2>



<p>The Chamber of Commerce made three compelling arguments against the SEC that could add more credibility to the companies and proponents fighting <a href="https://zycrypto.com/sec-action-against-coinbase-triggers-ballistic-reaction-from-crypto-community/">legal battles</a> against the SEC.</p>



<p>Firstly, they indicated that regulatory uncertainty stifles innovation in the United States. Secondly, the SEC is destabilizing the regulatory environment of cryptocurrencies. And lastly, the SEC is violating due process and the right to fair notification.</p>



<p>The last point relates explicitly to <a href="https://zycrypto.com/coinbase-goes-offensive-against-the-sec-with-lawsuit-targeted-at-regulatory-clarity/">Coinbase&#8217;s</a> lack of response from the SEC when asked to explain which assets offered on its platform are considered securities. The SEC, so far, has been unwilling or unable to respond, even after receiving a court order from a U.S. court to address Coinbase&#8217;s legal action.</p>



<p>As recently <a href="https://zycrypto.com/coinbase-v-sec-chamber-of-digital-commerce-weighs-in-argues-regulator-is-causing-substantial-economic-harm/">reported</a> by ZyCrypto, Coinbase is receiving support from various entities like the Chamber of Digital Commerce (CDC), the world&#8217;s largest blockchain advocacy and trade group, in its public battle against the SEC.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/xrp-holders-attorney-supports-chambers-allegations-of-secs-overreach-in-digital-asset-industry/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cardano Releases First Mainnet-Compatible Version Of Hydra-Node &#8211; ADA Looks To Ride the Wave to Major Gains</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/cardano-releases-first-mainnet-compatible-version-of-hydra-node-ada-looks-to-ride-the-wave-to-major-gains/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/cardano-releases-first-mainnet-compatible-version-of-hydra-node-ada-looks-to-ride-the-wave-to-major-gains/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jared Kirui]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 18:04:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADAUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=80827</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Cardano-Holders-Bullish-On-Upcoming-Vasil-Hardfork-As-ADA-Leads-Crypto-Majors-After-A-29-Jump.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Cardano Holders Bullish On Upcoming Vasil Hardfork As ADA Leads Crypto Majors After A 29% Jump" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Cardano-Holders-Bullish-On-Upcoming-Vasil-Hardfork-As-ADA-Leads-Crypto-Majors-After-A-29-Jump.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Cardano-Holders-Bullish-On-Upcoming-Vasil-Hardfork-As-ADA-Leads-Crypto-Majors-After-A-29-Jump-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Cardano-Holders-Bullish-On-Upcoming-Vasil-Hardfork-As-ADA-Leads-Crypto-Majors-After-A-29-Jump-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Cardano-Holders-Bullish-On-Upcoming-Vasil-Hardfork-As-ADA-Leads-Crypto-Majors-After-A-29-Jump-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>Cardano’s node Hydra Head, a collection of layer-2 protocols designed to boost the scalability of Cardano, has gone live on the mainnet, the blockchain developers announced Thursday.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Cardano-Holders-Bullish-On-Upcoming-Vasil-Hardfork-As-ADA-Leads-Crypto-Majors-After-A-29-Jump.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Cardano Holders Bullish On Upcoming Vasil Hardfork As ADA Leads Crypto Majors After A 29% Jump" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Cardano-Holders-Bullish-On-Upcoming-Vasil-Hardfork-As-ADA-Leads-Crypto-Majors-After-A-29-Jump.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Cardano-Holders-Bullish-On-Upcoming-Vasil-Hardfork-As-ADA-Leads-Crypto-Majors-After-A-29-Jump-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Cardano-Holders-Bullish-On-Upcoming-Vasil-Hardfork-As-ADA-Leads-Crypto-Majors-After-A-29-Jump-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Cardano-Holders-Bullish-On-Upcoming-Vasil-Hardfork-As-ADA-Leads-Crypto-Majors-After-A-29-Jump-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<ul>
<li>The scaling tool is part of a suite of products in Cardano for DeFi.</li>



<li>It is an off-chain ‘mini ledger’ shared between small groups of participants.</li>
</ul>



<p>Cardano’s node <a href="https://zycrypto.com/cardano-primed-for-meteoric-surge-as-first-hydra-head-opens-on-mainnet/">Hydra Head</a>, a collection of layer-2 protocols designed to boost the scalability of Cardano, has gone live on the mainnet, the blockchain developers announced Thursday.</p>



<p>Hydra Heads allow developers to integrate complex decentralized finance (DeFi) applications on Cardano &#8211; a part of the DeFi-upgrades released on the network this year.</p>



<p>Sebastian Nagel, one of the developers, shared the&nbsp;technical document&nbsp;describing how Hydra Head version 0.10.0 works: an off-chain ‘mini-ledger’ shared among a small group of users, which increases the transaction speeds and reduces fees.</p>



<p>‘‘After demonstrating Hydra Heads on the Cardano mainnet in recent monthly review sessions, we have released the first mainnet compatible version of Hydra-node today,’’ Nagel said in a series of tweets.</p>



<p>The first version of Hydra Head was released at the start of the month. With the successful deployment on the mainnet, Cardano developers have updated the API to accommodate the first batch of requests, preparing Hydra for real-world use cases. The next version, 0.11.0, is reportedly underway.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-cardano-s-series-of-defi-upgrades-unveiled-this-year"><strong>Cardano’s Series of DeFi Upgrades Unveiled This Year</strong></h2>



<p>This year, Cardano has focused on releasing upgrades targeting DeFi. In January, the network announced the launch of its decentralized stablecoin, <a href="https://zycrypto.com/cardano-based-djed-stablecoin-attracts-over-30m-ada-in-the-first-week-since-launch/">Djed</a>. It was followed by Lace Wallet, a platform that allows Cardano users to stake native ADA tokens.</p>



<p><a href="https://zycrypto.com/charles-hoskinson-to-test-cardanos-new-wallet-with-1000000-worth-of-ada-experiment/">Lace</a> is similar to MetaMask, a browser-built wallet where users can access and operate Cardano-based decentralized applications, sending and receiving ADA, non-fungible tokens, and other digital assets. With Lace, multiple assets can be transferred bundled as one transaction and charged a single fee, significantly saving costs.</p>



<p>Besides, Cardano’s Ethereum Virtual Machine layer, Milkomeda, announced last March that it was integrating a feature enabling every Cardano user to access EVM contracts from Cardano wallets. EVM stores Ethereum accounts and smart contracts for deploying dApps.</p>



<p>The announcement of Hydra heads had caused an increase in the price of ADA by 2% at press time to $0.3652. But more importantly, as Cardano blockchain expands its capability for smart contracts and DeFi, experts project the price to rise even higher.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/cardano-releases-first-mainnet-compatible-version-of-hydra-node-ada-looks-to-ride-the-wave-to-major-gains/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Elon Musk Announces New Twitter CEO – What It Means for Cryptos</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/elon-musk-announces-new-twitter-ceo-what-it-means-for-cryptos/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/elon-musk-announces-new-twitter-ceo-what-it-means-for-cryptos/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jared Kirui]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 17:32:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elon Musk]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=80821</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/Could-A-Cardano-Bitcoin-and-DOGE-based-Twitter-Rival-By-Elon-Musk-and-Hoskinson-Be-The-Next-Big-Thing.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Could A Cardano, Bitcoin, and DOGE-based Twitter Rival By Elon Musk and Hoskinson Be The Next Big Thing?" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/Could-A-Cardano-Bitcoin-and-DOGE-based-Twitter-Rival-By-Elon-Musk-and-Hoskinson-Be-The-Next-Big-Thing.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/Could-A-Cardano-Bitcoin-and-DOGE-based-Twitter-Rival-By-Elon-Musk-and-Hoskinson-Be-The-Next-Big-Thing-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/Could-A-Cardano-Bitcoin-and-DOGE-based-Twitter-Rival-By-Elon-Musk-and-Hoskinson-Be-The-Next-Big-Thing-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/Could-A-Cardano-Bitcoin-and-DOGE-based-Twitter-Rival-By-Elon-Musk-and-Hoskinson-Be-The-Next-Big-Thing-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>According to a Thursday announcement, Elon Musk has picked a new chief executive officer several months after acquiring Twitter. Following this step, there are many speculations as to how the crypto space would be under the new boss. Musk did not identify his replacement in the announcement but said that the new executive, a woman, [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/Could-A-Cardano-Bitcoin-and-DOGE-based-Twitter-Rival-By-Elon-Musk-and-Hoskinson-Be-The-Next-Big-Thing.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Could A Cardano, Bitcoin, and DOGE-based Twitter Rival By Elon Musk and Hoskinson Be The Next Big Thing?" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/Could-A-Cardano-Bitcoin-and-DOGE-based-Twitter-Rival-By-Elon-Musk-and-Hoskinson-Be-The-Next-Big-Thing.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/Could-A-Cardano-Bitcoin-and-DOGE-based-Twitter-Rival-By-Elon-Musk-and-Hoskinson-Be-The-Next-Big-Thing-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/Could-A-Cardano-Bitcoin-and-DOGE-based-Twitter-Rival-By-Elon-Musk-and-Hoskinson-Be-The-Next-Big-Thing-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/Could-A-Cardano-Bitcoin-and-DOGE-based-Twitter-Rival-By-Elon-Musk-and-Hoskinson-Be-The-Next-Big-Thing-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<ul>
<li>Musk did not immediately reveal the identity of his replacement.</li>



<li>Major outlets have identified the new Twitter boss as Linda Yaccarino, NBCU’s global advertisement chief.</li>
</ul>



<p>According to a Thursday announcement, Elon Musk has picked a new chief executive officer several months after acquiring Twitter. Following this step, there are many speculations as to how the crypto space would be under the new boss.</p>



<p>Musk did not identify his replacement in the announcement but said that the new executive, a woman, would start the job in six weeks.</p>



<p>The Wall Street Journal was the first media house to take a stab at who the appointee could be, identifying her as Linda Yaccarino, the chairperson of global advertising and partnerships at NBCUniversal. On Friday, NBCUniversal affirmed that Yaccarino would leave the company ‘‘effective immediately.’’</p>



<p>Following the news, the crypto community is speculating what the new appointment means for the digital asset space, considering the vital role Twitter plays in the sector. As it stands, nothing seemingly connects Yaccarino to the industry.&nbsp;</p>



<p>However, there is optimism that Twitter&#8217;s ambition regarding digital assets will continue after Musk assumes the role of the chair and CTO at Twitter, which he disclosed in the announcement.</p>



<p>&#8220;Excited to announce that I&#8217;ve hired a new CEO for X/Twitter. She will be starting in 6 weeks. My role will transition to exec chair &amp; CTO,&#8221; Musk <a href="https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1656748197308674048?s=20">said</a>, adding that he would &#8221;oversee product, software, and sysops (systems operations.).&#8221;</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-a-change-to-the-crypto-space-dynamics"><strong>A Change to the Crypto Space Dynamics?</strong></h2>



<p>Musk&#8217;s move comes when Twitter has shifted focus to cryptocurrency, especially integrating digital asset payments into the platform. At the start of the year, the social network <a href="https://zycrypto.com/dogecoiners-cheer-as-elon-musk-charts-a-bullish-course-for-twitter-crypto-payments/">announced</a> it was creating systems permitting payment for fiat and cryptocurrencies. Dogecoin, Musk&#8217;s favourite meme token, surged after the announcement.</p>



<p>Twitter has also taken steps to boost the adoption of digital currencies, including a partnership with crypto and stocks brokerage firm, eToro, enabling users to trade digital assets. Besides, in April, the San Francisco-based company <a href="https://zycrypto.com/dogecoin-soars-over-25-after-elon-musk-replaces-twitters-logo-with-shiba-inu-image/">replaced</a> the Twitter logo with that of Dogecoin, resulting in a jump in DOGE prices.</p>



<p>However, the announcement of the new CEO has yet to significantly impact the price of DOGE, which changed hands for $0.07107 at press time, a difference of +0.32% in the past day.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/elon-musk-announces-new-twitter-ceo-what-it-means-for-cryptos/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Dips Below $26,500 Amid US Government BTC Sale Rumors</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/bitcoin-dips-below-26500-amid-us-government-btc-sale-rumors/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/bitcoin-dips-below-26500-amid-us-government-btc-sale-rumors/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Newton Gitonga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 17:13:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XBTUSD]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=80818</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/Should-You-Buy-The-Bitcoin-Dip_-Analysts-Weigh-In-On-Bear-Market.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Should You Buy The Bitcoin Dip? Analysts Weigh In On Bear Market" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/Should-You-Buy-The-Bitcoin-Dip_-Analysts-Weigh-In-On-Bear-Market.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/Should-You-Buy-The-Bitcoin-Dip_-Analysts-Weigh-In-On-Bear-Market-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/Should-You-Buy-The-Bitcoin-Dip_-Analysts-Weigh-In-On-Bear-Market-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/Should-You-Buy-The-Bitcoin-Dip_-Analysts-Weigh-In-On-Bear-Market-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>Bitcoin, the world's largest cryptocurrency by Market capitalization, has seen a significant dip in its value, dropping below the $26,500 mark amidst rumours of a US government sale of BTC.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/Should-You-Buy-The-Bitcoin-Dip_-Analysts-Weigh-In-On-Bear-Market.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Should You Buy The Bitcoin Dip? Analysts Weigh In On Bear Market" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/Should-You-Buy-The-Bitcoin-Dip_-Analysts-Weigh-In-On-Bear-Market.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/Should-You-Buy-The-Bitcoin-Dip_-Analysts-Weigh-In-On-Bear-Market-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/Should-You-Buy-The-Bitcoin-Dip_-Analysts-Weigh-In-On-Bear-Market-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/Should-You-Buy-The-Bitcoin-Dip_-Analysts-Weigh-In-On-Bear-Market-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>Bitcoin, the world&#8217;s largest cryptocurrency by Market capitalization, has seen a significant dip in its value, dropping below the $26,500 mark amidst rumours of a US government sale of BTC.</p>



<p>Bitcoin has plunged by over 10% in the past week, becoming its second-worst week since its price tapped a 10-month high of $30,000 last month. The latest dip comes amidst rumours that the US government plans to sell a large amount of Bitcoin from its reserves, potentially flooding the market and driving down prices even further.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="647" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-13-1024x647.png" alt="" class="wp-image-80819" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-13-1024x647.png 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-13-300x190.png 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-13-768x485.png 768w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-13-1536x971.png 1536w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-13-2048x1294.png 2048w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /><figcaption class="wp-element-caption">BTCUSD Chart by <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BTCUSD/">TradingView</a></figcaption></figure>



<p>As ZyCrypto <a href="https://zycrypto.com/40000-btc-from-us-government-seizures-in-motion-what-could-it-mean-for-bitcoin/">reported</a>, on March 14th, the US government reportedly sold 9,861 Bitcoin, worth approximately $215 million, seized from criminals involved in illegal activities on the Silk Road website. According to a court filing in April, the US government revealed it further plans to sell another 41,490 BTC in connection with Silk Road in four separate batches this year. The online marketplace facilitated illegal activities and was seized by law enforcement agencies in 2013.</p>



<p>This week has been enough to spook investors and send prices plummeting, with roughly $44 million in BTC being liquidated in the past 24 hours. Meanwhile, independent analysts and research firms refuted the sale claims, with CryptoQuant describing the rumours as “coordinated fake news.”</p>



<p>“<em>Coordinated FAKE NEWS about US government selling Bitcoins leads to second-largest long liquidations in 2023. Many accounts retweeted this news without any fact-checking, and as a result, we saw the second-largest long liquidations in 2023, with over $36M being liquidated within one hour,”</em> Cryptoquant tweeted on May 11.</p>



<p>Arkham, another onchain crypto analytics firm, also distanced itself from the FUD, labelling recent claims showing the said sales with alleged data from its website as false. </p>



<p><em>“Users on Arkham&#8217;s platform can manually add and remove labels for their own private instances. Our platform provides Arkham Entities that can be edited by users in their own sessions. These do not reflect associations with wallets made by the Arkham Team.”</em></p>



<p>That said, while the US government&#8217;s potential sale of Bitcoin has caused a ripple effect in the market, investors should take the news with a grain of salt, considering it is not the first time rumours of the US government selling BTC have circulated.</p>



<p>At press time, the cryptocurrency was trading at $26,301, down 3.30% in the past 24 hours, as per CoinMarketCap data.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/bitcoin-dips-below-26500-amid-us-government-btc-sale-rumors/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
