<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>News Archives &#8902; ZyCrypto</title>
	<atom:link href="https://zycrypto.com/category/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://zycrypto.com/category/news/</link>
	<description>ZyCrypto Is A Cryptocurrency News Media, Focusing On Daily News, Expert Opinions, Analysis, Reviews, And So Much More.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 21:21:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/cropped-ZyCrypto-Site-Logo-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News Archives &#8902; ZyCrypto</title>
	<link>https://zycrypto.com/category/news/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>ARK Invest Gains Edge In Spot Bitcoin ETF Race With Epic Surveillance Sharing Maneuver</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/ark-invest-gains-edge-in-spot-bitcoin-etf-race-with-epic-surveillance-sharing-maneuver/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/ark-invest-gains-edge-in-spot-bitcoin-etf-race-with-epic-surveillance-sharing-maneuver/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Brenda Ngari]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 21:20:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ark Invest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XBTUSD]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=82455</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/Mark-Cuban-Says-He-Wont-Invest-In-Bitcoin-Futures-ETFs.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Mark Cuban Says He Won&#039;t Invest In Bitcoin Futures ETFs" decoding="async" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/Mark-Cuban-Says-He-Wont-Invest-In-Bitcoin-Futures-ETFs.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/Mark-Cuban-Says-He-Wont-Invest-In-Bitcoin-Futures-ETFs-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/Mark-Cuban-Says-He-Wont-Invest-In-Bitcoin-Futures-ETFs-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/Mark-Cuban-Says-He-Wont-Invest-In-Bitcoin-Futures-ETFs-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>Cathie Wood's ARK Invest has made a strategic move that potentially gives it an edge in the race for a spot bitcoin exchange-traded fund in the U.S.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/Mark-Cuban-Says-He-Wont-Invest-In-Bitcoin-Futures-ETFs.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Mark Cuban Says He Won&#039;t Invest In Bitcoin Futures ETFs" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/Mark-Cuban-Says-He-Wont-Invest-In-Bitcoin-Futures-ETFs.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/Mark-Cuban-Says-He-Wont-Invest-In-Bitcoin-Futures-ETFs-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/Mark-Cuban-Says-He-Wont-Invest-In-Bitcoin-Futures-ETFs-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/Mark-Cuban-Says-He-Wont-Invest-In-Bitcoin-Futures-ETFs-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>Cathie Wood&#8217;s ARK Invest has made a strategic move that potentially gives it an edge in the race for a spot bitcoin exchange-traded fund in the U.S. The firm has amended its application to include a surveillance-sharing agreement, similar to BlackRock’s recent filing.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-ark-amends-spot-etf-filing-to-include-blackrock-like-feature"><strong>ARK Amends Spot ETF Filing To Include BlackRock-Like Feature</strong></h2>



<p>ARK Invest has updated its Bitcoin ETF application with the SEC.</p>



<p>The <a href="https://cdn.cboe.com/resources/regulation/rule_filings/pending/2023/SR-CboeBZX-2023-028-Amendment-No-1.pdf">update </a>includes a surveillance sharing agreement with the Cboe BZX Exchange — on which the ETF would be listed —  and a U.S.-based crypto exchange, most “likely Coinbase,” <a href="https://twitter.com/EricBalchunas/status/1674055780058771463">according to</a> Bloomberg ETF analyst Eric Balchunas.</p>



<p>“The Exchange is proposing to take additional steps to those described above to supplement its ability to obtain information that would be helpful in detecting, investigating, and deterring fraud and market manipulation in the Commodity-Based Trust Shares,” Cboe BZX said in the revised application.</p>



<p>A surveillance-sharing agreement entails sharing data regarding market trading activity, clearing activity, and customer verification to guard against possible market manipulation.</p>



<p>ARK requested permission to list its native spot BTC ETF a third time in April after previous applications were rejected by the SEC back in 2021 and 2022. As a reason for the denials, the securities regulator indicated that it did not fully satisfy the rules of practice and Exchange Act provisions for listing a financial product.</p>



<p>The amended 19b-4 filing potentially puts ARK in competition with BlackRock to gain the first-ever approval of a spot bitcoin ETF in the United States, as the original filing for the fund came earlier than BlackRock&#8217;s.&nbsp;</p>



<p>As per Balchunas, the SEC’s decision is expected in August, and any potential delays could be seen as a really bad sign for approval unless the delay is followed by green-lighting of BlackRock’s ETF, which could signal a hint of “favoritism.”</p>



<p>BlackRock already tapped Coinbase to be its Bitcoin custodian if and when it&#8217;s granted approval. As such, there are concerns about whether the investment giant would allow Coinbase to enter into a surveillance-sharing agreement with another entity that could potentially overtake it on the market.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/ark-invest-gains-edge-in-spot-bitcoin-etf-race-with-epic-surveillance-sharing-maneuver/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>XRP Sees Ultra Bullish Use Cases After Colombia’s Central Bank Taps Ripple to Pilot CBDC</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/xrp-sees-ultra-bullish-use-cases-after-colombias-central-bank-taps-ripple-to-pilot-cbdc/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/xrp-sees-ultra-bullish-use-cases-after-colombias-central-bank-taps-ripple-to-pilot-cbdc/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aaron Feuerstein]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 21:08:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=82450</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/Ripple-Boss-Brad-Garlinghouse-Speaks-On-Likelihood-Of-XRP-ETF-Launching-On-US-Exchange.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Ripple Boss Brad Garlinghouse Speaks On Likelihood Of XRP ETF Launching On US Exchange" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/Ripple-Boss-Brad-Garlinghouse-Speaks-On-Likelihood-Of-XRP-ETF-Launching-On-US-Exchange.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/Ripple-Boss-Brad-Garlinghouse-Speaks-On-Likelihood-Of-XRP-ETF-Launching-On-US-Exchange-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/Ripple-Boss-Brad-Garlinghouse-Speaks-On-Likelihood-Of-XRP-ETF-Launching-On-US-Exchange-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/Ripple-Boss-Brad-Garlinghouse-Speaks-On-Likelihood-Of-XRP-ETF-Launching-On-US-Exchange-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>The initiative aims to leverage Ripple's recently launched central bank digital...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/Ripple-Boss-Brad-Garlinghouse-Speaks-On-Likelihood-Of-XRP-ETF-Launching-On-US-Exchange.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Ripple Boss Brad Garlinghouse Speaks On Likelihood Of XRP ETF Launching On US Exchange" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/Ripple-Boss-Brad-Garlinghouse-Speaks-On-Likelihood-Of-XRP-ETF-Launching-On-US-Exchange.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/Ripple-Boss-Brad-Garlinghouse-Speaks-On-Likelihood-Of-XRP-ETF-Launching-On-US-Exchange-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/Ripple-Boss-Brad-Garlinghouse-Speaks-On-Likelihood-Of-XRP-ETF-Launching-On-US-Exchange-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/Ripple-Boss-Brad-Garlinghouse-Speaks-On-Likelihood-Of-XRP-ETF-Launching-On-US-Exchange-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>Colombia&#8217;s central bank, Banco de la República, recently joined forces with blockchain technology firm Ripple and software development company Peersyst to pilot a project exploring the use of blockchain technology on the <a href="https://zycrypto.com/ripple-seals-major-partnership-with-canadas-biggest-university-to-launch-xrp-ledger-validator/">XRP Ledger</a>. The initiative, overseen by Colombia&#8217;s Ministry of Information and Communications Technologies (MinTIC), aims to leverage Ripple&#8217;s recently launched central bank digital currency (CBDC) platform.</p>



<p>In a tweet, Ripple Partner Peersyst stated, “The objective: Evaluate potential efficiencies of a solution using the Ripple CBDC Platform based on the core technology of the XRPLedger to improve use cases on the high-value payment system.<em>”</em></p>



<p>The partnership between Banco de la República, Ripple, and Peersyst is a crucial step towards incorporating blockchain technology into the nation&#8217;s financial infrastructure. The pilot project will examine blockchain&#8217;s possible use cases on the XRP Ledger and how they relate to central bank digital currencies. Banco de la República hopes to improve the effectiveness, security, and transparency of the nation&#8217;s financial transactions by utilizing Ripple&#8217;s CBDC platform.</p>



<p>The partnership may affect the value of XRP, the cryptocurrency behind the XRP Ledger. Although the cooperation might increase interest in XRP, it is important to consider other market factors that may affect the price. It must also be stressed that a Colombian CBDC will likely not use XRP itself, but rather the underlying XRPL distributed ledger technology (DTL). The success of the collaboration will therefore rely on how well the pilot project is carried out and how widely blockchain technology is embraced in Colombia&#8217;s banking sector.</p>



<p>This is a hugely significant collaboration in the context of digital currencies issued by central banks. The fact that Banco de la República is investigating Ripple&#8217;s CBDC technology demonstrates the growing awareness of the potential of blockchain to revolutionize conventional financial systems. The central bank of Colombia has shown that it is <a href="https://zycrypto.com/colombian-government-launches-national-land-registry-on-xrp-ledger-for-over-50-million-people/">committed to staying</a> on the cutting edge of technological advancement in the financial sector by cooperating with Ripple and Peersyst.</p>



<p>The partnership between Banco de la Republica, Ripple, and Peersyst comes as central banks worldwide investigate the advantages of blockchain technology and virtual currencies. Blocks like this open the path for broader adoption and the mainstream integration of blockchain-based solutions as governments and financial institutions come to understand the revolutionary potential of decentralized technologies.</p>



<p>The collaboration raises promise for the future of digital money in the nation, even though the pilot project&#8217;s specific use cases and results have not yet been determined. Colombia intends to strengthen its financial infrastructure, increase security, and promote innovation by utilizing the possibilities of blockchain technology and Ripple&#8217;s CBDC platform.</p>



<p>It is crucial to understand that the pilot project&#8217;s success will depend on several variables, including legal requirements, technological viability, and public acceptance. Stakeholders should closely follow the project&#8217;s progress and evaluate the possibilities for growing blockchain solutions in Colombia&#8217;s financial ecosystem as it develops.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/xrp-sees-ultra-bullish-use-cases-after-colombias-central-bank-taps-ripple-to-pilot-cbdc/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Leaked Draft Reveals EU Commission&#8217;s Plans for Digital Euro: A Closer Look at the CBDC</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/leaked-draft-reveals-eu-commissions-plans-for-digital-euro-a-closer-look-at-the-cbdc/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/leaked-draft-reveals-eu-commissions-plans-for-digital-euro-a-closer-look-at-the-cbdc/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aaron Feuerstein]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 20:45:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=82445</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/04/U.S.-Struggles-To-Keep-Up-As-China-Further-Develops-Its-CBDC.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="U.S. Struggles To Keep Up As China Further Develops Its CBDC" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/04/U.S.-Struggles-To-Keep-Up-As-China-Further-Develops-Its-CBDC.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/04/U.S.-Struggles-To-Keep-Up-As-China-Further-Develops-Its-CBDC-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/04/U.S.-Struggles-To-Keep-Up-As-China-Further-Develops-Its-CBDC-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/04/U.S.-Struggles-To-Keep-Up-As-China-Further-Develops-Its-CBDC-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>A leaked draft document from the European Commission has shed light on the institution's plans for the digital euro, providing an intriguing glimpse into the future of digital currencies.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/04/U.S.-Struggles-To-Keep-Up-As-China-Further-Develops-Its-CBDC.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="U.S. Struggles To Keep Up As China Further Develops Its CBDC" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/04/U.S.-Struggles-To-Keep-Up-As-China-Further-Develops-Its-CBDC.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/04/U.S.-Struggles-To-Keep-Up-As-China-Further-Develops-Its-CBDC-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/04/U.S.-Struggles-To-Keep-Up-As-China-Further-Develops-Its-CBDC-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/04/U.S.-Struggles-To-Keep-Up-As-China-Further-Develops-Its-CBDC-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>A leaked draft document from the European Commission has shed light on the institution&#8217;s plans for the digital euro, providing an intriguing glimpse into the future of digital currencies. According to the draft, the EU Commission wants to establish an openly available digital euro while also putting some limitations on programmability and interest rates.</p>



<p>According to the leaked document, the EU Commission&#8217;s fundamental goal is to make sure that everyone can use the digital euro, regardless of their socioeconomic level. In addition to highlighting the value of financial inclusion, the statement aspires to close the digital gap by granting everyone access to digital currency. The concept aims to provide a trustworthy and secure digital payment system that both individuals and companies can utilize.</p>



<p>But the leaked draught also clarifies that the EU Commission plans to restrict how the digital euro can be programmed. According to the document, the currency&#8217;s programmability would be limited to stop potential abuse and illegal acts. The goal is to balance innovation and regulatory monitoring, even though the precise details of these constraints have not yet been decided.</p>



<p>The leaked document also highlights an interesting development involving interest rates for the digital euro. It looks like the EU Commission is thinking about making interest in digital currency holdings illegal. This action is probably intended to avoid hoarding, discourage large-scale stockpiling of the digital euro, and encourage spending to boost the economy. Experts and economists are expected to disagree over the potential effects of the proposed interest rate restriction on the uptake and use of digital currency.</p>



<p>Smart contract proponents have expressed alarm at the leaked draught. According to the document, smart contracts may be de facto outlawed in the framework of the digital euro. Given that smart contracts might create complications and risks that call for meticulous regulation, this restriction is likely meant to safeguard the stability and integrity of the digital currency. However, critics claim that such a limitation would prevent the advancement and innovation of smart contract-based blockchain applications.</p>



<p>Even though the leaked draft provides valuable insights into the EU Commission&#8217;s plans for the digital euro, it is crucial to keep in mind that the document is not final and subject to parliamentary revisions. Before putting the plan in writing, the EU Commission will probably undertake more stakeholder meetings and consultations.</p>



<p>The EU Commission&#8217;s commitment to investigating and realizing the possibilities of central bank digital currencies is reflected in the leaked letter. The digital euro aspires to establish the European Union as a pioneer in the field of digital currencies while solving issues with accessibility, programmability, and interest rates as the world of finance continues to change. Although the future of the digital euro is still up in the air, this leaked memo provides an exciting look at potential developments for the European digital currency market.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/leaked-draft-reveals-eu-commissions-plans-for-digital-euro-a-closer-look-at-the-cbdc/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethscriptions Lands On Ethereum After Ordinals Inscription Success On Bitcoin</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/ethscriptions-lands-on-ethereum-after-ordinals-inscription-success-on-bitcoin/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/ethscriptions-lands-on-ethereum-after-ordinals-inscription-success-on-bitcoin/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aliyu Pokima]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 20:30:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=82437</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/There-Is-A-Good-Chance-Ethereum-Flips-Bitcoin-ETH-Co-Founder-Asserts.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="There Is A &quot;Good Chance&quot; Ethereum Flips Bitcoin, ETH Co-Founder Asserts" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/There-Is-A-Good-Chance-Ethereum-Flips-Bitcoin-ETH-Co-Founder-Asserts.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/There-Is-A-Good-Chance-Ethereum-Flips-Bitcoin-ETH-Co-Founder-Asserts-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/There-Is-A-Good-Chance-Ethereum-Flips-Bitcoin-ETH-Co-Founder-Asserts-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/There-Is-A-Good-Chance-Ethereum-Flips-Bitcoin-ETH-Co-Founder-Asserts-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>Ethereum developers have drawn inspiration from Bitcoin in non-fungible tokens (NFTs), an area of speciality for the decentralized blockchain giant. A new protocol that offers users a new way to create NFTs hit Ethereum over the weekend with lots of buzzes over its possibilities. Developed by Tom Lehman, the co-founder of Genius.com, the project is [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/There-Is-A-Good-Chance-Ethereum-Flips-Bitcoin-ETH-Co-Founder-Asserts.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="There Is A &quot;Good Chance&quot; Ethereum Flips Bitcoin, ETH Co-Founder Asserts" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/There-Is-A-Good-Chance-Ethereum-Flips-Bitcoin-ETH-Co-Founder-Asserts.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/There-Is-A-Good-Chance-Ethereum-Flips-Bitcoin-ETH-Co-Founder-Asserts-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/There-Is-A-Good-Chance-Ethereum-Flips-Bitcoin-ETH-Co-Founder-Asserts-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/There-Is-A-Good-Chance-Ethereum-Flips-Bitcoin-ETH-Co-Founder-Asserts-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<ul>
<li>Ethscriptions akin to BTC inscriptions are a new way for users to create non-fungible tokens on Ethereum.</li>



<li>Barely 48 hours after the launch, the project has recorded over 30,000 image NFTs with slight congestion on the blockchain. </li>



<li>Unlike BTC ordinals, the project has received widespread optimism among developers and users, although some feel it&#8217;s just a “<em>copycat.”</em></li>
</ul>



<p>Ethereum developers have drawn inspiration from Bitcoin in non-fungible tokens (NFTs), an area of speciality for the decentralized blockchain giant.</p>



<p>A new protocol that offers users a new way to create NFTs hit Ethereum over the weekend with lots of buzzes over its possibilities. Developed by Tom Lehman, the co-founder of Genius.com, the project is <a href="https://twitter.com/dumbnamenumbers/status/1670063380726423554?s=46&amp;t=sCvh3f3rMDfXyJcf1y1Eyg">termed</a> Ethscriptions, coined like inscriptions in Bitcoin because of the shared similarities. </p>



<p>Ethscriptions allow for non-financial data to be written on the Ethereum network so far as it is under 96 kilobytes. It currently only allows for image-based NFTs, but developers say it will be expanded in the future. Lehman noted that Ethscriptions utilize “call data” which is data derived within a call to a smart contract making it cheaper and more decentralized than others. </p>



<p>“<em>It guarantees global uniqueness of the content of all valid Ethscriptions. it&#8217;s skating to where the puck is going in an L2 world,” </em>he added.</p>



<p>The launch has already sparked significant interest in major players in the Ethereum network. Within hours of its launch, over 10,000 inscriptions were recorded. The figure grew to over 30,000 over the weekend, with its debut project, “Ethereum Punks” being claimed in a few hours. </p>



<p>Lehman hailed the project as a success, claiming that its high adoption almost led to a temporary crash of the official Ethscription site. </p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-community-backs-innovation">Community backs innovation</h2>



<p>Modelled along the lines of Bitcoin Ordinals, the developers Ethscriptions hope to achieve the same results as the community moved in unison, at least for now. BTC Ordinals was launched with huge dissenting views, with many calling it an “<em>attack” </em>against the normal use of the network.</p>



<p>These views got louder when the blockchain was <a href="https://zycrypto.com/bitcoins-surging-transaction-fees-viewed-as-direct-attack-by-a-cross-section-of-the-community/">congested</a> due to the high inscription volume recorded in May. For Ethscriptions, most users focus on the positives calling for more innovation and adoption. Adam McBride, an NFT enthusiast, capped off the community’s sentiment with his views.</p>



<p>“<em>The exciting thing for me about Ethscriptions, similar to Ordinals, is that developers are playing around again with blockchain technology. It’s this experimentation that drives innovation and adoption,” </em>he stated.&nbsp;</p>



<p>Despite this, McBride also noted that technology has existed on the network for years with few artists deploying it, noting that this would be the first time it gets massive publicity.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/ethscriptions-lands-on-ethereum-after-ordinals-inscription-success-on-bitcoin/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bank Of England Goes A Step Closer To Launch Britcoin Following Project Rosalind’s Positive Trial Study</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/bank-of-england-goes-a-step-closer-to-launch-britcoin-following-project-rosalinds-positive-trial-study/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/bank-of-england-goes-a-step-closer-to-launch-britcoin-following-project-rosalinds-positive-trial-study/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aliyu Pokima]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 20:11:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=82433</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/Georgia-To-Test-CBDC-In-2022-As-The-Race-Intensifies.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Georgia To Test CBDC In 2022 As The Race Intensifies" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/Georgia-To-Test-CBDC-In-2022-As-The-Race-Intensifies.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/Georgia-To-Test-CBDC-In-2022-As-The-Race-Intensifies-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/Georgia-To-Test-CBDC-In-2022-As-The-Race-Intensifies-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/Georgia-To-Test-CBDC-In-2022-As-The-Race-Intensifies-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>The report from Project Rosalind shows that Central Bank Digital Currencies (CBDCs) are beneficial to a digitized economy, especially a two-tier CBDC model. ]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/Georgia-To-Test-CBDC-In-2022-As-The-Race-Intensifies.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Georgia To Test CBDC In 2022 As The Race Intensifies" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/Georgia-To-Test-CBDC-In-2022-As-The-Race-Intensifies.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/Georgia-To-Test-CBDC-In-2022-As-The-Race-Intensifies-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/Georgia-To-Test-CBDC-In-2022-As-The-Race-Intensifies-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/Georgia-To-Test-CBDC-In-2022-As-The-Race-Intensifies-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<ul>
<li>A new study shows that CBDCs could make retail payments cheaper and more efficient with the right technology.</li>



<li>The study carried out by the Bank of International Settlements and the Bank of England backs CBDCs for a digitized economy. </li>



<li>Despite the successful trial, the Deputy Governor of the Bank of England insists that Britcoin is still “<em>some years away”</em>.&nbsp;</li>
</ul>



<p>The report from Project Rosalind shows that Central Bank Digital Currencies (CBDCs) are beneficial to a digitized economy, especially a two-tier CBDC model.&nbsp;</p>



<p>The Bank Of England, alongside the Bank of International Settlements, embarked on a joint experiment in July 2022 to determine how an application programming interface (API) could be deployed in retail CBDC transactions. The report was <a href="https://www.bis.org/publ/othp69.pdf">released</a> on June 16 and states clearly that CBDCs make payments between individuals and businesses less expensive. </p>



<p>According to the report, a two-tier CBDC model will allow firms to create new financial products to reduce fraudulent activities. There are widely two systems for launching CBDCs: single-tier and double-tier. The Central Bank fully operates the single-tier model, while the two-tier model leverages financial institutions making it more decentralized.</p>



<p>The Central Bank provides core infrastructure, while private firms handle service providers through APIs. Project Rosalind explored how these APIs would improve the overall experience of the digital currency. An intriguing discovery in the report is the way the model would drive adoption with its numerous use cases, explore decentralization and create an interoperable model. </p>



<p>The study developed 33 API functionality with over 30 CBDC use cases, including its deployment on smartphones, vendors, and retail stores. </p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-britcoin-is-still-years-away"><strong>Britcoin is still years away </strong></h2>



<p>“<em>The Rosalind experiment has advanced central bank innovation in two key areas: by exploring how an API layer could support a retail CBDC system and how it could facilitate safe and secure CBDC payments through a range of different use cases,” </em>Francesca Road, Head of BIS London said in a statement. </p>



<p>With success recorded in Rosalind, many observers say that all roadblocks have been removed, paving the way for UK’s Central Bank’s Digital Currency, popularly called Britcoin. However, the deputy Governor of the Bank of England, Jon Cunliffe, had pushed the date further when he stated that the country’s launch of the currency “<em>is still years away.” </em></p>



<p>According to a Bloomberg <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-06-15/boe-s-cunliffe-says-decision-on-britcoin-cbdc-is-some-years-away">report</a>, Cunliffe, while addressing financial experts at Politico’s Global Tech Day that the possibility of a CBDC rollout stands at “<em>seven out of ten.” </em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/bank-of-england-goes-a-step-closer-to-launch-britcoin-following-project-rosalinds-positive-trial-study/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>“Plan For MiCA Now”- Chainalysis Counsels Digital Asset Firms Ahead Of 2024 Implementation</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/plan-for-mica-now-chainalysis-counsels-digital-asset-firms-ahead-of-2024-implementation/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/plan-for-mica-now-chainalysis-counsels-digital-asset-firms-ahead-of-2024-implementation/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aliyu Pokima]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 19:55:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=82429</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Industry-Leaders-Upbeat-as-EU-Parliament-Passes-Much-Anticipated-MiCA-Regulation.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Industry Leaders Upbeat as EU Parliament Passes Much-Anticipated MiCA Regulation" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Industry-Leaders-Upbeat-as-EU-Parliament-Passes-Much-Anticipated-MiCA-Regulation.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Industry-Leaders-Upbeat-as-EU-Parliament-Passes-Much-Anticipated-MiCA-Regulation-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Industry-Leaders-Upbeat-as-EU-Parliament-Passes-Much-Anticipated-MiCA-Regulation-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Industry-Leaders-Upbeat-as-EU-Parliament-Passes-Much-Anticipated-MiCA-Regulation-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>The Markets in Crypto Assets (MiCA) regulation has been passed by the European Union Parliament, but it will swing into effect in two phases next year. Janet Ho, Chainalysis head of policy in Europe, has tasked digital asset companies to put their houses in order as they anticipate the implementation of MiCA. The regulation, which [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Industry-Leaders-Upbeat-as-EU-Parliament-Passes-Much-Anticipated-MiCA-Regulation.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Industry Leaders Upbeat as EU Parliament Passes Much-Anticipated MiCA Regulation" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Industry-Leaders-Upbeat-as-EU-Parliament-Passes-Much-Anticipated-MiCA-Regulation.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Industry-Leaders-Upbeat-as-EU-Parliament-Passes-Much-Anticipated-MiCA-Regulation-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Industry-Leaders-Upbeat-as-EU-Parliament-Passes-Much-Anticipated-MiCA-Regulation-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Industry-Leaders-Upbeat-as-EU-Parliament-Passes-Much-Anticipated-MiCA-Regulation-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<ul>
<li>Chainalysis EU policy head tells cryptocurrency firms to prepare for MiCA’s implementation to avoid regulatory setbacks.&nbsp;</li>



<li>Ripple lauds landmark crypto regulation as it plans its expansion in Europe and Asia amid US ambiguous policies.</li>



<li>EU leads the way: Crypto executives urge the United States to follow the steps of Europe and stop “<em>bottleneck regulation.”</em></li>
</ul>



<p>The Markets in Crypto Assets (MiCA) regulation has been passed by the European Union Parliament, but it will swing into effect in two phases next year.</p>



<p>Janet Ho, Chainalysis head of policy in Europe, has tasked digital asset companies to put their houses in order as they anticipate the implementation of MiCA. The regulation, which changes the entire scope and model of cryptocurrency regulation, will not be enforced until June 2024 for stablecoins and Dec 2024 for exchanges.</p>



<p>Address industry leads at a recent webinar; she warned firms and regulators not to become complacent while waiting for the deadline before making preparations. “<em>These are the preparations you want to start now – maybe even yesterday,” </em>she stated.</p>



<p>The need for haste comes with several obstacles firms may face from local regulators. According to her, it could take four to five months to obtain a MiCA license from local authorities if you factor in the timeframes for numerous stages of approvals or denials and re-application.&nbsp;</p>



<p>“<em>If you want to continue your business, you need to take into account that 4-5 months, if not more,” </em>she added.</p>



<p>In applying for MiCA licenses, she told executives to see the immeasurable positives of registration rather than the task itself. A MiCA license will enable firms to drive into other European countries without new hurdles. “<em>Once you get one license, you can also scale up the business within the EU,” </em>she noted. Firms with this license will be seen as compliant worldwide because no such regulations exist, making it the gold standard. </p>



<p><em>“If you’ve got the MiCA license, you are complying, you’re being verified,”</em> she explained. <em>“There are no standardized rules in any other part of the world.”</em></p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-europe-runs-away-with-the-torch"><strong>Europe runs away with the torch</strong></h2>



<p>For a larger part of the last decade, the United States led the way in web3 through new start-ups and technology, but those rosy years have been marred with regulatory uncertainty and countless lawsuits. In the last few years, the Securities and Exchange Commission has sued Ripple, Binance, Coinbase, and several other firms with no end in sight. </p>



<p>MiCA is touted as the first of its kind, placing EU nations in prime positions for new startups and established digital asset firms. Changpeng Zhao, Binance’s CEO, hailed MiCA as innovative for the entire crypto sector with expectations for a business-driven jurisdiction. Kadan Stadelmann, the CTO of Kodomo, added that other countries would have to play catch up with Europe after implementing the law.</p>



<p><em>“Other countries will probably choose a ‘wait and see’ approach before making their own regulations. Still, MiCA’s influence is clear; most nations will feel pressure to adopt some form of regulation to avoid getting left behind in a sector that has growing importance,” </em>he said.&nbsp;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/plan-for-mica-now-chainalysis-counsels-digital-asset-firms-ahead-of-2024-implementation/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>“Far From Securities”- Solana, Polygon and Cardano Issue Solid Statements Against SEC Claims</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/far-from-securities-solana-polygon-and-cardano-issue-solid-statements-against-sec-claims/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/far-from-securities-solana-polygon-and-cardano-issue-solid-statements-against-sec-claims/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aliyu Pokima]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 19:34:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Polygon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Solana]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=82427</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/04/Ripple-Nets-Legal-Victory-In-Quest-To-Access-SECs-Documents-Relating-To-Classification-Of-Cryptoassets-As-Securities.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Ripple Nets Legal Victory In Quest To Access SEC’s Documents Relating To Classification Of Cryptoassets As Securities" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/04/Ripple-Nets-Legal-Victory-In-Quest-To-Access-SECs-Documents-Relating-To-Classification-Of-Cryptoassets-As-Securities.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/04/Ripple-Nets-Legal-Victory-In-Quest-To-Access-SECs-Documents-Relating-To-Classification-Of-Cryptoassets-As-Securities-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/04/Ripple-Nets-Legal-Victory-In-Quest-To-Access-SECs-Documents-Relating-To-Classification-Of-Cryptoassets-As-Securities-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/04/Ripple-Nets-Legal-Victory-In-Quest-To-Access-SECs-Documents-Relating-To-Classification-Of-Cryptoassets-As-Securities-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>After the SEC lawsuit against Coinbase, which listed several cryptocurrencies as securities, including Solana (SOL), Polygon (MATIC), and Cardano (ADA), the organizations behind these projects are pushing back against the “securities tag.”]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/04/Ripple-Nets-Legal-Victory-In-Quest-To-Access-SECs-Documents-Relating-To-Classification-Of-Cryptoassets-As-Securities.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Ripple Nets Legal Victory In Quest To Access SEC’s Documents Relating To Classification Of Cryptoassets As Securities" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/04/Ripple-Nets-Legal-Victory-In-Quest-To-Access-SECs-Documents-Relating-To-Classification-Of-Cryptoassets-As-Securities.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/04/Ripple-Nets-Legal-Victory-In-Quest-To-Access-SECs-Documents-Relating-To-Classification-Of-Cryptoassets-As-Securities-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/04/Ripple-Nets-Legal-Victory-In-Quest-To-Access-SECs-Documents-Relating-To-Classification-Of-Cryptoassets-As-Securities-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/04/Ripple-Nets-Legal-Victory-In-Quest-To-Access-SECs-Documents-Relating-To-Classification-Of-Cryptoassets-As-Securities-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<ul>
<li>The organizations behind Solana, Polygon, and Cardano have issued strong statements against being classified as securities by the SEC.&nbsp;</li>



<li>The prices of the three assets have plunged 30% since the lawsuit against Coinbase though slight growth is trickling in.&nbsp;</li>



<li>The community joins the organizations and executives to criticize the Commission&#8217;s trigger-happy stance against the market. </li>
</ul>



<p>The Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) launched a new aggressive action against Binance and Coinbase earlier this month, leaving the market in the red zone with panic and tumbling asset prices.</p>



<p>After the SEC lawsuit against Coinbase, which listed several cryptocurrencies as securities, including Solana (SOL), Polygon (MATIC), and Cardano (ADA), the organizations behind these projects are pushing back against the <em>“securities tag.” </em>These three assets rank highly among the other tokens listed in the lawsuit, with a combined market cap of $21 billion. </p>



<p>The Solana Foundation tweeted its position asserting that SOL is not a security according to the laws of the United States. The organization delved further to explain how regulatory clarity would fix the prolonged problem between the SEC and digital assets. </p>



<p>“<em>We welcome the continued engagement of policymakers as constructive partners on regulation to achieve legal clarity on these issues for the thousands of entrepreneurs across the U.S. building in the digital assets space.”</em></p>



<p>Input Output Global, the association behind Cardano, also reiterated the same position as it claims ADA is not a security, adding that the lawsuit will not affect the operations of ADA in any way.</p>



<p>“<em>This latest filing from the SEC demonstrates that we still have a long way to go. Regulation through enforcement action does not provide either the clarity or certainty to which both the blockchain industry and consumers are entitled,” </em>IOG added.&nbsp;</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-mark-cuban-and-polygon-differ-from-the-rest"><strong>Mark Cuban and Polygon differ from the rest</strong></h2>



<p>Polygon, in its statement, did not directly state that MATIC is not a security but made an attempt to distance the asset from the United States market. According to the statement, Polygon was developed and deployed in foreign jurisdictions with a global presence.</p>



<p>They claimed that US-based investors were not targeted, a move which observers say they plan to use to argue against the legal jurisdiction of the SEC over the asset.</p>



<p>“<em>We are confident in the actions we took in the past. Given our focus on network security, we made sure MATIC was available to a wide group of persons, but only with actions that did not target the U.S. at any time,” </em>Polygon Labs added.&nbsp;</p>



<p>Meanwhile, Mark Cuban has noted that with the present state of things, firms can&#8217;t determine what constitutes securities calling for new regulations from Congress.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/far-from-securities-solana-polygon-and-cardano-issue-solid-statements-against-sec-claims/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>New Survey Points To Increased Web3 Utility; However, People Don’t Know What It Really Means</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/new-survey-points-to-increased-web3-utility-however-people-dont-know-what-it-really-means/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/new-survey-points-to-increased-web3-utility-however-people-dont-know-what-it-really-means/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aliyu Pokima]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 18:00:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Web3]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=82424</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Epic-Showdown-Alex-The-Doge-ALEX-vs-SHIB-Pepe-PEPE-who-will-be-the-head-honcho-1.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="New Survey Points To Increased Web3 Utility; However, People Don’t Know What It Really Means" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Epic-Showdown-Alex-The-Doge-ALEX-vs-SHIB-Pepe-PEPE-who-will-be-the-head-honcho-1.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Epic-Showdown-Alex-The-Doge-ALEX-vs-SHIB-Pepe-PEPE-who-will-be-the-head-honcho-1-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Epic-Showdown-Alex-The-Doge-ALEX-vs-SHIB-Pepe-PEPE-who-will-be-the-head-honcho-1-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Epic-Showdown-Alex-The-Doge-ALEX-vs-SHIB-Pepe-PEPE-who-will-be-the-head-honcho-1-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>Web3 adoption around the world is growing across all age demographics although many seem to be lost in the actual meaning of the world.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Epic-Showdown-Alex-The-Doge-ALEX-vs-SHIB-Pepe-PEPE-who-will-be-the-head-honcho-1.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="New Survey Points To Increased Web3 Utility; However, People Don’t Know What It Really Means" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Epic-Showdown-Alex-The-Doge-ALEX-vs-SHIB-Pepe-PEPE-who-will-be-the-head-honcho-1.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Epic-Showdown-Alex-The-Doge-ALEX-vs-SHIB-Pepe-PEPE-who-will-be-the-head-honcho-1-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Epic-Showdown-Alex-The-Doge-ALEX-vs-SHIB-Pepe-PEPE-who-will-be-the-head-honcho-1-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Epic-Showdown-Alex-The-Doge-ALEX-vs-SHIB-Pepe-PEPE-who-will-be-the-head-honcho-1-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<ul>
<li>Digital asset awareness surges across many regions, but several people fail to understand the true concept behind the terms.</li>



<li>Nigeria, Brazil, and South Korea lead the youthful drive of NFTs and Web3 despite recent perceived setbacks by authorities.</li>



<li>The majority of survey participants viewed blockchain and cryptocurrencies as the “<em>future of money”, </em>while few associated it with scams and money laundering.</li>
</ul>



<p>Web3 adoption around the world is growing across all age demographics, although many seem to be lost in the actual meaning of the world.</p>



<p>A recent <a href="https://consensys.io/insight-report/web3-and-crypto-global-survey-2023#05-crypto-awareness">survey</a> conducted by Ethereum software company, Consensys and YouGov shows an unprecedented rise in the growth of digital assets across all continents. The poll featured 15,000 participants who were quizzed on several areas, including their drive behind the technology, perspectives on the web3, non-fungible tokens (NFTs), and regulation among others.</p>



<p>92% of participants acknowledged that they have little knowledge of digital assets, as expected, but only 8% knew the intricacies of web3. This shows a massive disparity between the industry’s analysis of web3 and the general public. Web3 seeks to push innovation to current web2 challenges tailored to giving users control over their content, data, and privacy.</p>



<p>Polled participants also showed a wider acceptance of the general description of crypto as the “<em>future of money</em>” and an “alternative to traditional finance.” Only 8% regarded virtual currencies to be mostly associated with fraudulent activities like money laundering. Among participating continents, Europeans viewed cryptos more negatively, especially related to gambling.</p>



<p>Although the majority of votes showed that people are not familiar with the technicalities behind NFTs, 41% voted for improved usage of the tokens in the future. While 76% of Uk participants have never owned NFTs, Vietnam posted more adoption, with only 26% not owning NFTs. As a store of value, 56% of Argentinians were driven to own assets as a result of an unstable local currency. </p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-nigeria-and-south-korea-lead-adoption-drive"><strong>Nigeria and South Korea Lead Adoption Drive</strong></h2>



<p>According to the report, participants in <a href="https://zycrypto.com/nigerias-new-crypto-tax-policy-could-set-the-tone-for-africas-positive-web3-relationship/">Nigeria</a> recorded a 78% understanding of general digital asset knowledge and awareness of its potential. This was followed by South Korea with 63% while <a href="https://zycrypto.com/1600-pick-n-pay-stores-set-to-pioneer-mainstream-bitcoin-payments-in-south-africa/">South Africa</a> and <a href="https://zycrypto.com/bitcoin-takes-the-spotlight-as-brazil-and-argentina-mulls-creating-a-common-currency/">Brazil</a> recorded 61% and 59% respectively. On NFT awareness and usage, 56% of Americans who participated said they were either very or fairly familiar with the concept. </p>



<p>Generally, over 50% of participants in Nigeria, India, and the United States knew the details of web3, NFTs, and regulations. Another salient point the survey covered was data privacy, a major flaw of web2. Over 67% believe that users should be in total control of the internet, while 79% feel that their data is best in their hands without any third party. While participants from countries with strong data privacy laws did not collectively vote for a change in the status quo, countries without those laws, like Latin American and African countries, did. </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/new-survey-points-to-increased-web3-utility-however-people-dont-know-what-it-really-means/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>MicroStrategy Adds To Bitcoin Stash, Now Holds $4.6 Billion</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/microstrategy-adds-to-bitcoin-stash-now-holds-4-6-billion/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/microstrategy-adds-to-bitcoin-stash-now-holds-4-6-billion/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Brenda Ngari]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 17:44:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MicroStrategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XBTUSD]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=82422</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/07/2.2-Trillion-Asset-Manager-Buys-Stake-In-MicroStrategy-Gains-Indirect-Exposure-To-Bitcoin.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="$2.2 Trillion Asset Manager Buys Stake In MicroStrategy, Gains Indirect Exposure To Bitcoin" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/07/2.2-Trillion-Asset-Manager-Buys-Stake-In-MicroStrategy-Gains-Indirect-Exposure-To-Bitcoin.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/07/2.2-Trillion-Asset-Manager-Buys-Stake-In-MicroStrategy-Gains-Indirect-Exposure-To-Bitcoin-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/07/2.2-Trillion-Asset-Manager-Buys-Stake-In-MicroStrategy-Gains-Indirect-Exposure-To-Bitcoin-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/07/2.2-Trillion-Asset-Manager-Buys-Stake-In-MicroStrategy-Gains-Indirect-Exposure-To-Bitcoin-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>MicroStrategy has purchased another 12,333 bitcoin, bringing its total holdings to 152,333 BTC — worth $4.6 billion at the current market prices.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/07/2.2-Trillion-Asset-Manager-Buys-Stake-In-MicroStrategy-Gains-Indirect-Exposure-To-Bitcoin.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="$2.2 Trillion Asset Manager Buys Stake In MicroStrategy, Gains Indirect Exposure To Bitcoin" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/07/2.2-Trillion-Asset-Manager-Buys-Stake-In-MicroStrategy-Gains-Indirect-Exposure-To-Bitcoin.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/07/2.2-Trillion-Asset-Manager-Buys-Stake-In-MicroStrategy-Gains-Indirect-Exposure-To-Bitcoin-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/07/2.2-Trillion-Asset-Manager-Buys-Stake-In-MicroStrategy-Gains-Indirect-Exposure-To-Bitcoin-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/07/2.2-Trillion-Asset-Manager-Buys-Stake-In-MicroStrategy-Gains-Indirect-Exposure-To-Bitcoin-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p><a href="https://zycrypto.com/microstrategys-saylor-envisions-250k-btc-price-following-bitcoins-soaring-dominance/">MicroStrategy</a> has purchased another 12,333 bitcoin, bringing its total holdings to 152,333 BTC — worth $4.6 billion at the current market prices.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>An Extra 12,333 BTC</strong></h2>



<p>Enterprise software solution company MicroStrategy keeps adding to its Bitcoin bet.</p>



<p>A Wednesday filing with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) indicates that the firm had purchased an additional 12,333 bitcoins for roughly $347 million at an average price of $28,136 per coin. The purchase was made in cash between April 29 and June 27.</p>



<p>The recent purchase brings MicroStrategy’s holdings to around 152,333 Bitcoin, with the firm’s average cost basis sitting at $29,668.</p>



<p>The BTC acquisition was partially funded with the issuance of new stock, as the company noted:</p>



<p>&#8220;On May 1, 2023, MicroStrategy entered into a Sales Agreement with Cowen and Company, LLC and Canaccord Genuity LLC, as sales agents, pursuant to which MicroStrategy may issue and sell shares of its class A common stock, par value $0.001 per share (&#8220;Shares&#8221;), having an aggregate offering price of up to $625.0 million from time to time through the Agents.&#8221;</p>



<p>MicroStrategy has issued and sold a total of 1,079,170 shares as of June 28 under the agreement for total net proceeds of $337 million.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-microstrategy-s-michael-saylor-is-bitcoin-s-biggest-advocate"><strong>MicroStrategy’s Michael Saylor Is Bitcoin’s Biggest Advocate</strong></h2>



<p>MicroStrategy is the <a href="https://zycrypto.com/microstrategys-bullish-stance-on-bitcoin-stronger-than-ever-as-firm-post-q1-2023-profits/">world’s biggest corporate Bitcoin holder</a>, and its now executive chairman Michael Saylor, who stepped down as CEO in August 2022, has become known for his ardent belief in the asset. The company started purchasing the preeminent crypto in August 2020; Saylor said at the time that the reason was a hedge against inflation.</p>



<p>Needless to say, MicroStrategy’s strategy on Bitcoin seems to be paying off despite the top crypto having slumped from its historic high of $69,044.17 set in November 2021. The publicly-traded company’s stock, which trades under the ticker symbol MSTR on the Nasdaq, is up over 160% since its first BTC purchase in 2020.&nbsp;</p>



<p>Saylor recently revealed that MicroStrategy integrated Bitcoin Lightning into his corporate email address.</p>



<p>The Bitcoin-savvy firm is also working on an “enterprise Lightning solution” to help corporations move funds fast. The Lightning Network is a layer-2 payment protocol built atop Bitcoin’s blockchain that permits off-chain transactions, increasing payment throughput and reducing transaction fees.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/microstrategy-adds-to-bitcoin-stash-now-holds-4-6-billion/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>There’s A 50% Chance BlackRock’s Spot Bitcoin ETF Gets Greenlight From SEC, Top Bloomberg Analyst Predicts</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/theres-a-50-chance-blackrocks-spot-bitcoin-etf-gets-greenlight-from-sec-top-bloomberg-analyst-predicts/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/theres-a-50-chance-blackrocks-spot-bitcoin-etf-gets-greenlight-from-sec-top-bloomberg-analyst-predicts/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Brenda Ngari]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 16:11:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XBTUSD]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=82405</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Theres-A-50-Chance-BlackRocks-Spot-Bitcoin-ETF-Gets-Greenlight-From-SEC-Top-Bloomberg-Analyst-Predicts.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="There’s A 50% Chance BlackRock’s Spot Bitcoin ETF Gets Greenlight From SEC, Top Bloomberg Analyst Predicts" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Theres-A-50-Chance-BlackRocks-Spot-Bitcoin-ETF-Gets-Greenlight-From-SEC-Top-Bloomberg-Analyst-Predicts.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Theres-A-50-Chance-BlackRocks-Spot-Bitcoin-ETF-Gets-Greenlight-From-SEC-Top-Bloomberg-Analyst-Predicts-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Theres-A-50-Chance-BlackRocks-Spot-Bitcoin-ETF-Gets-Greenlight-From-SEC-Top-Bloomberg-Analyst-Predicts-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Theres-A-50-Chance-BlackRocks-Spot-Bitcoin-ETF-Gets-Greenlight-From-SEC-Top-Bloomberg-Analyst-Predicts-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>But according to Bloomberg’s senior ETF strategist Eric Balchunas, BlackRock actually has a 50% chance of getting its spot Bitcoin exchange-traded fund greenlit by the securities agency.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Theres-A-50-Chance-BlackRocks-Spot-Bitcoin-ETF-Gets-Greenlight-From-SEC-Top-Bloomberg-Analyst-Predicts.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="There’s A 50% Chance BlackRock’s Spot Bitcoin ETF Gets Greenlight From SEC, Top Bloomberg Analyst Predicts" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Theres-A-50-Chance-BlackRocks-Spot-Bitcoin-ETF-Gets-Greenlight-From-SEC-Top-Bloomberg-Analyst-Predicts.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Theres-A-50-Chance-BlackRocks-Spot-Bitcoin-ETF-Gets-Greenlight-From-SEC-Top-Bloomberg-Analyst-Predicts-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Theres-A-50-Chance-BlackRocks-Spot-Bitcoin-ETF-Gets-Greenlight-From-SEC-Top-Bloomberg-Analyst-Predicts-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Theres-A-50-Chance-BlackRocks-Spot-Bitcoin-ETF-Gets-Greenlight-From-SEC-Top-Bloomberg-Analyst-Predicts-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>So far, the SEC has rejected every spot market bitcoin ETF put before it, basically because it believes the bitcoin market can be easily manipulated.</p>



<p>But according to Bloomberg’s senior ETF strategist Eric Balchunas, BlackRock actually has a 50% chance of getting its spot Bitcoin exchange-traded fund greenlit by the securities agency. This is because Grayscale is more likely to win its lawsuit against the SEC.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-the-first-ever-spot-bitcoin-etf"><strong>The First-Ever Spot Bitcoin ETF?</strong></h2>



<p>$9.5 trillion asset manager BlackRock recently <a href="https://zycrypto.com/btc-primed-for-trillion-dollar-boost-as-blackrock-expects-landmark-bitcoin-etf-approval/">sought permission</a> from the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission to list a spot bitcoin ETF, giving its clients indirect exposure to the flagship cryptocurrency. The main reason behind the hype is mostly related to the investment giant’s ETF application approval rates. Notably, BlackRock boasts a 575-1 record when it comes to its ETF applications.</p>



<p>Bloomberg’s Eric Balchunas gives BlackRock’s spot BTC approval chance of 50%. Balchunas’s forecast follows an observation made by the senior legal analyst for Bloomberg Intelligence, Elliott Stein, who believes the chances of Grayscale defeating the SEC in the ongoing lawsuit are at 70%.</p>



<p>Balchunas noted that the SEC might give BlackRock’s ETF filing the go-ahead as a way to “save face” by authorizing an ETF from a “trusted ‘adult&#8217; TradFi” company instead of Grayscale. This means that this may be the first spot bitcoin ETF out the door.</p>



<p>As you might recall, Grayscale <a href="https://zycrypto.com/grayscale-flips-the-script-and-sues-the-sec-after-spot-bitcoin-etf-plan-rejection/">launched a legal challenge</a> after the SEC rejected its application to convert its Grayscale Bitcoin Trust (GBTC) spot into a Bitcoin ETF. On March 7, a panel of judges heard oral arguments of the two sides in the suit. According to Stein, Grayscale’s chances of emerging victorious in the lawsuit increased from 40% to 70% because “all three judges on the panel appeared to side with Grayscale” based on their “lines of questioning”.</p>



<p>“The SEC and chair Gary Gensler may be bracing for a loss and looking to preemptively soften it or make it meaningless by approving a spot Bitcoin ETF application before or around the same time as the court decision,” Stein added.</p>



<p>Although the lengthy and extenuating legal war with the SEC seems endless, BlackRock’s impeccable track record for ETF applications injected a breath of fresh air into GBTC&#8217;s share price, which currently trades at $19.18, as per <a href="https://www.google.com/finance/quote/GBTC:OTCMKTS"><em>Google Finance</em></a>.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>The SEC’s Spot ETF Kill Streak</strong></h2>



<p>SEC Chairman Gary Gensler, known for having lectured a Bitcoin and Blockchain course at MIT, has been a staunch adversary of the crypto industry.</p>



<p>Numerous investment managers have filed for spot crypto ETFs in the past, and have been shot down by the SEC, one after another. Many of these firms are now reapplying for ETFs, hoping that Blackrock’s filing will pave the way for a more friendly SEC.</p>



<p>New York-based asset management firm <a href="https://zycrypto.com/bitcoin-etfs-in-motion-an-analysis-of-open-spot-btc-etf-applications-in-the-market/">WisdomTree is seeking approval</a> from the SEC to list its “WisdomTree Bitcoin Trust” for a third time. A few hours after the WisdomTree filing, <a href="https://zycrypto.com/bitcoin-shoots-up-with-30000-in-sight-following-fresh-wave-of-spot-etf-applications/">Invesco</a>, another major investment company with as much as $1.49 trillion under its management as of May 2023, “reactivated” its application for a similar investment vehicle, followed by a <a href="https://zycrypto.com/spot-bitcoin-etf-craze-valkyrie-becomes-the-latest-firm-to-apply-for-sec-approval/">request </a>from Valkyrie Investments on June 21.</p>



<p>If the SEC ultimately greenlights the applications from these asset managers and the likes of Fidelity Investments, JPMorgan, Morgan Stanley, Goldman Sachs, BNY Mellon, and Bank of America seeking to offer similar services to investors, the crypto market would be opened up to companies with a <a href="https://twitter.com/Melt_Dem/status/1673362112653975554">combined $27 trillion </a>in assets under management.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/theres-a-50-chance-blackrocks-spot-bitcoin-etf-gets-greenlight-from-sec-top-bloomberg-analyst-predicts/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Deutsche Bank Enters Digital Asset Custody to Drive Institutional Adoption</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/deutsche-bank-enters-digital-asset-custody-to-drive-institutional-adoption/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/deutsche-bank-enters-digital-asset-custody-to-drive-institutional-adoption/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Marco Tulio]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 15:51:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=82401</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/Bitcoin-Retakes-57K-As-Hundreds-Of-US-Banks-Prepare-To-Offer-Crypto-Trading-And-Custody-To-Clients.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Bitcoin Retakes $57K As Hundreds Of US Banks Prepare To Offer Crypto Trading And Custody To Clients" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/Bitcoin-Retakes-57K-As-Hundreds-Of-US-Banks-Prepare-To-Offer-Crypto-Trading-And-Custody-To-Clients.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/Bitcoin-Retakes-57K-As-Hundreds-Of-US-Banks-Prepare-To-Offer-Crypto-Trading-And-Custody-To-Clients-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/Bitcoin-Retakes-57K-As-Hundreds-Of-US-Banks-Prepare-To-Offer-Crypto-Trading-And-Custody-To-Clients-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/Bitcoin-Retakes-57K-As-Hundreds-Of-US-Banks-Prepare-To-Offer-Crypto-Trading-And-Custody-To-Clients-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>Deutsche Bank, one of the world&#8217;s leading financial institutions, has applied to the Federal Financial Supervisory Authority of Germany (BaFin), intending to obtain regulatory approval to offer cryptocurrency custody services. According to Bloomberg&#8217;s report, the approval of the custodial license would enable the bank to store and manage digital assets on behalf of its clients, [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/Bitcoin-Retakes-57K-As-Hundreds-Of-US-Banks-Prepare-To-Offer-Crypto-Trading-And-Custody-To-Clients.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Bitcoin Retakes $57K As Hundreds Of US Banks Prepare To Offer Crypto Trading And Custody To Clients" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/Bitcoin-Retakes-57K-As-Hundreds-Of-US-Banks-Prepare-To-Offer-Crypto-Trading-And-Custody-To-Clients.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/Bitcoin-Retakes-57K-As-Hundreds-Of-US-Banks-Prepare-To-Offer-Crypto-Trading-And-Custody-To-Clients-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/Bitcoin-Retakes-57K-As-Hundreds-Of-US-Banks-Prepare-To-Offer-Crypto-Trading-And-Custody-To-Clients-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/Bitcoin-Retakes-57K-As-Hundreds-Of-US-Banks-Prepare-To-Offer-Crypto-Trading-And-Custody-To-Clients-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>Deutsche Bank, one of the world&#8217;s leading financial institutions, has applied to the Federal Financial Supervisory Authority of Germany (BaFin), intending to obtain regulatory approval to offer cryptocurrency custody services.</p>



<p>According to Bloomberg&#8217;s <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-06-20/deutsche-bank-applies-for-digital-asset-license-amid-growth-push?leadSource=uverify%20wall">report</a>, the approval of the custodial license would enable the bank to store and manage digital assets on behalf of its clients, providing a reliable solution for institutional investors seeking a secure way to store their digital assets.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-deutsche-bank-the-ideal-candidate-for-cryptocurrency-custody"><strong>Deutsche Bank: The Ideal Candidate For Cryptocurrency Custody?</strong></h2>



<p>Founded on March 10, 1870, in Berlin, Germany, Deutsche Bank was originally established as a bank for financing and foreign trade. However, it has grown to become the largest bank in Germany, managing over 1.476 trillion euros in assets.</p>



<p>Therefore, thanks to its reputation, it could become one of the ideal candidates for custodial services for cryptocurrencies on behalf of institutional investors.</p>



<p>However, like any other institution, it must comply with a series of regulatory requirements before offering custody services related to digital assets.</p>



<p>David Lynne, Head of Commercial Banking at Deutsche Bank, informed Bloomberg that the bank is &#8220;expanding&#8221; its business into &#8220;digital assets and custody&#8221; services through the application to BaFin.</p>



<p>On the other hand, Andreas Sack, Product Owner of Digital Assets Custody at DekaBank, a German provider of asset management solutions, stated that &#8220;Digital assets are a critical part of the future, a radical new way of representing assets, from currencies to real estate.&#8221; This statement came after allying with Metaco, a Swiss provider of digital asset custody and tokenization technology (recently <a href="https://zycrypto.com/ripple-expands-into-the-institutional-crypto-custody-market-following-250-million-acquisition-of-metaco/">acquired by Ripple</a>), for the custody and management of their digital assets.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>German Banks Aim to Secure Digital Assets</strong></h2>



<p>This is not the first time a German bank has attempted to enter the digital asset custody space. According to ZyCrypto, since April 2022, <a href="https://zycrypto.com/major-german-bank-applies-for-crypto-custody-license/">Commerzbank</a>, one of the largest traditional banks in the country, has applied for a cryptocurrency custody license from BaFin. However, it has not been approved as of yet.</p>



<p>As of April 2022, over 25 companies in Germany had applied for BaFin&#8217;s approval to operate with cryptocurrencies. Out of all of them, only 4 have obtained regulatory approval, with Coinbase Germany, the German subsidiary of the U.S.-based cryptocurrency exchange Coinbase, being a notable example.</p>



<p>Similarly, DZ Bank, Germany&#8217;s second-largest bank, applied for a crypto asset custody license in 2022 but has not been approved by BaFin thus far. This demonstrates the growing interest of traditional German banks in the custody of cryptocurrency assets.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/deutsche-bank-enters-digital-asset-custody-to-drive-institutional-adoption/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin ETFs In Motion: An Analysis Of Open Spot BTC ETF Applications In The Market</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/bitcoin-etfs-in-motion-an-analysis-of-open-spot-btc-etf-applications-in-the-market/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/bitcoin-etfs-in-motion-an-analysis-of-open-spot-btc-etf-applications-in-the-market/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aliyu Pokima]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 09:49:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Featured]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XBTUSD]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=82397</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-ETFs-In-Motion-An-Analysis-Of-Open-Spot-BTC-ETF-Applications-In-The-Market.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Bitcoin ETFs In Motion: An Analysis Of Open Spot BTC ETF Applications In The Market" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-ETFs-In-Motion-An-Analysis-Of-Open-Spot-BTC-ETF-Applications-In-The-Market.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-ETFs-In-Motion-An-Analysis-Of-Open-Spot-BTC-ETF-Applications-In-The-Market-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-ETFs-In-Motion-An-Analysis-Of-Open-Spot-BTC-ETF-Applications-In-The-Market-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-ETFs-In-Motion-An-Analysis-Of-Open-Spot-BTC-ETF-Applications-In-The-Market-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>The digital asset community awaits the first spot Bitcoin (BTC) Exchange Traded Fund (ETF) after many rejections by the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC).]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-ETFs-In-Motion-An-Analysis-Of-Open-Spot-BTC-ETF-Applications-In-The-Market.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Bitcoin ETFs In Motion: An Analysis Of Open Spot BTC ETF Applications In The Market" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-ETFs-In-Motion-An-Analysis-Of-Open-Spot-BTC-ETF-Applications-In-The-Market.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-ETFs-In-Motion-An-Analysis-Of-Open-Spot-BTC-ETF-Applications-In-The-Market-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-ETFs-In-Motion-An-Analysis-Of-Open-Spot-BTC-ETF-Applications-In-The-Market-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-ETFs-In-Motion-An-Analysis-Of-Open-Spot-BTC-ETF-Applications-In-The-Market-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<ul>
<li>Over the past few weeks, many proposals for a spot Bitcoin ETF in the United States have been filed, including applications from BlackRock, WisdomTree, etc.</li>



<li>All previous attempts by firms to get a spot Bitcoin ETF have been futile as the SEC continues to push back, citing threats of market manipulation.</li>



<li>The recent applications have led to a spike in the price of Bitcoin, leading to the top asset surging to a one-year high.</li>
</ul>



<p>The digital asset community awaits the first spot Bitcoin (BTC) Exchange Traded Fund (ETF) after many rejections by the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC).</p>



<p>An ETF is a type of investment fund that tracks the performance of an underlying asset, index, or pool of securities. ETFs give investors a good opportunity to diversify their portfolio at a lower cost as they gain exposure to the underlying asset, in this case, Bitcoin.</p>



<p>The first Bitcoin application came in 2013, and since then, multiple firms have applied, although to no avail. Pro-ETF traders have argued that it is still complicated for users to trade BTC as many are not used to exchanges, especially new entrants but a spot ETF will clear the hurdle. Here are some open spot ETF applications.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-blackrock"><strong>BlackRock</strong></h2>



<p>BlackRock, the world’s biggest asset manager with over $9 trillion worth of assets under management, officially <a href="https://zycrypto.com/institutional-investors-sentiment-for-crypto-surges-following-blackrocks-bitcoin-etf-filing/">filed</a> for a BTC spot ETF on June 15, 2023. The proposed filing would see Coinbase as the asset custodian and market data provider, while BNY Mellon would act as the cash custodian. The move came as a shock to many in both decentralized finance (DeFi) and traditional finance (TradFi).</p>



<p>Though previous applications have been denied by the SEC, industry experts opined that BlackRock’s application is the “<em>real deal” </em>because of the firm&#8217;s success rate with the SEC, which stands at 575-1. Recently, ex-Barclays CEO Bob Diamond praised the company, saying it has created a pathway for institutional investors.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-ark-invest"><strong>Ark Invest</strong></h2>



<p>Ark Invest filed its first application in June 2021 in partnership with 21Shares and would trade on Cboe’s BZX exchange. The company’s proposal got rejected twice, with the latest being in Jan 2023. The company has made its third application with hopes for a different story. Ark Invest has invested massively in the digital asset space, including Coinbase, Square, and Grayscale Bitcoin Trust.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-wisdomtree"><strong>WisdomTree</strong></h2>



<p>Like Ark Invest, WisdomTree has previously seen the SEC reject its BTC spot ETF application. It recently reapplied days after BlackRock’s application. Initially, crypto enthusiasts thought that the firm’s application would scale through as the SEC invited members of the public to comment on the safety of the ETF. However, the Commission rejected the proposal in 2021.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-invesco-galaxy-and-valkyrie-investments"><strong>Invesco Galaxy and Valkyrie Investments</strong></h2>



<p>Both firms filed for new spot ETF <a href="https://zycrypto.com/spot-bitcoin-etf-craze-valkyrie-becomes-the-latest-firm-to-apply-for-sec-approval/">applications</a> after BlackRock, pushing up the number of open ETF filings. Invesco initially filed in Sept 2022 and proposed an ETF backed by physical Bitcoin rather than derivatives. The firm boasts as the fourth largest ETF provider in the United States, a criterion many observers believe would be helpful in the long run. Valkyrie made its first BTC ETC application in 2021, a proposal that draws reference to the Chicago Mercantile Exchange’s price for Bitcoin.</p>



<p>Just like others, the SEC denied the application, but the company did not back down. In 2022, it obtained a BTC mining ETF from the SEC, a moving instrument backed by mining firms that use renewable energy for at least 77% of their operations, including Stronghold Digital, Cleanspark, Argo Blockchain, Bitfarms, etc. </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/bitcoin-etfs-in-motion-an-analysis-of-open-spot-btc-etf-applications-in-the-market/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin &#8220;Very Unlikely to Hit Bottom Again&#8221;, Pundit Asserts as Key Indicator Flashes Green</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/bitcoin-very-unlikely-to-hit-bottom-again-pundit-asserts-as-key-indicator-flashes-green/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/bitcoin-very-unlikely-to-hit-bottom-again-pundit-asserts-as-key-indicator-flashes-green/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Newton Gitonga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 09:40:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XBTUSD]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=82395</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/Chris-Burniske-Predicts-Bitcoin-Likely-to-Hit-Bottom-Near-3000.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Chris Burniske Predicts Bitcoin Likely to Hit Bottom Near $3,000" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/Chris-Burniske-Predicts-Bitcoin-Likely-to-Hit-Bottom-Near-3000.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/Chris-Burniske-Predicts-Bitcoin-Likely-to-Hit-Bottom-Near-3000-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/Chris-Burniske-Predicts-Bitcoin-Likely-to-Hit-Bottom-Near-3000-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/Chris-Burniske-Predicts-Bitcoin-Likely-to-Hit-Bottom-Near-3000-768x448.jpg 768w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/Chris-Burniske-Predicts-Bitcoin-Likely-to-Hit-Bottom-Near-3000-610x356.jpg 610w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>Following an impressive performance last week, Bitcoin started the new week on a strong note, with the largest crypto asset globally maintaining its position above the $30K threshold.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/Chris-Burniske-Predicts-Bitcoin-Likely-to-Hit-Bottom-Near-3000.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Chris Burniske Predicts Bitcoin Likely to Hit Bottom Near $3,000" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/Chris-Burniske-Predicts-Bitcoin-Likely-to-Hit-Bottom-Near-3000.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/Chris-Burniske-Predicts-Bitcoin-Likely-to-Hit-Bottom-Near-3000-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/Chris-Burniske-Predicts-Bitcoin-Likely-to-Hit-Bottom-Near-3000-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/Chris-Burniske-Predicts-Bitcoin-Likely-to-Hit-Bottom-Near-3000-768x448.jpg 768w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/Chris-Burniske-Predicts-Bitcoin-Likely-to-Hit-Bottom-Near-3000-610x356.jpg 610w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>Following an impressive performance last week, Bitcoin started the new week on a strong note, with the largest crypto asset globally maintaining its position above the $30K threshold. In the past seven days, Bitcoin surged by over 17%, tapping a one-year high of $31,397 and making it the best performing week since mid-march. </p>



<p>This strength has primarily been attributed to recent bitcoin ETF applications led by <a href="https://zycrypto.com/institutional-investors-sentiment-for-crypto-surges-following-blackrocks-bitcoin-etf-filing/">BlackRock</a> and <a href="https://zycrypto.com/spot-bitcoin-etf-craze-valkyrie-becomes-the-latest-firm-to-apply-for-sec-approval/">Valkyrie</a>, which coincided with a mini-bull market that kicked off earlier this year. This surge has also prompted speculation about the future trajectory of Bitcoin and whether it has reached its bottom.</p>



<p>On Sunday, Dan Lim, a verified analyst for onchain analytics firm Cryptoquant, shared his thoughts on Bitcoin&#8217;s current behaviour. The pundit highlighted that the substantial surge of Bitcoin since the start of 2023 has propelled the MVRV indicator, which gauges the present value of Bitcoin, to reach 1.51, surpassing the undervaluation range of 1.0. According to him, this suggests a potential shift in the market dynamics for Bitcoin&#8217;s future direction.</p>



<p><em>&#8220;In the past, when MVRV broke strongly above 1.0 at the bottom of a bear market and continued to rise for several months, there was no case where Bitcoin bottomed out again</em>,&#8221; said Lim.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img decoding="async" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/sdQLjQuTtZ2BgPlJgv-Qt_5jWaV3aswEvLLbhNnpfwL6_KxHCrFuaTwN3AZiQ32oFCbN8I8_VW-q0pFwPKYXBle4swCriqpuwB8jzuwC3KwkI_0-ODVnBjC8Pg_o5ZOuayavGJPTVzG2tyZblV4MZg" alt=""/></figure>



<p>Lim further highlighted the rise in Bitcoin dominance and the overall market, which often occurs at the beginning of a bull market. Based on these observations, Lim believed there might be only a limited time remaining in 2023 or the beginning of 2024 to make stable investments in Bitcoin and Ethereum.</p>



<p>He further acknowledged <a href="https://zycrypto.com/bitcoin-risks-crashing-to-20000-amid-blackrock-spot-btc-etf-filing-warns-bloomberg-analyst/">concerns</a> about a potential recession and uncertainties surrounding Fed policies. However, contrary to many&#8217;s belief that Bitcoin could slump in the face of a recession, Lim provided a different perspective. He suggested that the current moment could present an opportune time to consider buying Bitcoin, noting that once the market uncertainties are resolved, it might as well mark the end of the ongoing bull run, opening a window for a potential sell-off.</p>



<p>Lim&#8217;s insights remain significant, especially in light of other key Bitcoin indicators turning green, which further supports the notion of an imminent bull run. On Monday, Glassnode reported that following the aftermath of the COVID-19 crisis, there has been a consistent decline in the percentage of Bitcoin held within Exchange addresses. This figure has reached a current value of 11.7%, equivalent to 2.27 million BTC.</p>



<p>Importantly, this marks the lowest recorded level since December 21, 2017. The decline in Bitcoin holdings on exchanges indicates a potential decrease in selling pressure and a shift towards long-term investment strategies, which have historically been good for the price.</p>



<p>At press time, Bitcoin was trading at $30,322 after a 0.17% drop in the past 24 hours.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/bitcoin-very-unlikely-to-hit-bottom-again-pundit-asserts-as-key-indicator-flashes-green/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>XRP Lawsuit Continues To See New Twists and Turns As Alderoty Reveals Ripple&#8217;s Benefits In SEC Case</title>
		<link>https://zycrypto.com/xrp-lawsuit-continues-to-see-new-twists-and-turns-as-alderoty-reveals-ripples-benefits-in-sec-case/</link>
					<comments>https://zycrypto.com/xrp-lawsuit-continues-to-see-new-twists-and-turns-as-alderoty-reveals-ripples-benefits-in-sec-case/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aaron Feuerstein]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 19:39:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://zycrypto.com/?p=82381</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/07/Why-Seasoned-Corporate-Attorney-James-Filan-Is-Telling-XRP-Investors-Not-To-Expect-Settlement-In-Ripple-Lawsuit.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Why Seasoned Corporate Attorney James Filan Is Telling XRP Investors Not To Expect Settlement In Ripple Lawsuit" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/07/Why-Seasoned-Corporate-Attorney-James-Filan-Is-Telling-XRP-Investors-Not-To-Expect-Settlement-In-Ripple-Lawsuit.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/07/Why-Seasoned-Corporate-Attorney-James-Filan-Is-Telling-XRP-Investors-Not-To-Expect-Settlement-In-Ripple-Lawsuit-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/07/Why-Seasoned-Corporate-Attorney-James-Filan-Is-Telling-XRP-Investors-Not-To-Expect-Settlement-In-Ripple-Lawsuit-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/07/Why-Seasoned-Corporate-Attorney-James-Filan-Is-Telling-XRP-Investors-Not-To-Expect-Settlement-In-Ripple-Lawsuit-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p>In a recent interview Stuart Alderoty, Ripple’s Chief Legal Officer, voiced his opinions about the timing of the lawsuit and the company's dedication to defending the case in December 2020, when Ripple Labs was sued by...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="1200" height="700" src="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/07/Why-Seasoned-Corporate-Attorney-James-Filan-Is-Telling-XRP-Investors-Not-To-Expect-Settlement-In-Ripple-Lawsuit.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Why Seasoned Corporate Attorney James Filan Is Telling XRP Investors Not To Expect Settlement In Ripple Lawsuit" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/07/Why-Seasoned-Corporate-Attorney-James-Filan-Is-Telling-XRP-Investors-Not-To-Expect-Settlement-In-Ripple-Lawsuit.jpg 1200w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/07/Why-Seasoned-Corporate-Attorney-James-Filan-Is-Telling-XRP-Investors-Not-To-Expect-Settlement-In-Ripple-Lawsuit-300x175.jpg 300w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/07/Why-Seasoned-Corporate-Attorney-James-Filan-Is-Telling-XRP-Investors-Not-To-Expect-Settlement-In-Ripple-Lawsuit-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://zycrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/07/Why-Seasoned-Corporate-Attorney-James-Filan-Is-Telling-XRP-Investors-Not-To-Expect-Settlement-In-Ripple-Lawsuit-768x448.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></p><div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px;" class="sharethis-inline-share-buttons" ></div>
<p>In a recent interview <a href="https://zycrypto.com/ripple-counsel-gives-strong-argument-about-xrp-as-landmark-lawsuit-nears-end/">Stuart Alderoty</a>, Ripple’s Chief Legal Officer, voiced his opinions about the timing of the lawsuit and the company&#8217;s dedication to defending the case in December 2020, when Ripple Labs was sued by the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) right before Christmas. Ripple made it clear that they were battling not only for themselves but also for the whole crypto industry in the United States, despite the industry&#8217;s early scepticism.</p>



<p>Alderoty said: <em>“We said from day one that we were going to defend this case not only on our own behalf, but we were going to defend this case on behalf of the entire crypto industry in the United States. […] Everyone understands how important this fight is.”</em></p>



<p>As the case drags on, Alderoty feels that Ripple’s position has been validated and that others broadly supported and believed in their commitment to fighting the case. It has been acknowledged that Ripple&#8217;s determination to stand up to the SEC represents a significant victory for the whole cryptocurrency sector.</p>



<p>Mr. Alderoty conceded that <a href="https://zycrypto.com/xrp-moon-time-ripple-eyes-upper-hand-in-sec-lawsuit-as-ceo-garlinghouse-sheds-light-on-case-outcome/">Ripple</a> benefited in certain ways by being sued by the SEC at that specific time. Others in the sector who are just starting to deal with litigation from the SEC are finding inspiration in Ripple&#8217;s defences and story as they draw closer to the conclusion of their legal journey.</p>



<p><em>“And in many ways, Ripple in a perverse way, we&#8217;ve actually been benefited by the SEC suing us when they did because we&#8217;re at the end of our journey and others at the beginning of their litigation journey with the SEC,”</em> Alderoty said.</p>



<p>To some extent, Ripple&#8217;s experiences have prepared the ground and given those in a similar circumstance a blueprint.</p>



<p>Alderoty added: <em>“But I think if you look at the defenses and the narrative around what some of the actors who are now on the wrong side with the SEC, they are reading from the Ripple playbook and that is perfectly fine with us.”</em></p>



<p>The remarks follow the much-anticipated publication of the Hinman documents. The documents associated with the 2018 Hinman speech, which provided guidelines for deciding whether a token qualifies as a security, were recently unsealed. Ripple CEO Brad Garlinghouse stated days after the release that he thinks the SEC&#8217;s activities show a deliberate effort to exercise control through enforcement.</p>



<p>Garlinghouse emphasized that there is still more work to achieve regulatory clarity for the industry even though the SEC&#8217;s case against Ripple is about to conclude. Alderoty’s comments, therefore, highlight both the frustrations and the revelations the team at Ripple have been through the past years in the lawsuit with the SEC.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://zycrypto.com/xrp-lawsuit-continues-to-see-new-twists-and-turns-as-alderoty-reveals-ripples-benefits-in-sec-case/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
